♪ ♪
(heavy breathing)
(squelching)
(takes deep breath)
(blows)
(sizzling)
- You can't do that in here.
- (lighter snaps shut)
(Hutch groans quietly)
(dog grunts)
Okay. Who the fuck are you two?
Us?
- We're... (panting)
- (grunts)
(snoring softly)
("The Good Life" by José James
playing)
♪ It's the good life ♪
♪ Full of fun ♪
♪ Seems to be the ideal ♪
- (cat mews)
- BECCA: Morning, baby.
- Let me look at that.
- Hmm?
♪ Yes, the good life
lets you hide ♪
- (thunder crashes)
- ♪ All the sadness you feel ♪
♪ You won't really ♪
♪ Fall in love ♪
♪ 'Cause you can't
take the chance ♪
♪ So be honest with yourself ♪
♪ Don't try to fake romance ♪
♪ Yes, the good life ♪
- BECCA: See you, sweetheart.
- BRADY: Bye, Mom.
♪ To be free
and explore the unknown ♪
♪ Like the heartaches ♪
♪ When you learn you must ♪
♪ Face them alone ♪
♪ Please remember ♪
- ♪ I still want you ♪
- (groaning)
- (gunshot)
- ♪ And in case ♪
- ♪ You wonder why ♪
- (grunting and groaning)
♪ Well, just wake up ♪
♪ Kiss that good life ♪
♪ Goodbye. ♪
- (song ends)
- (high-pitched ringing)
(grunting fiercely)
(panting)
("The Power of Love" ringtone
playing)
(high-pitched ringing fades)
(Hutch inhales sharply, groans)
(panting)
(phone chimes, vibrates)
(continues panting)
(typing on phone)
(sighing)
(sizzling)
(TV playing indistinctly)
Sammy? Fruit, please.
- Okey dokey.
- BECCA: Brady, eat the protein.
I am good.
(Becca scoffs)
BECCA:
Clean your plate, please.
- Hey, that's Dad's.
- BRADY: Is he even home?
- Bye, Lasagna.
- (Lasagna meows)
Hey, cut him some slack, okay?
- Always.
- (horn honking outside)
BECCA:
Hold up.
- I love you.
- Okay. Love you.
- Hey, babe.
- SAMMY: My friends are here.
- Okay. Uh, have a nice...
- (horn honks outside)
(sighs) Hey, hon?
I, uh, slept in the basement
- so I wouldn't wake you.
- Uh-huh.
Okay, where's Brady?
I want to hear about the game.
Well, uh...
the other team was kind of,
you know, physical.
- Yeah?
- So he, um...
I'll let him tell you.
Very busy day.
I've got three showings
and one confirmed sale.
And, uh...
Oh. Brady stole your coffee.
You're gonna have to make
some more.
- Well, we had...
- Hutch, you're bleeding.
- All right, we should, uh...
- (door closes)
(clears throat, sighs)
(truck backup alarm
beeping outside)
Oh, damn it.
Hey!
Hey, buddy.
- Hey, man.
- BRADY: Bye, Mom.
- SAMMY: Bye, Mom.
- HUTCH: Yeah.
- BECCA: Have a great day!
- BRADY: All right.
- SAMMY: Hey, guys.
- FRIEND: Hi, Sammy.
- HUTCH: Hey, you...
- FRIEND: Love your shoes.
- BRADY: Morning.
- FRIEND 2: Oh, love yours, too.
- SAMMY: Yours, too.
- FRIEND 2: Thank you.
Yeah, I got 'em from the mall.
FRIEND 1: Are you going
anywhere for summer break?
FRIEND 2:
Yeah, I'm going bowling.
(conversation continues
indistinctly)
BECCA:
Hutch?
What's up, hon?
You know...
(scoffs)
Uh, summer break's
in just a few days, and...
We should do something
as a family. Yeah.
I, uh... I'll make a plan.
Today I'll make a plan,
and, uh, I'll tell you tonight.
- At dinner. I'll make lasagna.
- (sighs)
- Sure, Hutch. (laughs)
- No, I can do it. I...
I have... I have
one assignment today.
Uh, but then tonight you'll see,
uh, the whole thing planned out.
What's going on?
(Becca sighs)
Never mind.
♪ ♪
(elevator bell dings)
(quiet chatter)
(takes deep breath)
(jazzy melody playing)
There you are.
Looks like your day went long.
It was a bit more... big.
Bit more than the prep
said it would be.
The data card.
(clears throat)
(sighs)
It was a straightforward
snatch, Hutch.
It started as
a straightforward snatch.
You guys having fun
at the convention?
Asshole, we're not here
for the fucking convention.
- (grunting, yelling)
- (two gunshots)
- Where's the card?
- (whimpering)
(grunts, coughs)
(grunting and groaning)
(yells in pain)
Oh, my.
Please! Someone help us.
(stammers)
AUTOMATED VOICE: An operator
will assist you shortly.
(grunting)
(cries out)
(crunching)
(whimpering)
- (breathing heavily)
- (others groaning)
(gun cocks)
(elevator bell dings)
(body thuds)
Right. Straightforward snatch.
Yeah. Until the Corsicans
showed up with Uzis.
♪ ♪
Wait. No, they had MP7s.
- (explosion booms)
- (man yells)
Corsicans, huh?
With MP7s.
Well, we always suspected
there might be
another interested party
in the mix.
Only one?
(tires squealing)
("100% Feminista" by MC Carol &
Karol Conká plays over stereo)
(song continues
with lyrics in Portuguese)
(tires squealing)
(sighs)
(electrical crackling)
- (fierce grunting)
- ("100% Feminista" continues)
(grunting and groaning)
(song stops)
- Brazilians?
- HUTCH: Yeah.
With machetes?
The sharp kind.
(song resumes)
(song stops)
Oh, my.
Yeah.
(tablet beeping)
(trilling, beeping)
Well, I'd say it was worth it.
Because this checks out.
Which brings you
800 grand closer.
And how much more do I owe?
30 million, give or take.
(snaps fingers)
- Your next mission.
- (Hutch sighs)
(folder rustling)
I can't.
Hutch...
I'm trying to help you
pay off a debt.
One we very graciously paid
on your behalf
when you burnt all
the Russian's stack of money.
At the rate you're going,
you'll have paid off
the obshchak by spring.
Gonna take a va...
I'm gonna take a break.
♪ ♪
Good luck.
What do I need luck for?
You... take a break?
This job is in your nature,
and nature always wins.
Wherever you go...
...there you are.
(Hutch groaning softly)
(body thuds)
(chuckles)
Wild times await.
This summer,
drive to Plummerville,
smack-dab in the middle
of America,
and join me, Wild Bill,
for summer fun.
(laughs)
With the majestic midway.
Hey!
And to top it off,
America's first and finest
water park!
You kids having summer fun?
BOTH: Sure are,
Mr. Wild Bill... (screaming)
WILD BILL:
Slides for miles and miles!
Because Plummerville is...
(ducks quacking)
...Summerville!
So come on back to Wild Bill's
again and again!
Again and again...
(chuckles)
Yeah.
Um, that commercial
is really old.
Are you sure it's still a place?
Yeah, it's all there.
I-I checked. It's...
The hotel and the water park,
uh, the duck boats
and the midway.
What's a duck boat?
It's, um... it's like
a bus that floats.
Uh, it's a military vehicle.
Grandpa will love it.
- We're bringing Grandpa?
- Yeah, of course.
- (Brady sighs)
You know what?
Um, I volunteer to stay home.
- Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
- HUTCH: Yeah, Brady, listen.
This is gonna be the most fu...
What happened to your eye?
Somebody fouled me at the game.
What game?
The one you missed.
You're right.
We do need to spend
more time together
- as a family.
- Yeah.
This is one of those places
you went when you were a kid.
Okay, that makes it sound like
I went to a lot of places, okay?
Dad took us on one vacation.
One. To Plummerville.
♪ ♪
(clears throat) Listen.
In life, when times get tough,
you need to have happy memories
to carry you through,
and I just want to show you guys
the place that made me happiest.
You know,
make some memories for you.
Would you let me
do that, please?
- (snickers)
- (Lasagna meowing)
- Well, hello, Lasagna.
- (Hutch chuckling)
Okay.
All right, Hutch. Sure.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- (chuckling): Really?
- Yeah. (laughs)
Come on, kids,
it could be an adventure.
An adventure.
- Yeah.
- That's it.
("More Today Than Yesterday"
by Spiral Starecase playing)
(quiet chatter)
♪ I don't remember
what day it was... ♪
SAMMY:
Grandpa.
- HUTCH: Hey, Dad.
- Mm-hmm.
You got to put out the cigar.
Secondhand smoke.
(laughing)
♪ All I know is... ♪
No such thing.
(Sammy coughing)
♪ And if all my dreams
come true ♪
♪ I'll be spending time
with you... ♪
(sizzling)
Let's do this!
♪ In love with you ♪
♪ With each day
comes a new way... ♪
Hutch, start the car! (laughs)
- Here?
- Yeah.
♪ Every time I kiss your lips ♪
♪ My mind starts to wander ♪
(over car stereo): ♪ And if
all my dreams come true ♪
♪ I'll be spending time
with you ♪
- (turns up volume)
- ♪ Oh ♪
(singing along):
♪ I love you more today ♪
♪ Than yesterday ♪
♪ But not as much ♪
♪ As tomorrow ♪
♪ I love you more today
than yesterday ♪
♪ But, darling, not as much ♪
♪ As tomorrow ♪
♪ Every day's a new day ♪
♪ Every time I love ya ♪
- ♪ Every day's a new day... ♪
- (song fades)
BRADY:
Oldest water park?
Is that something
we want to advertise?
HUTCH:
Yeah, well, it's historic.
Kids, you're in here.
BRADY:
Oh, we're sharing a room.
- And where's Grandpa sleeping?
- Uh, he's next door.
Oh, Hutch, I think the kids
are too old to share.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
We can all sleep
in the old lodge.
N... Uh, not gonna happen.
(chuckling):
Just me, then.
Fine.
You can have my room.
- Thank you.
- Great.
Then, uh, Sammy,
you got this all to yourself.
The honeymoon suite.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
- Whoo! -(door closes)
- (Becca sighs)
Look at that, huh?
Take it in.
- Yeah.
- (chuckles)
(inhales sharply)
This is where
business gets done.
Yeah.
(Hutch chuckles)
You don't like it?
No, I'm-I'm taking it in.
I smell cigars.
But I'm happy that you're happy.
(laughs)
And that we're all together.
It's gonna be great.
(laughing)
("Tres Delinquentes"
by Delinquent Habits playing)
SAMMY:
Water park time.
- (Hutch clears throat)
- (Becca sighs)
- Uh, water park time.
- Yeah. Water park. Yeah.
♪ I flex my brazos hardcore,
down for the clicka ♪
♪ Who's that emanating funk
through the speaka? ♪
♪ Bass gets to thumpin',
rucas get to pumpin' ♪
♪ Who's that rockin'?
Got the party start jumpin' ♪
♪ Blastin' through, ha,
no need for the booyah ♪
♪ Right hammer with the one
knuckle eye-shot through ya ♪
♪ Step to the crowd,
I feel the strain ♪
♪ Throw chingasos
in the mosh pit... ♪
It's paradise.
- It's like the tropics...
- (laughing)
...mixed with Europe.
- Hello.
- Closed. Sorry.
- What?
- There was an incident.
Water park's closed
for the rest of the day.
- HUTCH: For how long?
- 24 hours.
Here's a coupon for hot dogs.
Come again. Sorry.
Lame.
I'm out of here, kids.
Checking out the old lodge.
Hot dogs.
♪ We're all going on
a summer holiday... ♪
COOK:
Number 52's up!
YOUNG HUTCH:
Harry, Dad's bringing the food!
YOUNG HARRY:
Yo, what's up, Hutch?
♪ No more worries
for me or you ♪
♪ For a week or two... ♪
Hey! It's the great Mansell's
family vacation, boys.
Wait till you see the lodge.
You'll see mosquitos
bigger than this hot dog.
(laughter)
MAN:
Something wrong, pal?
You got a problem?
♪ Summer holiday... ♪
Uh, no, I'm sorry.
I was just thinking.
♪ So we're going on
a summer holiday ♪
♪ To make our dreams come true ♪
♪ For me and you... ♪
You know, it's not polite
to eyeball the law.
Uh, sorry, Officer.
It's "Sheriff."
Did I do something wrong?
I don't know.
Did you?
(chuckles softly)
Um, Hutch?
Everything's good, hon.
- Okay.
- (bell dinging)
WAITRESS:
Mansell?
Uh, yeah, that's me.
- Hot dogs are ready.
- (clears throat) Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Fantastic. All right.
- Enjoy.
- Thanks.
- Hey.
(inhales sharply)
Worth the wait,
and look what we got.
Coupon for the arcade.
BECCA:
That's how they get ya.
- That's how they get ya.
- SAMMY: Can I see it?
All right. (sighs)
All four food groups
in one place.
- SAMMY: Thanks, Mom.
- (door closing)
- (machines chiming, dinging)
- ("Power" by Little Mix plays)
- Here you go. You bet.
- Thank you.
Oh, this is so hard.
- (bell rings)
- (laughs)
♪ Hold up... ♪
I wanted to talk to you about
that shiner you got in the game.
(quietly):
I didn't get it in the game.
Sorry, what's that?
I said I didn't get it
in the game.
But you got fouled,
though, right?
Dad, can you just stop?
Can I just... Okay?
Can I just play the game?
It's not a big deal, all right?
- I won, so...
- BECCA: Hutch!
HUTCH:
That doesn't make it...
- Yeah?
- (laughs) Um, play the winner.
Okay. I'll be right there.
Um, we-we will talk
about this more later, okay?
- For sure.
- Yep.
(girls laughing,
chattering indistinctly)
(bell ringing)
GIRL:
I know how to do this!
- GIRL 2: He's so cute.
- (microphone feedback squeals)
WOMAN (over speaker):
Howdy, girls and boys.
It's sizzling here in
Plummerville's ultimate arcade,
the one-stop
entertainment center...
You guys want some tickets?
(laughing):
Um, sure.
- Here.
- Thanks.
- I have a bunch.
- Hey, Brady.
Why'd you give them all away?
I have plenty, dude. Come on.
WOMAN (over speaker):
In less than half an hour
is our happy hour.
♪ Who got the power? ♪
Look at us.
We're decompressing like pros.
Yeah. We're getting there.
- Is that a badger? -WORKER: Yup.
- Come on, Max. Max.
- That one.
- All right.
- Hey.
- Thanks.
Nerd.
You getting some Nerds
with your tickets, nerd?
What's up?
Tell me you're sorry.
For what?
For hitting on my girl.
You're giving her tickets, man.
What if I tell you to fuck off?
That count?
(laughter)
Know who I am?
Last chance.
BOY:
Oh, what, are you gonna cry?
What, you don't...
you don't want another shiner
on your-your pretty
city boy face, do you?
Aw.
- (toy squeaks)
- Hey.
(toy squeaks)
BECCA:
Oh! Oh!
- Fucking touch my sister!
- Let him go!
What are you doing, you punk?
Coming into my house,
starting a fight?
Now settle the fuck down!
♪ Bike, bike, bike, bike,
bike, bike, bike... ♪
(breathing heavily)
- Hey. -No, Dad, Dad, Dad.
- SECURITY GUARD: Get out.
- This piece of shit...
- Get out of here right now!
- What happened?
- Hey, is that your kid?
- Yeah.
- Well, he's starting shit.
He's not starting anything.
I have cameras all over
this place. If you don't get
-your family out of here
right now... -Calm down.
...you and I are gonna
have a problem.
- Yeah, we are gonna have...
- BECCA: Hey!
We're leaving.
- Oh, okay.
- You hear me?
- Okay. Yeah. All right.
- All right, let's go.
- Listen to your wife, old man.
- BRADY: Why? Why?
No, Mom, I didn't do shit.
This guy did all of it.
- Yo, how's your arm?
- SAMMY: My badger.
SECURITY GUARD:
Leave it.
Ouch.
♪ ♪
- BRADY: Man.
- BECCA: Brady, hold up.
- No, I just want...
- Hold up, sweetie.
I just want to go.
BECCA:
Brady.
- What?
- I left my phone.
I'll be right back.
BECCA:
No, Hutch. Hutch, no!
(voice distorting):
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
♪ ♪
("Come Out and Play"
by The Offspring playing)
- Well, look who decided to...
- SECURITY GUARD 2: Oh, shit!
(yelling)
MAN: Hey! Trying to be
a hero, big man?
(grunting)
♪ The gangs stake
their own campus locale ♪
♪ And if they
catch you slippin' ♪
- ♪ Then it's all over, pal ♪
- (cartoony squealing on game)
♪ If one guy's colors
and the others don't mix ♪
♪ They're gonna bash it up,
bash it up ♪
♪ Bash it up, bash it up ♪
♪ Hey, man,
you talkin' back to me? ♪
♪ Take him out ♪
♪ You gotta keep 'em separated ♪
♪ Hey, come out and play. ♪
- (machine chiming)
- (yelps)
(song ends)
(groaning)
How's that feel?
- Huh?
- BECCA: Hutch!
(scoffing):
God.
Dad.
(horn honking)
BECCA:
S-Sir, we were attacked.
And I don't understand
why we're here.
I don't understand why
those bullies are not here.
Are we being charged
with anything?
Okay, is your son
prone to violence?
Is my... Are you kidding me?
Ma'am.
I'm just trying to gather
some information.
Uh, can you tell me exactly...
Sir, if we're not being charged,
I'd rather not answer
any more of your questions.
I understand protecting
your sister, Brady.
It's instinctual.
But... (clears throat)
there are other ways
to handle things.
You serious?
Y-You tell me to stay cool,
but then you go
and lose your shit?
Which I-I thought was awesome,
by the way.
- You know, the way that you...
- No.
No, it wasn't.
I'm just saying,
you have to be better
than your old man.
(Hutch sighs)
(Brady scoffs)
Whatever.
(banging)
(banging continues)
(chuckles softly)
Okay.
Let's go.
Get up.
Not you.
Just Dad.
♪ ♪
Sit your ass down.
(chair creaking)
You know who I am?
(clears throat)
No, but, uh,
the way you're sitting
behind the sheriff's desk,
- I'm guessing you're somebody.
- Damn right I am.
Name's Wyatt Martin.
I run this town.
Oh. I'm Hutch...
I already know who you are.
You're the tourist
fucked up my son.
- I didn't...
- Shut the fuck up.
Your son was the kid
at the arcade?
Shut the fuck up.
HUTCH: Well, your son may have
had something to do with...
Your son has got
an attitude problem.
And I'm pretty sure
I'm staring at...
My daddy built this town,
and he had a rule.
Tourists get a free pass.
You know why, right?
Bread and butter and all that?
But for this...
...your son... Brady, right?
Yeah.
Your son Brady messed up
my son's pitching arm.
I get it.
Do you?
Yeah, I get it.
I'll make my son apologize.
But you should watch
the security cam footage,
'cause one of those guys
smacked my daughter
and I lost it.
(takes deep breath)
What would you have done?
Walk 'em out.
BECCA:
Brady, come on.
So that's it, then? We can go?
Do yourself a favor.
Keep going.
Get the boys together.
DEPUTY DANN: Didn't Wyatt say
to leave them alone?
SHERIFF ABEL: I don't
give a fuck what Wyatt says.
Get rid of them.
(camera clicks)
Can you not?
What the hell, Hutch?
On our first day?
I'm sorry.
You just had to bring
that other side of you?
Brady's already aggressive,
and do you know why?
It's because of you.
Because he is watching you
and what you do.
Look, I lost it, all right?
It's over.
What's in the workbag?
What?
The black bag, Hutch.
- You've been trying to hide it.
- Listen.
Okay, so what's in it?
I'm not here for...
- I made a promise to you.
- Yeah.
And I meant what I said.
BECCA:
Yeah, I remember that promise.
Wine?
It's not just any wine.
♪ ♪
It's from Puglia.
Where we met.
And the year.
(Becca crying)
I'm sorry.
Where'd you find this?
Um, eBay.
- eBay?
- Yeah.
Wait, so you ordered it?
It took like six weeks.
You planned for this.
I knew who you were
the moment I met you.
I knew you were dangerous.
(laughing):
You were covered in blood.
- (sighs)
- Good times.
Good times.
("Run Run Run" by Jo Jo Gunne
playing)
♪ Run, run... ♪
Holy crap, Mom.
You've got an eye.
- (chuckles) Really?
- Yeah.
This is not a fair fight.
I'm on her side!
- (birds chirping)
- (insects trilling)
(humming)
♪ Run ♪
- ♪ Run... ♪
- HUTCH: Sammy.
- Where'd she go?
- (camera winding)
- (camera clicks)
- Sammy. Sammy, wait for me.
- Dad, guess where I am.
- Oh!
- (Sammy laughing)
- You got me.
I warned you,
this is a wonderland.
Off we go.
Ready?
- (camera clicks)
- (laughs) Supercute.
(camera clicks)
(laughs)
HUTCH: Grandpa doesn't know
what he's missing.
Duck boats are super fun.
They're trustworthy,
but they don't...
Four tickets for the...
Th-That's...
that's not a duck boat.
Uh, yeah, you see
the big duck on the top?
No, I told my son a duck boat
is a military vehicle.
Uh, more than...
more than one conflict.
I'm gonna...
Okay, four tickets.
One kid.
Yeah, here, honey,
hand these out.
- (Becca laughing)
- Really heavy-duty. Mil spec.
Yeah.
BRADY: Single-handedly
caused our loss at 'Nam.
GUIDE: Hey, only
a few seats left, folks.
Come aboard.
I hope you don't mind
getting wet.
BECCA:
Yes. Thank you.
Sweetie, why don't you
sit down there?
Uh, that's good. Thanks.
SAMMY: Dad's right.
It's like a bus that floats.
BECCA:
It is like a bus that floats.
Where is Dad?
(stammers) You're not coming?
Hon, I had too many churros
with my macchiato.
I'll see you at the park.
- BECCA: What? No.
- Have fun.
- BRADY: Bye, Macchiato.
- Well... eat better!
(duck quacking sound effects
blasting)
(quiet chatter)
♪ ♪
Looks like it's the end
of the line for you, pal...
BOAT DRIVER: All right, let's
get this party started. Vests.
Grab 'em off my arm.
- Vest?
- I'm good.
- Excuse us. Oh, hi.
- Excuse us. Excuse us.
- Yeah, yeah. Absolutely.
- Right up front?
BOAT DRIVER: Just head on up
to the front, yeah.
Uh, headphones should be
on the bench.
Find a seat in the back.
Just get comfortable.
You can stand if you want.
Just hold on really tight.
And we'll get going in a minute.
S-sit down.
(engine sputtering)
(engine starts)
BOAT DRIVER:
And we're sailing away.
(duck quacking sound effects
blasting)
Okay, so,
I'll be your guide today
as we cruise along
the great Plummerville lakes.
And, uh...
What's up, guys?
More than you know.
Yeah. You were told to leave.
So what are you still doing
in town, old man?
I'm here with my family,
making memories.
(laughing)
He's making memories, huh?
HUTCH:
There's no need for this.
This is all a big
misunderstanding. I'm here...
(yelling, grunting)
Be cool.
- (groans)
- (clangs)
(grunting, panting)
Come on!
- Hey!
- Use your words.
- (yells)
- (knife clatters)
What am I paying you for?
Fuck. He's right there!
("When the Saints Go
Marchin' In" playing)
BOAT DRIVER:
That's right.
My favorite, personally,
is the butter brownie.
Oh, and, um, speaking of...
(continues indistinctly)
(Hutch grunts fiercely)
Now no one gets the pole.
But I got a fucking knife!
(groans)
(straining)
You're dead, motherfucker.
These waters are home
to our native giant bass.
- (grunts fiercely)
- Cool it, man. Cool it.
Talk to me, okay?
Think of the children.
What?
(distorted groaning)
(distorted):
Fuck.
(straining)
You motherfuck...
That's what I'm
fucking talking about!
You said he was just
a fucking tourist!
That's all Abel fucking told me.
You're gonna pay us a lot more
fucking money now, Dann.
I lost a tooth.
(splashing, thumping)
♪ ♪
(grunting)
(yells)
(muffled grunting)
(distorted duck quacking
sound effects)
(screams)
Ah, fuck that! (screams)
- (whirring)
- (screams) Shit!
(yells)
Tell your boss
I'm... on... fucking...
vacation!
(grunting fiercely)
(flies buzzing)
WOMAN: So, we went to the beach,
now we're gonna get some
ice cream. What flavors? Yeah?
GIRL:
Yeah, I want ice cream.
- I want chocolate ice cream.
- (flies buzzing)
We're gonna get
some chocolate ice cream.
Come on.
Let's go this way. Yeah?
Yeah. Okay. I'm gonna
get strawberry ice cream.
Yeah, and vanilla.
(playing meditative melody)
HUTCH (over speaker):
Hey, Harry.
That wasn't a trumpet.
You were just being serenaded
by a shamisen, my brother.
Ah, you just got back
from Osaka, right?
Yeah, and I master shit quickly.
- What's up?
- Hey.
You remember Plummerville?
One of the happiest weeks
of my life.
Yeah. Mine, too.
Yeah, I remember...
I remember seeing the
other kids and their parents
and thinking
we were just like them.
Anyway, I came back here,
and, um...
Plummerville just isn't
as friendly
as I remember it to be.
It's an old trade route.
Used since the bootlegging days.
Why you think Dad took us there
for our one and only
family vacation?
Are you saying
he was on a mission?
You got it, Hutchy boy.
Oh, yeah.
HARRY:
The cops over there,
they in cahoots
with the big syndicate.
Hey, careful with that.
It's not my money.
I'm sorry, boss.
- I didn't mean to...
- Fucking moron.
HARRY: And they
would not want a guy like you
sniffing around, bro.
(indistinct shouting,
busy chatter)
How's it going?
Holy shit,
this is a big shipment.
What's in the blinking thing?
WYATT: The shit that's
gonna land Lendina
on Interpol's top ten.
(both chuckle)
This is great.
You want more guys here
just in case there's
any more trouble?
Hey.
Don't cause any trouble,
and there won't be any trouble.
Remember who's boss here.
Got it.
I got to get my son.
Watch this shit and be cool.
♪ ♪
Want me to take that?
Uh, thanks.
Do you think Dad is
eventually gonna grace us
with his presence or...
Wild animals!
CARNIE:
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't go too near.
That's a wild wolf dog.
Got to stay locked up, that one.
Well, Mom, you saved animals
back when you met Dad, right?
Uh, among other things,
but, um...
(yelps) -You know,
if you gain their trust...
- (barks)
- ...and you show them
that the world is
a safe place for them...
A world that is safe?
What world is that?
Okay. Let's go find Dad
for dinner.
(phone vibrating)
You caught our tourist, I heard.
Did he put up much of a fight?
(power tools buzzing loudly)
What's... I can't hear you.
Hey, turn that off.
Shut it off!
- What are you, new?
- (buzzing stops)
Wh-What was that?
DANN (over phone, slurring):
Uh, he broke my teeth, man.
What about your teeth?
(slurring):
He crushed 'em, okay?
He... he just...
he beat everybody.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Talking about the guy, okay?
I don't think
he's just some tourist.
(phone ringing)
Yes.
HUTCH (over phone):
I've got a problem.
Of your own making, I sense.
HUTCH:
Plummerville. You heard of it?
THE BARBER:
It's a back road.
Drugs, guns, viruses and worse
come down from Canada
and go on to points unknown.
All right.
Well, where does
the buck stop here?
There are layers.
Possibly an individual,
a unique individual
called Lendina.
Lendina.
♪ ♪
- LENDINA: Guy in the white?
- GUARD: Yes, ma'am.
- No, no. No new dealer.
- This requires a woman's touch.
But I'm winning.
On a roll here.
Congratulations.
Let's see how your luck goes.
(chuckles)
Beautiful. I split.
LENDINA:
Sure.
- Hit me.
- So how's your trip
- been going so far?
- Shut up and deal.
THE BARBER:
Plummerville is critical
to Lendina's larger empire.
Oh, shit.
Aw.
- (taps on table)
- It happens.
(chips clacking)
THE BARBER:
A lone wolf.
Operates unburdened
by any constraints... at all.
You piss off the Russians, they
come to your house with guns.
Lendina and her squad will slay
your family on the front lawn
and force you to watch
if you disrupt
their situations any further.
Yes.
(laughter)
Pay me. (laughs)
- (screaming)
- (bystanders gasping)
(laughing)
You're a winner.
DEALER: Ma'am, I swear,
I knew nothing...
- (bystanders screaming)
- MAN: Oh, my God!
MAN:
What's happening?
(screaming, frantic chatter)
Nobody cheats in my casino!
- (feedback squealing)
- (men groaning)
(neck snaps)
You'll want to de-escalate
the situation.
I mean, do you got any intel,
an... an address or anything?
I'll give you a lead,
but hear me on this.
You're on your own, Hutch.
- Aw, Killer.
- (dog whimpering)
I'm so sorry
that you had to see that.
My little baby should never see
those terrible, terrible people.
No.
What about them back there?
Leave no witnesses.
- Burn it down.
- You got it.
(bystanders screaming)
- (rapid gunfire)
- (screaming continues)
That was fast. Did it hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Maybe this is too soon.
Dad, really, I'm fine.
My arm's healing good.
- (ringtone playing)
- Hold on.
Max, I have to take
this damn call.
Won't be long.
(gunfire and screaming
in distance)
WYATT (over phone):
What?
LENDINA (chuckles):
Well...
that's no way to treat
your business partner.
Ex-partner.
(over phone):
This is my last shipment.
(sighs) Goodness.
My father's debt is all paid up.
I can count.
This, you know...
(choking up):
pays off the last of our debt.
Aw.
By my calculations, the debt
will never be paid off.
(scoffing):
No.
That's bullshit,
and you know it.
(laughing)
Ain't nothing funny
about what I said.
(Lendina laughing over phone)
Your father died
because he was distracted.
Are you distracted?
I'm not my dad.
It's over.
(Lendina scoffs over phone)
Well, then...
- we'll see.
- (phone beeps)
Well...
Hello?
♪ ♪
WYATT:
Hey, Max, where you going?
(door closes)
(phone vibrating)
Sheriff.
SHERIFF ABEL (over phone):
You can just call me Abel.
Sheriff, I need to make sure
Wyatt hasn't forgotten
who he works for.
Take something
that really matters to him.
Got it.
- Mom, it's your turn.
- Oh. (clears throat)
- BRADY: Hey, Mom?
- Yes?
- Is Dad in trouble again?
- Mm.
Why? Do you know something?
No, that's why... No.
- Mm, I'm sure he'll be...
- (knocking at door)
No, honey. Let me.
Hamburgers!
And s'mores for dinner tonight.
- BRADY: Ah, so nutritious.
- SAMMY: Yay.
Your dad's running late.
But come with me.
I promise you
it's the way to go.
(Sammy chuckles)
BRADY: Sammy, come on.
Help me pack up.
- You-you talked to Hutch?
- Talk later. Got to move.
BECCA:
Okay.
(sighs)
Walk in...
real smooth.
Keep everything room temp.
Yeah.
No escalating.
De-escalate.
Lead by example.
(inhales sharply)
"Hey, fellas. What a mix-up."
♪ ♪
It's a big shipment, but...
I guarantee you
we can do more next time.
Except those paintings
are a bitch.
But you got to see
what's in here.
Here is the special thing
the boss lady asked for.
- (muffled grunting)
- Wyatt's spoiled son.
(muffled):
Wait! Wait!
No! Wait! (continues shouting)
Now, I want you to tell
the boss that I said it was
- a pleasure to be of service.
- (banging on van door)
Okay? You understand?
MAX (muffled):
Hey!
Or do I need to get
a fucking translator?
(muffled grunting
and shouting continue)
I need to get
a fucking translator.
(liquid pouring)
Hey, fellas.
What the fuck?
How did you get in here?
- The door.
- (guns cocking)
Is that gasoline?
You're quick.
Now, listen,
I could torch this money,
it'd go up in a flash,
and whatever's
in those barrels would go boom,
and most of you
wouldn't make it out of here,
and those who do
will have to answer to Lendina.
I'm guessing this is all hers.
So then what the fuck
do you want?
Okay, well...
I want a break.
A break?
I just want a fucking break.
So if I walk out of here,
you leave me
and my family alone,
'cause that's all I want.
To de-escalate this.
(scoffs)
Are you fucking kidding me?
From the moment you've shown up,
you've put my men
in the fucking ER.
There's no way
you are just some family man.
De-escalate? Fuck you.
Plummerville was A-OK
before you showed up.
Wherever I go...
I could so easily
kill you right now.
But...
You're lucky.
You catch me on a good day.
Go.
Get the fuck out of here.
Go before I change my mind.
(guns clicking)
(banging on van door)
(grunts)
SHERIFF ABEL:
Fucking pick him up.
Jesus.
MAX (muffled):
No! Help me!
Help me!
No! (shouts)
(muffled shouting continues)
(engine starts)
(tires screech)
(engine revving)
(sighs)
SHERIFF ABEL:
You're on my last fucking nerve.
I told you
to get the fuck out...
- (clattering)
- (men yelling, groaning)
- (rapid gunfire)
- Who the fuck is this guy?!
(men yelling)
- SHERIFF ABEL: Wait! Wait!
- (gunshots)
(men screaming)
(gunfire continues)
(grunting and groaning)
(Max gasping, breathing heavily)
(choking)
(Max whimpering,
breathing heavily)
(gasping)
(man yells)
(grunting and groaning continue)
(whirring)
(straining)
(blade whining)
(whining stops)
(Max gasping, whimpering)
HUTCH:
(grunts) Okay, let's go.
(pained grunting)
- Stop, motherfucker!
- (gun fires)
(gun clicking)
- (clicking)
- (grunts, pants)
(groans)
("If I Ruled the World"
by Tony Bennett playing)
(panting)
- ♪ If I ruled the world ♪
- SHERIFF ABEL: Fuck! Fuck!
♪ Every day would be
the first day of spring ♪
♪ Every heart would have
a new song ♪
- ♪ To sing ♪
- Fuck! Fuck!
♪ And we'd sing of the joy ♪
♪ Every morning would bring ♪
- ♪ If I... ♪
- (song fades)
LENDINA:
How much did we lose?
Everything.
- The cash, the chemicals.
- The bio-case.
No.
GUARD:
All of it.
GUARD 2:
Wiped out all our men
and got away with Wyatt's son.
Who is this zealot?
Nothing about him is turning up.
There is one oddity.
He had a family with him.
LENDINA: My valuable shipment
was blown up
by a man who's a tourist
on a fucking family vacation?
Does nobody play
by the rules anymore?
Jesus fucking Christ.
I don't know
who the fuck you are,
but you crossed a line, asshole.
- (phone vibrating)
- Sheriff.
What do you know
about this threat?
I don't know, okay?
But I sent you the pictures.
And they haven't checked out
of the hotel.
You might want to bring
some others, all right?
H-How many of your...
I guess soldiers
can you bring with you?
- Because he's...
- Oh, shut the fuck up.
I'm on my way.
This guy's an idiot.
Hey, son.
Look who finally shows up.
Hey, Dad. Everybody good?
DAVID:
Oh, everybody's doing great.
Your son swings an axe
like a pro.
SAMMY:
Dad.
- Sammy.
- SAMMY: Where were you?
Oh, hey, Brady, that's Max.
I brought him here, so be cool.
We good?
Yeah.
BRADY:
Let's go inside.
How'd you get that shiner,
country boy?
Kidding.
You staying for the night?
I-I would love to stay, but, um,
I still got some
heavy lifting to do.
(chuckling):
Oh, you're...
you're right about that.
Let's go, Sammy.
Come on.
You can light the fire.
(sighs)
(Becca scoffs)
Arm's length, Hutch.
You were supposed to keep
danger at arm's length.
I didn't mean to...
Hutch, you promised me.
You promised.
(sniffles)
You broke your promise.
I don't have...
have control over this.
I'm just realizing that.
You should get away...
(sighs)
...from me.
Becca.
Becca, I'm not asking.
You don't tell me what to do.
You are a lot of things...
but most of all, you're a dad.
And you're my guy.
So go fix that shit.
Come on, son.
Answer your damn phone.
Come on, come on, come on.
(cork pops from bottle)
(drink pouring)
You.
What the hell are you
still doing in my town?
Well, I could use your help.
(grunting)
Oh, no, no.
Be cool. I've got your son.
- He's okay.
- You mess with my son,
you're a dead man.
No, you don't understand.
He's totally safe
with some people...
What the fuck
do you mean by safe?
(both grunting)
From Lendina.
(Wyatt breathing heavily)
We want the same things.
(grunts)
(sighs)
You burned all of it?
Yep.
You burned the money?
And whatever was in
those chemical barrels.
Th-they exploded.
You burned all of it?
I-I saved your son.
Thanks.
She's pure fucking evil, man.
She killed my dad.
Used Abel to take my son.
Backstabbing son of a bitch.
This empire that I inherited
from my dad
came with a lot of debts.
Wild Bill.
He was a lot of fun,
but the man liked the bad odds.
And I'm still paying
for his mistakes.
Lendina has run this town
for two fucking generations.
I will not let my son
be forced into this.
I know what you mean.
So wh-what would she do
if she found out
you burned her stash?
You burned it.
Okay. What would she do?
("Das Boot" by Beginner playing)
Okay, how-how do I put this?
♪ Dope dope beat beat,
dope dope... ♪
WYATT:
She's eradicated
entire bloodlines for less.
She's absolutely batshit crazy.
Vicious.
♪ Dope dope rhymes rhymes ♪
♪ Dope dope, dope dope,
dope dope... ♪
Where is she right now?
She's definitely
on her way here.
(song continues
with lyrics in German)
Ma'am, it's time.
- (song stops)
- (elevator rattling)
(dog whines)
♪ ♪
LENDINA:
Hit it, motherfuckers.
KARTOUSH:
Let's move.
(engines revving)
WYATT: My dad planned
to fight Lendina.
She got to him first.
I'm not sure
if any of it still works.
I wouldn't.
WYATT:
Now we lead her to
the most dangerous place
in Plummerville.
- Closed for repairs.
- Hey, we just got here.
So sorry, folks, but it's got
to be made safe. Here you go.
- You got free churros.
- Your website didn't say
- anything about...
- You're gonna get a free refund.
Let's go! Let's go now!
♪ ♪
Must be hard to say goodbye
to this place, huh?
(scoffs) -You know,
when my dad brought us here,
- these rides...
- You kidding me? It's a curse.
Water park leaks
like a motherfucker.
The fun house is nothing
but headaches.
No kid wants exactly
what their dad built.
Really?
That's actually good to hear.
Who the fuck is that?
HUTCH:
Harry?
You know, this place is much
smaller than I remember, man.
(laughing):
Oh, man.
- This is my brother Harry.
- Wyatt Martin.
- Good to meet you.
- What are you doing here?
I sensed you was having
an existential crisis.
♪ ♪
(grunting)
Okay, I want to talk to you.
Hey. (whistles)
Yeah. Good boy.
Yeah, go on. Go on. Go.
(wolf dog howling)
(grunting)
♪ ♪
(lighter clinks, ignites)
You know, Pops, remember that
you left us alone in that lodge
for two nights straight
by ourselves.
And all we had to eat
was hot dogs and s'mores.
That's partly why I'm a vegan.
Well, you guys were safe.
Mostly.
Did you ever worry
about us, though? I mean...
like about who we'd become.
You mean like
how you worry about Brady?
- Yeah. I want him to be...
- (David chuckles)
A better man than you.
Yeah.
And he will be.
Believe it or not,
you guys are improvements on me.
(chuckling)
HUTCH:
Hey, listen.
- You know where you're headed?
- I got it.
Okay.
You need any help up there?
Yeah, I got something,
uh, else in mind.
♪ ♪
Time's up!
They're in the water park.
Fun.
- What's that?
- Some sort of cabin.
We think his family's there.
Take a team and go there.
- And, Kartoush...
- Yes?
Scorched earth.
No prisoners.
...then open it
and put chocolate inside?
(conversation continues
indistinctly)
BRADY:
You know what you're doing?
SAMMY:
Yes, I do.
- BRADY: Nice, capture.
- SAMMY: Now I can't...
BRADY: On the offense,
just jump here and...
BECCA:
Um, kids?
I'm gonna go for a walk.
- Have fun.
- What?
You got this, Brady?
SAMMY:
What if I just move mine?
Yeah.
Be safe.
MAX:
That's a good one. Um...
- BRADY: Okay, tie game?
- MAX: I'm okay.
BRADY:
No, it's fine. It's a tie game.
Okay, so...
♪ ♪
Liking the new look.
Really suits you, Abel.
You kidnapping puto.
Cute.
You really lit a fuse
when you did that.
No.
I think you did that
the moment
you underestimated me.
See, I've been pushed around
for long enough,
so from now on,
I'm the fucking man.
And this is my fucking town.
So give me your guns,
walk in front of me
back to the car,
and maybe I'll get you
out of this.
Maybe.
What if we say no?
All hell breaks loose.
- Yeah, we'll take that. Yeah.
- Yeah, we'll take that.
(laughs)
What an ass pain he is.
- (over radio): Take him out.
- Copy that.
("Ring of Fire" by Des Rocs
playing over speakers)
GOON:
Move in!
Go, go, go!
- (sighs heavily)
- (goons shouting)
Go, go, go!
(yells)
(electronic chiming)
(bell clanging)
(screaming)
♪ Love is a burning thing ♪
♪ And it makes a fiery ring ♪
- ♪ Bound by wild desire ♪
- (goons shouting)
- Fuck him up!
- Go, go, go!
♪ I fell into a ring of fire ♪
(gunfire)
♪ I fell into ♪
- What the fuck is this?
- ♪ A burning ring of fire ♪
♪ I went down, down, down... ♪
- Huh?
- (all yell)
Oh, God!
(screaming)
(gunfire continues)
♪ The ring of fire,
the ring of fire ♪
(goons groaning)
♪ The taste of love is sweet ♪
♪ When hearts like ours meet ♪
♪ I fell for you like a child ♪
♪ Oh, but the fire ♪
♪ The fire went wild ♪
- Let's go!
- ♪ I fell into ♪
(distant):
♪ A burning ring of fire ♪
♪ I went down, down, down ♪
♪ And the flames
went higher... ♪
- (creaking)
- Oh, shit.
Open fire!
Move.
♪ ♪
(creaking)
HUTCH:
Hey, fellas.
(whirring)
- (rapid beeping)
- What the fuck?
♪ I fell into
a burning ring of fire ♪
♪ I went down, down, down ♪
♪ And the flames went higher ♪
GOON:
You can't hide!
(whimpering)
GOON:
There he is! Ball pit!
Go, go! Shoot!
(panicked grunting)
♪ And it burns, burns, burns ♪
Fuck him up!
♪ The ring of fire ♪
- (whirring)
- Shit.
♪ The ring of fire. ♪
(song ends)
HUTCH:
Hey, Wyatt, meet me at the pool.
WYATT (over radio):
I'm on my way.
(breathing heavily)
(goons shouting)
Watch the six!
(barks, whines)
(gasps)
- HUTCH: Hey. Good boy.
- (whines)
Yeah. I owe you one.
Go. Run.
- (wolf dog howling)
- GOON: Get over there! Go!
- (wolf dog snarling)
- (goons screaming)
- (whimpers) Fucking A!
- (indistinct shouting)
- (gun clicks)
- Fuck.
- (bullet strikes)
- (groaning)
GOON:
Got you now, motherfucker.
(panting)
GOON:
You're gonna die, old man.
(pained yelling)
You motherfucker.
(gurgling)
(grunts)
GOON:
Got eyes.
(water rushing)
- (grunts)
- (gunfire continues)
Huh? What the fuck?
- (grunts)
- (screaming)
(groans)
- (gunfire continues)
- DAVID: Hey, Hutch!
Dad, cover me!
- (gunfire stops)
- (high-pitched ringing)
(groaning)
(grunts)
(ringing stops)
♪ ♪
Dad!
Fuck you!
GOON:
There he is!
- Still not dead!
- Take him out!
We got him!
(groans)
Dad!
♪ ♪
Whoever's in there never leaves.
HARRY: The Mansell's
family directives.
Eighth principle:
In darkness,
let fear enhance your strike.
(groaning)
(whooshing)
(screaming)
- (whooshing)
- (grunts, screams)
(goon screams)
What the fuck?
(grunts fiercely)
HARRY:
Turn challenge
into opportunity.
The fifth principle.
(yells)
Whoa, whoa. Hey, hey, man.
Don't do this.
I'm just doing my job, kid.
BRADY:
Max!
- Protect Sammy!
- (Sammy screams)
Last man to challenge me,
I took his head.
Peekaboo.
(short grunt)
Don't bring a machete
to a fucking katana duel.
That's principle number one.
- (straining)
- (goon choking)
GOON (straining):
Please... don't k-kill me.
(both breathing heavily)
- (goon groaning)
- (door creaking)
(goon coughing)
(chuckles)
What's up, nephew?
(sighs)
Your father would be
proud of you, Brady.
- Wyatt. Hey.
- Hey.
I got shot in the fucking leg.
(groans)
(panting)
- (groaning)
- Ah, fuck.
All right.
Just hold that on there.
Thanks.
All right.
- Loaded. Ready to rock.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna check on my dad.
- All right.
- Dad?
- (someone whistling a melody)
(whistling continues)
Lendina?
(whistling stops)
Who sent you?
Nobody.
I'm here with my family,
making memories.
What are you doing here?
I'm here for you.
You know, I like
this little empire of mine.
Operative or a family man,
it doesn't fucking matter
because what I don't like
is people who try to fuck up
my peace of mind.
But, you know,
I'm just like that.
(fierce yelling)
(fierce yelling continues)
LENDINA:
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Mr. Making Memories.
What happened
to mai tais on the beach?
You just go and leave
a trail of destruction
everywhere you go.
Do you know how important
this town is for my business?
What the fuck are you thinking?
FBI park ranger.
Fuck, you are a nobody.
And now you're gonna
lose everything.
And do you want
to know why, buddy?
'Cause you fucked
with the wrong bitch.
Take him out.
I'm bored with him.
(grunts)
(gunshot)
(screams):
No!
- (screaming)
- WYATT: Fuck! Fuck!
(grunts)
Motherfucker.
(grunts weakly)
Puñeta.
LENDINA:
Lay down, fuck face.
You think you can
get away with this?
You need a lesson, asshole.
(groaning)
Fuck your memories,
fuck your family,
and most of all, fuck you.
Die, fucker.
(straining)
- (whooshing)
- (grunts)
Oh, fuck.
(panting)
Who are you?
I'm his better half.
(slow, heavy breathing)
(Lendina whimpers)
(Hutch grunting)
(chuckling)
(distorted grunt)
HUTCH:
Becca!
♪ The whispers in the morning ♪
("The Power of Love"
by Celine Dion playing)
♪ Of lovers sleeping tight ♪
(grunts, groans)
♪ Are rolling by
like thunder now ♪
- (radio beeps)
- (straining): Kill her.
♪ As I look in your eyes ♪
Don't fuck with a mama bear.
♪ I hold on to your body... ♪
- Hutch.
- (groans)
GOON:
You heard the boss. Kill her.
DAVID:
Fire...
in the fucking hole!
Crazy gringo!
♪ A love that I could ♪
- (goons screaming)
- ♪ Not forsake ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm your lady ♪
♪ And you are my man ♪
♪ Whenever you reach for me ♪
♪ I'm gonna do
all that I can... ♪
Are they gonna be okay?
Yeah. It's just another
Mansells vacation.
♪ We're heading for something ♪
- (camera winds, clicks)
- ♪ Somewhere I've never been ♪
♪ Sometimes I am frightened ♪
♪ But I'm ready to learn ♪
♪ Of the power of love ♪
♪ The power of love ♪
♪ Sometimes I am frightened ♪
♪ But I'm ready to learn ♪
♪ Of the power of love. ♪
AGENT:
We're not gonna ask again.
Who are you guys?
Us? We're, uh...
(clicks tongue)
We're married.
Yeah. We're married.
(phone vibrating)
(sighs)
Yeah.
(indistinct shouting over phone)
...Hutch and Rebecca Mansell...
(continues indistinctly)
Sir, I cannot do that.
There are bodies all over.
- This is like a war zone. I...
- (indistinct shouting)
- I don't give a fuck...
- Yes, sir.
(shouting continues)
Yes, sir, I hear you.
Loud and clear, sir. Yes.
(click, dial tone drones)
You're free to go.
Get the keys.
For the cuffs.
(door opens)
BECCA:
Hutch, after this vacation...
HUTCH:
Yeah?
- (whistles)
- (wolf dog barks)
BECCA:
...we need a vacation.
("More Today Than Yesterday"
by Spiral Starecase playing)
We did it.
(family laughing)
We went to Plummerville,
and we came back in one piece.
BECCA:
Yes. Yes.
Almost.
- BECCA (chuckling): Almost.
- Now, listen.
One thing that'll help us
never forget.
- So let's hear it for Sammy.
- (whooping)
BRADY: Wh-What is
the idea with this one?
- BECCA: Max and Wyatt!
- (Hutch chuckling)
You should call them sometime.
HUTCH: Honey, I think we've
caused them enough trouble.
SAMMY: I can't wait
for the next summer break.
You'll come with us,
right, Grandpa?
DAVID:
You got it, Sammy.
SAMMY:
I miss that ball pit.
BRADY (laughs):
Look at that.
I remember that.
Did you take that?
SAMMY:
Yeah.
♪ Every day's a new day ♪
♪ In love with you ♪
♪ With each day comes a new way
of loving you ♪
♪ Every time I kiss your lips ♪
♪ My mind starts to wander ♪
♪ And if all my dreams
come true ♪
♪ I'll be spending time
with you ♪
♪ Oh, I love you more today ♪
♪ Than yesterday ♪
♪ But not as much ♪
♪ As tomorrow ♪
♪ I love you more today ♪
♪ Than yesterday ♪
♪ But, darling, not as much ♪
♪ As tomorrow ♪
♪ Tomorrow's date means ♪
♪ Springtime's just
a day away ♪
♪ Cupid, we don't need ya now ♪
♪ Be on your way ♪
♪ I thank the Lord
for love like ours ♪
♪ That grows ever stronger ♪
♪ And I always will be true ♪
♪ I know you feel
the same way, too ♪
♪ Oh, I love you more today ♪
♪ Than yesterday ♪
♪ But not as much ♪
♪ As tomorrow ♪
♪ I love you more today
than yesterday ♪
♪ But only half as much ♪
♪ As tomorrow ♪
♪ Every day's a new day ♪
♪ Every time I love ya ♪
♪ Every way's a new way ♪
- ♪ Every day's a new day. ♪
- (song fades)
♪ ♪
(music ends)