Master Han!
What is it?
The Doctor is coming.
Stall her.
Go.
Go get Li!
The Doctor! Li, the Doctor!
The Doctor!
Welcome to Han Academy.
Are you looking to learn Kung Fu?
Never too late to start,
even for an old woman.
We start with jacket on - jacket off.
Take off jacket, put on jacket.
I know he told you to stall me.
I did nothing of the sort.
He did ask, sorry.
Go.
Where is my son?
Shall we get tea?
I'm not here for tea.
Where is Li?
Kung Fu is very empowering--
Uncle...
...with all due respect.
I already lost one son to your "path."
I will not lose another.
I understand.
I know what Li means to you,
but I won't have him put in harm's way.
We both agree.
If you could only see how Kung Fu helps him.
Each time life knocked me down, Kung Fu
helped me find my way back to the proper path.
This is for you.
What's this?
I got a new position at a hospital in New York.
New York?
It's a chance to restart for both of us.
Why two hats?
So you can give one to Li when he finds the
courage to come out from behind your screen.
Very smart.
Your mother.
Were you even going to ask me?
I was training, not fighting.
Hey!
Can I have your gloves?!
Whatever.
Oh my god.
See, the run up is key.
But the balance and the jump sells it.
Now you try.
I don't think I'm going to master this one.
You will.
One day, when you need it.
See, the run up is key.
How are you, Li?
Are we loving New York yet?
More missing Beijing.
The school misses you too.
Wait a minute...
Say hi!
Shifu...
I've made a new friend here,
who asked me to teach him Kung Fu.
Do you think Kung Fu can help your friend?
I think so.
Anything that helps others and
benefits yourself is a good thing.
...but downtown price is lower.
Please?
Okay okay, take it.
Thank you.
Free pizza, freshly made.