[♪ Melancholic music playing]
Okay. How about...
a rocket dog with space chips?
Spaghetti with meteors?
Galactic grape cup?
[sighs]
Elio, you have
to eat something.
Do you remember what your mom
used to order for you?
[sighs]
[friend] Major Solís,
what are you doing here?
[Solís] Hey!
Yeah, I-I'm with my nephew.
I'm trying to get him to eat.
[friend]
Oh, right. Your nephew.
I heard about your brother
and his wife. I'm so sorry.
[Solís] Thank you.
We're managing.
[friend] What about
the astronaut program?
- Weren't you about...
- [Solís] No. Not anymore.
The, um--
The timing just isn't right.
[friend] Of course.
But it's-- But it's been great
spending time
with my new roommate.
Right, buddy?
[gasps] Oh, no.
[indistinct excited chatter]
[laughs]
[♪ Mysterious music playing]
[recording speaking Spanish]
[recording speaking Italian]
[child's voice] Hello from
the children of Planet Earth.
[museum narrator]
Since the dawn of time,
humans have gazed at the stars
and wondered...
are we alone?
Voyager is our attempt
to find out.
This intrepid explorer is
on a mission,
traveling farther
than any human has ever gone,
to the distant reaches
of the cosmos and beyond.
Voyager will never see those
who made it again.
It will drift on,
solitary and alone.
But maybe one day,
distant worlds
will receive its message
and Voyager
will complete its mission,
proving we aren't so alone
after all.
[Solís] Elio! Elio!
[sighs] Elio...
Are you-- Are you hurt?
What happened?
Is life really out there,
Tía Olga?
What?
[Olga stammers]
Come on.
You can't run away
like that, Elio.
[Voyager recording
speaking Serbian]
speaking Dutch]
[recording] I would like
to extend the greetings
of the government
and the people of Canada.
[overlapping
Voyager recordings]
[recordings continue]
[child's voice] Hello from
the children of Planet Earth.
[tuning feedback]
Oh, wait.
- [zipper closes]
- [sighs]
Okay.
[♪ Talking Heads
"Once in a Lifetime" playing]
Elio!
Subtitle | www.movieddl.me
[snores]
- [♪ Mysterious music playing]
- Huh?
[gasps]
[♪ Music crescendoes]
- Hey.
- [exclaims]
[both groan]
Are you Elio?
Who wants to know?
You put flyers up
for a Ham Radio Club?
Uh... [chuckles]
Uh, I-I am Elio Solís,
president and leader
of the Ham Radio Club
of this beach.
Cool. I'm Bryce.
Great, cool, awesome.
Did you bring it?
Oh-Oh, yeah.
It's my dad's ham radio,
but I have my own call sign.
It's PXLOL... [chuckles]
...which sometimes
makes people I talk to laugh.
How far have you called?
On Friday I talked to...
Ohio.
Oh.
If I can pair these together,
I can double their reach.
Okay, you can go now.
Go? Wait.
Where's everyone else?
Unfortunately, most of our
members came down with, uh...
amnesia and forgot to come,
but I'll see you at the
next meetup in three months!
- What's up, Bryce?
- Hey.
Oh. Oh. Oh.
- One, two...
- [Bryce's friend] Oh.
[Bryce]
You almost messed up there.
Hey. Uh...
- [Bryce] Uh-huh.
- Oh.
[Bryce] Oh, yeah.
- Swoosh!
- Nice. [chuckles]
This is Caleb.
He wanted to come too.
Oh. Hey.
What's with the hat?
Uh... [clears throat]
Like I said,
the meetup's been postponed.
Shingles is no joke.
I thought it was amnesia.
Oh, my gosh, you're right.
It's spreading.
You better go
before you catch it. Bye!
- Yo, what's up with this guy?
- Dude, chill.
[Bryce] He's the kid
whose parents died.
Hey, that's
classified information.
As leader of this radio club,
I hereby...
- [mysterious sounds playing]
- [Elio gasps]
- Whoa.
- Did you do that?
Shh, shh, shh.
No.
- Is this supposed to happen?
- Don't. Stop it!
Hello? Hello? Can you hear me?
- Let me see that.
- Don't touch that.
- I was just looking at it.
- I have to respond.
- Let go!
- Quit it.
[groans] No!
[mysterious sounds stop]
- [gasps]
- Yo, that was not my fault.
- I-I didn't mean to...
- [growls]
- Uh...
- Oh, come on.
You suborbital, gaseous...
waste of mass!
- Whoa.
- Activate supernova blast!
[Caleb] Get off of me,
you little freak.
- Come on, guys, stop!
- [Caleb] He bit me!
Hey, what are you doing?
[Elio snarls]
Unbelievable!
Fighting on the beach,
skipping school?
Am I going to have to put
a tracker on you?
- [Olga sighs]
- [Caleb grunts]
[Olga]Now your eye. Ay Mamá.
The doctor said not
to touch it for two weeks.
- Elio!
- Oh.
You meant starting now.
This is serious!
What were you thinking?
I was minding my own business,
taking in the night air
and suddenly these ruffians
attacked me.
No, no, no.
Look at me in the eye
and for once,
tell me the truth.
[speaking other language]
No. I'm not learning Elioese.
[speaking Elioese]
[chuckles, growls]
Major Solís.
You going
to the seminar tonight?
There'll be a speaker from the
Astronaut Selection Program.
[sighs]
No. No, no.
Something came up.
[friend]
Oh, is this the nephew
we've heard so much about?
Yes, that's him.
- Gloodle!
- Stop it!
I don't know
if this is boundary testing...
...or sleep regression, or...
[groans]
Which one of these is you?
I don't know,
but I think that one is you.
[muffled screech]
Okay, I've got
one last meeting.
So, I need you to sit here
and not move or speak
or injure yourself
for ten minutes.
[sighs]
I have enough
to deal with already.
[sighs]
[soldier] What's with
this emergency meeting?
Oh, you didn't hear?
Melmac thinks he found aliens.
[soldier chuckles]
This ought to be good.
[indistinct whispering]
All right, Mr. Melmac,
let's hear it.
Major... [winces]
Major Solís, earlier today,
I found this signal coming
from interstellar space.
[mysterious sounds playing]
[Olga] Melmac, please.
- It's late...
- Wait, wait, wait.
Listen closely.
[child's voice, distorted]
Hello, Planet Earth.
In 1977, NASA launched the...
- The Golden Record.
- The Golden Record! Yes.
- The what?
- The Golden Record, sir,
was Earth's
message in a bottle.
[child's voice] Hello from
the children of Planet Earth.
Don't you see?
[child's voice, distorted]
Hello, Planet Earth.
I think someone
in interstellar space
found our message
and is sending it back to us
as a reply!
- Melmac...
- Major...
- Major!
We can't just leave it
like this, we have to respond.
I've already rerouted
every satellite
to send the signal back.
Sure, it might cause
a few system failures.
Whoop. Sorry.
Maybe a small electrical fire,
but it would be worth it
for first contact!
I have everything cued up
and ready to go.
Just say the word!
If someone or something
is calling out to Earth,
who on Earth do you want
taking that call?
- You...
- [gasps]
- ...should go home.
- Oh.
- Take a week.
- [soldier] Take two weeks.
No. You got to believe me.
Major, please!
They're out there!
Major! [screams] Unhand me!
[sighs] May I remind everyone
that we are orbital analysts.
We track space debris,
not rogue UFO signals.
Let's just... [sighs]
Let's just take five.
It's been a long night.
What a nut job.
[♪ Tense music playing]
This is Elio Solís
of the planet Earth. Uh...
I come in peace...
and I'm super excited
to join you. Uh...
I'm creative, hardworking...
shredded.
Uh, so please come and get me.
I'll be waiting.
Okay, bye. Love you.
Yes.
Yes!
[exclaims]
[chuckles]
[Olga] Oh, no.
Time is of the essence.
They could be here any minute.
I got to pack!
I take full responsibility,
but... [chuckles] ...I mean,
you have kids, right?
I'll be out of your way soon.
Don't worry.
Just need a few snacks
for the road.
Elio!
Sorry, ma'am. What was that?
Which flavor will you
miss the least? ¿Fuego?
- Fuego. Yeah.
- I-I understand.
Should I bring forks, or would
they think they're weapons?
Not worth the risk!
I'll bring spoons.
Nice, peaceful spoons.
- Where's my good cape?
- You too, ma'am.
- It's not in the wash, is it?
- Thank you.
- Ah. Here it is!
- Elio...
Blue or green? Which one says,
"Take me with you,"
but not in a desperate way?
Elio, stop! Please!
Aliens are not coming for you.
But that guy said...
You're out of control.
You got in a fight.
You shut down power
to the whole base
and I almost lost my job!
[Olga sighs]
We have to try
something different.
Boarding school? You're trying
to get rid of me.
No, this is just
their sleep away camp.
It's just a couple of weeks.
I can't go.
They're coming tonight.
You need to make friends
or just a friend.
I don't care about friends.
I need to meet aliens.
Why?
Because there's 500 million
habitable planets out there
and one of them's
got to want me!
Because obviously you don't!
Of course, I do! We're family!
You're not my family!
[sighs]
Your life isn't
up there, Elio.
It's down here.
[grunts]
[Olga]
I-I can't deal with this.
I don't know if anybody
can deal with this.
[sighs]
When I drop him off tomorrow,
I'm going to see if they can
enroll him in the fall.
I know,
but this just isn't how
I thought my life would be.
[narrator on recording]
It's an ancient human theme.
You can find it
in virtually every culture,
in, uh, religion,
folklore, superstition
- and now in science.
- [Elio crying]
The search for life elsewhere
is remarkable in our age,
because this is the first time
that we can actually do
something besides speculation.
We can send spacecraft
to nearby planets.
We can use
large radio telescopes
to see if there is any message
being sent to us lately...
and it touches to the deepest
of human concerns.
Are we alone?
[whistle blows]
[camper]
No contact! No contact!
[whistle blows]
[Olga] You know I went here,
too, when I was a kid.
You might not believe me
right now...
but this will be good for you.
Oh.
Counselor Truman,
could I have a word?
Of course, Major.
[gasps]
We got in so much trouble...
because of you.
Yeah. Thanks a lot.
- [Caleb grunts]
- [exclaims]
[Caleb]
Better watch your back.
- Yeah.
- [sighs]
[thunder rumbling]
[static on Ham radio]
Ugh.
[sighs]
[Caleb] He's going to be
so freaked out!
[Bryce] Shh. Follow my lead.
- [Caleb giggling]
- [camper] Shh, shh.
Quiet. Quiet.
We're not going to
hurt him, right?
- Just scare him a little?
- Come on, it'll be funny.
[gasps]
- [campers chuckling]
- Shut up! You'll wake him up.
- [Caleb] Come on.
- [camper] Quiet, quiet!
- [camper] Shh, shh, shh.
- [thunderclap]
[gasps]
[Caleb] Greetings, Earthling.
We come in peace!
[Bryce] Where did he go?
[panting]
Athena 5, there is
a decommissioned satellite
headed your way.
I'm calculating a new
flight path for you. Standby.
- [beeping]
- [astronaut] Go ahead, Montez.
Minus 53, plus 32, roll seven.
[astronaut] Yeah, copy that.
[Olga] Sorry about the scare.
There's been a lot of
satellite interference today.
[astronaut] Roger that.
Athena 5, over and out.
[sighs]
[pulsing]
[whirring]
[static on radio]
[musical notes playing]
- [interference]
- [musical notes continue]
[bleeping]
Uh...
[gasps]
[Caleb] Elio!
Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
[camper] Elio!
[Caleb] Don't you want to
hang out with us?
[camper] I thought you wanted
to meet some aliens.
[Bryce] Come on, it'll be fun.
[grunts, pants]
[Bryce]
He's out here somewhere.
[Caleb] Come on, Space Boy!
We know you're out there.
[punching keys]
[static]
[high-frequency humming]
[continuous humming
and beeping]
[gasps]
[phone buzzing]
- [electrical fizzing]
- [Olga startles]
[phone beeps]
[Bryce] Gotcha!
Yeah... You found me.
This is payback.
Eh, it's okay.
You don't need to pay me back.
Wait. What is that?
- Hope you like how it tastes.
- [campers laughing]
There's something back there.
- Look!
- Argh!
[breathing heavily]
You're so dead, Solís.
[Bryce] Hey, hold on.
Wait.
[Elio yells]
[Elio panting]
[gasps]
[panting]
[low humming]
[gasping]
[rhythmic pulsing]
Please.
[elongated gasp]
Yes!
It's happening!
It's really happening.
I knew it! I knew it!
Yes!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Yes, yes, yes! Yes, yes, yes!
[panting]
[Elio laughing]
Whoa-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Thank you!
[whooping]
Yes! Yeah!
[laughing]
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Oh!
[Elio exhales]
[chuckling]
Wow.
- [pulsing]
- [Elio gasps]
[panting]
[giggles] Hi.
[electronic burbling]
I knew it!
I knew aliens were looking
for me. You saved my life!
I promise I'll pull my weight
on this, uh... spaceship?
Is this a spaceship?
Anyway, where should we start?
Probes? Samples?
I've got plenty.
[musical notes playing]
[gasps]
[Ooooo, distorted]
Testing, testing...
[clear] testing.
Can you understand me now?
Yes. Wow.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
I am Ooooo,
a liquid supercomputer.
Allow me to adjust
your gravity.
- Oh, no, no, no. I'm fine.
- Gravity on.
- [thud]
- [Elio groans]
A welcome glass of glorp,
compliments of
the Communiverse.
Oh! Thank you.
Wait. The what?
Whoa.
[gasping]
[Ooooo] Welcome to
the Communiverse,
a pangalactic organization
of the advanced species
of the cosmos.
Whoa.
The greatest minds
of the universe come here
to share knowledge,
innovation...
[ambassador] And recipes!
Welcome!
- Welcome.
- Lovely.
- [gasps]
- Greetings, Ambassadors!
Absolutely ecstatic
to make your acquaintance.
Oop. You've run dry.
Let me top you off, old brick.
Huh. Thank you.
Hmm, yes.
One cerebellum, four lobes,
and... [gasps] a medulla.
Do you mind if I take
a little peek inside and see?
Questa, don't mind read him,
you've just met him.
[chuckles]
So sorry about that.
I am Questa of Gom.
Helix of Falluvinum. Mwah.
Tegmen of Tegmeg.
And you are?
[gasps]
Elio Solís of, uh... Earth!
A toast to our new candidate,
Elio Solís of Uh-Earth.
[Communiverse members
shouting]
- [ambassador 3] There he is!
- [member] Elio Solís!
[member 2] Look, it's Elio!
[ambassador 4]
It's a new candidate.
Salutations!
I love your eye!
[chuckling]
We search the universe
for like-minded souls
and new species,
and we think you're
an excellent candidate
for Communiverse membership.
You mean I could stay here?
If all the members agree,
then, yes.
You'll be one of us and be the
proud bearer of one of these.
Now come,
everyone's eager to meet you.
[Questa] Each of us brings
our specialized knowledge
and interest to share.
Greetings, Naos!
[Naos] Hello. Salutations.
Naos, here, created
the Communidiscs we all use
with controls for gravity...
[Elio yells]
- [Questa] ...temperature...
- [shivering]
...and all known languages.
[gasps] You know Elioese?
[in Elioese]
[both laughing]
-Gloodle.
- Gloodle.
[ambassadors] Gloodle!
This is my most recent design.
Try it.
Hello. I am
the Universal Users Manual.
I contain the secrets
of the universe.
What is the meaning of life?
What lies beyond a black hole?
Is there a purpose to...
[Elio]
Who would win in a fight?
One gorilla with
a baseball bat or ten chimps?
None who fight
are true winners.
Huh?
[UUM sighs]
The gorilla.
Wow.
These little critters
are mimollusks.
They use nanotechnology to
construct anything you desire.
[Elio laughing]
[gasps]
Are you kidding me?
[Questa] How dashing!
[gasps] This is
the most beautiful place
I've ever seen.
This is the bathroom.
[flushing]
[all] Whee!
[all laughing]
- [Questa] Gets me every time.
- Bracing.
It's like I was always
meant to be here.
I knew you were
looking for me.
Of course we were
looking for you.
Ever since we picked up
this charming little
spacecraft you sent us.
[gasps] Voyager?
[Helix] We found it
in an asteroid field.
[Tegmen] Nice craftsmanship.
Um... thanks?
[Helix] Curious about
the species who made it,
we sent an invitation
and were delighted to receive
your planet's official reply.
[distorted] This is Elio Solis
of the planet Earth
and I'm super excited
to join you.
I'm creative, hard-working,
shredded!
[static, interference]
So, please come and get me.
I'll be waiting.
Okay, bye. Love you.
- [Tegmen] Very touching.
- We are delighted
to finally make
your acquaintance,
Leader of Uh-Earth.
Ooh.
Uh...
[Tegmen]
Why is your face melting?
Um...
- Well...
- Ambassadors,
an urgent matter
requires your attention.
It involves
the other candidate.
- Oh, him.
- [Questa] Oh, dear.
[Helix] We should hurry.
Quickly now!
[Questa] Excuse us.
Please join us.
Your technology and my weapons
would be
an unstoppable alliance.
Now, admit me
to your Communiverse!
[ambassadors muttering]
Unfortunately,
Candidate Grigon,
it is our assessment
that you are
not a fit.
I, Lord Grigon,
Blood Emperor of Hylurg,
not a fit?
Well, we believe in tolerance
and open-mindedness...
I am tolerant!
So sorry, it's not you,
it's us.
[Tegmen] I thought we said
it was him.
[Helix] Shh!
If I cannot join
the Communiverse,
then I shall take it by force!
Prepare to be conquered!
[ambassadors screaming]
[ambassador 4] What a brute!
Why did he make a new hole?
[Naos] I suggest
we run and hide.
Yes, let's go to the edge
of the cosmos
and turn off all the lights.
Uh, that includes me, right?
Oh, so sorry, candidate Solís,
we couldn't possibly accept
new members
under the current situation.
Applications
are closed indefinitely.
- But I just got here!
- [Helix] Such a shame.
Let's check back
in a few thousand years?
Perhaps one of us
could talk to Lord Grigon.
- You do it!
- Not me.
- I am shy.
- I'm busy.
- I have allergies.
- [Naos] My battery is low.
Don't worry. I'll return you
to your life on Uh-Earth
just as it was...
[echoing] was, was, was...
Just as it was...
No, no!
I'll do it.
[panting]
I'm the leader of Earth.
I'm the perfect guy
for the job.
[Helix] What did it say?
- [ambassador 4] How curious.
- [Tegmen] I do not understand.
You would talk to Lord Grigon?
[Naos] But what would you say?
Are you an expert
on conflict negotiation?
[sputters] You kidding?
My life is nothing
but conflict
and I've got the battle scars
to prove it.
It would be a welcome change
not to flee every bully
who covets our treasures.
[in alien language]
Yes. What's in it for you?
Why would you agree
to such a dangerous mission?
Because...
you need me.
And at my age,
it's really about giving back.
If you can make Grigon
go away,
we'd make you a member
on the spot.
[giggles]
Then I, the leader of Earth,
am ready to serve.
- [Tegmen] Good. Very good.
- How impressive!
- [ambassador 2] What courage!
- [Naos] Wonderful!
Candidate Solís,
you continue to surprise.
When Grigon returns,
we shall be ready for him.
Until then,
as you say on Uh-Earth.
Okay, bye. I love you.
[ambassadors, together]
Okay. Bye. I love you.
Don't worry. I got this.
You're in great hands.
[restrained shrieking]
Just one last
order of business.
Oh, yeah, of course.
While you negotiate
with the warlord,
you'll need
a temporary replacement.
[Elio] Whoa.
[Ooooo] Can I trouble you
for a DNA sample?
Sure. Where do you want it...
Argh!
Yeow! [groans]
Wow. My first probe.
[Elio laughing]
World leaders,
such as yourself,
can't just disappear.
Your planet would descend
into chaos.
[ticking]
That's what cloning clay
is for.
[bell dings]
Whoa.
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[both] Whoa.
Is this...?
Are you...?
[both] Me?
[both laugh]
Rock...
Paper...
[both] Black hole! Oh!
- Space is the best!
- Space is amazing!
In you go.
Sorry.
It's a living.
So, what is my motivation?
What do you mean?
Should I change anything
or just stick with
the low self-esteem
and desperation to belong?
What?
I'm normal, just be normal.
No weird stuff, okay?
- Okay.
Have fun.
- [blow lands]
- [Other Elio grunts]
Intriguing Uh-Earth custom.
The warlord awaits.
Oh, uh, there was, uh,
just a few things
I wanted to brush up on.
Where was that thing that knew
everything about everything?
You mean this?
Hello. I am
the Universal Users Manual.
Would you like to learn the
meaning of life now? It's a...
No. I need everything
you've got
on how to negotiate
with the warmonger.
[sighs]
Certainly.
I have chapters on leading
with empathy.
Nope.
- [UUM]Fostering connection?
- Nope.
[UUM] Making the killer deal?
Yes, that one.
Do you have a pen?
In the increasingly likely
event that you will die,
would you like to notify
your next of kin on Uh-Earth?
No, that's okay.
[UUM] Start from
a position of power.
The most important thing
is to stay calm.
Don't you tell me
to stay calm!
What is this, huh?
A camp or a fight club?
He's an innocent little boy,
and if this is what you call
"building character,"
then I'll take it up
with your-- with your boss,
- or her-- her boss.
- [Other Elio humming]
Everyone's boss!
Unacceptable!
I never should have
left you here.
Yeah, they chased me
because I'm weak and small,
but there was pizza
for dinner.
So, overall,
a pretty good night.
How's the eye? Swollen?
- Did they hurt it?
- It's fine.
I'm-I'm... I'm so sorry
I didn't check in.
Something weird was happening.
That's okay.
I was tracking this
crazy signal from space...
Are we going home?
What's for dinner?
- [static on radio]
- Um...
Mac and cheese.
I just thought
you'd be interested
because if aliens
were calling from space...
[radio announcer]
Early morning fog and clouds
along the coast...
Elio?
Are we doing regular
or white cheddar? I'm starved.
So, you-you-you don't want
to talk about aliens?
Not really. I thought it'd be
better if I just dropped it.
- [radio stations changing]
- Really?
That's... amazing.
Good for you.
Ooh!
[♪ Juan Luis Guerra
"Como Abeja Al Panal" playing]
Oh. I love this song.
[song continues playing]
[gasps]
Do you see him?
[Helix]
Yes, and he's brought his...
compatriots. Heh.
Jolly good.
Okay. Be confident. Speak
from a position of power.
[ambassador 3] He's here!
He's here. There he is.
The man of the hour.
Ah. Sorry I'm late.
So, is Lord Grigon
coming here?
Oh, no.
You will be going out there.
[yelps, grunts]
Okay, bye. Love you.
[Elio] What is this?
Red? Green?
[ship]
Welcome, Captain Solís.
You have selected
a map of our coordinates.
Cabin pressure.
Shield function.
A nutritious shake.
A breath mint.
A bladder evacuation module.
Ah, he found the mint.
You have set our destination
to your home planet.
[Elio's voice] Uh-Earth.
[ship] Confirm or cancel?
Uh...
Good luck.
[exhales]
Cancel.
[screaming]
Uh, okay, okay.
[Questa] A little to the left.
Get your nubs at ten and two.
[Elio] Whoa!
What a heroic figure he cuts.
[shrieking, crying]
[breathing heavily]
[pulsing]
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
Hi. Take me to your leader?
Okay, look him in the eye.
Stand your ground.
You're the alpha,
you're the killer.
You're... [yelps]
This is who
the Communiverse sends?
You are more puny
than I expected.
I could say the same
about you.
- What?
- Uh...
What do you need to leave
the Communiverse alone?
Hylurgians prefer to negotiate
with screams in the air.
Pull!
[creature exclaims]
[gasping]
[yelps]
[groans]
[squeaks]
[gulps]
Recoil's a little heavy.
Your turn.
Darn! I, uh,
left my arm cannon at home.
Why-Why don't we...
[yelps]
Use one of mine.
So nice of you.
Uh...
[grunts]
I-I mean, we're both leaders
and, uh...
Pull!
[exclaims]
Surely we could find something
to everyone's mutual...
[yelps]
...benefit.
Ah, trick shot.
Perhaps we are able
to communicate...
Pull!
But those
Communiverse weaklings
look at me like
some kind of monster.
How dare they reject me!
[squeaking]
[all yelp]
Well, if they don't
want you...
why not find
someone who does?
Come again?
There's got to be
a place out there
that would love to have
a strong guy like you.
But is the Communiverse not
where the greatest leaders
gather?
Am I not great?
T-Totally.
But why waste your life
trying to connect with people
who don't get you?
It's time to move on.
Right, Gri-guy?
Gri-guy?
[chuckles] Hmm, yes.
What, Workko? What is it?
Your Wrath, the princeling
wants to see you.
For the hate of...
Tell him I am busy!
So, as we were saying,
forget the Communiverse. ..
You are a father, right?
Oh. Yeah. [chuckles]
It is so difficult!
He has no concept
of the importance of my work.
I get it.
If he's too hard to handle,
then just ship him off.
That's what I did with mine.
So...
[Grigon] "Too hard to handle"?
I-I mean...
Oh, you think I cannot
handle my own son?
No, no, no.
I-I don't think that...
No! Really. Tell me what
I am doing wrong!
[yelps] It's okay.
I'm a bad parent too.
What?
None of us know
what we're doing.
We-We didn't even
want this, right?
Let me remind you
who you are dealing with!
I am Grigon,
Blood Emperor of Hylurg,
scourge of the Crab Nebula
and a great father!
Pull!
[all scream]
[stammering] Right, why don't
we take a little breather...
The negotiation is over.
Gronk!
Show the prisoner
to his quarters!
Prisoner? What?
You will watch from a cell
as I destroy
your beloved Communiverse!
No, no, wait!
He's really
turned over a new leaf.
- Hey, Elio.
- Hey, Jim. How's your back?
- Oh, you know...
- I hear ya.
Oh, camp must've
really helped.
[chuckles] I guess it did.
But he was only there
for one day.
Oh, I overheard
the colonel raving about you.
[gasps] Really? She was?
Yeah.
You've been working
really hard.
Oh, that's so good to hear.
I thought I'd never
get off her bad side.
Oopsie.
Everyone's super impressed.
[both chuckle]
Wait, please.
You made a mistake.
I'm the leader of Earth!
[groans]
[♪ Melancholic music playing]
[coughs]
[sighs]
[bones crunch]
[groans]
[grunts]
[gasps]
Uh, gravity, um... off.
Whoa.
[grunting]
Okay, th-that's enough!
Gravity back!
[grunting]
Okay. I'll just get back
to Grigon.
Uh, what haven't I tried?
"Bargaining chip"?
Like, something valuable?
[scoffs]
Where am I going to find...
[screams]
[grunting, screaming]
[panting]
[creature chittering]
[whimpers]
[straining]
[gasps]
[chittering]
[Elio whimpers]
[growling]
H-Hi, there.
[screeching]
[exclaims]
I'm too young to die.
[disc whirs, beeps]
[distorted] What's happening?
[clear] What's happening?
Whoa. Translator disc, cool.
- Are you going to eat me?
- What?
Ew. I was just swaddling you
because you seemed scared.
That's what my mom does
when I get scared.
I'm rarely unswaddled.
You're just a little kid.
So? Don't have
to be rude about it.
Oh. No, no, no.
Hey, come back!
I wasn't making fun of you!
[strains]
Uh, my name's Elio.
W-What's your name?
You really want
to know my name?
Well, I really want
to get down.
I'm Glordon! No one's ever
asked me my name before.
[Elio screams]
I mean, I ask a lot
of questions all the time.
No one ever asks me about
questions about me, though.
Like what
my favorite color is.
It's purple, if you're asking.
Are you asking?
[yelps]
[shrieks]
What's wrong with you?
That's just my carapace.
- W-What?
- I'll show you.
Ta-da!
Whoa.
Every Hylurgian gets one
when they come of age.
It's got weapons
and bombs and stuff.
Ooh, and a cup holder!
It's bespoke.
So, if Hylurgians
took off their armor,
they'd look like you?
Yeah, but nobody
would ever do that.
To expose
your soft, warm flesh
would dishonor you
and your whole family
for all eternity.
I can't wait to get installed.
I'm going to look so hot.
[alarm blaring]
[voice on PA]
Alert! A prisoner has escaped.
- Oh, no.
- Are they talking about you?
Uh, it's a complicated
political situation.
You-You wouldn't understand.
Are you
a treacherous dissident?
[guard 1] Where is he?
Check every chamber!
[Glordon] Are you an assassin?
[guard 1]
You two with me. Move!
- What'd you do?
- Uh, uh...
Come on, I'm really good
at keeping secrets.
- [guard 2] Nothing here, sir.
- [guard 1] Keep looking!
The secret is...
I'm a kid.
What? Really?
Mm-hmm.
[whispering] And I kind of
tricked the Communiverse...
- [unintelligible whispering]
- Whoa.
What?
- [whispering continues]
- Oh.
No way!
[chuckles] You're crazy.
I know and now Grigon's
going to blow everyone up
unless I can find
a bargaining chip.
Something he values, but what
does he even value? [sighs]
Well, Dad values blood, glory,
the misery of his enemies.
Ooh.
There was this one time...
Hold up. Grigon's your dad?
I thought you knew.
I look just like him.
Check it out. [grunting]
I've been working on my back.
Can I ask you a big favor?
Sure.
[Glordon]
Bargaining chip. Cool.
I've never been
a bargaining chip before.
I've been a liability.
A disappointment.
- A deduction.
- Are we almost to my ship?
Not far now. I've also been
a pillow, an enigma,
a problem, a headache.
- Little help, please.
- [strains]
Lately, I've just
been ignored,
but now my dad's finally
going to pay attention to me.
Do your parents
pay attention to you?
Well, my Aunt Olga
doesn't care.
[straining]
With me out the way
she can do
what she really wants.
Like be an astronaut
or whatever.
She gave up being an astronaut
or whatever for you?
Wow. She must really love you.
No, no, she doesn't.
But now I'm free
to join the Communiverse,
which is where I belong anyway
and that's where you come in,
bargaining chip.
- [Elio grunts]
- Whee!
- [Glordon] Ow.
- Oof!
- [Glordon strains] Wiggle.
- [rumbling]
[strains] Wiggle.
[Helix] Candidate Solís?
Sorry to bother you.
It's just that
the Hylurgian ships
seem to be pointing
their cannons at us.
Is this part
of the negotiations?
Oh, that's just a drill.
Don't worry.
[strains] Wiggle.
[Glordon laughs]
- Whoa. [grunts]
- Come on.
What are these tunnels for,
anyway?
Oh, these are the lava flumes.
They power the cannons.
Glordon, I am not fireproof!
Really? Why didn't
you say something?
Glordon!
It's okay.
Just get in my mouth.
What? No way!
Trust me.
[screaming]
Hmm.
It's, uh, actually
kind of comfy in here.
[Glordon] It is?
I've never been in there.
Hold on.
[laughs]
Yeah!
Ah. Refreshing.
[coughs]
[muffled] You okay?
[Elio] Yes!
Lower me down.
[sighs] Thanks, Glordon.
Eh. It's nothing. Up top.
How long's the flight?
Any snacks on board?
Ah, it's Candidate Solís!
I'm sure he's bringing
good news.
Oh.
Look out!
[slow-motion screaming]
I'm so excited.
- Candidate Solís?
- What's happened?
Ooooo, open a line
to Lord Grigon!
- Of course.
- Who is this?
Who is responsible for...
- You!
- [Elio] Yes.
It's me! The leader of Earth.
And the negotiation
is not over
because now I've got this!
- [Helix gasps]
- Oh, my.
[gasps] Glordon?
Yes, and-and pretty soon
he's going to be Glor-done.
Hi, Dad.
I'm a bargaining chip.
No. Say the other thing.
Oh. Help me, Father.
He overpowered me.
He's too strong. Too shredded.
Quiet, you!
[laughing]
What is that unholy sound?
Stop! Stop!
Only if you swear...
[whispering]
On your Hylurgian honor.
Oh. On your Hylurgian honor
to leave the Communiverse
in peace and never return.
My Hylurgian honor?
Do you know
what you are asking?
- I will...
- [laughing]
[groaning]
Stop!
I-I concede!
I swear on my honor...
[all gasp]
You are full of surprises.
You have my vow.
I will come to collect my son,
but if even one hair
on a single nub is harmed,
you will feel my wrath.
Well done.
I knew you had it in you.
- [ambassadors clamoring]
- Thank you.
Oh, I can't wait
for this all to be over,
and officially welcome you
into the fold.
I'm customizing your
membership badge right now.
Do you like the color?
[gasps]
It's beautiful.
And so well-deserved.
But first, let's prepare
for Lord Grigon's arrival.
Come, everyone. Chop-chop.
[ambassadors chattering]
Uh, you guys go ahead.
I'll take care
of the bargaining chip.
Very good, Candidate Solís.
Now, does anyone know
a good caterer?
[ambassadors chattering]
Oh, we did it.
[shivering]
Yeah. You were so cool.
Oh, you okay?
I've never been
outside before.
It's cold here.
[sighs] Wow!
This thing's amazing.
Watch this.
Gravity off.
Whoa.
- Whoo-hoo!
- [Elio laughs]
You think this is cool?
Come on!
Your Wrath,
the shuttle is ready.
Shall we depart?
No, not yet.
The princeling was taken
because he was vulnerable...
exposed, soft.
Prepare his carapace.
But that will take time,
Your Bloodness...
Do it!
We will perform Glordon's
ceremony on the Communiverse
and they will quiver
at the full might of Hylurg!
[Glordon chuckles]
- [Elio] Ready?
- Yes.
No.
0-okay, yes!
On three.
One, two...
- Two and a half.
[in unison] Three!
[both screaming]
[♪ Upbeat music playing]
[both exclaim]
- Again?
- Heck, yeah, again.
[Elio] On three.
[in unison] One, two.
- [Glordon] Whoo-hoo!
- [Elio laughs]
- Whoo-hoo-hoo!
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
[retching]
[both laughing]
[Glordon gasps]
[♪ Upbeat music continues]
Whoo!
[chomping]
[retching]
[both laughing]
Ha-ha!
Shmeepa skiddopoo-peh.
No, no.
Skiddopop-puh.
Noice.
Shmeepa skiddopop-popopop-puh!
So, everyone speaks Elioese
on Earth?
Nah, just me.
And my parents.
Or at least they did.
My aunt's not into it,
but I keep using it
so I don't forget.
[splashes]
Did something happen
to your parents?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I know it's not the same,
but my mom's gone a lot.
Fighting the Blood Wars.
I miss her a ton.
Sometimes it feels like
Dad doesn't even want me.
I know what you mean.
The only people who wanted me
are gone.
But I don't know.
What if...
What if there's nothing
about me to want?
I thought Earth
was the problem,
but...
what if it's me?
Well, I like you.
And you seem fine to me.
[rumbling]
[♪ Ominous music playing]
[thrusters whine]
[Elio] Oh.
He brought your carapace.
[Glordon] I guess so?
But that's good, right?
Yeah. I mean,
it has a flame thrower,
a circular saw, acid gun.
I'll get to fight,
and conquer, and kill, and...
Glordon,
do you not want
to get into your carapace?
Yeah. I mean, kind of, well...
No, no.
I've been pretending
to want it,
but I've been living a lie!
[wails]
Once I'm installed, I'll never
get to play, or swim,
or do anything.
It'll be the worst!
[wailing]
But why didn't
you say something?
Because all Hylurgians
have to do it!
It's tradition.
And if I don't...
[sniffs]
...my dad would hate me.
[no audible dialogue]
Glordon, you're not
getting in there.
But... [sniffs]
I don't have a choice.
We'll figure it out.
I don't know how, but...
Oh, wait.
Ha!
What?
Ooh. What are we doing?
We're going to give your dad
what he wants.
Me?
Well, yes, but also no.
Cloning clay?
A-Are you sure about this?
Yeah. Why not?
[groans] I don't know.
Would a clone
really fool my dad?
He's pretty smart.
Oh, it's going to work.
I'll show you.
Ooooo? Ooooo?
- Yes?
- Can I check on my clone?
Certainly.
Mmm. That smells good, papito.
It's a secret recipe.
[Other Elio]
You're going to love it.
[Olga] How are you
so good at everything?
[both laughing]
[Olga] Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Wow. I guess it does work.
Okay, let's do it.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Okay. Your dad will take
your clone back to Hylurg,
I'll become an Ambassador,
and neither of us
will have to see Hylurg,
or stupid Earth again.
It's a win-win-win.
- [bell dings]
- [gas hissing]
- Whoa.
- Yes.
I'm Glordon!
Wow! Am I really that ripped?
You, follow us.
You got it.
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
You'll be safe in here.
No one else can open it.
All right, Glordon,
get in the ship.
[both] Okay.
I can't tell you apart.
- Yes!
- [Elio] Whoo-hoo!
Seriously, though,
which one's real?
Me.
Stay inside
and don't make a sound.
I'll be right back.
Come on.
You look so good. I can't
even tell the difference.
[Olga] Mmm.
I can't even
tell the difference.
I know.
Who knew yogurt is just
as yummy as butter...
- [Olga chuckles]
- ...and half the cholesterol?
[both laugh]
It's perfect.
Let me get that for you.
Aw. Thanks so much.
[humming]
[yawns] Well, I'm going to
turn in for the night.
All right. But first,
get over here, kiddo.
- Mwah.
- [chuckles]
Good night.
[chuckles]
[♪ Tense music playing]
Hmm.
[glass cracking]
[shatters]
What the?
[gasps]
[sniffing]
[♪ Tense music continues]
[gasps]
[♪ Ominous music playing]
Hi. We should probably talk.
[Questa]
And for my next trick,
think of a number.
- Uh, wait. Uh...
- [Grigon scoffs]
Okay, got it!
Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
[whispering] I don't know
how much longer we can stall.
Where is Candidate Solís?
I'm sure he'll be here
momentarily.
I sense the number is
- seven.
- What?
- Aw, she's right.
- [Grigon] Enough!
Where is my son?
He's here. He's right here.
Daddy.
- He did not abandon us.
- He's here!
Thank the stars.
Lord Grigon, we return
to you Prince Glordon.
My son. Did he harm you?
Nope. Everyone was super nice.
Hmm. Are you prepared
to become
the greatest war machine
in the universe?
To make your enemies tremble
at the sight of you?
To prove the might of the...
Yep! Let's do it!
Oh.
A-Actually, I had more to say,
but, yes,
I-I-let us get on with it.
[ambassadors talking]
[chuckles]
[Glordon chuckles]
[rhythmic pounding]
[Hylurgian soldiers chanting]
[horn blaring]
[chanting continues]
[Hylurgian soldier vocalizes]
[chanting, pounding stop]
[pulsing]
[beeping]
[continuous beep]
[electronic noises]
Whoo!
Oh, yeah.
[grunts]
- Whew.
- [ambassadors] Whew.
Witness the power of Hylurg.
[Grigon] Witness!
- What a good show.
- Very impressive.
That's right.
As you have kept your word,
I will keep mine and leave
this place, never to return.
Hylurgians, fall back.
[Questa] Candidate Solís,
you did it!
- [all clamoring]
- [Helix] Well done.
What an exceptional specimen.
You good, Son?
Oh, yeah. I can't wait
to make endless war
and pillage the unworthy
and bring eternal night...
May I have the honor
of joining the Communiverse?
The honor would be ours,
Candidate Solís.
Or should I say,
Ambassador Solís.
- You're one of us now.
- You're amazing!
- [Tegmen] I like you.
- [ambassador 3] Welcome!
[explosion]
Ah.
It was a clone.
Where is my son?
But... [grunts]
How could you tell?
A father always knows.
You, read his mind.
Find the truth.
No.
Unhand me!
I'm so sorry.
No. [straining]
No.
No, no. No, no, please. No!
[gasps]
What? What did you see?
Your son is in a diplomatic
ship in the docking bay.
[Grigon] Send the troops!
[Glordon humming]
Oh, more pudding, Elio?
Why, thank you, Glordon!
- [thudding]
- [Glordon gasps]
[gasps]
Elio?
[grunting]
[yelps]
[ship] You have selected
a map of our coordinates.
Neck pillow. Lip balm.
A breath mint.
Mmm.
[ship] Destination...
[Elio's voice] Uh, Earth.
[ship] Confirm or cancel?
What? Confirm?
Ooooo, open a portal to Earth.
What are you doing?
Will you tell them, or must I?
Please don't.
He is not the leader of Earth.
[ambassadors exclaiming]
He is not the leader
of anything.
He is just
a child.
- What?
- Oh, no.
- I do not understand.
- No.
She's... She's wrong.
- I am the leader of Earth.
- [ambassadors gasp]
I can still help!
Just please,
please let me stay.
He is not there!
- What?
- But I saw him!
We are as surprised as you.
Arrest them all!
The Communiverse is now
under Hylurgian control.
[shouting]
[Auva] Don't touch me. Stop!
[ambassador 2]
We can sort this out!
- [Tegmen] Ouch.
- It's his fault, not ours!
Liar! Betrayer! Coward!
Leave! Now!
I'm so sorry.
You've done enough!
[distorted] No!
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[♪ Melancholic music playing]
Tear this place apart
until you find my son!
[yells]
[gasping]
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[inhaling, coughing]
No. [breathing heavily]
[♪ Melancholic music playing]
Don't leave me.
Please.
[crying]
[Other Elio giggling]
- [gasps]
- Oh, I'll take that.
Thanks, kiddo.
[Olga] Shoot.
I left the, um... That, uh...
I know what it is.
Be right back.
- Thank you.
- [Other Elio laughs]
[speaking Spanish]
[in English]
You couldn't find it, huh?
Would you toss me those?
Come on!
Stupid flashlight!
Sorry.
[sighs]
Are you okay?
No. I feel crazy!
I'm on the beach
trying to make contact
with I don't know what.
I just...
feel so...
alone.
[sighs]
You wouldn't understand.
Actually,
I do.
[crackling]
[Olga sighs]
[inhales deeply] Oh.
I didn't think you'd miss me.
I missed you.
I've missed
everything about you.
But...
this isn't the life
you wanted.
The only thing I want
is you.
[sighs]
- [helicopter whirring]
- [Other Elio panting]
Tía Olga! Oh.
Oh, hey, you're back!
Whew.
Something's going on
at the base.
[sirens]
[gasps]
[Elio] Wait.
That's my spaceship.
- Glordon's in there!
- Who?
My friend.
- You made a friend?
- You made a friend? Nice.
Yeah, and he needs our help.
You have clearance, right?
Not for this.
[groans] There's got to be
some way to get in there.
0-okay, okay. Let me think.
[Elio groans]
Well, if you don't
need me anymore,
I will begin
my decomposition process.
Feel free to spread me
over a plant
as nutritious fertilizer.
[warbling]
[both] Wait!
- [soldiers clamoring]
- [tires screech]
[bell rings]
They, uh, mention what it is?
Negative. But AARO's here
and NASA's on the way.
Is it extraterrestrial?
[scoffs]
What, like little green men?
Don't tell me you believe
in that stuff.
[echoing laugh]
Who's there?
[♪ Tense music playing]
[sighs] It's a kid.
Hey, you shouldn't be here.
[neck cracks]
Can you help me?
[♪ Tense music continues]
Huh?
[distorted]
I don't feel so good.
[screaming]
- Get it off me!
- [soldiers screaming]
- [clamoring]
It's in my mouth!
Why is it sour?
It's on me too!
[soldier 2] Help! Help!
[soldiers clamoring]
Thank you for your service.
- [indistinct radio chatter]
- [scientists grunting]
[♪ Uplifting music playing]
[muffled shout]
[panting]
[beeping]
[door hisses]
[gasps] Glordon!
[Glordon panting]
[panting and wheezing]
Is that your friend?
[distorted] Elio?
[distorted]
What are you doing here?
Why didn't you stay
where I told you?
I'm sorry.
[distorted] I accidentally
turned on the ship.
- [Glordon growling]
- [beeping fading]
Glordon? Glordon!
- Is he sick?
- His disc is broken.
It's too cold for him here!
- Hey!
- [both gasp]
Put your hands up!
Back away from the specimen.
[panting]
I said, back away! Now!
Shmeegle shmarpie blop.
[gasps] You learned Elioese?
[in Elioese]
Hey, what are you saying?
- Oh, you mean "glöp."
- Stop that!
[all grunt]
Gun it!
[panting]
Oh, my gosh. Oh...
This is so...
Oh, my gosh.
[Glordon growls]
Hold on, Glordon.
Olga, you got to drive!
- B-But how?
- Please!
[ship] Welcome, guest pilot!
[groaning]
Give me your jacket.
I'm so sorry, Glordon.
This is all my fault.
[growls]
Don't worry.
I'm going to get you home.
Ship, get us
to the Communiverse.
[ship] Hyper-speed unavailable,
path blocked.
What? It's totally clear.
[ship] I said,
"Hyper-speed unavailable,
path blocked."
Oh, come on!
[Elio groans]
- What?
- Shh.
[both exclaim]
[gasps]
We're in a debris field.
- Let's just get out of here.
- No!
These objects are faster
than bullets.
But this is what you do.
From the ground.
I don't know where
the debris's coming from.
I-I need altitudes,
velo... [gasps]
[sighs] If I could just
contact someone on the ground.
[groans]
But the base is on lockdown.
Maybe someone with a--
with a ham radio.
- I don't know!
- [gasps]
Elio?
Bro, I bet that UFO was real.
Oh, what if they're here
for food
and the only thing they eat
are hamsters?
I'm fine with that.
[mysterious sounds]
[Elio] PXLOL, please respond.
PXLOL, come in!
Hello? This is PXLOL.
Bryce! Uh...
This is Elio.
[Bryce] Solís?
I'm sorry about what happened.
Caleb can be
a real butt sometimes.
It's okay, I was a butt too.
Look, you might not
believe this,
but we're in an alien ship
that just...
That's you? Aw, man!
There's a lot of radio chatter
about that.
[Elio] Yeah, that's us.
We're trying to fly
through debris,
but we need to know
where it's coming...
[both scream]
How's your math? Physics?
Are you good at physics?
Whoa. Uh...
Bryce, I really
need your help.
Please.
I don't know anything
about debris,
but I know someone who does.
He's a legend
in my radio group.
The boss. The eyes in the sky.
He's...
Melmac reporting for duty!
I'll take it from here, PXLOL!
Elio, you better come back
in one piece, okay?
I'll tell you all about it.
Thank you, Melmac,
I owe you a huge...
[Melmac]
Never mind that, Major.
A Master of Ham
always helps in a jam.
Ha!
Let's get you
through this debris field.
I'm pulling up
the network now.
Get ready.
We need a fixed target.
[gasps] Orion's belt.
Perfect.
Drive straight toward it,
- and be ready to dodge.
- [Elio] Okay.
Uh, ship, can you, um--
can you project a grid?
Okay. Melmac,
anything out there?
Hurry, before we're
out of range!
Uh... Okay. Large rocket body!
Altitude, 407 kilometers,
velocity, 766.
Got it.
There.
Where? I-I don't see it!
Just pull back. Now!
[screams]
Another one! 788 kilometers,
velocity, 7.46.
- Climb fast! Now!
- Roger!
Whoo! We are going ham!
[Melmac laughs]
You're doing great.
Melmac, keep them coming.
Major, you're leaving
the comm window.
Just stay on this frequency.
Stay... frequency...
- Melmac? Melmac?
- [beeping]
[ship] Shields at 80%.
[Glordon groaning]
Glordon.
Is anyone there?
Please, anyone? Mayday!
Mayday! Come in. Come in!
[both exclaim]
- [ship] Shields at 60%.
- [alarm beeping]
[both grunt]
[ship] Shields at 41%.
[thud]
- [ship] Shields at 23%.
- [Elio grunts]
Mayday! Mayday!
Come in. Come in!
- Hello?
- [ship] Shields at 16%.
[both exclaim]
- Is anyone out there?
- [Elio grunts]
[echoing] Can anyone hear us?
- This is...
- [radio crackles]
...Senegal.
[ham operator 1] Bonjour.
This is Masters of Ham
in Senegal.
Yes, yes. We read you.
[ham operator 1] Large debris
at 1,300 kilometers,
velocity, 7.2.
Pull back! Hard!
Thank you. Thank you.
[ham operator 1] Masters
of Ham at your service.
[on radio]
This is Giulia from Italia.
This is awesome!
- 2,224, velocity 6.81.
- Right.
This is Anoush in Armenia.
- Velocity, 6.75.
- Right!
[ham operator 3] Namaste.
- This is Vikram from Mumbai.
- Climb!
[Vikram] Debris at 2, 753,
- velocity, 6.61.
- Left!
-This is Hoang in Vietnam.
- Velocity 6...
[ham operator 4]
Konnichiwa from Japan.
You can do this!
- You're going to be okay.
- You're not alone.
- Go, go, go!
- [laughs] Come on, kid!
-Keep going!
- You're almost there!
[ham operators cheering]
[ham operator 5]
There's one more piece!
Move, move, move!
- Which way?
- I don't know.
[low rumbling]
[both grunting]
[ship] Path cleared.
[sighs, laughs]
[♪ Hopeful music playing]
[gasps] Glordon?
[control panel beeping]
[ship] Engaging hyper-speed.
[♪ Dramatic music playing]
[grunts]
[both groaning]
[gasps]
[♪ Ominous music playing]
Help us. Please.
- [Olga] Elio.
- [Elio] Glordon. No!
[Olga]Get off me! [grunts]
[Elio struggling]
[crying]
Glordon.
Glordon, wake up.
No.
I can't lose you too.
- [roars]
- [gasps]
No!
[roaring]
[growling]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[Glordon grunts]
[both sigh]
[both growl]
[speaks Hylurgian]
Explain yourselves.
Huh?
I-- I can't.
Just tell him.
He loves you.
Look how much
he wanted you back.
[gulps]
I-I...
I don't want to be
a war machine.
[sighs]
You already know?
Yes.
I may not always
understand you,
but I still love you.
[sighs]
[stammers]
It's a loose swaddle.
I do not have
your mother's touch.
You did great.
I have never uttered
these words before,
but I am...
[elongated] ...sorry.
[sighs]
Release them all.
[ambassadors chattering]
[♪ Uplifting music playing]
[Questa] Congratulations,
Ambassador Solís!
But I-I lied to you!
And then you sacrificed
yourself to save another.
You behaved as admirably
as any real planetary leader.
And you did bring peace.
Eventually.
You have earned
your place here.
I could stay?
Yes, yes, yes!
- [Elio laughs]
- [Naos] Excellent.
[Glordon]
We can hang out every day.
[chattering continues,
distorted]
[sighs]
[♪ Melancholic music playing]
This place is amazing,
but Earth is...
home.
I didn't give it
a chance, but...
now...
I want to try.
With you.
[gasps]
Are you sure?
We're family.
[gasps, sighs]
This isn't goodbye.
It's just not yet.
We understand.
You are unique, Elio of Earth,
and "unique" can sometimes
feel like "alone."
But you are not alone.
Okay.
Bye.
I love you.
Okay. Bye.
[distorted] I love you.
[distorted] Okay. Bye.
I love you.
[ambassador speaking
alien language]
[distorted] Okay. Bye.
I love you.
[speaking alien language]
[growls]
[♪ Emotional music playing]
I love you, too.
Let's go home.
[♪ Emotional music continues]
[spaceship whirs]
[narrator on recording]
It's an ancient human theme.
You can find it
in virtually every culture.
In, uh, religion,
folklore, superstition,
and, now, in science.
The search for life elsewhere
is remarkable in our age
because this is the first time
that we can actually do
something besides speculation.
We can send spacecraft
to nearby planets.
We can use
large radio telescopes to see
if there is any message
being sent to us lately.
And it touches to
the deepest of human concerns.
Are we alone?
[radio static,
frequency changing]
[growling through radio]
Glordon, your disc is muted.
[Glordon] Oops, sorry.
Now, tell me everything.