Captain!
Can we talk?!
We must break through the ice.
The men are hungry and exhausted.
We cannot keep up this
pace without consequence.
Listen up, men!
The more we delay the labor,
the firmer the grasp of the ice will become.
The work continues.
Rotate each group.
Sir, with respect,
the men need assurances.
Assurances?
Yes, that we will head back
to St. Petersburg once we free the ship.
They don't think we'll be seaworthy
for long and they want to know--
Listen up!
It's neither your place, nor the officer here to think anything.
We signed up for a mission and
we'll see it to completion.
We will reach the North Pole.
Is it understood?!
An explosion, Captain.
About two miles away.
Get the men.
The sled dogs are unharmed.
Then where does all this blood come from?
Over here, Captain!
A wounded man, he's lost a lot of blood!
Wound to the shoulder.
His leg is broken.
Bear attack?
I don't think so, Captain.
Larsen, help me with his boot.
A prosthetic leg.
Put him on the board.
Hurry to the ship!
Larsen, that thing is coming.
Ready the rifles!
On my command.
Aim!
Fire!
All to the ship!
Where's the man we brought onboard?!
Where?!
What is that thing?
What does it want?!
The Blunderbuss!
Larsen, get the Blunderbuss!
I killed it.
It's still alive!
Ladder!
Pull up the ladder!
How many shots are left?!
One, but it can't kill it!
I know!
I'm not aiming for him.
Come down, your father is arriving.
I'm here, Mother.
I'm here.
Three.
Two.
One.
That's impossible.
It's Mother.
Help him.
Help him!
You better come with me.
Nothing.
Sir, the watchman saw him.
Circling the ship in the mist.
We all saw him drown.
Sir, the men are terrified.
They think that man should be surrendered
to the ice and be done with this.
He's under my protection, and the protection of the Crown!
Weapons down.
- Put them down!
- I am responsible for my men.
He can leave.
We're free!
Captain, what are your orders?
Man the sails.
Turn around.
Do you want to tell the men?
Men!
We're sailing home!