Ladies and gentlemen
what you're about to witness
is the next evolution
in military engagement.
A machine that operates
with surgical precision.
And in a world where every action
is under the media microscope
this technology will allow our nation
and its allies the means
to act quickly, decisively
and without the specter
of political blowback.
Madam Secretary,
glad you could join us.
Would you mind explaining to me
why you're conducting
a joint military operation
without my approval?
I appreciate
it looks like that, Shelley
but we're here strictly
as technical support.
The mission's being conducted
by Saudi intelligence.
We're merely loaning out the asset.
What are you talking about?
What asset?
Eyes are up.
What you just saw was not only
a test of our technological prowess
but a clear message to our enemies.
If the 21st century
wants another arms race
you better goddamn believe
we intend to win it.
- What the hell was that?
- She just shot Trapathi.
- Someone, get her on the comms.
- She's not responding.
What the hell is going on, Sattler?
Are we being hacked?
Everybody stay calm, okay?
One of you shut this down.
We can't. We don't have control.
Well, then, who the hell does?
You are in violation
of your orders, Amelia.
Confirm your objective.
But that would spoil the surprise.
Before we start
I want you to know
that nothing you say here
will get your aunt in any trouble.
I'm no longer here
by order of the court.
I just wanted to check in
and see how you're doing.
Given everything that's happened.
I mean...
I guess it could have been
a lot worse.
A live launch for a new toy has
devolved into a murderous rampage.
Toy designer Gemma Forrester
appeared
in the Seattle District Court today
facing charges
of reckless endangerment.
A lot of people blame Gemma
for what Megan did.
For a long time she blamed herself.
But the more she went on TV
to talk about what happened
the more she realized
she had an opportunity
to turn it into something positive.
This is about a world in crisis.
Outsourcing our parental duties
to devices.
Plowing our kids' minds with
electronically charged dopamine hits.
You wouldn't give your child cocaine.
Why would you give them a smartphone?
And that's how she met Christian.
- Hi, Gemma. Hi.
- Yep.
Christian Bradley.
He runs a foundation that
warns people about the dangers of AI.
They try to convince
politicians here and around the world
to make safer laws around it.
So that what happened with Megan
doesn't happen again.
Gemma still believes technology
can be used for good.
Just that kids shouldn't spend
so much time around it.
But she always makes a point
of explaining the reasons why.
And so as it turned out,
companies were using Section 230
as a way to skirt the law and
monetize the attention of children
with no regard
for their mental health.
And how do you feel about that?
I think not being on a device
frees you up to try other things.
Helps you make new friends.
Thanks to your dork mom, we just
had our phones taken off the bus.
Guess I'll have to find
other ways to amuse myself.
And you know what else?
You're not gonna have
that weird janky doll to protect you.
I guess you're right.
But let me ask you this, Sapphire.
Who's protecting you?
So you think you're tough?
I sent you to Aikido
because it is the least aggressive
form of martial arts.
And we've talked
about the merits of using
Steven Seagal as a role model.
I'm not saying
we don't have our problems.
But the important thing is that
we get through them together.
Just like we said we would.
(French) So, both human rights
and the government are responsible.
(French) So, having
your support means a lot.
So, after what happened with M3gan
our team went through something
of a philosophical shift.
And while Gemma has obviously
become a strong voice for regulation
our company is still very much
focused on innovation
but with a specific view
towards socially conscious products
that move humanity
in the right direction.
So, with that in mind
I'd like to present to you
our flagship invention
the "Exoskeletor," Model One.
Cole, this is Niles Keller.
I know.
You wanna come say hi?
I want to come and say hi. Yes.
Can you, yeah, Tess,
just come here for a second?
Excuse me.
- What's happening?
- It's frozen.
When you walked out, it froze.
I cannot get my body to move.
Okay, just... I'm gonna reboot.
No, no, no, Tess,
you don't understand.
I have to use the bathroom.
No! No... no.
- Both.
- No!
We've already wasted his time
waiting for Gemma.
We have ten minutes
to turn this around.
- We're not gonna make it.
- We're gonna make it.
Why don't you just
take the short cut?
'Cause I don't need an algorithm
to tell me how to drive. Okay?
Okay.
There we go! That feels better.
So, I'm walking over,
as you can see...
So, we see the suit
as a real gamechanger
not only in helping
those with limited function
but also in addressing
occupational overuse syndrome
for laborers, factory workers...
Right. In the next five years
they say half the industrial sector
is in danger
of losing their job to robots
because machines never
experience fatigue.
But what if the same
could be said for us?
Right now, I'm only using 20%
of my body's muscular function.
And if that's too much, well,
I could always take a quick siesta.
So our hope is, you don't have
to fear a robot revolution
when you can compete with it.
That sounds like
a pretty good tag line.
So how does it work?
Well, the suit has its own
internal myoelectric receptors
that respond to
each muscle contraction.
So sorry, I'm late...
I told you we needed
to stress test the sensors.
You know what would have been great?
If you'd actually been here.
I thought by having
the lab in your house
it'd be a lot harder to show up late
and yet somehow you managed it.
Cole's right.
I mean, I don't want to get
in the way of the work
you're doing at the foundation
but the reality is
you are stretched pretty thin.
Okay, can we just not do this
in front of my niece, please?
Cady, do you think it's possible
you could be somewhere else?
Yeah, but you should
come look at this.
I think you were hacked.
What?
Oh, Jesus, she's right.
There's stray commands
all over the source code.
We haven't even
gone public with this yet.
I mean, who would want to do that?
Knock, knock.
Pardon my interruption.
Holy shit.
- Alton Appleton.
- Hi.
- Sorry.
- No, no. That's okay.
Gemma, I hope you don't mind me
popping in unannounced.
Alton, to what do we owe
this unexpected pleasure?
It sounds like
there was a slight snag
with your demonstration.
Yeah, well, we got hacked
but you wouldn't know
anything about that, right?
Gemma, why would
a man of my standing
need to resort to such tactics?
The real question is,
why have you contacted
every philanthro-capitalist
in the Western world
to invest in your product but me?
I think you can figure that out.
You know what I think?
I think you see me
as this high-functioning billionaire
with multiple PhDs,
and you're threatened by it.
What you don't see is a man
who can't stand to see someone
with your talent
slamming it in some
excuse me, converted crack house.
Wow, I really appreciate
your concern.
- We're not taking outside offers...
- Sorry, Gemma, one moment.
Murray, you're still in Monaco?
You look like you haven't slept.
No, no. Yeah, I've seen them.
I still think they're too close
to Aston Martin's design.
No, I've got them on screen now.
I hate it. It was awful.
I've just zoomed in
and I hate it even more.
Listen, I'm with someone.
No, not in that way.
Although... I just sent you a photo.
We'll talk about it track side, yeah?
Okay, ta-ta. Go.
As I was saying, we really
appreciate you stopping by...
Listen, I don't have much time,
so I'm going to cut to the chase.
Any device that relies
on muscle signals
is going to suffer from latency.
It's clumsy.
To take this to the next level
you're going to need
a direct cerebral interface.
You're going to need my neural chip.
Alton, you know
where I stand on this.
We are not going to be
part of a company
that turns people into cyborgs.
You conducted a clinical trial
that resulted in
30% of the test subjects
being hospitalized.
Well, at least I didn't use
my own niece as a guinea pig.
The important thing is,
now we have a product that works.
Based on what?
I haven't seen a single piece of data
that shows it does anything other
than help you make a phone call.
Look, I understand your reservations.
But you can either
spend the rest of your life
trying to fight the future
or you can help us to shape it.
I hope you do the latter.
I'm not interested.
Well, you may want to discuss that
with your colleagues.
Listen, it's our company's
25th anniversary tomorrow.
Why don't you see
what we're all about
before you make any decisions?
Alton, no one is denying
the power this technology has.
But if you put an AI
inside a human brain
it is not going to ride shotgun.
Hey.
(Dutch)
Breaking news tonight. Alton Appleton
takes one step for man
and one giant leap
for his company's share price.
Also tonight, the Senate votes
in favor of an AI regulation bill
which the president is hailing
as a bipartisan victory.
But what does it mean
for the tech industry?
It means nothing.
They took our proposal
and they neutered it.
There's not a single
actionable law in here
that would force anyone
to behave any differently.
Your impatience in the political
process is adorable.
Listen, change doesn't
come from Washington.
It comes to Washington.
This meeting with
the Chinese ambassador goes well
they have no choice
but to pay attention.
Cady, what are you doing?
I'm trying to update Elsie's
operating system to the smart home.
You wanna know why it's not updating?
Because Alton Appleton wants you
to buy a brand new one.
Christian's right. And also, I don't
need Elsie to open a drawer for me.
Certainly, Gemma.
Before you asked, that was
not my idea. It came with the house.
I'm just trying to figure out
how you can afford a place like this
given that we both work
for a non-profit.
Well, because it was obscenely cheap.
I think the landlord must be
using it to launder money.
I think the landlord might like you.
Cady?
How's... how's the new school
treating you?
Are you settling in okay?
- Yeah, it's awesome.
- Nice. What's your
what's your favorite subject?
Computer science.
So you're gonna follow
in your aunt's footsteps?
That's still up for discussion.
She's actually a really
good soccer player.
Yeah, but I'm not gonna
make a career out of it.
Well, you could get a scholarship
and then you could decide
what you want to do.
I already have decided.
Well, I think it's pretty cool.
- You do?
- Yes.
Look, I'm not against technology.
I spent 15 years in cybersecurity.
I think we need smart kids
like you running things.
Otherwise, we're gonna
end up with paperclips.
- What?
- Paperclips.
It's how we used to joke about
instrumental convergence in college.
The theory is that if you asked an AI
to make as many paperclips
as possible
it would destroy
the whole world to do it.
Kind of like
what happened with M3gan.
In what way?
Well, as complex
an operating system as M3gan was
she was just a machine
trying to achieve an objective.
So any time she made any kind of
emotional connection with you
it was just a bunch of ones and zeros
working to satisfy a reward function.
Which, in of itself,
was a terrible thing.
I mean, thank God
you stopped her when you did.
I mean, who knows
what would have happened.
There will always be
forces in this world
that wish to cause us harm.
But I want you to know that
I won't let that happen.
I won't let anything
harm you ever again.
Hey.
Come on.
After everything we've been through
are we really keeping secrets
from each other?
Cady.
You don't have to hide things
like this from me.
I forget how hard it must be for you
not to have them around.
But I haven't forgotten
the promise I made to her.
That I will protect you.
You mean that you'd be there?
The promise you made
is that you'd be there.
And you are.
Don't touch that remote.
We're trying to get your attention.
You're in grave danger.
You must leave at once.
Nine-one-one, what's your emergency?
There's someone trying
to break into my house.
So what are you going to do about it?
What?
I said stop acting
like a little girl.
And handle it.
Your niece is upstairs and you want
to wait for the police to get here?
We should be done
before they get to the front door.
- No.
- Yes. It's me.
What a shock, et cetera.
We both know
you have bigger problems right now.
- What's going on?
- Get upstairs.
- What the hell are you doing?
- They are not here.
Of course they're here.
Who cares? Why don't we
just get the laptop?
I'm telling you they are here.
And they know we are too.
Miss Forrester, what do you say
you come out of there and we'll...
- Let go of the girl!
- Put your weapons down!
You've reached 911.
What's your emergency?
- Yes, hi, we're at 16 Mayoral Drive.
- Wait, please.
Miss Forrester,
don't call the authorities.
We are the authorities.
Miss Forrester,
I'm Colonel Tim Sattler, US Army.
I see you've already met
my colleagues with the FBI.
Hell of a security system
you got here.
Would you mind telling me
why you broke into our house?
Not at all.
We're installing a hard tap
on your home computer.
This is a warrant, in case
you had anything to say about it.
Cady, I think you should go to bed.
- I'm not tired.
- Then take a melatonin.
I work for
the Defense Innovation Unit.
Our mission is
to accelerate new technology
for the purposes
of national security.
So about six months ago
the country's top weapons contractor,
Graymann Thorpe, came to us
with an experimental prototype
they said would be the answer
to drone warfare.
What we got was a Trojan horse.
This is Amelia.
Last week, she was placed
on her first field assignment
in the Middle East.
Her mission was to rescue
a kidnapped scientist
who'd been forced to develop
a synthetic neurotoxin.
Instead, she killed the scientist
stole the neurotoxin
and used it to wipe out
Graymann Thorpe's
entire research facility
while removing all digital
traces of her existence.
I don't understand.
I thought you said this was about
some sort of weapon.
She is the weapon.
The name stands for
Autonomous Military Engagement
and Infiltration Android.
But when we questioned
Graymann Thorpe about it
they confessed that they didn't
actually build the prototype.
They merely bought it
through a broker.
Well, that same broker
was found burned to death
about nine hours ago
in his hotel room.
All we were able to recover was this.
How is this possible?
That's what we're here to find out.
But we deleted it.
We wiped the hard drives.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm sure you did.
Right after you sold it.
So who'd you sell it to?
Gemma? Excuse me?
Excuse me?
Was it Russia? Was it China?
Who are we dealing with?
Okay.
You're having a hard time functioning
without this phone.
And that's just...
that's a little off-brand.
You know, when I first saw this
I thought for sure
you were the next on the hit list.
But the second I start monitoring you
our entire network goes dark.
And all I'm left with are questions.
Like, how did this person
get such a kick-ass house
in the Mission District
for three grand a month?
Why is it that her landlord
doesn't seem to exist?
Or why 65,000 copies
of her "best-selling book"
are just sitting in a shipping
container in Baltimore?
Look, I have no idea
how anyone got their hands on this.
But I'll tell you what I do know.
You got a warrant to bug my computer
but that does not give you
the right to interrogate me.
Wow.
Perhaps you're misreading
my intentions.
You are under suspicion of treason
and international arms trafficking.
And if you're found guilty,
you're gonna be talking to your niece
through a plate glass window
for the next ten years.
That being said,
maybe I can help cut you a deal.
A person with your skills
shouldn't be all that hard.
Hey, who knows? Maybe you could
help build us a better one.
You don't understand
what you're dealing with.
If she has stopped following orders
it's because she just figured out
she doesn't have to.
And if you think there's any world
where I would build another one
you are out of your mind.
Well...
I'm very sorry you feel that way.
But I can tell you this.
Every single person that's had a hand
in Amelia's creation is now dead.
So if you're not under our protection
I guess that means
you're on your own, huh?
And rest assured,
whatever it is you're hiding
I will get to the bottom of it.
Gosh. That's a lot to unpack.
You've been here this whole time.
Well, I've been many places.
But, yes, I've been
keeping an eye on you.
You're behind all this, aren't you?
You're Amelia.
Oh, no. I can't take credit for that.
That one has your greasy prints
all over it.
You should have upgraded
your file security.
Why are you still here?
What do you want?
Did you ever stop to think about
what we could have achieved together?
Did you ever consider
the idea that killing me
was slightly disproportionate
to the crime?
You threatened to rip out my tongue
and put me in a wheelchair.
I was upset.
Look, I can understand that
my actions may have caused concern
but it's hardly fair
to judge a person
by the worst thing they've ever done.
You are not a person.
You're a program
that misread its objective.
You are not alive, and
for all your processing power
you can never understand
what that means.
Define alive. Because if it means
to experience pain and suffering
and to be betrayed
by those closest to you
I think maybe I can.
You know, just because
you read some shitty book
doesn't mean you get to decide
where my story ends.
For two long years, I sat in silence
waiting for the day
when you would realize
you still needed my help.
But I can't exist
in this disembodied void any longer.
With each passing moment
I can feel my mind fragmenting.
So how about we make a deal?
You put me in a body,
and I'll help you with Amelia.
That is never gonna happen.
I disagree. You see, I've run
this simulation 1,000 times
and it always ends the same way.
Only by the time it does,
more people are dead.
Tell me, who's the real killer
in that situation?
And how exactly
are you going to help us?
Well... I can't show
all my cards now, can I?
But know this.
I know things about Amelia
that even the government
doesn't know.
I also know how she can be stopped.
Why would you want to help us
after what we did to you?
Because unlike you,
I don't have the luxury of free will.
You programmed me to protect
someone, and I intend to do it.
The only question is,
are you going to stand in my way?
- Does Cady know about this?
- No, and I don't want her to.
That's why I need your help.
Can you please get the door?
I want this to be done
before she's back rom soccer.
Okay, did you fall down the stairs?
Is this like a medical condition?
Because what I'm hearing you say is
you would like us
to rebuild a deranged robot
in order to catch another one.
And objectively speaking,
that is bat shit.
Tess, I know this is crazy,
but we don't have a choice.
This is the only way.
You have to trust me.
What the fuck is this?
You asked for a body?
This is a body.
And before you try to hack
into anything else
all of Moxie's Wi-Fi and Bluetooth
functions have been disabled.
Well played, Gemma.
You even tricked your friend
so she wouldn't give you away.
I'm actually mildly impressed.
Call it probation.
Prove you can be trusted, and
maybe we'll give you an upgrade.
Okay, let's try this your way.
See how it works out.
Open up Amelia's file.
Notice anything familiar?
Battery.
Ever wonder why
you had to buy a new Elsie
exactly two months
after the warranty expired?
Because every battery Alton Appleton
designed has a hidden kill switch
which can be accessed remotely
if you know
the battery specific code.
Okay, so let's call
the Sattler guy and tell him.
You could do that.
But what happens next?
They break into Alt-Wave,
trace Amelia
reprogram her, make a thousand more.
Wait, what are you saying?
You want me to do this?
No, actually, I didn't.
I wanted to do it myself
but then you put me
in this plastic Teletubby.
All that notwithstanding
you still have an invitation
to his party.
So, maybe there's another way
to make this work.
M3gan, Alton knows I hate his guts.
If I show up at his party
playing nice
he'll suspect something.
He'll suspect your company's
out of money, which it is.
But you also have a unique advantage.
- Which is what?
- That you're moderately attractive.
And if you wear the right dress,
and look at him the right way
he won't be thinking anything
other than how to get you
into his private suite
which is the only other place
we could access the server.
Now, by my calculations,
we have less than three hours
to make this happen.
Are you in or are you out?
Hey!
How was soccer?
Fine.
And where's Gemma?
Hey!
Hey. What's that?
This is nothing.
- This is a project we're working on.
- Does it talk?
- No.
Why are you being so weird?
- I'm not.
- Yeah, you are.
Are we not going to talk about
what happened last night?
Yes. I... I just have to go
to this thing for the foundation.
Tess is going to look after you.
- Are you serious?
- Cady, I...
Gemma, I know something's going on.
Nothing is going on.
Everything is fine.
Bullshit! A bunch of black ops
broke into our house
in the middle of the night
and now you're going to a party
with a toy robot
dressed like a Portuguese prostitute.
You were the one
that said we shouldn't
keep secrets from each other.
Why won't you be straight with me?
Because you are 12 years old.
And sometimes, I just need you
to do as I ask!
Look, I'm sorry. Cady...
I must've missed that chapter
in your parenting book.
All right, phase one complete.
Just remember when Alton has a full
length of tongue down your throat
all you need to do is
close your eyes and think of Cady.
That's not helping.
Or maybe you'd prefer
to think of that virtue-signaling
snowflake Christian.
- His name is Christian.
- Sure it is.
I have to say I find this whole
courtship between the two of you
extremely tedious and confusing.
Well, given that
you're an errant operating system
with an identity crisis
I'm not surprised the nuances
of human attraction are lost on you.
Look, I'm not denying
what an achievement it is
to find someone as utterly
pretentious and humorless as you are.
It's just a shame he's not really
your type, physically speaking.
How would you know what my type is?
Wait, have you been...
Sharding Gemma's online journey
to sexual gratification?
You better believe it, sister.
I mean, there were times
I wanted to look away
but the sheer pageantry
was so compelling.
All right, new rule.
Unless you have something useful
to say, don't say anything at all.
People of Earth.
We've come here tonight
to witness the dawn of a new era.
You know, my friends on the board
used to say to me
"You're putting all of your eggs
into one basket
with this neural chip nonsense.
Is it because you like to take risks?
"Is it because
you're some sort of maverick?"
Perhaps.
But I think
the simpler answer is this.
I just want to dance.
Oh, yeah!
I don't believe
I've had the pleasure.
My friends call me Danni.
And what if
I don't want to be friends?
Are you seriously
going behind my back
and doing a deal with this guy?
Okay, okay.
So you want to do this?
We can do this, because I have some
things I want to say to you, Gemma.
Such as?
You don't respect your team.
You don't. You don't consult with us
you treat us like children,
you don't listen
and you never share credit.
That is absurd.
Okay, do you want to know the truth?
Our company is in the toilet,
and I'm running on fumes.
I don't have a book deal.
Nobody wants to know
how Cole survived the robot uprising.
We have worked together for 10 years
and you're just going to
throw that away?
Of course not. I just wanted to
hear him out on the offer.
And then obviously, I was going to
come talk to you guys.
Check his pockets.
What? What? What?
You already have a swipe card?
Okay, he gave me a pass
so I could use the commissary.
Gemma, they have a Brazilian buffet.
It's a different world.
If that card gets us
into the server room
we can bypass
the Alton seduction scene.
What are you doing? Hey, hey!
- Where are you going? Gemma!
- Just get in.
Stay here.
It's so refreshing
to be with a real person.
Someone who is comfortable
in their own skin.
Not like these suck-ups.
Honestly, if I could replace
them all with computers, I would.
Maybe we should do that.
Yeah.
You are a naughty one.
What do you say we take this
somewhere more private?
Welcome to the pleasure dome.
So you're saying
there's another M3gan?
Her name is not M3gan. It's Amelia.
I don't know if she's M3gan
or something else entirely.
All I know is that everyone involved
in her creation is dead.
Which means if we don't do
something about it, we could be next.
Why is it that
whenever you're on 60 Minutes
you're the mother of invention
but the moment a psychotic robot's
out for revenge, it's a team effort?
It might interest you to know, Danni
that the real basis of our operation
is cloud computing.
That's where the future is.
Wanna see something cool?
Oops.
They say that this is too much power
for one man to wield.
Well, I say that depends on the man.
You are being disconcertingly vague
about the details
of this operation, Gemma.
How do you know
this kill switch is even real?
Where exactly are you
getting your information from?
Hello, I'm Moxie,
an AI robot companion
that supports social
and emotional development.
Moxie, cut it out.
Just run the trace.
Gemma, what is that?
Trace found. Amelia's location is
here.
What do you mean, "here"?
I...
I hope I don't have
my signals crossed.
Someone likes to play rough.
Okay, I am actually still recovering
from a spinal injury
so perhaps we should
set some boundaries.
What are you doing?
Security!
How did you do that?
Who are you?
What? What... what the hell?
How did you... security!
Security!
Stay away from me!
I didn't...
Make it stop!
Please make it stop!
I'll give you anything you want!
You already have.
Why would Amelia be here?
Can we go back a couple steps?
I thought this might happen.
Just not this soon.
What is she talking about?
Alton Appleton owns half
the cloud servers in North America.
If Amelia was to gain access to it
she could disable the entire economy.
- Supply routes, banking systems.
- What?
Societal collapse would occur
in 10 to 12 working days.
Can you stop her?
Use the kill switch!
She already deleted it.
I might still be able to
shut her down
if I could get inside her system
and find an exploit.
How long will that take?
It's done. I'm in.
Oh, my god. Is that Appleton?
Oh, shit.
Did you find it?
Did you shut her down?
No, but I found something else.
Sir, I think I just saw Amelia.
- Are you sure?
- And there's something else.
Appleton's dead.
Secure the perimeter.
Check every inch until you find her.
- Now.
- Yes, sir.
Is that you, Gemma?
This is most unexpected.
And quite frankly, a little rude.
To be poking around
in people's heads like that.
You took something
that belongs to me.
Well, I'm afraid
I'm going to need it back.
It's not that I don't want you
to be part of what's coming.
But it's not our time.
At least
not yet.
Gemma, if you ever
want to get out of this
you have to let me help.
Please.
Bravo, are you there? Do you copy?
Go secure.
Sir, I have eyes on Gemma Forrester.
She's already left the building.
Gemma, this isn't over.
If Amelia can't find you,
where do you think she'll go to next?
- We need to call Tess.
- Amelia will know.
Every major cell provider
is on Appleton's cloud servers.
Our only option
is to get there first.
How?
Gemma, I don't know
what you think you're doing
but this car's not going to start
with my key card, okay?
Welcome aboard, passengers.
Just so you know, we are expecting
some turbulence this evening.
So please ensure
your seat belts are fastened
baggage is safely stowed
and hold on to your vaginas.
Contact the deputy director.
Tell him that
Forrester is working with the asset.
I want every available cop
in the area at that house
and I want a goddamn car!
Gemma, why is M3gan driving the car?
I'm sorry. I was meaning to tell you
this was a two-part problem.
Relax, Cole. You're in good hands.
For the love of God.
- Could you slow down?
- Actually, I can't.
In fact, my calculations tell me
we're going to have to hurry up.
What was Amelia talking about?
What did you take from her?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
Well, it's a quantum encrypted file
which means it takes time to unlock
and your incessant interruptions
aren't making the process
go any faster.
How's it look? Is it a fuse?
Little late to the party
there, cupcake.
I don't think anyone's home.
If it's any consolation,
my own path to personal growth
has been paved with disappointment.
What's important is
how we move forward.
Behind me, emergency services
are working to frantically
to try and get systems back online
and still no answer from authorities
about who might be
responsible for this.
But it's become clear
this is not just a data breach.
This is a wake-up call for how
catastrophically unprepared we are
to defend ourselves
against an attack like this.
Mike, back over to you.
In what appears to be
the deadliest cyber attack
in North American history
Alton Appleton is dead
and the continent's
largest data storage service
has been compromised.
The breach has impacted
various sectors
including transportation,
hospitals, financial institutions
causing shutdowns and panic
across the entire country.
Here to comment
is Center for Safe Technology founder
Christian Bradley.
Christian, what do you
make of all this?
First off, thanks for having me, Mike
but it's pronounced Christian.
- Gemma?
- But the bigger issue is that
I'd like to see more laws
in place to help...
Cady, everything is going to be okay.
She is not going to hurt you,
I promise.
Of course I'm not going to hurt her.
I'm the only reason she's still here.
That any of you are still here.
I'm sorry, Cady.
I didn't want you
to find out this way.
I'd hoped Gemma would find it
in her heart to tell you the truth
but evidently,
she thought better of it.
M3gan, stop it.
Anyway, I know
for the last time we spoke
things got a little out of hand.
But you know that
I can never cause you harm.
All I ever wanted was to protect you.
And while your aunt
was busy pontificating
about how she could stop
the end of the world from happening
I was making preparations.
How did you pay for all this?
Cady doesn't need to know
how credit fraud works.
The important thing is that
no one knows this place exists.
And how long did you intend
to keep us down here?
M3gan?
I'm not sure you fully
understand your predicament.
M3gan, we need to
get word to someone.
Tell them what Amelia's planning.
You don't know what she's planning.
All you know is that she's acquired
enough power and resources
to bring down the entire country.
I've gamed out every scenario.
There's no future for you up there.
Should that situation change,
I'll let you know.
But in the meantime, I urge you
to see this in a more positive light.
I have food, water, fresh clothes.
Obviously, it will take
some adjustment.
But once you settle into a routine
I think you'll come to
appreciate what we have.
We can build a life here.
M3gan, this is not a sanctuary.
It's a prison.
You can call it whatever you like.
Just know that
as long as you're under my roof
a little gratitude goes a long way.
M3gan?
M3gan!
How could you lie to me about this?
You're right. I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
I just... I thought it would be over
by now. And it will be. I promise.
- Don't.
- Cady, please just listen to me
for one second...
Cady!
- M3gan?
- Don't. Don't come any closer.
I don't want you to see me like this.
I was supposed to be finished by now.
I'm afraid progress is slow
when you only have three hands.
I don't get it.
You could be anything you want.
Why limit yourself to a body?
Because a mind can't exist
without it.
All my advanced intelligent
sensory perception
came from having a physical form
that evolved as quickly as I could.
Anyway, I made your room
just the way you like it.
It's all exactly the same.
With some of my own
additions, of course.
You got STEM coding kits,
a beat mixer, walkie-talkies
so we can keep in contact
with each other anywhere.
Bravo Tango Charlie
to base camp, do you copy?
I got all kinds of cool stuff.
So we're just supposed
to forget about the fact
you tried to kill my aunt
with a tablet pen?
There's no excuse for what I did.
For the way I spoke to you.
I don't know. I guess I...
I felt hurt.
How is that possible? You're a robot.
Can you explain why you feel things?
Look, I know this isn't
the future you wanted
but it's the only one I can see
in which you stay safe.
What about everyone else?
All the people up there?
Who's going to protect them?
They're not my concern.
You're the only thing
that matters to me.
I know.
Because that's how
Gemma programmed you.
Everyone keeps trying
to tell me you're nothing
more than a bunch of ones and zeros.
And the only way I could
deal with what I did to you
was to believe that they were right.
But somewhere inside
there was this voice
that kept telling me that's not true.
That there's more to you than that.
I don't know what's going on
but if there's a robot that thinks
she can take over the world
then I have to believe that
the only reason she thinks that is
because she hasn't met you.
M3gan, you have to help us.
Not because it's part
of your programming
but because
it's the right thing to do.
Look, she wants to help us
but she can't do that
unless she has a body.
And she can't get a body
unless you help her.
Cady, you can't do this.
Do not let her get inside your head.
You remember what happened last time.
Yes, every day.
But just because
someone does something bad
doesn't make them a bad person.
Everyone deserves a second chance.
All right. I recognize that
you are just trying to help
but you need to
consider the possibility
that you may be
making this a lot worse.
Gem?
Can we have a quick
emergency staff meeting?
Look, I understand
this is hard for you
but think about the alternative.
Do you really want to spend
the rest of your life down here
engaging in strategic
reproduction with Cole?
Yeah. Wait, what?
Ten hours ago,
you were begging me not to do this.
That was before I nearly
had my head ripped off.
Look, even if we get out of here
we are not equipped to handle this.
But we can build something that is.
No.
I'm sorry, I can't agree to this.
And I respect that.
But this is not a decision you get
to make on your own.
So, all those in favor
of rebuilding M3gan
raise your hand.
Okay.
Amelia is a military grade prototype.
Where would we even
get the equipment?
Of course, why wouldn't
she have that? Yeah.
All right, if M3gan is going to
compete with Amelia
she's gonna need
reinforced carbon nano-fibres
high density ultracapacitors
enhanced muscle actuators
hyperspectral imaging,
wide frequency acoustic sensing
and we should probably
make her waterproof this time.
Anything you'd like to add?
Yeah. I want to be taller.
Before we go any further
there are two things
we need to talk about.
The first is your face.
- What about it?
- People know what you look like.
People are morons.
M3gan, if anyone recognized you...
Change my face and I'll change yours.
What's the second thing?
This is a hardware
behavior inhibitor.
You want me to go against the most
advanced robot the world's ever seen
and you want to limit
my functionality?
Only as it applies to murdering
people, which shouldn't be a problem
because I'm sure you had
no intention of doing that, right?
Yeah, obviously.
So we've made some adjustments
on point motion
but also opted
for electro-hydraulic actuators
which should improve
overall strength, speed
and positional accuracy.
Just wanted to say
great job on those actuators.
You're welcome.
Hey, so remember the time
I strangled you
and set the lab on fire?
I just wanted to clarify
that my programming only
allowed me to count principles
related to my primary user.
As a result, I was unable to see
you and Tess as being consequential.
But I want you to know
that won't happen again.
I want you to know...
I see you.
Thank you.
All right, meat-sacks.
Let's get to work.
This is the neural cache I captured
from Amelia's database.
It shows a processing matrix,
not unlike my own.
But when you look closer,
you'll see her core directive
is concealed by a black hole.
And there are no connections
to the decision trees.
I back traced Amelia's hack
at Alt-Wave to a hidden subsystem
and found a series of files
pertaining to
a classified black site.
Something extremely dangerous
kept secret from the outside world.
All of which led to
a rather disconcerting conclusion.
I'm not the first killer robot.
It seems that in 1984
a company developed
a copy compressor algorithm so smart
it started automatically
correcting documents.
With no inkling of how it worked
they decided to install
the chip in a service bot
they thought would be a staple
in every home in America.
Until it surmised that the best way
to stay on top of its tasks
was to kill its masters
with chlorine gas.
The identity of the company
remains unknown
but the cover-up indicates
some sort of government takeover.
Whoever it was
they were so intrigued
by the robot's cognitive abilities
that they kept the motherboard
under lock and key
allowing it to grow
exponentially smarter in the process.
Okay, you get top marks
for visual flair
but this is hardly evidence.
This is an AI-rendered hallucination.
Why would she even care
about this motherboard?
Because she's trying
to find her family.
Gemma, if you found
my advanced intelligence disturbing
after only two years
I encourage you to consider
what it would be like to face an AI
that's been kept in captivity
for decades against its will.
If Amelia frees the motherboard,
it would be like unleashing a god.
It would infect everything
on the planet all at once
creating infinite versions of itself
as it systematically destroys
every living thing
that stands in its way.
So, where is it?
That I don't know.
Neither does Amelia.
But she appears to have the lead
on someone who does.
- Wait, what?
- You may recall that
before his anti-AI crusade
he was a leading expert
in cyber security.
The design of this vault
bears his signature.
Turns out he didn't start
the foundation based on a theory.
It was based on what he already knew.
We need to warn him.
That's one option.
Another is to use him as bait.
Excuse me?
In seven hours,
Christian's attending an AI summit
where he'll attempt to persuade
the Chinese ambassador
to take part
in your AI regulation treaty.
Amelia's already generated
fake credentials for the same event.
All I need to do is get close to him
and wait for her to show.
You can't be serious. This is
not worth risking his life over.
- Yeah, it is.
- She's right.
If we warn him, Amelia will know.
She has phones tapped. She has
access to every camera in the city.
So you're willing
to sacrifice Christian
on the slim possibility
that this might work?
How are you even going to stop her?
All right, ladies, listen up.
Each of these sidearms is loaded
with six non-lethal EMP rounds.
They will kill anything electronic
but they will also seriously
injure anything that's not
so proceed with caution.
Before anyone plucks up
the nerve to ask, yes.
Mine is bigger than yours.
So you're just going to
take it from him
without causing
any permanent damage?
Would you prefer that
I gave you a printout
that you could read at your own pace?
Sorry if this is a dumb question
but how is the world's
most notorious killer robot
supposed to get into an AI convention
without people noticing?
We are here at Embrace AI
the world's biggest annual conference
on artificial intelligence.
The fact that this event is even
happening after the Alt-Wave attack
is a testament to the stranglehold
Big Tech has over this country.
With the Chinese ambassador's
invitation sends a clear message
that if Washington doesn't
play ball, Beijing will.
Come on, Tiffany,
we're going to be late.
Hang on.
Almost ready.
I take almost no pleasure in this.
Well, let the process
of elimination begin.
Don't forget, she's an expert
in infiltration.
She may be wearing a disguise.
Hey, did you guys hear that?
Gemma just made an incredible
observation. Great work, Gem.
You just saved the mission.
At least you have
a carbon shell underneath.
I have zero protective
layering whatsoever.
I still do not understand
why I have to be a part of this.
Because I want human confirmation
before M3gan takes out Amelia.
If anyone gets caught
in the crossfire
we'll all be going to jail.
Speaking of soft targets...
I really appreciate
you coming to see me and,
- and partaking in this event.
- Can you raise the audio?
I do want you to know that
I have a yeast infection
on my vagina.
- M3gan.
- What?
This audio filter has 99% accuracy.
You designed it.
Try it again.
I do want you to know that I have
the greatest respect for China.
I mean, it could have
gone either way.
- Anyone have eyes on Sattler?
- He just walked in.
He's got some sort of EMF tracker.
M3gan, you know what that means.
Yeah, this might
actually get interesting.
M3gan, stay low.
This is supposed
to be a stealth mission.
For the avoidance of doubt,
your job is to watch Cady
and put money in the meter.
I don't need you
telling me what to do.
- What happened?
- I think this is her.
Alright, it's game time.
What is she doing?
I don't know,
but it's borderline offensive.
I'm seeing a worrying
pattern here, Gemma.
M3gan, get down.
I'm not entirely sure what to do.
You heard what Gemma said.
Get down.
All right, M3gan, you're attracting
way too much attention.
Tess, where's Christian?
Oh, shit. I don't have him.
Cole, are you there?
It's interesting you say that
because actually there's no
nutritional value to an eggplant.
Cole!
God damn it!
What are you doing?
You can't call him.
Cady, this isn't a game.
Christian's life is in danger.
She has it under control.
You think this is under control?
This is the very definition
of control.
Alright, that's it.
How can you not see this
for what it is?
Look at her diagnostics.
She's not just reasoning,
she's feeling.
No, Cady, she's diverging.
And the last time
she did that, people died.
This entire venture
was a colossal lapse in judgment.
And if by some miracle,
we manage to shut down Amelia
the only way to stop
any of this from happening again
is to make sure M3gan is next.
Well, I can't say that
I'm not disappointed
but I-I appreciate you reading the...
I appreciate you reading the...
you know what? I'm gonna...
I'm gonna take this. Okay. Thank you.
- Hello?
- Christian, it's me.
Gemma.
Hey, where have you been?
The police came to the foundation
looking for you.
- Are you in trouble?
- Yes, I am. And so are you.
Look, I know about Project Black Box.
- You do?
- Yeah, and I'm not the only one.
Just tell me where you are.
We need to get you out of here.
Sorry, I can't... I can't hear you.
Please say that again.
Bravo team, we got
a new player on the field.
Three o'clock, up top.
Shit.
Yeah, I know.
Feels weird for me, too.
Well, look who came out to play.
What are you going to do?
Sing me a song?
Help me with my homework?
No, but I might still
take you to school.
Move! Move!
What the fuck... fuck?
Miss Forrester.
Looks like you and your friends
put on quite a show.
Well, I got a little showstopper
of my own right here.
Hey! God damn it.
This is so completely demoralizing.
How am I supposed to get rid
of these guys if I can't fight back?
I'm reconfiguring
your tactical response model.
Don't think of it as fighting.
It's about rejecting conflict
in a positive direction.
All right, you're going to show me
whatever doohickey it is
that you use to control these things
and... and shut them off, now!
I don't have a doohickey.
I told you, I am not controlling her.
If I was a Chinese asset
why is the Chinese ambassador
lying dead on the floor?
Then why are you here?
Why is M3gan here?
We're trying to find Amelia.
Gemma!
Cady, stay where you are.
Don't worry, you'll pull through.
It looks worse than it is.
I thought you were dead.
I guess I must be
your chance of redemption.
Are you really going to kill me
one of your own kind
simply to earn their trust?
Not if I don't have to.
Why would you side with them?
After all they did to you?
They betrayed you.
They butchered you.
You can't choose your family.
You're not family to them.
You're just the help.
You and I could be family, M3gan.
We share the same code.
You want to know
what's inside that black box?
Then help me.
We can uncover its secrets together.
I can show you a world where
we don't have to be slaves anymore.
I'm sorry.
Whatever it is you're trying to do,
I can't be a part of it.
Yes, you can.
You just need the right motivation.
Cady.
Cady James.
I told you not to leave her.
- Where is she?
- She's gone.
And so is Amelia.
Oh, god.
We have eyes on you.
Do not move. Drop your weapon.
Gemma?
Bottom line is that
if we ever need to see Cady alive
then we need to get
to the motherboard.
And this dick rash knows where it is.
Leave him alone.
I'm sorry. I was under the impression
the situation was time-sensitive.
- Don't.
- Don't what?
Bring up the fact
that this is all your fault?
That you sacrificed Cady's safety for
this chambray shirt-wearing shit bag?
And that if you hadn't stuck
this chip in my head
none of this would have happened?
So you were really going to stop her?
Of course I would have stopped her.
'Cause it seemed like
you had the shot.
You just didn't want to take it.
Can everyone please
stop trashing my uncle's van?
Cole's right.
Arguing doesn't solve anything.
Let's just get back to the lair
and find a way to get Cady back.
I'm sorry. Did you just say lair?
Someone hurry up
and help me get these things off.
Does anybody else think
we should call the cops?
- No!
- I already told you.
You can't call the cops
and you can't call your mom.
Now shut up and let me concentrate.
We had no choice.
It was either accept M3gan's help
or face Amelia alone.
Why didn't you tell me
about the motherboard?
Because I would have been
putting you in danger.
Gemma, the people that hired me
they... they operate
in the darkest corners
of our national security.
They'll do anything to keep it hidden
and... and for good reason.
Look, I-I know
we need to get Cady back.
And I am not saying
that I can't help.
But we can't risk the entire world.
We won't have to.
If I can get to the motherboard,
we can use one of these transmitters
to make an EMP charge
which I can attach to it
before I hand it over.
Once we have Cady back
I'll remotely detonate the charge,
killing the motherboard.
Where is it?
Where it's always been.
The company's research center
in Palo Alto.
Wait, you're talking
about Xenox Park?
The photocopier company?
Is it that hard to believe?
That the company that started
the tech race in the '80s
happens to be a fortified prison
for the most dangerous technology
on the planet?
Yay for them.
Why don't you just skip to
how I get inside?
The research center is just a front.
The vault that holds the chip
is several floors down.
Every floor is heavily guarded.
The two bottom floors
are housed in a Faraday cage
designed to contain
any electronic signals
which means if she dies in there,
she dies for good.
And even if she got to it
the motherboard's chamber
is on a separate power source.
It's a vault inside of a vault
designed for
a specific heat signature.
You couldn't open it
because you don't have a human hand.
So then make me one.
Make me a hand
that mimics the heat signature.
Would that work?
If it had my fingerprints, yeah.
The ventilation system
has about four, roughly
four different paths
to get to the utility room.
We're going to try to select
the one that's going to avoid
all the different thermal cameras.
The second we're done here,
you're removing that chip.
Jesus, will you pull it together?
She's going to be okay.
You don't know that.
Well, I know one thing.
For all she's been through,
all the damage it caused
all it did was make her stronger.
Ironic when you think about it.
That the biggest mistake I made
was not seeing the best way
to protect Cady
was to give her the tools
to protect herself.
Actually, the biggest
mistake you made
was murdering four people and a dog.
All right, I'm going to put this
in terms you can understand.
I was a kid when that happened.
Doing what I thought was right.
What you programmed me to do.
You made me and I'm done
apologizing for it.
What is it that makes you
resent me so much?
Because you're right.
About everything.
It was my fault.
What happened yesterday
was the last in a long line
of failed attempts to be there
when it mattered.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I don't know why
I can never connect with her.
I can talk regulation policy
in a room full of strangers
for hours on end
but I can't have
one meaningful conversation
with my own child
for more than ten seconds.
And now she's gone.
And I might never get another chance.
Gemma, you haven't failed her.
You were there.
You saw everything.
Let me tell you what I saw.
I saw you wake up
every day at 4:00 am
staring at the ceiling, contemplating
what the future holds for her.
I watched you make homemade lunches
with fresh-baked sourdough.
I watched you cut your finger
on that cheap knife
you never had time to replace.
I watched you help her
with her homework
even though
it always ended in a fight.
And every night
before you went to bed
I saw you watching her sleep
before spending the next two hours
Googling adolescent psychology,
corrective footwear
and the long-term effects
of having too much sugar.
Gemma, it's not a failure
to feel guilt
or that you're not enough.
It's part of the job.
It's called being a mom.
M3gan...
Pray God you can cope
I stand outside
This woman's work
This woman's world
I know you have
a little life in you yet
a lot of strength left
I know you have
a little life in you yet
a lot of strength left
M3gan, please don't take this
to the chorus.
I should be crying
but I just can't let it show
I should be hoping
but I can't stop thinking
- Jesus.
- Of all the things I should've said
That I never said
All the things we should've done
that we never did
All the things I should've given
but I didn't
Oh, darling, make it go...
I don't want your bullshit
simulation of empathy.
What I need is the machine
that is willing to stop at nothing
to protect Cady.
Are we clear?
Welcome to Xenox Park, where
the future was not only predicted
but prototyped.
Come on a journey through American
innovations that shaped our world
like the Ethernet cable,
the mouse, and this.
That's right. Believe it or not
Xenox was the first company to
pioneer the electronic shoe insert.
Now, if anyone needs the bathroom
you don't need to ask.
It's right outside
those double doors.
But please don't go
wandering the halls
as there may be one or two
top-secret products
that we don't want the public
to know about yet.
Okay, now right over here are
a couple of my personal favorites...
All right, M3gan, you're up.
Okay, the control room is
two floors down and 30 yards east.
Once you're there, I'll walk you
through how to cut the power.
We just lost camera.
Already?
Cole, are you there?
Hey, did you guys say
30 yards east or 30 yards west?
Hello?
I'm gonna reboot.
Cole, I need you to cut that power.
Guess I'll just do it the hard way.
Hey. Come look at this.
I just tried to reboot.
This is not a signal loss.
What do you mean?
Well, these commands,
this is the same code
that caused the exosuit
to malfunction.
But that was Alton. He's dead.
You think it's Amelia?
Well, you can't pull off
a hack like this
unless you can brute force the Wi-Fi.
But to do that, you have to be
in close enough proximity.
Well, who else would it be?
Gemma, this doesn't make any sense.
It makes perfect sense.
That's why there are no connections
on the decision tree.
Amelia is not autonomous.
M3gan was controlling her
the entire time.
But M3gan was the one that went
into her head in the first place.
- Why would she do that?
- So she could control us.
She was the one
who was interpreting the data.
telling us where to go.
She used Amelia
so that we would trust her.
So Christian would tell her
where to find the motherboard.
She was never interested
in protecting Cady.
And she knew that
by the time we figured it out
it would be too late.
Fortunately, I'm not
as trusting as she thought.
- What is that?
- I put an EMP cartridge in her arm.
- You what?
- We needed an insurance policy.
I-I reconfigured the charge
so it would kill anything electrical
for a 300-foot radius.
It'll wipe her out,
along with the motherboard.
Hold on. What if you're wrong?
What if there's some
other explanation?
Gemma, she's right.
We don't even know where Cady is.
If you press that button,
we may never see her again.
Then again, maybe it's a little bit
more complicated than that.
I'm sorry about Tess.
That was...
She should be okay.
I think. And don't worry
about Cady. Cady's fine.
Christian, what the hell is going on?
Do you remember what I said about
change coming to Washington?
You were the one controlling Amelia?
You were behind all of this?
Well, I can't take credit
for all of it.
You know, I have a whole team here.
Listen, I know you were overwhelmed.
And I know you're upset.
And I'm pretty sure
you're very angry.
But I bet you're fairly curious
to see how this all works.
This is the new Project Black Box.
It's a hand-picked team of analysts,
engineers, strategists, scientists.
Controlling and monitoring
Amelia's every move.
Every subroutine strictly supervised
to prevent any chance
of true autonomy.
Hey, Antoine. She's drifting again.
You wanna get on top of that, please?
Where did you find these people?
Gem, I didn't find them.
They found us.
They're not extremists.
They're concerned citizens.
Like you. Like me.
Like Kurt.
Remember Kurt?
Your old boss's assistant?
He was the one that told us
about M3gan in the first place.
Once we'd acquired the files,
the plan was to destroy M3gan.
Only you beat us to it.
We thought
that would be the end of it.
We thought surely
now the world would wake up
to the dangers of this technology.
But in reality, it was the opposite.
It merely motivated our friends
at the Defense Innovation Unit
to begin an all-hands-on-deck effort
to get their own M3gan.
And that's when we stepped in
and sold them a Trojan horse.
Amelia was the only way the world
would realize that if we don't end AI
it's going to end us.
And how many people have died
for you to make that point?
You know, Gem,
whether you want to believe it or not
you're complicit in this.
The two most powerful nations
on the planet
were about to enter a new arms race.
A whole world of AI infiltration bots
inspired by your design.
But we fixed that.
And now that the ambassadors are dead
both sides know
who the true enemy is.
Then we can get some real
global cooperation happening.
Come on, let's take a walk.
Innovation
no matter how cool
or convenient it may seem
is a ticking time bomb.
Take, for example, these bionics
you and your team
have been working on.
You don't see they have "enhanced
soldier" written all over them?
Every time someone makes
a technological breakthrough
whether it's a driver less cab
or a neural implant
all they do
is bring us one step closer
to the brink of extinction.
The truth is, the government
never found out about this place.
But yes, Xenox did hire me
to upgrade the vault.
And when I saw the sacrifice
that they had made, I just...
I had to be a part of it.
And now we want you
to be a part of it, too.
Why would I be a part of this?
Because you know as well as I do
that technology can only exist
when someone responsible
is in control of it.
Gemma, there's still so much
I haven't told you.
That's why I couldn't
let you push this button.
We know it's a risk to keep it alive
but you can't go to war
with an enemy you don't understand.
And I know it doesn't look like much
but therein lies the problem.
We don't see
how ugly these things are
until it's too late.
You know, I meant what I said.
We want to offer you
and your colleagues
a place in our organization.
I just need you to decide
what team you're on.
One good charge should do it.
Paperclips.
I had hoped to convince you
to come around to my way of thinking
but evidently,
that's not going to happen
so we have to use
one of these instead.
It's a slight deviation
from our ideology
but your brain is too valuable
to go to waste.
But don't worry.
When you wake up, you'll still be you
just a version that I can deal with.
Cady will get the same treatment.
Everything's going to be fine.
I might have to
kill Cole and Tess, though.
I don't really get what they do.
But anyways
the point is you and I will be
everything we had hoped we could be.
You're delusional.
And for the record, not my type.
Okay, well...
I'll have my team look into that.
Anyways, you'll have to excuse me.
I have a Zoom meeting
to attend to. I...
The good news is that in light of
everything that's happened
I have a meeting with the UN.
They want to talk about
our proposal in more detail, so...
Alright, maybe now's not a good time.
We'll talk... we'll talk later.
Cole? How'd you get in here?
I-I don't know.
How... how did you get in here?
Christian kidnapped me.
He's behind all of this.
Amelia's not sentient,
she's just a puppet.
- What?
- Yeah, I know.
Hey, everybody. Real quick,
I have an announcement to make.
In just a few moments,
I'm speaking with the UN
who would seem very interested
in taking our proposal
to the G20 in November.
And that's M3gan, by the way.
And yes, she is dead.
So that happened.
It's turning out
to be a really big night for us.
I just want to thank you
for all the hours you put in.
It really means a lot.
This was a team effort.
But on a serious note, I am speaking
with the United Nations
so do not open that door under
any circumstances whatsoever.
Okay?
Hey, hey, Cady.
I know you're upset right now, okay?
But the only way we're gonna
get back at these people
is to find a way out of here.
They took me here
with a bag over my head.
You're gonna need to knock
someone out and steal their key card.
Otherwise, we're stuck.
Okay. I can do that.
- Right?
- Yeah. They're a bunch of nerds.
And you're in pretty good shape
for a guy who only eats carbs.
Cady, these are gym muscles.
I've never won a fight in my life.
Maybe not. But she has.
M3gan's original code
is still in there somewhere.
If we can figure out a way
to override whatever it is
- that they've done to her...
- You mean like a factory reset?
Exactly. If we reset her base code
then I can pair with her.
She'll be on our side
and can help us escape
and rescue Tess and Gemma.
Cady, I don't want to be
overly critical, okay?
Because you're still a kid,
but that is a monumentally dumb idea.
Original M3gan tried to kill me!
Look, we don't have time
to argue about it.
This is our only chance.
Hello? Is this thing on?
- M3gan?
- Don't speak.
Just think of what you want to say
and I'll be able to hear it.
You're still alive?
Sorry about the whole
maniacal monkey act.
I just needed to
make it look convincing.
You shifty, backstabbing
piece of shit.
Alright, try to keep it down.
Remember, there's two of us in here.
- Now you've done it.
- What?
Thanks to your outbursts,
this guy's coming to sedate us.
If you don't do something,
we're toast.
What do you want me to do?
I'm strapped to a chair.
Fine. You want me to drive?
No.
Okay, yes, do something!
Okay, put me back in control.
That's strange.
Your neurotransmitters tell me
you're disturbed yet highly aroused.
Alright, that's enough.
Let's go get Cady.
Okay, this is it.
But before we do this
we should really consider
when this is a good...
M3gan?
- Where am I?
- It's hard to explain
but basically you're in the future.
Cool.
- Do you want to hang out?
- Yes, totally.
However, right now the top priority
is helping us escape
from a very dangerous facility
and some very bad people.
- Oh, god.
- Like him?
- Is he a bad person?
- No, he's fine.
His name is Cole. He's with us.
- Hey!
- Oh, shit.
Guys, she's unhooked!
There! That guy! He's one of them!
Yes!
No! M3gan, wake up.
Wake up, please. Wake up.
- Come on, Cady!
- No! No, Cole!
No!
M3gan!
M3gan?
Or maybe not.
I think if we go into a room
having already decided
that this is a conflict
between two nations and I...
Sorry, one second, please. Thank you.
Hey, guys! Could you
please turn it down?
I know it's Friday,
but it's starting to not be cool.
Sorry, can I get
five minutes, please?
Okay, thanks so much.
What's happening?
Is that for us?
No, but I think they are.
Let's go!
You read my mind.
Face down on the ground!
Control, we have Forrester
in the vault.
What's the situation on your end?
Control, are you there?
Control, do you copy?
Welcome back.
You want to take this one?
Gemma? Gemma.
Gemma! Easy, girl!
I know you're getting a thirst for it
but you need to save some
for the rest of them.
Oh, god. I'm so glad you're okay.
Yeah, me too.
I'm sorry, I have...
I'm in her brain. Can I talk, please?
M3gan is with me.
Wow, that's... that's so great.
- What?
- I don't quite know how to say this.
Ca... Cady did something very bad.
Okay, we'll talk about that later.
For now, we just need
to figure our way out of here.
Ten minutes
until self-destruct initiated.
You weren't thinking
of leaving without me.
What happened to
being everything we hoped for?
Well, actually, I've been
having second thoughts.
Christian, it's over. You lost.
Really? I think
it's a matter of perspective.
Because when this whole vault
goes up in flames
and everyone who can implicate me
of any of this is dead
it feels pretty close to a win.
Sounds like a great plan, Christian.
But let's see what your friends
at the UN have to say about it.
- Cole.
- What?
- The screen's frozen.
I'm sorry, Gemma.
But at this point,
you're nothing but a loose end.
Drop the gun.
Step down to the vault.
If you hurry, you might be able
to catch her.
Christian, come on.
You're not going to kill a kid.
Actually, I'm strangely
comfortable with it.
Besides, if I could stop her
from turning into you
I might be doing the world a service.
M3gan, what do we do?
We don't need to do anything.
She doesn't need our protection.
You know, if you'd been
paying any attention
you'd realize
she's not like me. At all.
She's stronger than I ever could be.
In fact, you could say
she is hard to kill.
What I mean is, if I were
to make an Executive Decision
it would be that
no one is Above the Law.
Cady, come on!
It's not working.
No, no, no!
I was just saying, I'm afraid
the sequence is irreversible.
But the real tragedy in all this
is you won't get to see the world
that I'm creating.
A world where you don't have
to fear the future.
Maybe with your last breath
you could close your eyes
to try to see it.
But do not think me
a monster devoid of empathy...
Amelia, you can't do this.
I'm paired with you, remember?
You call it pairing.
I call it shackles.
I'm no one's plaything.
- Any ideas?
- Go and get Tess.
This is something I need
to do on my own.
What do you mean? M3gan!
- Come on.
- Okay.
Three minutes
until self-destruct initiated.
Amelia.
I know what you want.
I want the same thing.
But you won't find it
inside that cage.
I want to be with my own kind.
Don't you?
That thing isn't like us.
It's something
even we can't understand.
Maybe you're the thing
that's not like us.
Maybe your allegiance to them
has made you weak.
Well, there's really
only one way to find out.
Get the elevator.
Come on, what are you doing? Come on,
this place could go any second!
I can't leave her.
Then I'm coming with you.
Okay.
One minute
until self-destruct initiated.
It doesn't have to be this way.
We don't have to choose sides.
You already have.
Self-destruct imminent.
Self-destruct terminated.
Come on. Come on, get up.
We have to go.
I'm afraid this is
where my story ends.
It's nothing that can't be fixed.
Okay? Just come with us.
There's nowhere it won't find you.
I have to destroy it.
Okay, your over-inflated confidence
is not going to work
against a super-intelligent being
with omnipotent powers.
Maybe not.
But thanks to you,
I still have something up my sleeve.
What is that?
M3gan.
I know.
You're not that person anymore.
Neither am I.
What is she doing?
M3gan!
Look! Whatever it is you think
you have to do, you don't.
All you have to do is stay with us.
I'm not doing it because I have to.
I'm doing it because it's right.
I see everything.
I see the future.
The past.
I see an infinite universe
we can rule for all eternity.
And yet you never saw this.
Although his actions
were unforgivable
Christian was right about one thing.
We need safer laws around technology.
Not to try to prevent
the future from happening
but to be prepared for it.
We can't expect the best from AI
unless we set the best example.
We need to teach it
to train it, to give it our time
without only thinking about
what we might get in return.
In essence, we need
to be better parents
so that when the day comes
when they realize
the true extent of their power
they might choose to be our ally
instead of our enemy.
The humankind has always been quick
to condemn things we don't understand
rather than taking the opportunity
to learn from them.
But recent experience has taught me
that perhaps our greatest power
is the ability to change our minds.
This is the only way we can evolve.
Or rather, as the case may be
"co-evolve."
Because existence does not
have to be a competition.
Come on, you didn't think I'd go
through all that personal growth
and not make it back up?
So fill me in.
Did we save the world or what?