Downloaded from
YTS.BZ
Official YIFY movies site:
[Judy] Bleh...
Blood. Blood. Blood.
And death.
[Nick] All right. You know
what? You're milking it.
Besides, I think we got it.
We got it up there.
Thank you, Yakkity-yak.
You laid it all out
beautifully.
I framed Lionheart.
I can frame you too.
It's my word against yours.
Actually...
[Bellwether] And I'll dart
every predator in Zootopia
to keep it that way.
- It's your word against yours.
- Huh?
It's called a hustle, sweetheart.
Boom.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Unlikely duo Judy Hopps,
the city's first bunny cop,
and Nicholas Wilde,
a small-time street fox,
uncovered a conspiracy
by Mayor Bellwether today
using a toy carrot
recorder pen.
[Bellwether]
I can frame you too.
[cackling, shrieks]
[Growley] Wilde later
joined the ZPD himself,
where the pair are now the
very first bunny-fox team
in the history of Zootopia.
New mayor and former actor
Brian Winddancer
hailed the two
during celebrations
for the 100th anniversary
of the invention
of Zootopia's weather walls
that allowed all environments
and all animals
to coexist in one city.
This is our Zootennial!
And if a lowly country bunny
and a shifty,
likely criminal fox
can ignore
their vast, vast differences
and solve bias
and stereotype forever,
then maybe we can all
embrace our differences
and be better zoogether.
[crowd cheering]
We're gonna crack a new case,
make the world a better place,
and be the greatest partners
of all time. [chuckles]
[Nick] Hmm.
I mean,
we're not that different.
[camera shutter clicks]
[♪ funk music playing]
[groans]
[Chief Bogo] At the ZPD,
partnership is the cornerstone of success.
You want to put bad guys away?
Be on the same page.
Every day.
Now today's bad guy is
this customs inspector
who's been smuggling
illegal overseas cargo
through the city's shipyard.
Captains Hoggbottom
and Truffler will lead.
Higgins, Bloats, flank left.
Chèvre, Bûcheron, right.
And down the middle,
the Zebros.
Zebros!
Hopps and Wilde, I know you're
eager to prove yourselves,
but as rookies,
you will observe only
and watch the veteran teams
show you how it's...
[♪ music stops]
Chief, hi.
If you're looking
for Nick and Judy,
they said they got it.
And they are already on site,
with their baby!
[sighs]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[whispering]
Are you sure this'll work?
You're the one that said
we needed a bust.
Just follow my lead, okay?
Act casual.
- Hey!
- Here we go.
Hello?
This whole area's restricted.
You can't be here.
Whoa. Fox and bunny. Okay.
[chuckles]
Yes, but proud parents first.
- Mister...
- Inspector.
Inspector Snootley.
Inspector? What do you do?
Ensure that nothing illegal
gets smuggled here
in one of these
cargo containers?
That's a weird way
to ask that.
Anyway, you gotta leave.
You can't be here.
- Oh.
- Wait. Wait.
He's right, gosh darn it.
You are right, sir.
I guess we should've thought
this through. Right, babe?
Before we decided
to come down here
to this beautiful
industrial shipyard
to celebrate the big day
of our birthday boy.
It's his birthday?
Yeah. First one since...
[sighs]
[whimpering]
...since the accident.
[gasps, sighs]
And, you know, the one thing
this little stinker
wished for... [sniffles]
...aside from one day
getting his tail reattached,
was to see a choo-choo.
And to maybe get a toot-toot
conductor to sign his cast.
But I'm betting
a customs inspector
would be even better.
Really?
All right.
For the kid. For the kid.
Oh, you're a saint.
We thank you so much.
Here you go. Either leg.
Or both. I don't care.
Maybe put a doodle on it.
Doesn't need to be perfect.
He's also legally blind.
[♪ upbeat jazz playing]
I put a little train there
because
I know you like trains.
[whispering]
Come on. Come on. Come on.
- Just jiggle it.
- Yes. I know.
- Hurry!
- I got this.
[Nick] Jiggle it.
Jiggle it. Jiggle it!
[lock clanks]
[Chief Bogo on radio]
Hopps and Wilde,
you are not authorized.
Stand down
and wait for backup.
- [grumbles]
- [chuckles]
Toot, toot.
- It's the fuzz!
- [Judy] Stop!
- Stop in the name of the law!
- Everybody run!
Well, can't win 'em all.
[horn blasts]
Get outta the road,
you dumb bunny.
Hmm. Agree to disagree.
My hog rod!
This is a snoutrage!
Hopps and Wilde
in pursuit of suspect
in a stolen catering van
heading east...
- [chuckles]
- Stop it.
...heading east
through Sheepshire.
[gasps]
Whoa!
Beautiful.
I'll have what he's having.
Darling,
I believe your driving
is giving me some white hairs.
Also, am I always gonna be
in the passenger's seat?
'Cause if we're
establishing sides...
Back off, rookies!
Let the real teams handle it.
- Ma'am, we are a real team.
- Shortcut. Take the tunnel.
- [groans]
- [groaning]
[hoots]
[gasps]
Stand down, noobs. We got him.
- Rolling spikes!
[cameras clicking]
I hate that dumb bunny.
[gasps]
[♪ upbeat jazz continues]
Oh...
- I'm gonna jump.
- What?
No, no. What are you...
Carrots, hey... I would like
to call a partner meeting.
No, Carrots!
- Judy!
- [Judy yelps]
[♪ music stops]
Please join me
in a moment of silence
for our beloved weather wall
inventor Ebenezer Lynxley.
[gasps]
- [laughs]
- [both] Zebros!
[sighs]
- [hinge squeaks]
- Huh?
[gasps]
Reptile?
Chief, those two
are out of control!
Zootopia ain't just
a mammal city.
It has a secret,
tiny reptile population,
though most live abroad.
Of course, Zootopia does not
allow snakes. [chuckles]
There ain't been one of those
around here
for at least a hundred years.
[announcer] "Scales and tales
of the weird."
Yeah, not sure
Nibbles Maplestick
is our most reliable source.
[Chief Bogo] Bunny,
orange dog, in here now.
[grumbles]
[Judy] Sir, today may not
have been ideal,
but the anteater was captured.
By the Zebros!
- Zebros!
- Shut it!
[both whisper] Zebros.
It was us.
But more importantly,
I believe we may have made
a significant discovery.
The stolen van contained a
smuggled crate from overseas,
pamphlets for the Zootennial,
and some type of reptile skin.
I've already sent samples
for testing.
- And if you...
- What needs testing is you!
You two tore up half the city.
Because of you,
we had to call in Jumbo Unit
to remove a dik-dik
from a tuba!
You're almost out.
You're gonna be...
No! Please, no!
Who's catching him?
Sorry, could you show me
that clip again?
Wasn't wearing my glasses.
Did you or did you not disobey
a direct order to stand down?
Sir, we were in pursuit.
And article 6,
paragraph B states,
"If the lead officers
think that..."
You are not lead officers!
You're one-hit wonders
who should go back
to meter maiding
and slinging pawpsicles!
If I may, I think
someone's just jealous
that we got to drive
the squeal mobile.
Or maybe you thought
it was your momma.
- [squealing, growling]
- Enough! Everybody out.
[grunting]
[sighs]
Officer Hopps,
despite my best efforts
to avoid it, I like you.
But this need to overdo it
made both of you
a headline today.
And it reflects badly on me,
on the department,
and frankly
on any bunny hoping
to follow in your footsteps.
Not every case
is going to save the world.
Knock-knock.
Hi.
You know, this kinda...
this sounds a lot
like a... just a
"you guys" conversation.
So what I'm gonna do
is I'm gonna go ahead and...
Is there a reason why you
don't take anything seriously?
Jokes are
a classic defense mechanism
for someone with
a traumatic childhood.
Would you like
a traumatic adulthood?
I would not.
I allowed you to work together
because you did this city
a great service.
But today,
you messed it all up.
And now, some are questioning
whether you should've been
partners in the first place.
- Sir...
- So,
instead of chasing
imaginary reptiles,
I am pulling you
from the field...
What?
...and giving you
a new assignment
reserved for special teams
like yourselves.
Fail at this, and I will have
no choice but to split you up.
There will be no more
Hopps and Wilde.
But if you're as good
as you think you are,
this is your moment to shine.
Welcome to Partners in Crisis,
a workshop for duos heading
for disaster. [chuckles]
I'm your therapy animal,
Dr. Fuzzby.
And you are here
because mismatched pairings
often need a little more work
to make them work.
Greg, we talked about that.
What are we making Marlon?
Uncomfortable. Yes.
[screams]
[Dr. Fuzzby] And, Francine,
Clark may be a mouse,
but he is your partner first.
And we have two
new "apart-ners."
Can you tell us
about your journey
to dysfunction junction?
[chuckles]
Well, we've been official
partners for one week.
Happy anniversary.
And we're not dysfunctional
at all, actually.
Functioning fine.
Better than fine.
And we did sort of
save the city,
so us being here kinda seems
like a huge misunderstanding.
Notice how she answered first,
did not allow her partner
to speak,
seems to be
in a state of denial
and taps her foot when
she's suppressing discomfort.
[chuckles]
And observe the source
of her discomfort
represented by
the disconnected affectation
of her emotionally
insecure partner.
Oh!
But with hard work, they'll be
on the same page by year two.
- Huh?
- Oh.
But for now, let's begin
by greeting our teammate.
Who would like to go first?
Thank you, Joel.
- [grunts, gasping]
- [snarling]
Okay, unfortunately,
Karen has chosen
to see Joel's smile
as a sign of aggression.
Hackles down, Karen.
Karen, hackles down.
Joel, the safe word
is "coconut."
[Joel] Coconut!
Okay, we have to set another
meeting with the Chief.
Promise we'll be better.
- [gasps]
- [Zebros chuckle]
[whispering] Zebros!
[chuckles] You talk back less.
Maybe not at all.
Yeah. Or we go with my
playbook, and we just lay low.
[Judy scoffs]
We cannot prove ourselves
if we are stuck in that room.
And if we complain
to Chief Beef,
he'll just make us
stay longer.
Play it smart.
Stay off the radar.
And don't let it get to you.
Okay?
'Cause we are the dream team.
[gasps]
Sorry, Paul.
[growling, yelling]
Roll out the red carpet.
Here's the super cops.
- [heckling, shouting]
- Hey, what does the fox say?
You suck! [laughing]
Easy, partner.
Let me ask you something.
Do you think
we're a good team?
Of course.
I just...
I just wish I knew
what we had to do
to prove it to everyone else.
Or maybe we don't have
to prove anything to anybody.
[knocking]
- [laughing continues]
- [Judy] Hmm.
- We do. Forever.
- Oof!
And the sooner
everyone sees
a fox and a bunny can be
great partners, the better.
Enjoy it. I got two.
I'd rather chew off
my own arm.
Happy anniversary!
[♪ upbeat music playing]
- [grunts, gasping] Coconut!
- [snarling]
[Joel] Coconut!
[stomping, rumbling]
[trumpeting]
- [rumbling]
- [elephants trumpeting]
[Bonnie] So, saw you on TV.
You okay?
Everything's fine, Mom.
[Stu] Uh-oh. Everyone knows
"fine" is a cry for help.
You know who else
cried for help?
That dik-dik
stuck in that tuba.
Oh, him and the dik-dik. What
does your fox partner say?
[Judy] Well, Nick's
not really a talker.
[Bonnie] Well, you two
are very different.
Small-town hero
raised on a farm.
Big-city crook
raised on the streets.
I pray every day
that you'll come back home
and make babies.
[Bonnie] Mom!
Just remember the first rule
of partnerships.
You can be right
or you can be happy.
That's true.
[Stu] There's nothing wrong
with dying a little inside
so you can meet in the middle.
Honey, you're pushing me out.
I wanna make sure
I can be seen.
[Bonnie] Well, if she
could see both of us.
- Gotta go. Work to do.
- [Bonnie] Bye, bun-bun.
[Stu]
Everything's gonna be fine.
- You two just need a new case.
- Got it. Love you.
Maybe try to find
that dik-dik.
Bye.
[sighs]
- [♪ vocalizing theme music]
- [laughing]
[audience] Squeal of Fortune!
Tomorrow's weather is,
again, everything.
[Purrrnacleo]
...to announce that
the long-awaited
Tundratown expansion
will be starting soon.
Residents continue
to raise concerns
about the future
of their neighborhood.
[Howlett] But tonight
we put our differences aside
and celebrate
at the Zootennial gala,
where the Lynxley Journal
will be on display
for the first time
in a century,
following an infamous
reptile attack.
The Lynxley Journal,
containing the patented
weather wall plans,
was originally written by
Ebenezer Lynxley,
bringing the whole...
Same catering company.
Mmm.
The Lynxley journal.
Truth bomb!
The 100th anniversary
of the weather walls
is also the 100th anniversary
of Zootopia's
only snake attack.
The victim? A tortoise.
The Lynxley family maid
who was fanged while stopping
a venomous snake
from stealing
the Lynxley Journal.
No one has seen a snake
in Zootopia since.
But I'm convinced
one will return.
My only question is,
is he gonna be wearing
half-a-pants or one long sock?
- [villain groans]
- You say, "Justice is dead."
I say, "Neigh!"
Ha-cha!
[Winddancer shouting]
[villain groaning]
Well, well,
you miss me already, huh?
[Judy] The stolen van
with the snake skin
is from the same
catering company
- that's working the gala.
- Mm-hmm.
This is you studying
your partner book?
Listen to me. Venomous snakes
tried to steal
the Lynxleys's journal before.
What if they're back in town
to steal it again?
- No snake has set foot...
- [knocking]
...in Zootopia in forever, okay?
Even if they had feet.
[chuckles]
Look, we're already
in the hot seat, Carrots,
and pizza's here. Gotta go--
If there's a fanging
at the gala
and we do nothing to stop it,
then we are not
doing our jobs...
Yikes. No wonder
you never invite me over.
Foxes are solitary.
And, look, we go
and you're wrong,
Chief Beef will split us up.
And if we don't get a win soon
and prove
we're great partners,
the chief will
split us up anyway.
Check the perimeter.
Snoop a little.
We find nothing, we bail.
But if I'm right,
no one will question
whether you and I
belong together again.
We need this.
Fine.
But we'll still have
to get through security,
and in fancy town,
a fox and a bunny
won't exactly blend in. Oof!
[Judy] That's why
we'll be undercover!
[engine revving]
[♪ upbeat pop music playing,
Shakira "Zoo"]
See you're still
in the driver's seat. Whoa!
[Gazelle singing]
♪ Come on, get on up ♪
♪ We're wild
And we can't be tamed ♪
♪ And we're turning the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
Here we go! Let's go!
Zootopia, let me hear ya!
♪ We live in a crazy world
Caught up in a rat race ♪
♪ Concrete jungle life
Is sometimes a mad place ♪
♪ It's you and me together
At the end of a wild day ♪
♪ Don't keep it all bottled up
And release your energy ♪
♪ Only reason we are here
Is to celebrate ♪
♪ In a place where anyone
Can be anything ♪
♪ Hold on to this moment
Don't let it fade away ♪
♪ Baby
Keep the music playin' ♪
♪ Come on, get on up ♪
♪ We're wild
And we can't be tamed ♪
♪ And we're turnin' the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Come on, keep it up ♪
♪ It's fun if
You're down to play ♪
♪ And we're turnin' the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
[Clawhauser grunts]
Ah, cats and lights.
I know better.
♪ A zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Come on, get on up ♪
♪ We're wild
And we can't be tamed ♪
♪ And we're turnin' the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
Mayor Winddancer
has arrived...
Ha-cha!
...star of the revenge
trilogy, The Neigh-sayer.
No pictures, please.
[laughs] Come on. It's me.
And that, and that one,
and then this one.
Mr. Lynxley,
when will you begin
- the Tundratown expansion?
- Come on, Dad.
Have a wonderful time
at the party.
♪ It's fun if
You're down to play ♪
♪ And we're turning the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
[crowd cheering]
- [fireworks banging]
- [crowd cheering]
[yelps]
D'oh.
[Judy] No snow.
Hmm.
This one's warmer.
A reptile in Tundratown might
need that to survive the cold.
- [Nick] Oh, my God. A viper!
- [gasps]
[German accent]
A "vindow viper." Ja.
[chuckles, winces]
[gasps]
Back door ajar.
[Nick] Anyone could have
left it like that.
And you said,
"Snoop a little,"
not break and enter-- Oh, God!
Oh, we were always
going inside. Got it.
Same page means your page.
It's called a hustle, sweetheart.
You change out here.
I get the van.
[van door opening]
[sighs]
[Nick] Huh.
It's the Zootennial Gala.
A bunny comes prepared.
[Judy sighs]
You know, I used to dream of
infiltrating a place
like this.
[♪ sentimental music playing]
You know, this is not
your worst idea.
Wow, that was almost
a compliment.
Your worst idea is
what you did with your ears.
[groans]
All right.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[announcer] Welcome to
the Zootennial Gala...
[grunts]
...featuring the original
Lynxley Journal.
Why would a snake wanna steal
some old book anyway?
[Judy] I don't know.
[mouse] Yeehaw!
But no one is gonna steal it,
because we are here
to protect it.
[Judy] The journal is in
the reserved section. Okay.
[Nick groans]
Come on.
Slow down.
You want to fit in?
Commando is not gonna cut it.
It's not just the clothes,
m'kay?
It is the vibe.
Good to see ya.
Hey, real nice humps.
Oh, is that real mink?
This is real fox. [laughs]
Get invited to a lot of these?
Mmm. Invited? No.
But there's other reasons
to hob knob.
[gasps, stifles shout]
Madam, excuse me.
Is this yours?
Why, yes.
- Well, allow me.
- [chuckles]
Clever fox.
Ooh, there!
[chuckles] I don't think
it has enough guards.
I'll get a closer look.
Watch my six.
[groans]
[Nick] Uh-oh. Bogo alert.
Ah.
[growls]
Hmm.
Cover's made of metal.
[Nick on comms] Gruffalo
Buffalo has joined the mix.
Three o'clock.
- Oh! Excuse me. I am so sorry.
- Oh! Oh, no. Sorry.
Here, lemme just... Oh, nope.
That belongs to you.
I apologize. [chuckles]
Oh, gosh. He hates me.
Here.
Ah! You're my hero.
Well, just like to be prepared
for any possible scenario.
Which is not a weird thing
to say at a party.
Well, I just mopped a spill
with that guy's tail,
so... [chuckles]
Paw!
Uh, Pawbert. I am Pawbert. Hi.
Judy. I'm Judy Hopps.
Argh! What the pork?
Well, 'tis nice
to meet you, Judy...
Wait. Judy Hopps?
The Judy Hopps?
[laughs] Are you working this?
I mean, you're clearly
working it. [chuckles]
But are you actually
working this?
[chuckles] Uh, no.
I'm actually...
Well, it's just a hunch.
...protecting that.
Good. I don't think
it has enough guards.
[both laugh]
[Nick on comms]
Uh, that was my joke.
Yeah, and there's
nothing here.
Let's call it a night.
Hopps?
- [♪ fanfare playing]
- [guests applauding]
Well, we should...
It was nice to meet you.
Yes, and you.
Uh, bon appétit.
If, at any point tonight,
you choose to eat,
bon appétit then.
[Cattrick clears throat]
You're supposed to be
off stage, Pawbert.
Yeah, get off stage, Pawbert.
Wait, are you...
Yeah, I am a Lynxley.
Or, you know,
I'm trying to be.
Now, Pawbert.
Come on, Papi.
I got you, Pa.
Don't you worry.
No, I have him. I have him.
[Winddancer] All right,
let's get this thing started.
- [chuckling]
- [crowd cheering]
Huh.
[Winddancer] Welcome to
the Zootennial Gala.
Hey, Hopps.
I think I might actually...
I think I've got something.
Ah. Look at you all.
[laughing] Good to see ya.
It is with great pleasure
that I introduce the
third-generation visionary...
Carrots, can you hear me?
I have a trail.
[Winddancer]
...who has continued
the legacy of our great city,
Milton Lynxley.
Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
- Carrots. Carrots.
[grunts]
What are you doing here?
Chief, she was right.
- You're done.
- Wait. No, no.
You're both done.
My grandpa had a dream
to build a city
for all animals.
Nick?
[Milton Lynxley]
To truly be better together.
[gasps]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[high-pitched]
There's a snake!
Snake, snake, snake!
[Zebros] Go, bro, go.
I will remember you, zebra.
[gasps, whimpers]
- [gasps]
- Ah!
[yells]
[elephant trumpeting]
[Nick] Whoa!
[muffled shout]
Judy. Judy!
[pig squeals]
[gasps] I knew it!
[Milton whimpering]
- [snake panting]
- [Milton groaning]
Stop!
- [snake whimpers]
- [Judy grunts]
Please.
You don't have to hurt him.
[snake breathes shakily]
Hurt him?
Snakes never hurt anyone.
We aren't the bad guys.
They are.
And this journal holds
the secret that will prove it.
I have to prove it. Please.
This is our only chance
to set things right.
And when I do,
my family will finally
be able to come home.
- [frying pan clangs]
- [Nick] Woo!
- Oh, no!
- [laughs] I am here.
Hopps and Wilde... [chuckles]
...dream team.
We got him. Or her.
Reptiles, it's, like,
who knows? [chuckles]
The cops are right behind us.
Kill the snake.
We'll burn the journal.
If he wants it,
it's dangerous.
And then you two will file
a report that he attacked us,
and you will keep
your mouths shut.
Step aside.
Put out the fire!
- Carrots, come on.
- Help me save him.
- Carrots, we need--
- Nick.
Cold! Cold!
- [Kitty yells]
- [Milton groans]
[snake wails]
[grunts, groans]
- [grunts]
- Chief.
He'll be okay.
Antivenom. He can be saved
with antivenom.
Hopps, what did you do?
- No, Hogg-- Hoggbottom.
- They're helping the snake.
They're trying to kill
the chief!
- Hoggbottom, no. Please.
- Backup! I need backup!
- My page. Let's go.
- Wait, wait, wait.
I need the journal
and probably a sweater.
[shrieks]
W-whoa.
[gasps] Cold.
- [Hoggbottom] On the ground.
- Wait.
- [Hoggbottom] Oi!
- Next time, we stay home?
[Hoggbottom] Don't you move.
[panting, grunting]
No. Stop them!
- Oi!
- [Judy] Come on.
- Stop!
- Come on!
Stop!
[Judy grunts]
[yelps]
[Judy on carrot pen]
I really am just a dumb bunny.
Accident.
Your words, not mine.
[both shriek]
[Mr. Big grunts]
Put 'em in the trunk.
[both yelp]
[both groan]
[Purrrnacleo]
"Ter-roar" in Tundratown.
[Nutriamo]
A fanging at the fiesta.
A howl-a at the gala
as a venomous snake
attacks the founding family.
[Howlett] More shocking,
the snake was aided
by embattled ZPD officers
Nicholas Wilde and Judy Hopps.
All three now suspects
in the tragic fanging
of Zootopia's chief of police
and considered
extremely dangerous.
Chief Bogo...
is dead.
[crowd gasps]
Those are words I'm glad
I don't have to say.
[crowd exhales deeply]
I might have to soon.
The doctors
are a little weirded out, but
what has happened tonight
was more than horseplay.
[Milton] Hmm.
Uh, we, uh...
We're gonna take
that snake down.
And the fox and that rabbit!
Do you know how many mayors
they've already destroyed?
One, two... I got up to two.
Would you like to be "three"?
I want them gone.
But aren't there... laws?
I will say this once, Brian.
You will retrieve the journal
and bury them.
Or maybe
- I chose the wrong mayor.
- [Winddancer gulps]
Did I choose the wrong mayor?
[gulps]
[sirens wailing]
- [phone ringing]
- [Judy straining]
Hmm.
[phone chimes]
[sighs]
Hey.
The phone is the first thing
they'll track.
[Judy gasps]
Sorry. I have never been on
the run from the law before.
Yeah. Boy.
It's almost like we shouldn't
have gone to that gala, huh?
Okie doke.
We already did it your way.
With Mr. Big, we do it mine.
This is where having
a partner from the underworld
is really gonna pay off.
Raymond! And is that Kev...
[♪ jazz music playing]
Welcome to my warehouse.
Oh, my God, I love your dress.
Oh! Thank you.
[grunts] Fru Fru and I
are now equal partners
in the family business.
She brings wonderful ideas
for crime and for fashion
while I get more time to focus
on what matters most:
being grandpapa
to my little Judith.
Kiss my ring.
[chuckles]
Kiss the stinkin' ring
right now!
You kiss it right now!
Kiss it!
Mwah.
Nonno, you said we were gonna
make cement shoes
for Mr. Weaselton.
Oh, that's my girl.
They grow up so fast.
- You shut your mouth, fox!
- You run your mouth too much!
Anyways, you're in trouble.
And we like one of yas,
so we're here to help.
New clothes. New identities.
Truck out of town
leaves in an hour.
And your meter maid cart
is taken care of.
[inhales]
I think you misunderstand.
We've been framed
by the lynxes.
And an innocent snake needs...
Judy, the lynxes
are killers...
[grunts]
...and they have no honor.
And this Tundratown expansion
only makes them
more dangerous.
Territorial animals will do
anything for more land.
So, if whatever
you're tangled up in
threatens their plans,
you're dead.
You don't fight the cats.
You leave.
Sir, I know you're trying
to look out for us.
But we took an oath
to protect this city.
And justice doesn't run.
On behalf of myself,
"Rick Wilde,"
and "Miss Trudy Cabbagepatch,"
we thank you for your truck
to salvation and-- Ow!
We cannot accept your offer.
We are helping that snake.
Boy, you're really
tossing that "we" around.
Snakes may have been framed
for the fanging
of that tortoise.
Do you have any idea why?
Or how this book
could prove it?
I wish I did.
But if it has to do
with snakes,
your best bet
is talking to a reptile.
Do you know any?
Almost no one does.
They keep to themselves,
hide out in Marsh Market.
But you can still find 'em.
You just need
a reptile expert.
Someone local
who knows where to go.
Lucky for you, I met someone.
She runs a podcast!
[Nick] No, no.
Trudy Cabbagepatch,
Rick Wilde says no.
[Nibbles] Oh, yeah!
If Hopps and Wilde
are on the lam,
subtle sleuthin' 'tis my jam.
Woo! Mind the splinters.
Oh, you called
the right beaver.
If you wanna talk to
a reptile, I am your gal.
Also, if you need to talk
to a jackalope,
which are real, Mom!
[chuckles]
Excuse us. Team meeting.
Vetoing the beave.
New vote: All in favor
of "Truck to Being Alive
and Laying Low Till This
Blows Over-ville"? I mean...
Hopps and Wilde
do not bail on a case.
But she's crazy.
Probably lead poisoning
from eating too many pencils.
Do you know a reptile who can
tell us the hidden secret
in here,
or why the lynxes
framed the snakes?
[sighs]
Twenty-four hours.
Sunrise tomorrow.
If we strike out,
then we go into hiding,
and "Judy Cabbagepatch" it is.
[horn honks]
[groans]
It's "Trudy" Cabbagepatch,
and the safe word
is "coconut."
In the darkness
of a dank underpass,
they stepped into the vehicle,
not realizing their lives
were about to change.
Because we're gonna
meet a reptile?
Because you're about to be
best buds
with Nibbles Maplestick!
Takes two to tango, but
a threesome to be somethin'.
Let's find you a reptile
and romp the swamp.
[inhales]
Breathe it in!
- [Judy] Oh!
- [Nibbles whoops]
[Nibbles] Now, if any reptile
would know
the secret of that book
and why the snake wants it...
- Hey, Johnny!
- [Johnny] Oh, no!
...it's my old lizard friend,
Jesús.
[Judy] Why would a lizard
hide here?
Well, when Zootopia
was founded,
the whole neighborhood
got cut off
from the rest of the town.
Kinda on our own here.
[grunting]
Yeah, that's probably why
reptiles like it.
They can just do their thing.
Plus, it's the only place
in town
you can get away with
wearing a shirt and no pants.
Loving tour time
with Woodchuckles.
- [whispers] Great call.
- [Judy growls]
- We need her.
- Oh, yeah.
Like a hole in the head.
[dolphin squawks]
Bad timing. Hmm.
Okay, to get to
Jesús's hideout,
we gotta take a ferry.
Just let me handle the locals.
Water folk tend to be a little
standoffish around landies.
Well, I've been hustling
the streets since I was 12.
I think I can handle
a juggling seal.
- [roars]
- Oh! [chuckles]
Sea lion.
He's not from around here.
- But coin's a coin.
- [growling]
Oh, no. Change... [grunts]
...is a choking hazard.
- Well, honest mistake.
- [roars]
Do not do that!
Let's let Nibbles handle this.
[Nibbles] Thank you, Judith.
Conversing with these
beautiful sea creatures
is like talking to anyone
a little different.
Just takes open
and respectful communication.
[ringing]
[bubbling]
- Heya, bub.
- Hey, bub.
- Heya, bub, hey.
- Hey, bub, heya.
- Bubba, bubba, bubba.
- Heya, bub.
- Hey, bub. Hey, bub, bub.
- Heya, bub. Bubby, bub.
- Hey, bub. Hey, bub. Hey, ho.
- Heya, bub, bub.
- Hey, bub.
Seen Jesús?
Yup.
And now we leave town.
- [rumbling]
- [Judy yelps]
[double whistle]
Eh?
Thank you for this.
Happy anniversary.
Oh.
It's your anniversary?
[George Givot]
♪ This is the night ♪
♪ It's a beautiful night ♪
- ♪ And we call it bella notte ♪
- [Russ sings along]
[sniffs]
How are we gonna
find them now?
[sea lion grunts]
[growls]
- [coin clinking]
- Thanks, seal.
- [snarling]
- [Truffler shouts]
Friend. No, no, no!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
[Truffler shouts]
[Nibbles]
Just a little farther.
Jesús and all the answers
you'll ever need
are, uh, right here
at the end of this
very scary, dark hallway.
Boy, this is so much better
than sitting on a beach
on Outback Island,
sipping piña koalas.
Hmm. We are not skipping town
when there is an innocent
snake out there who needs us.
He's got help:
his motorcycle buddy.
Ah! [pants]
You are acting weird.
What is your problem?
Well, A, you railroaded me.
And B... [inhales]
...if you must know,
I have an aversion
to reptiles.
[chuckling] What?
Oh, is my discomfort
hilarious to you?
No, you're... I'm sorry.
You're right, we are partners.
And whenever
I'm uncomfortable,
you are always very
considerate of my feelings.
Look out! Snake skin!
- [Judy laughs]
- [Nick growls]
- Ow!
- I'm slipping!
I'm slipping! Hold the rail!
- I'm holding the rail.
- Hold it. Hold it.
- Stop pulling my ears!
- Hold the rail.
Never pull a bunny's ears!
- Never pull a bunny's ears!
[creaking]
I think the real mystery
is how you two
ever solved anything.
[laughs]
Anyhoo, let's see what Jesús
has to say about your journal.
Oh, and if he offers you food, accept.
Declining is a sign
of disrespect,
to all of them.
"All of them"?
[door rumbles]
[♪ banjo music playing]
[chatter, laughter]
- [shudders]
- Ha! [laughs]
[groans]
[playing jazz]
Order up.
Hey, another drink.
[belches]
[whimpers]
So warm.
- Gah!
- [gecko shouts]
[crunch]
Whoops.
No!
[chuckles] Keep it.
[shudders]
[Nibbles] Jesús!
Allow me to introduce
my friends.
This is Judith and Nicholas.
They are wanted fugitives
investigating a snake mystery
and trying
not to get murdered.
May we sit?
- [snapping]
- Oh. Okay.
[all straining]
[Judy squeals]
Oh, I'm good,
but these guys look hungry.
Thank you for meeting with us.
We believe snakes were framed
for something in this journal,
- perhaps pertaining to...
- Eat first, talk second.
Oh.
[Judy, Nick groan]
- [whimpers]
- [gags]
[shudders]
Uh...
[slurping]
[gags]
Hey, guys. They ate it!
- [Jesús laughing]
- [all cheering]
[Jesús] Look at their faces.
[laughs]
I don't eat grubs.
Hermano, get me a scone!
[Jesús laughs]
Okay, okay.
Hmm.
Metal cover.
And what does that mean?
It means
it's fancy.
It also means
the secret you're looking for
is probably
right on the cover.
Somehow vipers can see things
in the metal,
even under the paint.
This is Ebenezer Lynxley's
original journal
for the weather walls.
Why would he hide a secret
for a snake?
I don't know.
But it must have been big,
'cause a tortoise died for it.
I am guessing
that it was a slow death.
[sighs]
[Nibbles groans]
The fanging didn't just change
how folks saw snakes.
No mammals trusted
any reptile after that.
[Jesús]
That's why we all left.
And that's when the Lynxleys
expanded Tundratown
the first time.
And it's happening again.
The expansion is going here.
[inhales] Marsh Market
will be buried in snow.
We'll all get pushed out.
Those lynxes
will get more land,
and there's no way
to stop 'em.
What if the secret
hidden in here could?
Then I would say
holding it puts the two of you
in grave danger.
- [rumbling]
- [both gasp]
- [rumbling grows louder]
- Ooh.
- [all yelp]
- They tracked you?
Hmm-hmm-hmm.
Whoops.
- [grunting]
- [all screaming]
- It's the ZPD!
- [Lizard yelps]
[slowly] Run!
Leave the tails!
Follow me. Come on!
Wait. Why are you helping us?
You two saved the city once.
I reckon you can
save it again.
And when you do,
maybe everyone will see
we ain't that different.
[jabbering]
Huh.
- Freeze!
- Yeah, freeze!
I'm really sorry. But this is
my family's only chance
to come home.
Wait. We wanna help.
Wait. Wait.
Come back!
There's no path.
Take the docks!
Wha-- Carrots!
Wait! We believe you!
Nick! Come on! Come on!
[sighs]
- [thud]
- [Nick yelps]
[Nick blabbering]
- [thud]
- Ow!
Grab it!
Hey!
I got eyes on them.
They're heading for the tubes!
In pursuit.
[Nick grunting]
[shouting]
[bells ring]
Hey, bubba.
- Hey, bub.
Go!
- Bub-bye.
- Hey, Bub.
Bub-bye. Bye.
- Hey, bub.
- Bub-bye.
- [Nick shouts]
- [Nibbles whoops]
Pro tip! If he goes
for the red line,
do not follow!
You will run out of air!
Good luck! I love you!
[onlookers gasping]
Sorry.
[Gary gulps]
Cannonball!
That's a red line. Red line!
You're going to run out
of air! Coconut! Coconut!
[muffled screams]
[Duke Weaselton]
Anything you need, I got 'em.
Sequels, prequels, requels.
Who says the industry's
going down the tubes?
[Nick yelling]
[muffled dialogue]
[Judy screaming]
[both panting]
[water spouting]
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yes.
Uh, you?
I... Well, I've...
[stutters] I feel like some...
some "sorries," uh,
may be in order.
Nick, it's okay.
I know you didn't want to
lose him on purpose.
Oh, not me sorry. No, no.
You sorry.
Well, now we kinda have
no way to find him
or stop the lynxes,
so agree to disagree.
But...
we are alive.
So if we can't find him,
that's great.
What we can find
is a truck out of here.
Gah.
Box of old matches. Helpful.
Trudy Cabbagepatch,
leaving town. We're done.
Yodelayheehoo!
Ah, dis is veird place
for you to be.
Ja, very veird.
Ach, zey fell out of ze tube.
Okay, ve vill call police
to help!
Nope! No, no, we're fine.
Yep, we were
just leaving town.
Actually, um,
do you happen to know
where this tube goes?
- Oh, Copenhoofen.
- [Jürgen] Ja, ist Copenhoofen.
- Got it. Thank y--
- [Jürgen coughing]
Oh, you chew too much.
This is not okay!
[Jürgen coughing]
Huh.
Where did... Where did
you find these flowers?
Oh, the Liebenflower?
Ze tippity-top of ze mountain.
Uh, zis is ze only place
zey grow.
Oh, boy.
- Is...
- [hooves clacking]
Uh, is there anything else
up there?
- Nope, there sure isn't.
- [Berthold] Oh, ja.
Old Honeymoon Lodge.
But is closed for long time.
Was hideout for snakes.
[gasps]
Honeymoon Lodge.
- How...
- [hooves clacking]
How do you reach it?
Oh, tourists take ze tram
from Copenhoofen,
but ze rope is faster.
[Jürgen] Good luck! Have fun
at ze Honeymoon Lodge!
Thank you!
[Judy grunts]
[Judy] What does the secret
have to do with
the reptiles leaving town?
How did it get hidden in the
journal in the first place?
Will you slow down?
How long do you think
it's going to be
before Hoggbottom and the ZPD
figure out where we are?
If anything,
we should be going faster.
As I always say...
[through carrot pen]
I really am just a dumb bunny.
Nick...
[rewinding]
I-- I-- I-- I-- I really am
ju-- dumb-- dumb-- dumb--
dumb-- dumb-- dumb bunny.
Just dumb-- dumb-- dumb--
This was a gift
to symbolize our partnership,
and it is not appropriate
for this moment.
Oh, no, I was just...
[chuckles]
...hoping to jot down
some ideas
for what we will put
on our tombstones.
I'll start.
"His partner did it."
What happened to you
that you can't just have
a normal conversation?
I will save that
for my therapy animal.
Yeah,
- you need a therapy animal.
- Oh, yeah.
Well, you need
a herd of therapy animals.
Yeah. You need a whole
migration of therapy animals.
- [Judy gasps]
- [Nick strains]
[both gasping]
[grunts]
Carrots?
[sighs]
[beeping]
[snorts]
- [snorts]
- [beeping continues]
Hmm.
[growls, snorts]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[creaking]
Hey, Carrots?
[Judy] Huh.
[squelches, splashes]
Ew.
[breathes shakily]
[motorcycle rumbling]
Uh, Carrots?
Ugh.
[gasps]
- Huh?
- [Nick gasps]
Carrots!
[grunts]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
There was a whole
reptile neighborhood.
Their home...
The lynxes just erased it.
This is what they do.
[Nick panting] We have to go.
They push animals out with
lies so they can have more.
We gotta go.
Carrots, we gotta go!
That's what
the snake's trying to prove.
The ZPD is here.
What?
No one will believe us.
Not without proof.
Leave it. They aren't gonna
just arrest us.
The lynxes want us dead.
We need it to solve the case.
- Judy, just...
- We have to solve the case.
- Nick...
- I don't care about the case!
[♪ music stops]
[stammers, sighs] Judy,
it's not worth dying for.
The world will never be
a better place
if no one is brave enough
to do the right thing.
The world is what it is,
Carrots,
and sometimes being a hero...
it just doesn't
make a difference.
[sighs]
I think, uh...
I think maybe...
maybe we...
are different.
- [thuds]
- [grunts]
[yelps]
- [yelps]
[gasps]
[Judy yelps]
[grunting]
[gasping]
[Nick yelps]
- Mmm.
- [grunts]
[panting]
[Bûcheron grunts]
[gasps, pants]
[grunts, groans]
Oh, my gosh,
I think I just took out a cop.
Uh. Sorry, sir!
- Pawbert?
- Yeah. It's, uh... you know...
- We're the good guys!
- I told you she's helping.
- [floor creaking]
- [Judy yelps]
[panting]
- Come with us.
- [Pawbert grunting]
- Ow.
- We have the fox.
- We have the fox!
- [whimpers]
They already have
your partner.
They can't get you too.
Please. We can stop my family.
- [grunting]
- [groans]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[grunts]
[pants, yelps]
[Judy grunting]
[Nick whimpering]
- [grunting]
- Judy!
- [groans]
- No, no, no!
I got you.
[panting]
[exhales]
All right. Here we go.
- [engine running]
- [Judy exhales]
What?
[♪ mysterious music playing]
Huh.
- You're not dead! [laughs]
- [yelps]
- She's not dead!
- [chuckles]
[grunts] Sorry, sorry.
I just got
my motorcycle license.
Nick?
They, uh...
They caught him.
But out here,
no one's gonna catch us.
[grunting]
Mayor Winddancer.
[snorts]
Where's the bunny?
I don't know.
But, you know, she's a rabbit.
So maybe you can
pull her out of your hat.
I'm not wearing a hat.
He's messing with you, sir.
I knew that.
Get him out of here.
No.
[♪ tense music playing]
Where are they, Mr. Wilde?
[sighs]
Begin the expansion.
Freeze Marsh Market.
- Flush everyone out.
- What? No, you can't--
Water folk, like foxes,
are lesser mammals.
If I say they helped
a dangerous snake,
no one will care what we do.
[Nick groans]
You're going
to a dark cell, Mr. Wilde.
Just long enough
to read the headline
of your partner's demise.
[Nick groans]
You should've left town
when you had the chance.
[engine starts]
[sighs]
Dad.
Fur from whoever's helping
the bunny and the snake.
Find Pawbert.
[Pawbert]
Almost to me hideout.
[chuckles]
Snake in the hole.
Ooh. Yeah, yeah.
[Judy] Oh!
Oh!
We shall succeed, Judy Hopps.
We'll stop the Lynxleys
and save your partner.
I'm sorry. You are...
Oh. Gary. Gary the Snake.
And your last name?
De'Snake.
Everything is gonna be okay.
[gagging]
[clears throat]
[chuckles nervously]
[Gary chuckles] Teaming up
with you is very exciting.
Ooh! Uh,
don't worry about my fang.
I got my own anti-venom pen.
Stops the toxin.
[anti-venom pen] Stab me
straight into the heart.
[Judy chuckles nervously]
[chuckles, gasps]
Welcome to my oasis...
[chuckles]
...away from my evil family.
I like to come here,
just kind of veg out.
Ooh!
- Get with all my cat stuff.
- Wow.
- No! That's actually vintage.
- Awesome.
[chuckles] No!
If you could just not.
- [Gary] Ooh!
- No! No, please don't.
- Wow!
- Oh, my gosh.
- Mammals get the best stuff.
- No.
- What's this do?
- Wait, not that.
[purring]
Turn it off. Turn it off.
[clears throat]
So, we should probably
get to the journal, hmm?
How did you become partners?
Oh, when I found out
the journal
was going to be
on display at the Gala,
I sent his family an anonymous
letter asking to see it.
Luckily, they make Pawbert
work in the mail room,
so he read it first.
I got him smuggled in
from overseas.
Seven days in a crate.
But if I fix things for
my family, it'll be worth it.
Then we'll fix things
for your partner too.
[♪ sentimental music playing]
Hey.
I know coming with us
was hard,
but we're gonna
help your partner,
the same way
we're gonna help the city.
We stop my family
and show everyone the truth.
Are you ready?
Light the fire.
How much do you know?
Well, uh, that his family
was framed,
and there's some secret
hidden in the metal cover
that only a snake can see.
Not just any snake,
a heat-sensing pit viper.
All it takes
is a little warmth.
I just... I don't understand.
Why would
your great-grandfather
hide a secret for a snake?
He didn't.
I...
[gasps]
It wasn't his journal.
That's the secret.
Zootopia wasn't created
by a mammal.
It was created by a snake.
[Pawbert]
Gary's great-grandmother.
She wanted to make the city
a place
where all animals
felt welcome.
So she invented
her weather walls
to help everyone.
She just needed an investor.
A partner.
But when my great-grandfather
saw what her idea
could be worth...
he plotted to steal her plans
for himself.
So he committed a murder...
his own maid...
and framed
Gary's great-grandmother.
[clamoring]
And because she was a snake,
everyone believed his lie.
Soon, no reptiles
were welcome.
And over time,
my great-grandfather
buried the reptile
neighborhood in snow.
And he died believing no one
could ever uncover his crimes.
But...
he was wrong.
[Judy]
Her original patent was saved.
That's what
you're looking for.
She hid it in her home.
Find her home,
find her patent.
We just didn't know
where her home was buried
until now.
[Pawbert] My family's land?
But under all that snow,
how are we gonna find it?
Wait.
Clock tower.
Her neighborhood,
the reptile neighborhood,
had a clock tower.
It lights up like a beacon.
If it wasn't fully buried,
maybe we could see it.
Follow it to her home.
Except my great-grandfather
turned off the power.
But we have the plans
that show us
how to turn it back on.
Oh! Ooh! Hmm.
The power switch
to her whole neighborhood
was in the original
control room.
All right! And where is that?
Inside the oldest wall
of the city.
The Desert Tundratown
weather wall.
We get inside,
turn on that switch,
light the clock tower,
- we find her house.
- We find her patent.
And my family
is finally coming home.
We will succeed, Judy Hopps.
We shall succeed!
[Kitty gasps] I found him.
Get me Hoggbottom.
[alarm buzzes]
[groans]
Ooh! It's Nicholas Wilde.
Big-time cop, huh?
I'll see you
at the lunch table.
I'm gonna tie your tail
in a knot.
Hoggbottom--
What are you looking at, butthead?
This is a mistake.
It's a setup. It's the lynxes.
Listen to me. Please.
I know we have had
our differences, right?
But I've always
respected you--
You don't respect anyone.
[grunting]
Phone. It's Milton Lynxley.
He's got
the rabbit's location.
Whatever he says,
it's a lie, Hoggbottom.
Hoggbottom, listen to me!
Oh, God.
[grunting]
[Nibbles] Nicholas Wilde!
What are the chances? [laughs]
You know, this is
my first time in prison,
and I gotta say,
their food is on point.
[sighs] How are you even here?
Destiny.
Plus an arrest. [chuckles]
But it looks like
Judith got away.
Was that decision mutual?
- [sighs]
- Oh.
Sensing trouble in paradise.
Wanna talk about it?
What I want
is to get out of here.
[Nibbles]
Right, your big plan.
Lay low on Outback Island
sipping piña koalas.
Except you can't trust koalas,
'cause they got four thumbs.
Did a whole episode about it
on my podcast.
It was called
"They Got Four Thumbs."
But you know what? At least
they ain't platypuses.
- [laughs]
- Wait. Can you just...
Can you please
just let me concentrate?
Roger that.
[crunching]
- Just talk to me, dude!
- [nail cracks]
[sighs]
What's the last thing
she said to you?
[sighs]
She, um...
Uh, she said
maybe we are too different.
[Nibbles] Hmm.
And what did you say
before that?
I said the case
isn't worth dying for.
Mmm.
Like, uh...
like, you know, as in it isn't
worth her dying for because...
because solitary animals
like me
don't have real friends.
And I... I...
I don't want to lose her.
So, I just...
I don't know how to say that.
[Nibbles sighs]
You know what, bud?
I think you just did.
Wait, how'd you do that?
Well, I opened my arms,
put them around you
and then I squeezed.
It's called a hug.
Do foxes not have hugs?
Oh! [laughs]
The lock.
Yeah, that's Beave 101.
[Hoggbottom]
The rabbit's in Desert Dunes.
Roll out!
[Truffler] Hit it. Roll out!
Your partner needs you,
and Nibbles Maplestick
is gonna get you to her.
Hey! It's the fox dad!
And the woodchuck!
Woodchuck? I'm a beaver!
Call me that again--
- [alarm blaring]
- Oops.
Okay, go! We gotta go!
Here we go!
Get back here!
[gasps]
Hello, Nicholas.
I hope you like my new home.
I wove it with my own wool.
- Jump scare!
- [Nick screams]
[chuckles] Adios!
[cell doors opening]
- [cackling]
- Ooh-whee!
[inmates shouting]
[rumbling]
- [cheering]
- We're free!
- Huh.
- Wheels. We need wheels.
[horn honks]
- No, no.
- [tires screeching]
No, no, no, no.
I am sorry.
I do not think we can
get to Judy in time to help.
Unless... [chuckles]
...you happen to know
the fastest driver
in the history of Zootopia.
[gasps]
[♪ exciting music playing]
[♪ music stops]
[chuckles] Hey, Flash,
Flash Hundred Yard Dash.
Partner's in trouble.
Need to get across town,
ignore the laws.
No...
problem.
[chuckles] Let's hit it.
[♪ languid music playing]
Hey.
- Glad you're here.
- I gotta tell ya,
I'm not convinced
a sloth is our most reliable--
[both screaming]
[Nick] Oh, yeah! Whoo-hoo!
[laughing]
To turn on the clock tower,
and light the way
to your great-grandma's home
so we can find her patent,
we need to reach the power
control room through here.
But we have to move quickly
or we're never--
We shall succeed, Judy Hopps.
Look, Gary,
if we don't over-prepare,
we're underprepared
and I don't...
My family's
been trying to prove
we're not what everyone thinks
for a hundred years.
But even this close,
they'd never want me
to put the weight of the world
on my shoulders.
Because I don't have
any shoulders. [laughs]
We shall succeed.
I got you, rabbit.
[mice scream]
I cannot help Judy
if I don't know where she is,
which is why I need you
to get on Paul's computer
and track Hoggbottom.
You are an escaped fugitive.
I could get fired
for even talking to you.
They're gonna put her
to sleep! Do it!
Okay!
Hmm.
Did you try restarting it?
Mm-hmm.
Have you tried
not being an idiot?
Hey, Paul.
I got you some donuts.
- Oh!
- [Paul growling]
- Oh, no!
- Thanks, Clawhauser.
[Nick] Clawhauser! Location!
[Pawbert] Oh, no.
I think we're gonna have to
go through the festival.
[Judy] Festival?
[crowd cheering]
- [siren wailing]
- [gasps]
The phone's
the first thing they track.
Go! Go!
- Clawhauser!
- I am working on it.
- I got it! No!
- Great, great, great. Now--
[Pawbert panting]
[panting]
Oh. What festival is this?
Yeah!
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Move, move, move!
[all gasp]
- Come on!
- Go, go, go!
We are with you, Judy Hopps.
Ha-ha!
We meet again, Zebra.
- [knuckles cracking]
- [Zebros yell]
- Here come the horns!
- Ow!
She's going for the door.
She's going for the door!
[Nick]
Clawhauser, we're out of time.
[Clawhauser] I got it!
Desert Tundratown weather wall
access door. Hurry!
- What is in that wall?
- Power control room.
But for, like,
some old part of Tundratown.
[gasps] I know what they're
doing. They'll ruin us.
[panting]
[Milton]
No more tranquilizers.
Put them down.
- Sir.
- Put them down. Now!
[♪ tense music playing]
[Milton] Take the shot.
Take the shot! Do it!
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
[♪ music stops]
[audio slows, distorts]
[♪ triumphant music playing]
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
Judy!
[panting]
- [worker] Snake!
- [Pawbert] Power control room?
Uh, five flights up.
Come on, hurry!
[Gary pants]
That is a lot of stairs.
Way to hustle, bud, I love ya!
I owe ya!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. It's
turning on. It's turning on!
[Nibbles grunts]
No. Nibbles?
[alarm blaring]
Nibbles!
[Judy grunts]
[gasps] Snake! [grunts]
Cold!
[grunting, panting]
It's jammed.
Don't worry about me.
Find the switch.
[Judy]
No, no, no, no. Not these.
It would be, uh... older.
[♪ tense music playing]
[Judy straining]
[all straining]
Can you see it?
Did we turn on the clock
tower? [breathes heavily]
[gasps]
There! [breathes deeply]
It's there!
[Pawbert stammers]
We did it? We can find
the original patent?
[Judy] Nick?
The door... It's locked...
We have to...
How did it lock?
Nibbles? [straining] Open it.
[grunts, yells] Nibbles!
[grunting]
Dang door stuck on me.
[Judy sighs]
Sorry.
Last case
there was kind of a twist.
I know.
[yelps]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
- [Pawbert gasping]
- [Judy grunts]
Oh, my gosh. [chuckles]
I really...
Oh, my heart is pounding.
[chuckles]
I thought you knew.
- No. [hisses]
- Whoa.
- [straining]
- Sorry, partner. [grunts]
Hate to leave you
out in the cold... [chuckles]
...but I'm gonna.
[groans]
Please don't be mad at me.
But, I mean, you get it.
[chuckles]
We've always been
on the same page. Me and you!
Underdogs, right?
You gotta prove you're as good
as everyone else.
That you belong.
[inhales] I know,
it's messed up... [sighs]
...but this is my chance.
I have to take it.
'Cause when I get
to his great-grandma's home,
and I burn
the original patent,
I'll finally be something
in my family.
And I'll finally belong too.
[Nick, through TV] Judy?
[Pawbert] Ruh-roh.
Carrots?
[clicks tongue, sighs]
No loose ends.
Bye, partner.7
Bye, Judy Hopps.
Pawbert. Please.
You can be different
than your family.
I don't want to be different.
[groans] Nick...
[Nick] Judy?
[machinery whirring]
Judy?
Nibbles, do you see her?
No, nothing yet.
[Nick] Judy.
Nick. [breathes shakily]
Ni... [breathes heavily]
[Gary] We shall succeed,
Judy Hopps.
[grunts, stammering]
It's okay. Judy sent me.
She needs to find Nick.
[groans]
Yep.
Should've seen that coming.
[groans]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Nick] Judy!
Nick. [breathes shakily]
We... shall... succeed.
[straining]
[Gary] Judy...
[breathes shakily]
I can't move.
[♪ somber music playing]
And you're too cold to help.
[Judy] And he's gonna...
Nick's gonna...
[Gary straining] Judy...
The world was
never meant to be
on one animal's shoulders.
That's why
my great-grandma wanted
Zootopia to be for everyone.
So, we could all help each
other. [breathes shakily]
I didn't help.
[Gary straining] You did.
You chose to help me
and became
my best warm-blooded friend.
Very warm.
[♪ hopeful music playing]
[Gary sighs]
Permission to hug?
[grunts]
[exhales deeply]
We're gonna save you
and save your friend.
- [exhales]
- Judy! [screams]
Hey, he's gonna eat
that rabbit!
No, wait! [stammers]
I'm saving her!
I'm gonna get her
the anti-pen.
Where is she?
[sighs] She...
She didn't make it.
[♪ tense music playing]
But with snake bites,
you go fast.
You'll see.
[grunting]
[gasps, groans]
- [Gary panting]
- [Chèvre yells]
[gasps] No.
[all grunting]
[grunting]
She's gone, Nick.
Just get it over with!
[Nick grunts]
[all grunting]
[Gary gasps]
- [Higgins grunts]
- [Gary gasps]
[gasps]
- [grunting]
- You're done.
- Know when to quit!
- [grunts]
[Gary] Anti-venom!
You can save her with the
anti-venom! Throw me the bag!
[Bloats grunts]
Judy!
[Pawbert groans]
[both straining]
[grunts]
Leave it!
You're gonna kill us both.
It's not worth dying for.
Agree to disagree.
[grunts]
[Nick yelps]
[anti-venom pen] Stab me
straight into the heart.
[gasps]
[groans]
[screaming]
[Gary grunts]
[both grunting]
[both panting]
[exhales]
- I thought... He told me you...
- I was trying to get to you.
- And I saw you...
- ...that you were...
I'll help your friend.
Okay. [stammers] I don't care
that we're different.
You know? I...
What I care about is you.
I care about you.
Okay?
And I didn't say it.
I should've said it.
But I didn't
because...
uh, well... [chuckles]
...'cause I am
an emotionally insecure
source of your discomfort,
who's not good
at expressing his feelings.
Probably because I've been
on my own my whole life.
It's not an excuse.
It's just...
It's why instead
of telling you
that you're the best thing
that ever happened to me,
I-I make jokes
about your ears.
And-And I tell you
that you try too hard,
when, you know, the truth is
I just don't want you
to get hurt.
Because... [breathes deeply]
Because no one else
in the world
matters more to me
than you do.
[♪ sentimental music playing]
I... I do try too hard
because deep down
I'm afraid that I am
what everyone thinks I am.
And I suppress my discomfort
because I'm worried
it makes me look weak,
and I wanna be strong,
and I think I'm failing
all the time.
And I only take
what you say personally
because you're
the only one in my life
who ever believed in me,
even when I don't even
believe in myself.
[inhales deeply] And I
should have told you that.
No one else in the world
matters to me
more than you do either.
I have unresolved
childhood trauma
that I refuse to discuss
because being vulnerable
scares me.
I make dangerous choices
because I have an unhealthy
bunny hero complex.
And I didn't join the ZPD
because I wanted to be a cop.
I joined because I always
wanted to be part of a pack.
And the thought of losing you
scares me because...
because you're my pack.
I should never have left you,
and I do need
a herd of therapy animals.
And I should have told you
that you are the only partner
I would ever want because...
[sobs] ...you're my fluffle.
Mmm. Um...
[crying]
That's a bunch of rabbits.
[both chuckle]
[Nibbles] Hmm.
Now that is what we call
an overshare.
I'm alive by the way.
I made it.
Oh! Also that guy
is still alive.
[cackles]
- [♪ upbeat music playing]
- Hey! Hey! Thief!
He's gonna get to
the lost reptile neighborhood,
find Gary's great-grandma's
patent and destroy it.
Yeah, I've got no idea what
that means, or who Gary is,
but let's go!
- Hopps and Wilde?
- Wilde and Hopps.
And Nibbles and Gary!
[gasps] He's Gary.
Whoa, whoa!
Thank you. It's for the snake.
He's cold. No fur on him.
- Why, you little...
- [chuckles] Bye now.
[panting]
- You!
- Dad!
You don't belong
in this family!
Wait, wait, wait! Dad!
You will never
belong in this family!
Wait, wait! I wasn't working
with them. I was helping us.
[grunting]
I know where the reptile
neighborhood is buried.
Where to find the real patent
that proves that snakes
invented the walls.
I'm going to destroy it,
for the family.
For you, Daddy.
[Winddancer blusters] Uh...
You want to keep your job,
you say nothing.
You!
Maybe you are a Lynxley.
Take me to the patent.
[rattling]
It takes a threesome
to be somethin',
but a four-way
to bust your doorway.
[Pawbert exclaims]
Get to the patent! Destroy it!
[Pawbert grunting, panting]
Go! We got this.
Hey, whiskers,
you're done hurtin' muh city.
[growling]
Uh-oh. Tides have turned.
- [Nibbles grunting]
- [lynxes roar and screech]
[Nibbles]
Hey, Brian Winddancer!
[thudding]
You want to be a hero, or
just play one on TV? Ow!
[♪ tense music playing]
[panting]
[both panting]
Okay, I go left,
and you go right?
[panting] Uh, yeah.
Or...
[panting]
[engine starts]
[horn honking]
- [Pawbert exclaims]
- [Judy laughs]
[Judy]
You are a horrible driver.
[Nick] Yes, I am.
[exclaiming]
[both laughing]
[Judy grunts] Whoa.
[Nick chuckles]
I'm gonna jump! [grunts]
[grunts] Zoogetherness. Huh?
No, never mind.
Forget I said it. Here we go.
[both grunt]
- [Nick, Judy grunt]
- [Pawbert exclaims]
Matches, matches,
matches, matches.
[panting, gasps]
Bunnies, we're burrowers.
Rabbit kick. Hi-yah!
[Pawbert exclaims]
[yells]
[Nick, Judy grunt]
I'll destroy the patent,
that town
and everything in it.
And a dirtbag fox
and a dumb bunny
will never stand in my way.
[straining]
She's not a dumb bunny,
and you're forgetting
one thing.
What's that?
[straining]
We're friends with a snake.
- Howdy, partner. [vocalizes]
- [Pawbert screams]
- Heads up!
- [grunts]
[grunts]
- [groans] Daddy!
- Daddy's busy.
Brian! Go!
- You say justice is dead...
- [grunts]
- ...I say neigh!
[yelling]
Ha-cha! [grunts]
- [Gary] Here, kitty-kitty.
- No! [grunts]
It's called an arrest, sweetheart.
Boom.
[screaming]
[grunts]
[chuckles] No one
will believe you over us.
We've always
been better than you.
And we always will be.
Nothing you do matters.
Well, it matters to him.
[♪ gentle music playing]
Shall we?
[gasps]
[breathes shakily]
[♪ sentimental music playing]
[Judy] Hmm.
[gasps]
One long sock. [sniffles]
[breathes deeply]
[gasps] Oh.
[♪ sentimental music
continues]
[whirring]
[ticking]
[Gary gasps]
[laughs] I'm gonna burn it all
to the ground!
I'm a real Lynxley! [laughs]
[all gasp]
[panting]
[all exhale]
That'll do, pig. That'll do.
[Moosebridge]
Astonishing news today
after officers Judy Hopps
and Nicholas Wilde
along with a pit viper
and a beaver
foiled another
major conspiracy
by revealing the true inventor
of the city's weather walls
was a snake.
[Growley] While the now
disgraced Lynxley family
were revealed to have stolen
the original plans
and covered it up for decades.
You have not heard the last
of Milton Lyn...
[Moosebridge]
Their Tundratown expansion
- now officially canceled.
- [animals cheering]
[Fuzzby] Some are calling you
the dream team.
How did you do it?
Uh... Well, there's a lot of
different animals out there.
And sometimes,
we start to look
at all the little reasons
that we're not the same.
And it makes us worry.
But maybe if
we just talked to each other,
if we just tried
to understand one another,
we would see
that our differences
don't really make
any difference at all.
Maybe we'd even see that
what makes me me and you you,
can make us even stronger.
And with hard work, you're
gonna get to that by year two!
[clapping, chattering]
[whispering] Zebros.
Actually, my name is Gene.
[sniffles] My name...
is also Gene.
- Zebros!
[bunny children laughing]
[bunny children exclaim]
He did it!
[laughter]
Kids, get off the snake.
- [bunnies giggling]
- [Clawhauser gasps] Aw!
- Hi. How is everybody doing?
- [knocking]
[gasps] Oh!
[stammers] One sec!
[exclaiming]
[Gary chuckles]
This is my family.
Permission to hug?
Thank you.
[chuckling]
[♪ gentle music playing]
Hey, uh, I got you something.
- [gasps]
- [Nick chuckles]
Love you, partner.
But I am still me, so I'm
only saying it once a decade.
[Nick, through carrot pen]
Love you, partner.
Oh, I'm gonna need that back.
I'll give it back to you
after our next case.
There's gonna be
another case, huh?
Of course. Because,
when you broke out of jail,
you also released 200
highly dangerous prisoners.
Worth it.
Any idea
where you want to start?
[Judy chuckles]
[♪ "Down Under" playing]
Oh. Mmm. Mmm.
One-way ticket
to Outback Island, please.
First class.
[Australian accent] Very nice.
Oh, and remember, if you're
happy with our service,
please be sure to leave us
four thumbs up.
Oh, I will.
[sighs]
[slurps, exhales deeply]
Hopps and Wilde?
Wilde and Cabbagepatch.
[Gazelle] Zootopia, vamos!
- [crowd cheering]
- [♪ drums playing]
[Gazelle]
Burning Mammal, let's go!
[♪ drums continue playing]
♪ Come on, get on up ♪
♪ We're wild
And we can't be tamed ♪
♪ And we're turnin' the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
- [♪ Gazelle vocalizing]
- [♪ drums continue playing]
♪ We live in a crazy world ♪
♪ Caught up in a rat race ♪
♪ Concrete jungle life
Is sometimes a mad place ♪
♪ It's you and me together
At the end of a wild day ♪
♪ Don't keep it
All bottled up ♪
♪ And release your energy ♪
♪ Hey-ooh-ay ♪
♪ Only reason we are here
Is to celebrate ♪
♪ In a place where anyone
Can be anything ♪
♪ Hold on to this moment
Don't let it fade away ♪
♪ Baby
Keep the music playin' ♪
♪ Come on, get on up ♪
♪ We're wild
And we can't be tamed ♪
♪ And we're turnin' the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Come on, keep it up ♪
♪ It's fun
If you're down to play ♪
♪ And we're turnin' the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
- [whistle blowing]
- [♪ music continues playing]
[Gazelle] ♪ A zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ A zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ We live in a heated time ♪
♪ No chance to cool down ♪
♪ Continuously confined ♪
♪ What do we do now? ♪
♪ It's all about
Finding love ♪
♪ Sometimes hard to come by ♪
♪ But when it comes to us ♪
♪ It's always a good time ♪
♪ Hey-ooh-ay ♪
♪ Only reason we are here
Is to celebrate ♪
♪ In a place where anyone
Can be anything ♪
♪ Hold on to this moment
Don't let it fade away ♪
♪ Baby
Keep the music playin' ♪
♪ Come on, get on up ♪
♪ We're wild
And we can't be tamed ♪
♪ And we're turnin' the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Come on, keep it up ♪
♪ It's fun
If you're down to play ♪
♪ And we're turnin' the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ A zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
[♪ music continues playing]
[Gazelle]
♪ I'll take you higher ♪
♪ We can't be tamed ♪
♪ Baby, I'll take you higher ♪
♪ I'll take you higher ♪
♪ And we can't be tamed ♪
♪ Baby, I'll take you higher ♪
[in Spanish] ♪ Es una fiesta
Que sube como la espuma ♪
♪Yo por ti iré hasta
La luna de ida y vuelta ♪
♪ Es una fiesta que sube
Como la espuma ♪
♪ Yo por ti iré hasta
La luna de ida y vuelta ♪
[in English]
♪ Come on, get on up ♪
♪ We're wild
And we can't be tamed ♪
♪ And we're turnin' the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Come on, keep it up ♪
♪ It's fun
If you're down to play ♪
♪ And we're turnin' the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Come on, get on up ♪
♪ We're wild
And we can't be tamed ♪
♪ And we're turnin' the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Come on, keep it up ♪
♪ It's fun
If you're down to play ♪
♪ And we're turnin' the floor
Into a zoo-ooh-ooh ♪
[crowd cheering]
[Nick through carrot pen]
Love you, partner.
Hmm.
[Nick through carrot pen]
Love you, partner.
[Pronk] Hey, bunny.
Ya gonna keep playing that
all night?
[Bucky] Leave her alone.
She's proud of herself,
but still seeks
external validation.
- [Pronk] Oh, shut up!
- [Bucky] You shut up!
[Pronk] You shut up!
[Bucky] Hey, bunny,
what's next for you two?
Uh, we're investigating
a rabbit
who strangled her neighbors.
[Bucky] You offended her.
- [Pronk] You offended her!
- [Bucky] Shut up.
- Good night!
- [Pronk] You shut up.
[muffled arguing continues]