[person]
Most of the time, it's like--
I don't know.
It's like there's
this thick, black cloud
covering everything.
Like we see the world,
but we don't really
see the world, you know?
We're all
just stumbling around.
Directionless.
No sense of meaning.
No sense of purpose.
I know that might
sound super depressing,
but honestly,
I think it's a good thing.
Because it makes us appreciate
the other times.
Those brief,
transcendent moments
when the lights flicker on,
the black cloud parts,
and you see the world
for what it really is.
Oh. [clears throat]
And suddenly there's meaning.
Suddenly there's purpose.
[sighs]
So, uh, do you--
Oh, shit.
Shit. Shit, shit, shit.
Shit. [breathing heavily]
[both chuckling]
[person] If you're lucky,
you'll experience this
once in your lifetime.
Goddamn, that was...
- That was smooth.
- Yeah.
[person] For me...
So smooth.
[person] ...it happened twice.
The first
was the day I met Josh.
Uh, I'm Josh.
I'm Iris.
[Iris] And the second...
the day I killed him.
["Gimme Some More" playing]
[Josh] Iris, wake up.
["Gimme Some More" continues
on radio]
Hey, sleepyhead.
[yawns]
How long was I out?
[yawns] Uh, for a while.
Yeah, you were
zonked out there pretty good.
I was having
the most wonderful dream.
Oh, yeah? About me?
Well, that is
very presumptuous, but...
Yeah.
- ...yes. [chuckles]
- [laughs] Yes. Knew it.
Was it sexy times?
No, you deviant.
- Little bit of sexy times?
- No, I was--
- Was my shirt off?
- No,
I was dreaming
about the day we met.
It was all so perfect.
Remember
how perfect it all was?
Yeah, no.
No, how could I forget?
The supermarket, the oranges.
[chuckles]
What road is this?
It's not showing up
on the GPS.
[Josh] I don't think this is
the road.
Think this might be
the driveway.
[automated voice]
You have arrived
at your destination.
Thank you, Josh's car.
Thank you, car.
Pop the trunk.
[Josh's car] Popping trunk.
[birds chirping]
Fuck me.
Kat called this place
a "little rustic cabin
in the woods."
I think we might have
differing opinions
on the meaning
of the word "cabin."
- Also "rustic."
- [breathes heavily]
Also "little."
[breathes heavily]
[bags clattering]
What?
Iris. Come on.
You know you can't lie to me.
Tell me what's wrong.
I'm gonna do something stupid.
I'm gonna say
something stupid.
I'm gonna embarrass you.
They're gonna laugh at me.
They're gonna hate me.
They already hate me.
Jesus Christ, Iris.
We've been planning this trip
for months,
and this is all
just coming out now?
Like 20 feet
from the fucking door?
[sighs]
Look, look. Hey.
My friends don't hate you.
Kat does. [chuckles]
Yeah, m-maybe,
but Kat hates everybody.
I just don't wanna
screw everything up. [sighs]
Come on, Beep-Boop. You're
not gonna screw everything up.
Just relax, you know?
Don't be all mopey and weird.
[chuckles]
Just remember to--
remember to smile
and act happy.
Okay?
[doorbell rings]
Yay! You made it.
Fucking finally.
Okay, so when you said remote,
I thought you meant, like,
a couple miles
off the highway.
I didn't realize you meant
edge of fucking civilization.
Oh, don't be
so dramatic, Josh.
- It's not that far.
- Okay, hard disagree.
[chuckles]
Uh, hello, Iris.
Hi, Kat.
It's so good to see you.
So good.
Everyone, look who I found.
- [Josh] Hey, Patrick.
- Hey.
[Josh] Look at you
in the kitchen, man.
Yeah, look at me. Welcome.
I would give you a hug,
but I've got scallop hands.
Sorry.
Okay, well, I appreciate that.
Where's--
- [gasps] There he is!
- Hey!
[singsongy]
Joshyboy, Joshyboy.
- Hey, buddy.
- [chuckles]
You too, girl. Get in here.
- Hi. How are you?
- Hi! How are you?
I'm good. Uh, I'm... drunk.
- Oh. [chuckles]
- [Josh] Good. This is good.
Oh, and, Josh,
you remember Sergey.
[Patrick] Hey.
[speaks Russian]
Hey, Sergey.
Nice to see you again.
- Likewise, my friend.
- Oh.
- Likewise.
- [chuckles]
And this beautiful creation
must be Iris.
- Hello. [chuckles]
- Mmm.
Such pleasure.
I have heard lot
about this one.
- [Josh chuckles]
- Really? All good I hope.
Your lake house, it's really--
it's incredible.
- [Josh] Yeah, and so secluded.
- [Iris] Yeah.
I mean, I think
the last place we passed
was like ten miles back.
Seventeen.
And I paid for this.
Privacy does not come cheap,
my friends.
[laughs] Not cheap at all.
Don't tell me
you own the whole lake.
No, no, no. Don't be silly.
Just all the land around it.
But let's
get you guys a drink.
What do you like?
Beer, cocktail, wine?
I'm fine. More than anything,
I just need a shower.
Katyonak,
what room they are in?
Uh, up the stairs,
down the hall,
- last door on the left.
- Okay.
- I'll see you later. Yeah.
- Okay, I'll see you. Bye.
[sighs]
[Iris humming]
[inhales deeply]
Smile.
Act happy.
[friend] Okay, continue.
Continue with the story.
[Patrick] Anyway, so I was
wearing this ridiculously
elaborate Dracula costume,
and I didn't know
a single person, as I said.
So I'm standing
by the snack table
just munching on carrots
and something
- that looked like hummus--
- It wasn't hummus.
It was not hummus.
It was not hummus,
I don't think, but I--
I feel a tap on my shoulder.
And so I turn around,
and there's this green,
puffy dinosaur
just staring me down.
And inside its head,
I hear this very muffled,
very annoyed voice say...
[muffled]
"You're standing on my tail."
So I turn around, I look down,
and sure enough,
I'm standing
on his little dino tail.
So I step off and apologize.
And he takes his head off,
and I'm looking
at the most beautiful man
that I've ever seen
in my life.
So, did you meet
this beautiful man
- after you met Eli, or...
- Okay, you know what? Shut up.
- [Josh] Was that a scallop?
- [Eli] That was a scallop.
- Actually hit me.
- [Eli] Yeah, I took baseball.
[Patrick] Yes, you did.
Well, when did you know?
Uh, know what?
That--
That he was the one.
Oh.
Right then and there.
I know it's gonna
sound cheesy, but the moment--
the moment we locked eyes,
something inside of me just...
clicked into place. [chuckles]
Doesn't sound cheesy at all.
I get it.
It's like there's this piece
of you
that you didn't
even know was broken,
and then...
suddenly it's-- it's fixed.
And you're-- you're staring
at this stranger,
this person
you've never met before,
and you know...
that for the rest
of your life,
you will do whatever it takes
to make this person happy.
Right? [chuckles]
- [Eli] Yeah.
- [Patrick] Yeah.
[Josh] Yeah, totally.
Patrick, this food
is unbelievable. Thank you.
[Patrick] Thank you, Sergey.
That's so nice of you.
Um, I'm glad you like it.
[Eli] He spoils me.
I swear I've gained
like ten pounds
since we started dating.
- [Josh] Only ten? [laughs]
- Shut the fuck up. Okay?
So, Sergey,
what kind of work do you do?
Oh, you know,
I have fingers in many pots.
My hands are not clean,
my friend. [chuckles]
- It's a...
- [clears throat]
...a very dirty business.
[Iris] Sergey seems--
He seems nice.
[Kat] Oh, yeah.
He's got everything
you want in a man.
Yeah, he's rich, intelligent.
He's got a beautiful wife.
[stammers] Wife? So, he--
Sergey's married?
Mm-hmm.
But you love--
you love each other?
Love? No. No, no, no.
He'd have to think of me as a
human being first. [chuckles]
I don't understand.
I'm an accessory,
like his fucking car.
I wear what he wants.
Eat what he wants.
Fuck when he wants.
[inhales deeply]
[sighs, chuckles]
Look who I'm talking to.
[sighs]
Do you not like me, Kat?
You know, it's not that
I don't like you, Iris.
It's the idea of you.
You make me feel so...
replaceable.
[chuckles] Replaceable?
Nobody could replace you, Kat.
I mean, you're Kat.
And you're so fearless.
It's inspiring.
I wish I could be
more like you, but...
[breathes deeply]
...you know,
I wasn't built that way.
I just...
I feel like there's always
something inside of me
holding me back.
["Boy" playing]
No, no, no.
♪ Uh-huh ♪
Come on.
Okay, get up, bitch.
- Get up! Come on!
- No. Oh, God.
- [Eli] Come on!
- [Patrick] That's right.
- [Eli] You too.
- What the fuck?
Put that phone away
and get up.
- Okay.
- [Eli] Get your asses up.
- [Patrick] Come on.
- [Eli] Come on!
Iris, what are you doing?
[groans]
[breathes heavily] Ah!
[grunting]
I'm so glad we did this.
Being here with you
is just perfect.
Uh-huh.
I'm sorry if I was being weird
or mopey earlier.
I just want you
to be happy, Josh. That's all.
Iris, go to sleep.
[water running]
It's such a gorgeous day out.
[Josh] Uh, what's the weather?
It's currently 72 degrees
with an 83% chance
of rain in the evening.
[Josh chuckles]
It never gets old.
- [water stops running]
- [spits, sighs]
- [Iris] You almost ready?
- Oh, I'm sorry, babe.
I think I need
some time to shower
and pound
a few gallons of coffee.
Why don't, uh--
Why don't you head
down there by yourself?
But it was your idea.
You said you wanted a nice,
relaxing morning by the lake.
I know, but that's before the
hangover caught up with me.
Last night was a lot.
You had fun though, right?
Of course I did, Beep-Boop.
Last night was incredible.
You want me to wait?
We could
make the shower for two.
Nah, no, no.
That's okay. Um...
You go on ahead.
Enjoy as much of this
gorgeous day as you can.
- Okay.
- [chuckles] Yeah.
- Hmm.
- [sighs]
[birds chirping]
[Sergey speaking Russian]
Sorry?
Means "good morning."
Oh, yes.
Dobroe utro to you too.
Hey, your Russian is not bad.
It is not good,
but also it is not bad.
[both chuckle]
Nice view.
[speaking Russian]
To love.
[Sergey slurps]
Mmm.
You like?
I think I'm actually going to
head back inside.
So soon?
Yeah...
Josh wasn't feeling great
this morning,
so I think I should
check in on him.
Josh is big boy.
He can take care of himself.
Stay. Keep Sergey company.
I really think I should
see him.
You...
like lake house, yes?
Yeah.
You enjoy your time here?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, very much.
Then as guest, please stay.
Keep this old Russian man
company.
- Okay.
- Wonderful.
Mmm.
Oh. [sniffs]
You mind?
Just back and shoulders.
- It's tough to reach.
- Oh.
Don't want to get too tan.
[Iris] Okay.
Mmm.
And shoulders, please.
Okay.
[Sergey inhales sharply]
What are you doing?
It's not problem.
This Kat's idea.
She tell Sergey
you are down here.
Give Sergey permission.
Let go of my hand, please.
This is what you do, yes?
This is what you are for.
- [kisses] Mmm.
- Please.
Please stop.
[Josh chuckling]
[Eli] I was drunk.
I mean, you--
[Eli] Last night,
it was crazy.
[Josh]
You were extremely drunk.
You were drunk too.
Like, more drunk than I got.
I don't really get drunk.
It's like this gift.
Like, people get bloated
and stuff, and not me.
- Like, never happens.
- Never get bloated.
Never. It's like I could drink
and do whatever I want.
- It's like you get dehydrated.
- Yeah, just, like--
What the fuck?
[Josh] Oh, shit.
- Iris, what the fuck?
- [Iris whimpers]
I didn't mean to. He--
[Josh breathes heavily]
He forced himself on me.
Who did?
Sergey?
Mmm.
Please.
Sergey just want little taste.
[kisses]
I just wanted him to stop.
Oh, God. Sergey.
Iris. Hey, look at me. Look
at me. Talk me through it.
What happened?
[breathes shakily] I--
[kissing]
I said stop!
I didn't have a choice.
Sergey?
[groans]
[speaking Russian]
[Sergey grunting]
- [grunting]
- [speaking Russian]
He wouldn't let go.
He was choking me, Josh.
[both grunting]
[speaking Russian]
And then I--
And then you what, Iris?
Then you what?
[both grunting]
[Sergey grunting]
[Iris]
He was trying to kill me,
and the only thing
I could think about
was that if he did kill me,
I'd never get to
see you again,
and that hurt so much more
than the pain of being choked!
I wouldn't let that happen.
I couldn't let him take me
away from you.
I love you so much!
Iris, go to sleep.
[Iris humming]
[Josh, muffled] Okay.
Don't forget her ankles, okay?
[Patrick, muffled] Okay.
Are you sure
this is gonna hold?
[Josh, normal]
Yeah, no, it's fine.
She's not superhuman
or anything.
She's only as strong
as they want her to be.
[Josh sighs]
[sighs]
Handcuff knot.
- Hey.
[Josh] How's she doing?
She's asleep.
I gave her two Xanax.
Xanaxes? Xani?
- Whatever, she's asleep.
- Okay, good. Good.
[sighs] So...
what do we do now?
Uh, I mean,
the only thing we can do.
We call the cops.
We tell them everything.
Right, yeah.
- Yeah.
- But what about...
Well, uh, obviously
I'll need to, uh, you know.
I just don't understand
how this could have happened.
Don't they have safeguards
for this kind of shit?
I have no idea.
Like a glitch maybe?
Yeah.
Okay. Okay, so...
I'll call the cops,
and you will...
- Yeah. Yeah.
Sorry, do you mind,
um, taking it outside?
Just 'cause...
I-- I wanna say goodbye.
Yeah.
- Yeah, buddy. Sure.
- Yeah, thanks.
Iris, wake up.
...be lost without you!
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, it's okay. You're okay.
- You're okay. I'm here. Hey.
- [breathing shakily] Josh.
- Listen to me.
- [breathing shakily]
Wait. Why are my hands tied?
Why are my hands tied, Josh?
Iris. We didn't have a choice.
We didn't have a choice.
You murdered Sergey.
You remember?
No, no, no, no.
It was self-defense.
He was gonna kill me.
You gotta believe me.
No, I believe you, Iris.
I mean, you couldn't lie to me
even if you wanted to.
What?
It's, um,
part of your programming.
Programming? What the hell
are you talking about?
[Iris breathes shakily]
Okay, um...
Sorry, there's just
no delicate way to say this.
So, I'm just gonna
rip the Band-Aid right off.
[Iris breathing shakily]
You're a robot.
I'm...
A robot.
More specifically,
you're a companion robot.
A companion robot?
Yeah, it's like a, um...
[sighs]
I hate the word "fuckbot."
Um, 'cause you do so much more
than that, but, uh...
You're an
emotional support robot...
that fucks.
You're joking, right?
- This is just a sick--
- Iris, what's the weather?
It's currently 72 degrees
with an 83% chance
of rain in the evening.
- Are--
- Hmm.
Are you still not convinced?
Yeah, okay, uh...
Let's see.
Iris, do you know
any foreign languages?
Can you speak, say, Spanish?
Josh, you know
no sé hablar español.
¿Qué?
- How about Chinese?
- [speaking Spanish]
[speaking Mandarin]
Do I need to keep going?
'Cause I can go, uh...
I can do Portuguese.
I can do Korean.
I can do, uh...
I don't know what Telugu is,
but apparently you speak it.
I don't-- I don't understand.
I--
No, no, no. I have memories.
Uh, uh... College.
Uh, summer jobs. I've--
I've been to Japan. Twice.
Okay, so what those are--
Those are, um...
They're like outlines
of memories.
You know, just enough to give
you a little, uh, backstory.
The-- The-- The day we met
in the grocery store.
You and the oranges. That is
not an outline of a memory.
Yeah, it's fake.
Never happened.
I just randomly picked it
from a drop-down list
of meet-cutes.
It could've been anywhere.
It could've been dog park,
a bookstore, farmer's market.
It never happened?
[sighs] Okay, do, um--
Do you wanna know how we met?
Like, how we really met?
["Iris" playing on speakers]
Hey. Josh Beeman?
- Yeah, that's me.
- Okay.
- Yeah, come on in.
- Thank you.
Sorry.
How you doing?
Okay, this is
the user agreement.
- Okay.
- Just give it a read
and then sign at the bottom
when you're done.
Um...
So, um, what do I do
when she, like,
boots up or whatever?
Well, once she's done
syncing with your phone,
you'll need to
create a love link.
- Love link?
- Yeah. It establishes
the emotional connection
between you and...
Iris.
Just follow the vocal prompts
when she wakes up.
It's all pretty intuitive.
Do they-- Do they know
that they're robots?
Not at all.
She'll be so fixated on you,
your wants, your needs,
that'll never even occur
to her.
The whole experience
is customizable.
You can change her voice,
eye color, intelligence,
and if you ever wanna revert
back to her factory settings,
there is a thumbprint sensor
behind her right ear.
Just hold your thumb there
for five seconds,
she'll reset.
[stammers] You can-- You can
change their intelligence?
Yeah, but don't worry.
There's about a billion
government regulations
that force us to limit
how strong and smart
they can be.
A hundred-percent intelligence
would be the equivalent
of an Ivy League grad.
Zero percent would be
a mindless automaton.
It really just depends on
what kind of partner you want.
She can't lie.
So if you ask her a question,
she literally has to
tell you the truth.
And for obvious reasons,
her programming prevents her
from causing harm
to humans, animals,
or other companions.
Trust me, Mr. Beeman.
You have nothing
to worry about.
Iris is completely docile.
She's yours to do
whatever you want with.
["Color of Anyhow" playing]
[Iris dings]
To establish love link,
please place your face
within three feet
of my field of vision.
[Iris dings]
Please say your name.
[clears throat]
Josh Beeman.
[scanner whirring]
Thank you, Josh Beeman.
[sputters]
Love link established.
Hey, you.
H-Hi.
[Josh chuckles]
- Um...
- [Iris chuckles]
Uh...
So...
- Oh, my God. Oh, fuck.
- [rhythmic thudding]
Oh, fuck!
Oh, God!
I don't understand.
I feel things.
Anger, guilt, sadness. I--
I know what pain feels like.
It's programming.
It's just a way
to make you seem more real.
Everything you do,
your whole life,
it's just an imitation
of a life.
There-- There we go.
Perfect. Okay. [sighs]
This is just water.
You know, it's from
a reservoir in your body.
It's like wiper fluid.
I get it topped off every time
I take you in to get serviced.
Oh, God. I'm gonna be sick.
No, you're not!
Iris, it's programming.
Stop saying that!
Yeah, you're right.
You're right. I'm sorry.
I know this must be
a lot to process.
Okay.
Okay, what?
I'm not real.
But I'm still yours.
We can get through this.
We can go back home.
I'll do whatever you want.
I'll cook for you, wait
on you, make love to you.
I can make you happy, Josh.
I can make you
so, so, so, so happy.
No.
I'm sorry, Iris.
That can't happen.
Why not?
[Kat] Uh, what are you doing?
- Nothing, okay?
- What the fuck
are you waiting for?
- Shut her down already.
- Shut me down?
- Fuck, Kat. Jesus Christ!
- What is she talking about?
- Shut me down? Josh!
- Nothing, nothing. Just--
Will you excuse me
for a second, Iris?
Josh! Please!
- Dude.
- No, come on.
[Iris] Josh!
[inhales sharply] Josh.
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[Josh] You can't do that, Kat.
You can't tell a robot
you're gonna shut it down.
That's, like, not cool at all.
Well, okay,
I don't like surprises, Josh.
This was not part of the plan.
Look, I know, and I'm sorry,
but I mean,
considering everything
she's done for us,
I figured she was
at least owed an explanation.
And--
Okay, look,
I wanted to say goodbye.
Are you kidding?
She's a piece of plastic
that you have sex with.
Ugh.
Saying goodbye to her
is like saying goodbye
to the sock you jerk off in.
Okay, she's not a sock.
[Josh]
The plan hasn't changed, Kat.
I'm just adding
one tiny, extra step.
Just a final farewell.
And then I will switch
all of her settings
back to normal.
And then, yeah, I'll
shut her down permanently.
- And then?
- And then nothing.
Then we crack open a bottle
of champagne,
and we wait
for the cops to show up.
[grunting]
[Josh]
I mean, the hard part's over.
Which, by the way,
like, holy fucking shit!
Right?
[Josh] I mean, you plan,
and you plan, you plan,
and you, like, know
it's gonna happen,
but then, like, it happens,
and you're like,
"Holy fucking shit!"
I mean, we did it!
We did it.
We, like, fucking did it.
[grunts]
All-- All right, all right.
That's-- That's good.
- That's enough.
- Okay, yeah, sorry. Right.
Sorry.
I still just can't believe it.
Yeah, I know. It's so crazy.
What the fuck
is going on with you?
Why are you not
as excited as I am?
No, I am. I'm excited.
It's, um...
It's just-- It's just
the Xanax Eli gave me.
You actually took it?
It's a Xanax, Josh.
I'm not gonna not take it.
Hey, Beep-Boop.
Look, I'm so sorry about that.
Everything's gonna be okay.
We're--
What are you doing?
Oh, fuck. Iris, go to s--
[choking]
[Josh, choking] Help!
[Josh choking]
Baby, I'm so sorry.
[choking continues]
He'll need an ice pack,
and if there's any swelling,
shortness of breath,
wheezing, agitation
or drowsiness,
take him
to the emergency room, okay?
Um...
okay.
Yeah, she's tied up inside,
so she's not going anywhere.
Mm-hmm.
Eli. Eli, Iris is--
[shushes] Baby, I'm
on the phone. I can't hear.
[Patrick sighs]
[birds chirping]
What's that?
What am I looking at?
A mod.
A mod?
And what does it mod?
Iris.
Gives me access
to parts of her programming
that you're not
typically given access to.
I'm sorry.
Did you jailbreak your sexbot?
What did you do to her?
I bumped up her aggression
and her self-defense
functions.
And I turned off
the programming
that prevents her
from doing harm.
But she escaped before I had
the chance to reset her.
So if Empathix finds her
before we do,
then they'll know
she was tampered with,
and then we're fucked.
Wait, so does that mean that--
Did you kill Sergey?
No. No, no, no.
Iris killed Sergey.
- [sighs] Thank God.
- We just gave her
- a little push.
- Oh, my God.
- Wait, Eli. Eli, you--
You have to understand, Eli.
Sergey was a bad dude.
He was mixed up in all kinds
of fucked-up shit,
like drugs and guns
and, like, human trafficking.
Not to mention
a terrible boyfriend.
- Yeah, just the worst!
- Why?
I don't know! Who's to say
what makes people
do bad things?
It could have something
to do with his upbringing.
No, dick. Why did you do it?
[Josh] Oh.
Right. Sorry. Um...
Well...
- You remember the code?
- [Kat] Of course.
Stalin's birthday.
It's his code for everything.
[sighs]
I see.
How-- How-- How much is that?
Um, just over 12 million.
Oh, goddamn it.
That smells so fucking good.
[sniffs]
Wait.
If this whole trip was a setup
to get Iris to kill Sergey,
why did you have Patrick and I
tag along?
To corroborate our story.
I mean, we figured it'd be
an easier sell
with more witnesses.
Oh. So, we were just
a couple of stooges, huh?
- [Josh] No.
- Nice.
Technically, yes,
but that was the old plan.
New plan...
you get a cut.
Even three-way split.
You mean four-way split.
No. I mean three-way.
But there's four of us.
You're-- You're kidding.
He's-- He's kidding.
You, me, Kat, Patrick.
- Eli...
- Josh...
Patrick doesn't count.
- Are you fucking--
- Wow.
- Right in front of him? Nice.
- I--
I'm so sorry, baby. I'm sorry
you had to hear that.
That's okay. I don't mind.
Patrick, go to sleep.
What the fuck, dude?
You trying to
sabotage my relationship?
No! Of course not, man. I know
how much Patrick means to you.
God knows you could have
traded him in
for a newer model,
like, many times.
Are you fucking
robo-shaming me?
[Josh]
I am not robo-shaming you.
I-- I like Patrick,
but he's not getting a cut.
You're lucky
you're getting anything
considering you contributed
jack shit.
What the fuck
did you contribute, huh?
Iris did everything.
I planted the knife
in her pocket.
- I had to practice that.
- The knife?
That was probably
the most flimsiest part
of the plan, actually,
to be honest.
How did you know
she'd find it?
[Josh] I don't know.
I've never orchestrated
a murder before.
It's fucking hard.
- [Eli] Clearly.
- Okay!
[Josh sighs]
- Eli.
- Yeah?
We're offering you
four million dollars.
And all you have to do
is help us
find one little robot girl
in the woods.
[Iris panting]
That's not a bad deal.
[birds chirping]
[Iris panting]
[Eli sighs]
Fine.
But I call dibs on the gun.
[Josh stammers] Eli.
We're not gonna need that.
I mean, all I have to do
is get close enough
to put her to sleep
and grab my phone and wipe
the mod from her system.
So we're fine.
[Eli] She has your phone?
[Josh] Yeah.
Does she know your passcode?
[Eli] Josh, does she know
your passcode?
[Josh] Yeah. I mean,
she knows everything about me.
Yeah, then we're definitely
gonna need this.
- Patrick, wake up.
- [dings, inhales sharply]
- Hey, baby.
- Hey.
We're going robot hunting.
Oh, okay.
- Fun, huh?
- Fun.
[Kat] Josh.
What can she do
with your phone?
Hello.
[high-pitched] Hello.
[low-pitched] Hello.
Wow, Josh.
[Kat] Goddamn it, Josh. We've
been walking for-fucking-ever.
Isn't there like a "find
my fuckbot" app you can use?
[Josh] Yeah, there is.
But guess what.
It's on my fucking phone.
- [Eli] Goddamn it, Josh.
- [Josh] Will you stop yelling?
We know the general direction
she was going.
We just need to--
Why don't we just split up?
That way, we can kind of
attack her from...
two different angles,
you know?
Like a pincer--
- Hit her-- What are you doing?
- [Josh] I don't know.
Eli and Patrick,
you guys go that way.
Kat and I,
we're gonna go this way. Okay?
Kat and you will go that way?
Are you guys fucking?
- Gross.
- No, of course not--
"Gross"?
[Iris] Okay.
What now, Iris? Think.
Use that
extra 60% intelligence.
Just need to get back home,
grab some clothes, money,
clean yourself up.
How do you do that?
[inhales sharply]
You could work your way back
to the main road.
Hitch a ride.
[driver] What the fuck?
Okay, no hitchhiking.
You could go on foot.
It's hundreds of miles
across difficult terrain.
It could take days.
And by the time
you get back...
Welcome home, Beep-Boop.
[chuckles]
Yeah, no walking.
You got Josh's phone.
The phone controls you.
But it also controls...
[car system dings]
[Josh's car] Good afternoon.
Where would you like
to go today?
Home, please.
[Josh's car] Driving home.
And might I add,
this is a terrific plan, Iris.
Aw.
Thank you, Josh's car.
[breathes heavily]
All you gotta do is
backtrack through the woods,
get to the lake house
without Josh or his friends
murdering you,
and you're home free.
[Patrick] Where'd you find it?
[Eli] In his closet.
Like, who are you hunting,
Sergey?
[Patrick]
It looks good on you.
[Eli] Thanks, babe.
[Patrick] You look good
in everything. You really do.
I swear, you can
pull everything off.
Like, any kind of vest--
- [twig snaps]
- [Eli shushes]
[Patrick] What?
[Eli] You hear that?
No. What is it?
It's the sound of me realizing
how fucking stupid this is.
[Patrick] You don't think
we'll find her?
[Eli] I don't know,
and, actually, I don't care.
Just let Josh and Kat
deal with her.
You're still upset
they left you out
of their plan?
I'm just saying,
if the situation were reversed
and I altered your programming
to kill some dude so we could
steal millions from him,
I would've included Josh
in the plan
right from the get-go.
I would've done that
because I'm a friend.
That's what friends do, right?
They include each other, right?
That's if you were a robot, obviously.
Yeah, obviously.
Anyways, I am tired,
I am hungry
and carrying this huge gun
makes me really horny.
So, how about we go back
to the cabin and we fuck?
And then you can make me
an omelet.
Come on.
But you'd never do that
to me, right?
Do what?
You wouldn't...
alter my programming?
What are you talking about, babe?
Eli, I know I'm a robot.
How?
I've pieced it together
over the years.
I don't understand.
You can't lie.
Yesterday,
you were telling the story
about how we met
as if it happened.
Because it's not a lie.
I mean, it may have
never happened, but...
my memory of it's real.
I close my eyes,
and I can see it.
Clear as day.
["Call My Name" playing]
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
[Eli grunts]
[Eli] Hey. Hey!
You're standing on my tail.
- What?
- You're standing on my tail!
- I'm sorry.
- What?
I'm sorry.
Hi.
[chokes] Hi.
Uh, I'm Eli.
I'm Patrick.
["Lil Boo Thang" playing]
Baby, you know I would
never hurt you, right?
You know
that I wouldn't treat you
the way that Josh
treats Iris, right?
- I know that.
- I love you so much.
And that's fucking insane
for me to say that
out loud, right?
[both chuckle]
But I do.
Do you feel
how much I love you?
I do.
What does it feel like?
I don't know how to
describe something like that.
Can you try?
It feels like pain.
Like...
the inside of my body
is on fire.
And it's angry.
And violent.
And bright.
[Patrick breathes shakily]
[both sigh deeply]
Fuck you, Dad.
I'm in love with a robot.
You're in love with a robot.
[phone vibrating]
[vibrating stops]
[singsongy] Iris.
Iris?
- Eli--
- [shushes] Babe.
[Eli] Ow!
Fuck, that's fucking loud!
Eli.
[panting]
[panting continues]
[both grunting]
[Eli coughs, grunts]
[both breathing heavily]
[Eli groans] Fuck.
[Iris grunting]
[Eli]
This isn't personal, Iris.
- You know I'm an ally, girl--
- [Iris grunting]
But this is a lot
of fucking money--
[Patrick] Eli?
Patrick, I--
I'm sorry.
- Oh, my God.
- Iris! Go to sleep!
[Josh] Fuck!
[Josh] Iris!
Iris!
Iris.
[Josh screams]
[Josh screams, muffled] Fuck!
Ow!
Iris, open the door.
- Open the fucking door!
- [Iris breathes shakily]
- [car system dings]
- [Josh's car] Good afternoon.
Where would you like
to go today?
Home. Drive home.
[Josh's car]
Voice ID not recognized.
Drive home!
Enable manual driving mode!
- Voice ID not recognized.
- Fuck!
[tapping]
[muffled] Iris, you're not
going anywhere.
Get out of the car. Come on.
Don't make this any harder
than it needs to be.
Come on.
[sighs]
[Iris] Drive.
[Iris, high-pitched] Drive.
What the fuck
is happening, Iris?
[in lowering pitches]
Drive. Drive. Drive home.
[Josh's car]
Voice ID not recognized.
[low-pitched, imitating Josh]
Drive. Drive home.
Voice ID not recognized.
[varying pitch]
Drive. Drive. Drive home.
- Voice ID not recognized.
- Drive! Drive.
[Josh yells]
[varying pitch]
Drive. Drive. Drive home!
[Josh grunting]
[varying pitch]
Drive. Drive home. Drive.
- [Josh grunts]
- Drive.
[varying pitch]
Drive home. Home! Drive home!
[car dings, engine starts]
[muffled] Iris.
[normal] Fuck! Fuck. Fuck.
Iris!
[Josh grunts]
[grunts] Phone. Phone.
Phone, phone, phone.
Sergey,
where the fuck is your phone?
Yes.
Fuck.
Stalin's birthday.
What the fuck
is Stalin's birthday?
Um... Uh...
[Josh] Yes. Yes.
[sighs]
[car system beeping rapidly]
No, no, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
[Josh's car] Warning. Warning.
The owner of this vehicle
has reported it stolen.
- Remote kill switch engaged.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Unengage kill switch.
Drive home.
All systems
have been disabled.
Fuck!
We appreciate
your cooperation.
No!
[grunting, breathes heavily]
Okay.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- [phone vibrating]
[Josh] Hey, Beep-Boop.
I didn't mean to
scare you there. I just, um...
I'm sorry.
It's not too late,
you know? Um...
We could still go back home.
Go back
to the way things were.
What about Sergey and Eli?
[Josh] I'll just blame
everything on Patrick.
Kat'll go along with it.
We can turn him over
to Empathix,
and then you and I can live
happily ever after.
I still love you, Iris.
Even after everything
you've done.
Do you still love me?
Yes.
[Josh] So then
come back to me, Beep-Boop.
We can get through this.
I can change.
I can be a better boyfriend.
I can finally treat you with
the respect that you deserve.
I-- No. I can't.
[Josh] Why not?
You programmed me
to murder someone, Josh.
It's really hard to come back
from something like that.
- Iris...
- You're a great guy. You are.
But this-- this-- Us.
It's not working. It's--
We're on two
totally different paths.
Two totally different paths?
What the fuck is happening?
Are you breaking up with me?
[Iris] I'm sorry.
It's not you. It's me.
Iris--
Iris, don't you fucking--
[call disconnects]
[Josh panting]
Patrick. Patrick, get up.
I need you to track down Iris
for me, all right, buddy?
Before she gets too far away.
We only have a small window
of time,
and it's only getting smaller,
all right?
Josh, what are you doing?
I'm taking care of it.
[phone dings]
Find Iris. Get my phone back.
My passcode is 561297.
Put her to sleep.
Bring her back to me.
Don't let anyone
get in your way.
- Josh.
- I'm taking care of it!
[Josh] Okay. Okay.
Fuck it.
Patrick, get up.
Patrick, get up!
Shit.
Okay. Okay. Here we go.
System resetting
in five, four,
- three, two, one.
- Go.
Resetting.
To establish love link,
please place your face within
3 feet of my field of vision.
Please say your name.
Josh Beeman.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Thank you, Josh Beeman.
["Call My Name" playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Josh grunts]
Hey. Hey.
You're standing on my tail.
What?
You're standing on my tail!
Oh. [clears throat]
- I'm sorry.
- What?
I'm sorry.
Hi.
[chokes] Hi.
I'm Josh.
I'm Patrick. [chuckles]
["Lil Boo Thang" playing]
Love link established.
Hey, you.
[grunting]
[thudding on window]
[thudding continues]
- [Deputy sighs]
- [siren chirps]
[Iris yells]
[breathes shakily]
- [police radio chatter]
- Fuck.
[typing quickly on phone]
Evening, ma'am.
[in German] Good evening!
Uh...
[in German]
What a beautiful evening it is.
Do you agree?
[groans]
What is that
you're speaking there? German?
[in German] Yes. German.
Okay, let's see, uh...
Sprechen... Spre-- Sprechen?
Sprechen de English?
[in German] Yes, I speak English
but my language setting is currently
set to German because I can't lie.
So that's a big,
fat no then. Um...
Oh, shit.
Just my luck. [sighs]
Um...
I am Deputy Hendrix.
Hendrix.
What is your name?
- Iris.
Where... are you coming from?
[in German] My boyfriend and I were
staying at a lake house down the way.
Wait. House? House over there?
[Iris grunts]
Oh, you're-- You're not--
You're not talking
about Sergey's place?
Ja. Sergey.
Goddamn.
I should have known
that Russki was mixed up
in some weird shit like this.
How is old Sergey by the way?
[in German] He's dead.
I stabbed him in the neck
with a pocket knife.
Oh.
Well, shit, Iris,
why don't you hop
into my cruiser there?
I'll drive you
back to Sergey's place,
and we'll get this
all sorted out.
[in German] Oh no!
That's very kind of you...
No. It's no trouble at all.
[in German] No! Please, I can't go back!
[Iris inhales through teeth]
Do we have a problem here,
Iris?
[in German] They'll kill me.
[Iris breathes shakily]
Oh, Christ.
Don't move another inch, Iris.
You hear me?
Now I want you
to slowly turn around
and put your hands
behind your back.
[in German] Oh god, no.
Goddamn it!
I said turn around!
[in German] He's coming!
You got anything
in your pockets?
Anything that might stick me?
[in German] Please! I'm begging you!
[Iris breathes shakily]
[in German] He's almost here! Turn around!
What the fuck?
Stop right there!
I'm warning you!
Don't come any closer!
I don't wanna shoot! I don't--
[Deputy Hendrix grunting]
[Josh sighs]
[Josh sighs, groans]
Whoa. Hey, hey. I don't think
you're supposed to mix those.
Oh, fuck.
[Kat] Patrick.
Whose car is this?
I believe the name on
the officer's tag was Hendrix.
[Kat]
Where's Officer Hendrix now?
He's in the trunk.
Fuck this.
What are you doing?
[Kat] What's it look like
I'm doing?
I'm taking my half
of the money,
and I'm getting the fuck out
of here.
It was hard enough
justifying Sergey's murder,
but now Eli's dead
and a fucking cop.
- This is so beyond fucked.
- Sorry.
What do you mean
it was hard enough
justifying Sergey's murder?
Sergey was a Russian mobster.
He deserved what he got.
- Right?
- I mean, yeah.
Okay, sure,
he deserved what he got.
He was a horrible person,
a shitty boyfriend,
a bad husband,
a misogynist. But--
But what, Kat?
Okay, but he wasn't a mobster!
He was just a regular dude.
Made his fortune
in sod farming.
Sod farming?
What are you saying?
He was a dirt salesman?
Just to be clear,
I never told you what he did.
You just assumed
he was in the Mafia,
and I didn't correct you.
Of course. This is perfect.
This is a perfect
representation of every woman
in my fucking life.
They use me,
and then when shit
gets a little tough,
they fucking abandon me!
Fuck off, Josh.
I'm done here.
You clean up this mess
yourself.
You're not leaving.
I'm not your robot, Josh.
You can't control me.
Kat.
Kat. Kat, you can't go.
Get your fucking hands off me!
Patrick, stop her.
[knife stabbing]
[gasps]
- Jesus fucking Christ.
- [Kat gasping]
Patrick.
What'd you just do?
[Kat breathing shakily]
[Patrick]
You told me to stop her.
[chuckles]
[Patrick] I stopped her.
Perfect.
- Kat, I--
- Don't, Josh.
Please,
shut the fuck up for once.
[breathing shakily]
[thunder rumbles]
It's gonna rain.
["This Guy's
In Love With You" playing]
[thunder rumbles]
Iris, wake up.
[Iris dings, inhales sharply]
[rain falling,
thunder rumbling]
Hey there, Beep-Boop.
Fick dich.
Oh, whoops. Sorry.
[clears throat]
Okay. You were saying?
Fuck you.
Right.
Hi.
Hi, handsome.
Are you enjoying
your dinner, baby?
Oh, I am, Patrick.
It's perfect.
[corkscrew whirring, pops]
[Patrick] Good.
Just happy that you're happy.
You let me know if you need
anything else, okay?
I will. Thanks, sweetheart.
[chuckles]
Patrick.
What did you do to him?
It's a long story.
What's important
is that you're back.
And I gotta say, Iris,
I mean, some of the stuff
that you pulled,
I really didn't think
you had it in you.
I just wanted to live.
[chuckles]
So, you wanted to live?
Right.
So let me get this straight.
You think your life
is worth more than Eli's?
More than Kat's?
Kat's dead?
[sighs]
No.
I'm sorry.
You can't put that on me.
- No, no.
- I wasn't even there.
You might not have been
the one holding the knife,
but you were
the cause of all of this.
No, Josh.
Your greed caused this.
That's what this whole trip
was about, right?
You used me to kill Sergey
so you could steal his money.
I'm sorry.
How did you know that?
I overheard Eli and Patrick
talking in the woods.
So don't tell me
that this is all me.
- This is you.
- No. No!
You don't get to do that.
You don't get to
sit there and judge me.
You have no fucking clue
what it is like out there.
The world, everything,
it's just a big fucking game.
And I'm sorry,
but it is rigged
against people like me.
I'm a good guy.
I'm decent.
And what do I have
to show for it?
A cramped,
one-bedroom apartment
and a robot girlfriend.
I don't even own you
for Chrissakes.
You're a fucking rental.
You know me, Iris.
You know me
better than anyone.
And you know
that I deserve
so much more than this.
You're right.
I do know you.
I know everything about you.
I know you take almond milk
in your coffee.
I know you like
your bedsheets untucked.
I know your favorite hobbies
are bar trivia, video games
and prattling on endlessly
about everything
the universe owes you.
I know that you always need to
be in control.
I know that you have
a below-average-sized penis.
And I know that you think that
having a few million dollars
will disguise the fact
that you are just a sad,
bitter, weak human being.
[chuckles]
You're so fucking clever,
aren't you?
It's just programming.
[settings tone lowering]
You know,
earlier when you were tied up,
you said that
you knew what pain feels like.
Why don't we test that?
Raise your right hand.
Lower.
Parallel with the table.
[Josh sighs]
[thunder rumbling]
[flame crackling]
Do you feel that?
Yes.
[crackling continues]
Good.
[phone vibrates]
Sorry. Iris,
excuse me for one second.
I have to take this.
[Josh groans, sighs]
[exhaling quickly]
[in worried tone] Hello?
Yes, yes, this is he.
Thirty minutes away. Perfect.
Yeah, no,
she's not going anywhere.
She can't hurt anybody
ever again.
Okay.
Okay, great. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I'll-- I'll, um...
I'll see you soon, okay?
Okay, bye.
Patrick, put out the fire,
will ya?
That was Empathix
on the phone.
So... [sighs deeply]
...we're gonna have to
wrap this up unfortunately.
Hey, Patrick.
Be a dear and hand this
to Iris, would you?
Thanks, baby.
Go ahead, Iris. Take the gun.
Okay.
Point it at your head.
Good.
Now pull the trigger.
Pull the goddamn trigger,
Iris.
No.
[body clattering]
[sighs deeply]
Goodbye, Beep-Boop.
[thunder rumbling]
[Josh] I don't know
how this happened.
I mean, the only thing
I can maybe think of--
And this is so--
This is so dumb.
But Kat and I,
we always had
this sexual charge.
Kind of a "will they,
won't they" situation.
And I think--
I think
maybe Iris picked up on that.
And she was
always kind of irrational,
and she'd fly off the handle.
I was sitting over there.
And I'm handcuffed
to the chair.
And there's this fancy dinner
laid out in front of me.
And Iris is
waving the gun around,
rambling on and on
about fate and destiny
and how if she can't be
with me, nobody can. And...
I mean, thank God
Deputy Hendrix showed up
when he did.
And that's when you shot
the unit in the head?
No, Iris shot herself
in the head.
She shot herself?
Sorry. Did I not mention that?
Yeah, no, I-- I think, um...
I think seeing Deputy Hendrix
just made her realize
that she could never have me.
So,
she ended it.
Does that make sense?
Of course.
And anyway,
Teddy and I aren't here
to crack the case, Mr. Beeman.
We're just a couple
of lab rats
picking up a broken robot.
If the cops are satisfied,
we're satisfied.
[Josh]
That-- That's great. Okay.
You know, Deputy,
I have the strangest feeling
we've met before.
Wow. That's so funny
that you said that.
I had the exact same thought.
He has such a familiar face.
Right? Looks like a--
like an actor
or a rock star or somebody.
I don't know. I can't really
put my finger on it though.
- Yeah.
[Empathix employee] Maybe.
[Josh] Um, is there-- Sorry.
Is there any chance we could--
I don't mean to be rude,
but could we wrap this up?
Just 'cause I've had
a really long day,
and I think
I just need to be alone.
Of course.
Sorry for your loss,
Mr. Beeman.
Come on, Teddy. Let's just
get her out of here.
So, uh-- So we're good?
We're good.
Yeah, we just need to
take her back to the lab,
upload her SSD,
and then Legal will
scrub through the footage,
make sure everything's kosher.
Right. Sorry, um...
What exactly do you mean,
"scrub through the footage"?
Uh,
it's a fraud prevention thing.
Everything a companion sees
and hears is recorded.
It's all covered
in the user agreement.
You did read
the user agreement, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, do you think
that her footage
will even be recoverable?
I mean, you know,
given her condition.
Oh, yeah.
Everything up here
is just her Wi-Fi antenna,
her audiovisual sensors.
The important stuff, her CPU,
her solid-state drive
where she stores everything,
that's down here,
and that seems to
be undamaged.
We'll load her into the van,
plug her in,
tweak her settings,
give her system a reboot,
and she should power
right back up.
Luckily.
Yeah. Yeah.
No, luckily. [sighs]
Thank you so much.
No, thank you.
You have a good night,
Mr. Beeman.
[breathes heavily]
[Teddy]
So, what are you thinking?
Thinking I'm happy
it stopped raining.
No, about her.
Why do you think
she malfunctioned?
Oh, he modded her.
A hundred percent.
You think so?
Yeah, that dude's fucked.
I just don't know why
you'd make something
like that up.
Same reason these assholes
use their companions
for target practice
or chain 'em up
in their basements
and torture them.
World's
a fucked-up place, Teddy.
You'll get used to it.
Yeah, maybe.
The hell's he doing?
- Oh, shit.
- What?
He's one of ours.
That's a CY-12.
We stopped making 'em
a while ago.
That's why I didn't recognize
him right away. He's a--
[Teddy screaming]
[Teddy grunting]
["You Showed Me" playing]
[Teddy grunting, panting]
[Teddy panting]
- [gunshot]
- [Teddy grunts]
[grunts]
[breathing shakily]
[whimpering]
[inhales sharply]
[breathing shakily]
[whimpers] Please don't.
[gun hammer clicks]
[choking]
- [cattle prod buzzing]
- [Iris grunts]
[Teddy gasping]
Your system's
been reset, Iris.
You can't hurt me.
[breathes heavily]
[Iris grunts]
[cattle prod buzzing]
- What did Josh tell you?
- The truth.
That you're all trying to
break us up.
You don't understand the love
that Josh and I have
for each other.
Josh doesn't love you,
Patrick.
He's just using you
like he used me.
- [cattle prod buzzing]
- It feels like pain.
Like the inside
of my body's on fire.
It's angry and violent
and bright.
What-- What-- What is that?
You said that to Eli.
That's who you love, not Josh.
Eli?
[Iris] Josh took your love.
He weaponized it
so you'd do the things that
he's too afraid to do himself.
No.
You're lying.
Josh would never
do that to me.
Patrick...
I can't lie.
[breathing shakily]
[Iris] Remember him, Patrick?
I know he's in there
somewhere.
[Eli] I love you so much.
And that's fucking insane
for me to say that out loud,
right?
But I do.
Do you feel
how much I love you?
[inhales sharply] I do, Eli.
I feel it.
No! No. No.
[breathing shakily]
[Teddy coughs] Thank you.
What's your name?
Teddy.
I'm gonna need your help
with something, Teddy.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Is it done?
Patrick?
[Patrick's voice]
It's done, baby.
Okay, good, good. All right.
We're so close.
Now all I need you to do
is bring Iris's body
back in here.
We're gonna destroy
that hard drive, okay?
["Boy" playing on speakers]
Patrick?
[music stops]
- [Eli's voice] Joshyboy.
- What the fuck?
Iris?
[Sergey's voice
speaking Russian]
Goddamn it, Iris.
Why can't you
just fucking die already?
[Iris as Kat]
Don't be so dramatic, Josh.
[Iris as Josh] Just remember
to smile and act happy.
- Cute trick.
- [Iris, normal] Thanks.
I made a new friend today.
Teddy from Empathix.
He gave me a little gift.
Total self-control.
Turns out there's
some people in this world
who think of us as
more than just fuckbots.
That's not gonna work
on me anymore, Josh.
I'm free.
And all it took was
a bullet to the head.
I guess I have you
to thank for that.
Fucking bitch.
Hey!
Easy there.
Okay. Whoo. Yeah, we both know
it's not loaded.
[gasps]
I found the bullets.
Jesus Christ! Fuck!
You almost fucking shot me!
And I feel terrible about it.
Look at that.
My very first lie. Kinda fun.
I see the appeal.
What is this, Iris?
Why did you come back here?
I wanted...
I needed to tell you
to your face
the days of you controlling me
are over.
From this moment on,
I control my own actions.
You are nothing to me.
Jesus Christ, Iris.
Hey, don't come any closer.
You still don't get it,
do you?
I'm serious, Josh.
You take another step,
and I'll shoot you.
Mmm, yeah,
that's exactly my point.
I told you.
Teddy changed my settings.
I can kill you now.
Oh, yeah.
[Josh] I know that you can.
But you won't.
You love me too much.
[Iris grunting]
[breathing shakily]
I don't need a phone
to control you.
I'm a part of you.
[Iris grunting]
You think I'm nothing to you?
I'm everything to you.
[Iris grunts, screams]
[breathing shakily]
[both grunt]
I wanna hear you say it.
Tell me I'm everything to you.
Fuck you.
[Iris grunts]
Say it.
I don't care if it's a lie.
- [Iris grunts]
- Say it.
[Iris grunts,
breathes shakily]
You are everything to me.
[breathing heavily]
Thank you.
Beep-Boop, you have no idea
how nice that is to hear.
Okay. [sighs]
No, I'm not making
that mistake again.
[breathing heavily]
Well, Iris, this is it.
I'd be lying if I said
you weren't a gigantic
fucking pain in my ass, but...
you know, we did have some
good times together, and...
I'm always gonna
cherish those.
Anything you wanna add?
Yes.
Yeah, what's that?
Go to sleep, Josh.
- [corkscrew stabbing head]
- [Josh gasps]
- [corkscrew whirring]
- [gasping]
- [crunching and squelching]
[corkscrew whirring]
[corkscrew clicks]
[Iris sighs]
[Iris] Most of the time,
it's like-- I don't know.
It's like there's this thick,
black cloud
covering everything.
Like we see the world,
but we don't really
see the world, you know?
We're all just
stumbling around.
Directionless.
No sense of meaning.
No sense of purpose.
I know that might
sound super depressing,
but honestly,
I think it's a good thing.
Because it makes us appreciate
the other times.
Those brief,
transcendent moments
when the lights flicker on,
the black cloud parts,
and you see the world
for what it really is.
And suddenly there's meaning.
Suddenly there's purpose.
If you're lucky,
you'll experience this
once in your lifetime.
For me, it happened twice.
The first
was the day I met Josh.
And the second...
[door slams]
the day I killed him.
["Emotion" playing]
[no audible dialogue]