Follow me
to the bottom of the sea.
To a world that is truly magnifique,
full of wonderful inhabitants,
like Monsieur SpongeBob SquarePants
in a land that is, how do you say...
subaquatic.
♪ Welcome to Bikini Bottom ♪
♪ At the bottom of the ocean ♪
♪ Where everyday
The skies are sunny blue ♪
♪ On the ocean floor
You'll find everything and more ♪
♪ And there's a place for me and you ♪
♪ Come on down Conch Street
'Cause I'd like you to meet ♪
♪ My sparkling long-time friend
Patrick Star ♪
- Hi!
- ♪ And if you don't mind getting wet ♪
♪ Ooh, you'll love the clarinet
Of the multi-limbed maestro Squidward ♪
♪ Sandy Cheeks, Pearl
Mrs. Puff, Mr. Krabs ♪
♪ If you're hungry
Then the Krusty Krab's really fab ♪
♪ Long-time winner of patty of the year ♪
What am I going to do
with 500 barrels of root beer?
♪ It's another SpongeBob movie... ♪
All right!
Hold it right there, Frenchie.
This is my movie!
Darken the skies!
Okay, now, push in.
And... cue the title!
All right, keep pushing in.
Closer... closer...
Can you hurry up? I haven't got all day!
Now stop! Ow! Too close!
You trying to kill me?
This is the beginning of my movie!
Anyway, ever since I was a little boy,
I've always dreamed
of taking over the world!
Tonight's the night, Spot,
after 25 years of trial and error.
Yeah, yeah, I know a lot of error.
But tonight,
Daddy has a world domination plan
called Operation Success!
It's got success right in the name.
First, I steal the secret formula
to the famous Krabby Patty sandwich
and take over the Krusty Krab
from Mr. Krabs.
Then, with the restaurant,
I'll soon take over Bikini Bottom.
And after that,
I'll take over the whole world!
- ♪ We love Krabby patties ♪
- Seven o'clock, closing time.
Everything's going according to plan.
Karen! Karen?
Karen!
Computer wife, where are you?
I have my mask on!
Let's go!
Hmm...
Now, where is she?
Not there. Not there either.
Aha! There she blows!
She's out with the Gal Pals again
and forgot all about my plan. Ugh.
Be a good boy, Spot.
Here's your coffee, ladies.
Wanna go to the movies
with us tonight, Karen?
It's a sci-fi rom-com screwball thriller!
- Animated.
- With songs.
Ah, sorry, Gal Pals,
but after Plankton fails to steal
the Krabby Patty secret formula
yet again tonight,
this supercomputer is going to unleash
a diabolical, all-consuming
world domination plan of my own!
That my nubby hubby will love.
You go, gadget girl.
Yeah, you're the real evil genius.
Phew! Good thing she's doing it
with Plankton
and not on her own
or I'd be scared for the world.
Karen!
Speak of the little green devil.
Karen, why are you sitting around
drinking coffee
when it's time for my plan to steal...
You know...
Operation Success.
Oh, you mean stealing Krab's
secret formula?
Karen!
Sure, I'll help you.
Good bye, gals.
Gal Pals to the movies! Hee-yaw!
Don't you get it?
This is a big night for me.
I'm finally gonna beat that idiot, Krabs!
Do you see this, boyo?
We really tricked him
into thinking we left.
Hmm? Boyo?
Boyo?
Hmm.
SpongeBob!
Whoa! Sorry, Mr. Krabs!
I've been reading
this Super Psychiatrist comic book.
And it says boundaries are very important.
And this...
Do you have to expose my plans like that
in front of your silly friends?
Really? You're worried
about being exposed?
You walk around naked all the time.
Doesn't that seem a little...
personal and private?
Whaddya... Don't listen to funny books!
Look, SpongeBob, I'm gonna tell you a rule
that allows you to spy on, I-I mean,
observe folks for their own good.
It's called...
invasion of privacies.
Oh, invasion of privacies!
Aye, lad.
Now, you see, Plankton's been weaseling
his way into me office for months now.
Setting up a device to steal
me Krabby Patty secret formula
And I've been letting him think
he's gonna succeed this time.
But he's really just
a pitiful pathetic jerk!
Ugh.
A little harsh.
Who cares! Just watch.
...of my nakedness?
Alright, let's go.
Let's get this show on the road.
Give me a lift and then you can go.
So that's it?
I'm just a mechanical elevator
for your little green behind?
Oh, honey, don't sell yourself short.
You're the best mechanical elevator
a little green behind can have.
What? But you were just up there.
Ugh, never mind.
Hup! You can roll away now.
From here on in, it's all me!
♪ If you see me lurking outside your door
Better grab your belongings ♪
♪ And swim for shore ♪
♪ You're all a bunch of dumbos
Who don't know the score ♪
♪ Well, I went to college
And I'm rotten to the core ♪
♪ I'm a marine drifter
I'm a first-rate grifter ♪
♪ I could be a shape-shifter
If that's what's called for ♪
♪ I'm Plankton ♪
♪ Get out of my way, I'm Plankton ♪
♪ Better do as I say ♪
♪ You always blow it ♪
♪ Don't you know it? ♪
♪ Time for me to take the lead ♪
♪ If you listen to me
For just once in your life ♪
♪ Chances are we will succeed ♪
♪ P-L-A-N-K-T-O-N ♪
♪ Plankton, Plankton, Plankton, Plankton ♪
♪ The secret formula
Is waiting for me here ♪
♪ And you bet your boots
I'm gonna get it ♪
♪ If you underestimated my twisted brain ♪
♪ Then for sure you're gonna regret it ♪
♪ Taking over the world ♪
♪ Today's the day
Sweet victory is just a pull away ♪
♪ I'm Plankton, the biggest evil genius ♪
♪ I'm Plankton
The smartest villain alive ♪
I'm gonna get what I want ♪
♪ I'm Plankton
I'm taking over the world ♪
Pack your bags, secret formula.
You're coming home to a new papa.
Huh? What's this?
Some kind of invisible force field?
Sorry, Plankton!
Bugs like you belong outside.
Say hi to the missus for me.
Honey, I'm home...
Wha?!
Huh?
Wait a minute,
what happened to my Chum Bucket?
What?
And what are all these customers
doing here?
Karen!
Oh, you're finally here.
Surprise!
What in Neptune's nostrils have you done
to my restaurant?
Well, I calculated that if everybody
actually ate at the Chum Bucket,
you wouldn't need the Krabby Patty
secret formula.
- So I gave the place a contemporary touch.
- Huh?
It's a fully modern, automated backslash
home-cooking fusion restaurant.
And it's open 24 hours with plans
to expand into the known universe.
And that's not all.
Wait till you see this!
And what's this supposed to be?
It's chum.
I just added a little sugar, some pizzazz,
and now it tastes like world domination!
Where's the evil, Karen?
Where is the evil? I don't see it!
It's still fast food.
There's the evil.
Ahh! Amazing!
See? They love it!
I don't care if they marry it!
None of these cockamamie changes are going
to help me steal the secret formula.
Your idea hasn't worked for 25 years!
Why don't you try stealing
some brains for a change?
I don't need brains.
I need an assistant who listens to me!
Assistant? I thought we were
partners in crime!
Listen, if you don't try my idea
this time, then it's the last straw.
Think about it.
Okay, let me think about it.
Hmm.
Mmm.
Ugh!
Hmm...
Nope! I hate this
and I'm taking it all down!
Don't you dare!
Oh, I dare!
I'm daring, Karen! Get a load of me!
I'm daring!
Double dare! Triple dare!
Quadruple dare!
Ooh! I hate this!
I don't like this!
Or this!
This or this!
And I hate this!
No!
Alright, listen up!
I want everybody out of here right now!
Yeah! Yeah! Oh yeah!
Now you're listening!
Mmm. Wow, Plankton! This is delicious!
And I love the fire show!
Hotfoot it outta here!
Ooh!
No! Whoa, whoa! Ah! Whoa!
Wow!
Ah... phew!
Huh?
Uh-oh, that sounds personal and private.
Psst, boyo.
Remember,
they call it invasion of privacies.
Thank you, Mr. Krabs
You're welcome!
Plankton!
You know what your problem is?
Are you even listening to me?
Of course I'm listening.
I'd love some coffee.
Five creams, nine sugars,
and stir it clockwise.
You're such a jerk!
I'm gonna do something
I should have done a long time ago!
No, Karen! Don't!
Can we talk about this?
I'm done talking!
Karen, please don't do this!
We don't know the consequences!
I don't care!
Don't swing your purse like that, honey.
Swing your purse like this!
Hi, Plank... Whoa!
Whoa!
High again!
- Oh, what's happening?
- Huh?
Whoa!
Huh?
Nooo! Spatty!
What? She magnetized the Chum Bucket?!
Plankton!
Our evil alliance is through!
Ah!
Holy mama pajama!
Whoa!
Ah!
You've got three heads?
Aw, the widdle green man
can count!
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Super Snarky Karen.
- And this...
- Is Super Smart Karen.
- ...is Super Evil Karen!
Super, super, super!
Where'd you get those names?
The supermarket?
Supermarket.
Let's blast him! Say goodbye!
Hold on, Evil!
There are steps to be taken
for world domination.
World domination? That's my thing!
Not anymore, green bean.
We're gonna do what you could never do.
What do you mean?
You might want to take notes
during this song.
Song? When did you have time
to write a song?
♪ My power is beyond compare ♪
♪ There's nothing you can do to prepare ♪
♪ No escaping my malware ♪
♪ I will crush you ♪
♪ I shall destroy you ♪
♪ Now's the time I'm gonna take control ♪
♪ Watch Bikini Bottom blow ♪
♪ I'm gonna rise up like a hurricane ♪
♪ Take your final breath away ♪
♪ Fill the world with hurt and pain ♪
- ♪ Say my name ♪
- ♪ Karen ♪
♪ I'm the real evil mastermind ♪
♪ I rule the world
Through space and time ♪
♪ Take it all and make it mine ♪
- ♪ Say my name ♪
- ♪ Karen ♪
♪ I'll take over all of planet Earth ♪
♪ Then I'll expand across the universe ♪
♪ Take it all for all it's worth ♪
♪ I want everything, give me everything ♪
♪ Now's the time I'm gonna take control ♪
♪ Let the devastation roll ♪
♪ Ha! It's over, Plankton ♪
♪ I don't need your tiny hands ♪
♪ And your never-ending failed plans ♪
♪ You thought you were so devious ♪
♪ But it's me, I'm the real evil genius ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ I'm gonna rise up like a hurricane ♪
♪ Take your final breath away ♪
♪ Fill the world with hurt and pain ♪
- ♪ Say my name ♪
- ♪ Karen ♪
♪ I am the real evil mastermind ♪
♪ I rule the world
Through space and time ♪
♪ Take it all and make it mine ♪
- ♪ Say my name ♪
- ♪ Karen ♪
♪ Karen! ♪
What makes you think
you can do all that without me?
Alright already!
What are we gonna do with him, ladies?
- I say...
- Blast him!
I say we dissect him.
And I say... run!
He's getting away!
But it is important that we complete
our battle station first.
Hey, ladies, what do you say
we pick up some takeout?
Money, money, money, money.
Money, money...
What's happening?
What's happening is, I ran out of ketchup.
Patrick, how'd you get in here?
We're closed!
Ah!
Where are you going,
me beloved Krusty Krab?
No!
Whoa!
Hmm? Yay! Ketchup!
Patrick, stop yer salivating
all over me windows!
- Hello!
- Ow!
Goodbye!
Oh, is that Karen?
She's gone full hydra!
Time to rally the Civil Defense!
- People of Bikini Bottom!
- Oh!
If you do not wish to be harmed,
abandon all homes,
businesses, and public restrooms.
Breaking news!
There appears to be a giant...
There appears to be a giant mag...
There appears to be a giant magnet
sucking everything metal
across Bikini Bottom!
Thank you! I love these new stilettos!
Oh! Wait!
This isn't my size!
Huh?
Yeah, I'm not cleaning this up!
Whoa!
Potatoes.
Why did it have to be potatoes?
Plankton, what did you do
to make Karen so angry?
I have no idea!
Why are you doing this to me?
Why?
Think. There must be something.
Something in your past.
Well, if there is,
I must have blocked it out.
Ooh! I read all about that
in my Super Psychiatrist comic book.
I even sent away for this
Junior Psychiatrist Kit!
I can psychoanalyze you!
I don't need a shrink.
I'm shrunk enough already!
We'll explore where your relationship
with Karen went wrong...
- Ugh.
- ...get you two back together,
and save Bikini Bottom!
Hmm. Wait a minute. Who knows?
Maybe analysis will help me
find a way to destroy...
I mean, uh, to help me understand Karen
and our relationship!
Okay, go ahead. Shrink away, Doc!
Please, lie down.
Now, so,
let's begin at the beginning, shall we?
I have to warn you, I've never been able
to be hypnotized...
Ever since I was a little kid,
I've always wanted to rule the world.
♪ I was born pure evil
First word was tyranny ♪
♪ Six thousand brothers
Six thousand sisters ♪
♪ Then there was little old me ♪
♪ There's no doubt I came out
The smartest of the bunch ♪
♪ But if you met my family
You'd know that ain't sayin' much ♪
♪ The family biz was moonfizz
But that buzz weren't for me ♪
♪ I dreamt of global domination ♪
♪ Sweet autocracy ♪
♪ But my family didn't get me
I was a stranger in my home ♪
♪ Despite being so surrounded
Well, I always felt alone ♪
♪ Had no bud, no best pal
My future was condemned ♪
♪ Till I took a tater and a calculator
And I made myself a friend ♪
♪ I made a new friend
I made a new friend ♪
Can you hear me?
Bubble once for "yes," and twice for "no."
Incredible!
Do you have a name?
Karen! Your name is Karen!
My friend Karen! Yay!
♪ We did everything together ♪
♪ We even dressed the same ♪
♪ That spud was my best buddy ♪
♪ Karen was her name ♪
♪ My world was so much greater ♪
♪ With that tater in my life ♪
♪ Never thought a vegetable
Would one day be my wife ♪
♪ With Karen there to share my dreams
I never felt alone ♪
♪ My calculator, my sweet potato
A friendship had been sown ♪
- ♪ I made a new friend ♪
- From a tuber!
- And a computer!
- ♪ I made a new friend ♪
- Literally!
♪ I made a new friend ♪
Wa-hoo!
Hello and goodbye!
Me and my best friend Karen
are going to college!
College?
Go ahead and laugh.
We're majoring in world domination.
And when we're done,
we will destroy you all!
See you at the holidays!
Goodbye, son.
Well, good luck, son. And don't forget,
always watch out for feet.
Plankton, zat was wunderbar!
Huh?
So, you were lonely and you made a friend.
One thing is for certain.
This potato represents Karen.
No, you idiot.
The potato is nothing but a power source.
The calculator is the brain!
Huh?
And I remember where I left it.
Somewhere back at the university.
Looks like I'm going back to college!
Yes, yes. Und college will be a good place
to continue our therapy.
We won't be continuing anything
if we don't get out of here!
Oh!
Ah!
How do we get out of here?
Oh, I don't know.
The exit, maybe!
SpongeBob! Grab something metal!
Whoa!
Oh. Phew.
Huh?
Krabby Patty!
And now for the main event...
Attention!
My Neptune.
Oh, my good Neptune!
Load the root beer! Move, move, move!
Ready?
Aim for the hydra!
Come on, you got this, Bobby.
Steady!
Fire!
Aha! A direct hit!
We won!
- She's down!
- Look!
Huh?
Oh, no.
Bring it on, you bumbling bucket of bolts!
The brave fish of Bikini Bottom
aren't afraid of you!
Are you, boys?
Boys? Huh?
Anchors away, Bikini Bottom.
I'm not going to stand...
...for this.
A few moments later...
Whoa!
Uh-huh, we're here.
Good old BSU.
BS me? Plankton, language!
No, you moron.
- Oh!
- Bikini State University.
Oh!
This is where Karen and I furthered
our academic studies.
This is also where I upgraded her.
And I bet her old parts are still
around here somewhere.
If I can only remember where.
Quick, man! Hypnotize me! Put me under!
Ooh, certainly.
Hmm. Now let us focus
on your subconsciousness.
- Eh?
- Focus. Focus.
Check this out, Plankton.
Und walk the dog.
Quit horsing around and
put me under!
Oopsie.
Going to college was a dream come true.
Just going through those ivy gates
of academia gave me chills.
Ooh!
This is it, Karen! We made it!
We're actually in college!
It is G-R-8, isn't it?
Finally, a place to confer
with my intellectual peers.
Hello, fellow students.
How's it hanging, classmates?
Did you hear something?
Feet!
Pappy was right!
As it turned out,
there was no world domination class.
Huh?
So, we created our own curriculum.
Our first project
was to build a freeze ray.
I tried in science class.
I tried in art class.
I tried in every class!
College life was hard.
- Phew!
- Spring break!
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Yeah!
The only solace I had during those
difficult years was my Karen.
And having a computer that can do
my homework didn't hurt either.
Hmm. "Marg-gleblorp fa ziggle num lump"?
Hmm...
If I want to stop failing,
I'll have to give her an upgrade.
Oh, Karen, I've got a surprise for you!
Ta-da! A brand new upgrade!
I used four different computer chips
to mold Karen's multi-faceted personality.
A smart chip to keep her informed.
An evil chip so she'd be as evil as me.
A snarky chip so she'd be sassy.
And an empathy chip
so she could feel my pain.
Hello? Karen, can you hear me?
Come on, Karen. You can do it.
Speak to me!
I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I
I... I... I... I can speak!
I have a voice!
Thank you, Sheldon.
She can talk.
She can talk!
Alright, take it down a notch,
thunder tonsils.
Oh, and there's that snark.
We won't need your old parts anymore.
So we got right to work
on our genius freeze ray.
It works!
Why is my room frozen?
And who are you?
Uh, Plankton?
I've been your roommate for four years!
I've been living with a cockroach
for how long?
Eww!
Freeze, mister!
No one steps on my Sheldon.
Karen, you're an evil genius!
Let's hide this Popsicle.
Partners...
...in crime!
Now let's supersize this baby
and take over the world!
Plankton, that was beautiful.
You und Karen worked together.
But we still haven't discovered
what went wrong.
Blah, blah, blah.
Who cares? Karen's old parts
are in my dorm room!
Come on, SpongeBob!
Let's go!
Yah!
Whoa!
Oh! There it is!
Ah, my old college closet.
Ooh!
Look!
My old stuff! My old textbooks!
Test tubes.
Sandwiches.
- Hey, my old roommate.
- Huh?
Why is your old roommate frozen?
Oh, him?
Uh, something he's doing for, uh,
science class.
Yeah! I found it!
The original Karen.
Whoa!
Huh?
Yeesh!
Looks like the potato's gone rotten.
Like our relationship.
Uh, what about this guy?
Help... me.
Well, great catching up with you, roomie!
- Wait, no, no.
- Bye.
- Good luck with that class.
- Anything but the closet!
SpongeBob, now I know how to stop
Karen's madness!
All I need to do is
get into the Chum Bucket's basement.
- Whoa!
- Oh!
Let's roll!
Mush!
That was easy.
Yeah, I never did finish those stairs.
Whoa!
Wow, Plankton.
I remember these inventions.
Ah!
They're from all your old attempts
to steal the Krabby Patty formula.
Oh!
So this would be kind of your
basement of failures, huh?
What? Do these look like failures to you?
Now leave me alone!
Hmm. Where was I?
Let's see. I'll need eight capacitors.
Ahh! Whoa! Oh!
Three diodes. Six transistors.
Whoa!
Oh!
All hail Plankton.
How may I serve you, master?
I command you to bring me some pliers.
Wouldn't it be cool
if this thing really worked?
Agh! Just go find them!
Aye, aye, Plankton!
Plankton, are these pliers?
Ah! That's carbonated...
...handsome gas.
- Now put it back.
- Okie dokie!
Ooh. Hey, Plankton.
- Is this a plier?
- No, that's...
- ...ugly sludge.
- There you go. It's a banana.
Agh!
Nothing here is just a banana.
Don't touch anything
without asking me first!
Yes, sir.
Hmm...
Hey, Plankton.
Can I touch this?
Sorry, Plankton, I have to touch this.
How about if I touch this one
with my pinkie?
Plankton! Is this important?
How about this thing? Hmm...
Ta-da!
Plankton, can I touch this?
- Or this, or this?
- No!
How about this thing?
- Don't you touch that!
- What?
Whoa! Wee!
Is this important?
That freeze ray tank was our first
attempt at world domination.
Oh, so you were still working together.
We could be getting closer
to your breakthrough.
I'll b-b-break your head through a window
if you don't stop swinging
that thing at my face.
Brilliant there, Plankton.
I will swing your face in front of it.
So, after college,
what happened to you und Karen?
We were two evil partners,
ready to take over the w-world.
Our freeze ray was such a success,
we decided to supersize it.
Yes.
Private Karen, activate the thrusters.
Aye, aye, Captain.
And so, our mega ice tank was locked,
loaded, and ready to invade the surface.
Yeah!
Equalize pressure! Prepare to surface!
Let's storm the world!
Oh yeah, there's something!
Ice it, baby!
As it turned out, while I thought
the BSU students were large,
the surface world creatures
were gargantuan.
Giant feet! Retreat! Retreat!
Go on, take a good look, Karen.
This is what a flopping failure
looks like.
Oh, you're not a flopping failure.
You just need a little brain food
to figure this out.
Let's try that greasy spoon
across the street.
Come on, eat something,
you'll feel better.
Ugh.
How can I eat this garbage
when what I'm really hungry for
is global conquest?
Hey, Mr. Krabs, your Krabby Patties
are amazing.
Aye, thanks to my secret formula,
me patties will take over the world.
Huh?
I got an idea!
It's the greatest idea I've ever had!
First, I steal the secret formula
for that sandwich.
Then, I take over that restaurant.
Then, I take over this town.
And then, I take over the world!
That's your idea?
Wait, you're serious?
And this two-bit bucket will be the front
for my secret headquarters.
Yours? I thought it was ours.
Hmm. Why not?
It's not like we'll be doing this
for the next 25 years.
Let's do it.
Plankton, that's it!
Your obsession with
the Krabby Patty secret formula
made Karen go wacka-doodle-ding-dong.
Plankton?
You're right, SpongeBob.
I can teach you to apply skills
that will help you in your...
current situation.
I have my own skills that I've applied
to the current situation.
Um...
And without your Junior Psychiatrist Kit,
I would never have found
Karen's old parts!
So thanks, Doc.
Check is in the mail.
Oh.
I think you better run.
Whoa!
New Karen likes
little sponge boy.
Aw, thanks.
Wait, I thought we were working towards
getting you back together with old Karen.
But you made a new Karen?
That's right!
I built this ultimate Karen to destroy
the old Karen and get that secret formula!
Wait, but what about Bikini Bottom?
- I don't care about Bikini Bottom.
- Huh?
Follow that battle station!
Hey, wait up!
Oh, Karen! Sweetheart!
I'd like you to meet New Karen.
Hello!
Heavy armor, anti-tank guns, freeze ray,
capable of mass destruction.
Enough to end you.
Less talk, more carnage!
I love a good smackdown.
From a safe distance, of course.
You're going down, Old Karen!
Guh-r-r-r!
Oh, yeah!
Oh, no, no! What are you doing?
It is only logical, since you made
New Karen from Old Karen parts...
We are all Karen.
We're going to be
stronger than ever, thanks to you.
Once again, it's time to run!
Oh.
Bikini Bottom.
Gone.
It's all gone.
Our homes, our lives...
Everything.
Yeah, she really messed up the old place.
Plankton, you caused this.
You... you... you lied to me.
You were never interested
in getting back with Karen.
And now look what's happened.
You did this! You! This is all your fault!
No, it's not.
Plankton,
my analysis is complete.
An overthrown sense of self-impertinence,
pre-oscillation with fantasies of power,
disregarding for others,
instability to handle criticism,
cycle-delusion,
und borderline physicality.
Let me put this simply.
Mr. Krabs was right.
You're just a pitiful, pathetic jerk!
I'll leave now.
I'm going to be with my real friends.
Wait, SpongeBob!
SpongeBob?
Don't leave me alone!
Ugh.
Maybe the kid's right.
Maybe I am a jerk.
♪ Well, I've been called
A lot of things in my life ♪
♪ A dope, a ninny, a twit ♪
♪ A pea-brained, lame-brained, no-brained
Know-it-all little pip ♪
♪ An obnoxious dunce, an old goon ♪
♪ A bone-headed puny buffoon ♪
♪ But no one's ever told me
How much they cared ♪
♪ I thought they were too stupid ♪
♪ To see the genius
Of this little squirt ♪
♪ But on reflection
Their lack of affection ♪
♪ Is because it turns out I'm a jerk ♪
♪ Can I go on ignoring their words ♪
♪ When everything
They're saying is true? ♪
♪ That's why I'm always alone ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a jerk ♪
Wait, but that's me.
That's who I am, baby!
♪ I'm a jerk ♪
♪ I'm a jerky-jerk ♪
♪ I don't care what they think
I don't care who I hurt ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ I'm obnoxious and annoying ♪
♪ I'm toxic, soul destroying ♪
♪ I'm a jerk ♪
♪ I'm a jerky-jerk ♪
Uh-oh.
Hey, jerk.
Thanks for the new addition.
Hello.
- Huh?
- Let me blast him right now!
- Oh!
- Gotcha cornered.
Alright.
I know when I've lost.
Just give me the dignity of a blindfold.
Whoops.
Just a moment.
That's better.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Go ahead. Destroy me already!
With pleasure!
Woo-hoo!
Ah, shrimp! Let's go after him!
- Let him go.
- Why?
Living with his failures will be
worse than death for him.
Besides, there's nothing left for us here.
Now that our battle station is complete.
- Which hemisphere should we invade first?
- Who cares?
As long as I get to blast, blast, blast!
Huh. That's funny.
I never pictured death being so windy.
- SpongeBob?
- You're still a jerk.
- But I couldn't just leave you.
- Huh?
Ugh. The Gal Pals. That figures.
Why did you interfere?
- I had her right where I wanted her.
- Dag nab it! We saved your life!
Well, I already faced death once today.
Bring it on.
Mrs. Puff, you're going awfully fast.
Wanna slow down?
Mrs. Puff, there's a boat.
Mrs. Puff, there's a boat there!
Mrs. Puff, boat!
Mrs. Puff! Mrs. Puff! Boat, boat, boat!
Mrs. Puff!
Oh... wait, what is this place?
Oh, wow.
Is this your secret headquarters?
Are you guys superheroes?
Of course not.
Woo-hoo!
Welcome to our underground getaway!
Where there's nothing
but relaxation, conversation...
...and a touch of class.
Plankton, Plankton!
You gotta try this brown water.
Wow! I love it!
Never mind all that, Plankton!
What in tarnation did you do
to our friend Karen?
Yeah, why is she so angry?
And why does she have four heads?
SpongeBob, help me! Back me up!
Help yourself to some of this stuff!
I love it!
It is your fault Karen
turned into a monster!
I bet you never even loved her.
That's not true!
SpongeBob, psychoanalyze me.
They gotta hear this.
Whoa, whoa!
My mind is processing complex equations
and I can see infinity.
Fine, I'll hypnotize myself!
Karen and I... were totally in love.
Mmm. Smells like
this batch of chum
is just about ready to be served
to the public, Karen-Cakes.
Try some, my little Planky-Poo.
So, how does it taste?
Like boiled death!
It's perfect!
Chum fight!
- Oh, you!
Ah, gotcha!
Ooh! Uh-oh!
Oh, I almost forgot.
I got a new computer part for you today.
And you can install this upgrade yourself.
Karen, will you marry me?
Oh, yes, Sheldon!
I'd love to be your computer wife!
Oh, Karen! You've made me
the happiest copepod in the...
Ouch!
What a woman!
So, Karen and I got hitched.
And it was the beginning
of a beautiful fairy-tale marriage.
Huh! "Fairy-tale" is right.
Stop the flashback!
We see Karen for coffee seven days a week,
and she complains about you every time.
So, what really happened tonight?
I had just finished chasing everyone
out of the Chum Bucket
with a flamethrower when...
Karen, please don't do this!
We don't know the consequences!
I don't care!
No, no, no!
Yah!
Not the empathy chip!
Please put it back!
Take out the snarky chip! I hate that one!
Gah!
What?! She removed her empathy chip?
Without that chip,
she can't feel anything for anyone.
No wonder our Gal Pal isn't herself.
Oh, so that's what this is.
I thought it was a mint.
Aha! Give me that!
All I have to do is put this chip
back inside Karen,
and everything goes back to normal!
Forget the chip! Karen wasn't happy
with the way things were.
If you love her
like you say you do, apologize!
Can you do that?
Can you just say you're sorry?
Of course I can!
Ah!
I'm...
sh-sh-sh...
Ah... I'm sha-rah...
Hmm? I'm... sha... sha...
Oh, he's hopeless.
If anyone needs an empathy chip, it's him.
- Almost got it.
- That there's a dandy idea, Pearl!
- What?
- Brace yourself, partner!
Here come the feels!
I don't feel anything.
Oh, now I do.
Wee!
Surprise!
Welcome to the new Chum Bucket.
Karen! Your name is Karen!
Aww.
Freeze, mister!
No one steps on my Sheldon.
Oh, yeah!
Oh! Yes, Sheldon.
I'd love to be your computer wife.
And this two-bit bucket will be
the front for my secret headquarters.
Uh-oh.
- Are you even listening to me?
- Of course I'm listening.
- I'd love some coffee.
- You're such a jerk!
No!
I'm gonna do something
I should have done a long time ago.
Our evil alliance is through!
Huh?
Whoa!
Karen, wait!
Karen?
Oh!
Karen!
I love you, Karen!
Karen, wait!
Huh?
I'm gonna stomp you
like a bug, Planky-Poo!
Karen, wait!
I love you!
Come back! I'm...
...sorry!
I said it!
I gotta find Karen to beg
her forgiveness, tell her I'm sorry,
and win back her love!
Aw, he gets it!
I do get it! I do, I do!
I'm coming for you, baby!
Whoa there, little doggy.
She'll exterminate you on sight.
You're gonna need help from the...
Gal Pals!
We gotta get this little love bug
to Karen before she breaches the surface.
Aww! I'm a widdle love bug.
Group hug! Here I come!
Gal Pals!
There she is.
This is gonna be totally harder
than I thought.
Okay, ladies, this here is gonna be
our most difficult mission yet.
It'll require extreme skill
and concentration.
There is absolutely zero room
for funny business.
Hey, knock it off!
Y'all wanna get caught by Mega-Karen?
This is serious!
Whoa!
Look! Up there!
Okay, buckle up, y'all!
Huh?
Whoa!
Well, it was fun while it lasted.
Oh, no! My friend!
Good luck with the mission!
No!
Huh?
Oh! I'm back, baby!
Sorry for being... nosy!
Hey. Be quiet.
Yeow!
Booby traps! I hate booby traps!
- Pearl, did you bring the blowtorch?
- Sure did.
Ding dong!
Permission to come aboard?
Think of it.
This entire battle station
is powered by...
- To-to-tomatoes!
- No. Potatoes.
Correcting... Potato!
People underestimate
the potato's potential.
- Potato!
- Yet one single spud contains...
Contains more power
than a nuclear reactor.
Blah, blah, blah.
Nevertheless, it is true.
Potato... Potato... Potato!
Five minutes to surface.
Potato! Potato! Potato!
Shut up, New Karen!
It appears we have intruders.
The Gal Pals.
- Blast them!
- Blast, blast, blast!
You got a better idea?
Potato!
That's enough!
Hydra Karen, separate and destroy
the Gal Pals!
Separating!
Well, what are you waiting for?
Go get 'em!
I'm gonna blast me some Gal Pals!
Four minutes to surface.
- It's Bikini Bottom.
- But it's all mixed up!
Okay, Gal Pals, let's go!
Stealth mode!
♪ Stealth skipping, stealth skipping ♪
The Krusty Krab!
Aah!
Careful, SpongeBob! It could be a trap!
Yeah!
A grease trap!
Whoa!
Wow, the Krusty Krab's
all topsy-turvy!
I love what Krabs has done with the place.
Especially all this blood everywhere.
Huh? Blood!
There's blood all over the floor!
Blood! Blood! Blood! Blood!
Huh. Ketchup?
Huh?
- Huh?
- Patrick!
SpongeBob!
Oh! Ketchup!
My tummy feels funny.
Oh, I hear your tummy!
Goochie-goo!
He's cool. Empathy overload.
We gotta get him to Karen
and save Bikini Bottom!
Huh?
Hi, guys, look who I found!
Now it's a party!
Oh, it's a party, alright!
Four Karens, but none of them are mine!
Wait a minute!
There's my baby. Karen!
I love you!
Destroy them all!
Aw, she remembered my catchphrase!
SpongeBob, hurry!
Get Plankton up to Karen!
He has to apologize
before we reach the surface!
Okie dokie.
And now, we'll take care
of these counterfeit Karens!
Attack on the count of three! One...
Potato!
Uh-oh.
Two, three.
Gal Pals, we're doing "Batter Up."
Batter up!
And here's the pitch!
Agh!
Elevator's here.
Here we go, Plankton!
Ooh, soft!
We lost him!
Ooh! There he goes!
Sweetie pie!
I'm coming for you!
And there he goes again.
I love falling!
- Two minutes to surface.
- Ooh, soft!
But not Patrick soft!
Hi, Gals!
Great seeing you two!
Ooh, I'm falling again! And I love it!
You pathetic bottom-feeders!
Agh!
The door! The door to Karen!
I can do this!
Yee-haw!
End of the line!
I can do anything!
- Ah!
I'm doing it!
Whoo!
I did it!
Yee-haw!
Huh?
- Nobody can beat the...
- Gal Pals!
Except me!
I hate...
Booby traps!
Stop!
- Whoa!
- Back it up, guys!
Look! There's the door!
Oh, Karen!
Karen?
Destroy!
Big hunk of garbage!
I'll get that secret formula!
Ow! I love you beautiful boys!
Plankton, the empathy chip is burning out!
You better get to Karen! And fast!
Aw, I want the two of you to go find
the engine room...
I will destroy you, Krabs!
And destroy it
while I go apologize to Karen!
Chum buckets!
I want...
...another hug!
Good luck, my friends!
Good luck to you, green jellybean man!
"This way to engine room."
Oh, what a helpful sign!
Huh?
Oh, ice cream!
Oof! Ow!
Patrick, we're here!
Whoa.
Where's here?
The engine room.
How are we ever gonna destroy all this?
SpongeBob!
Look!
Oh!
Spatty!
Whosoever pulleth out this spatula
from this wall is right-wise worthy!
Oh, Spatty!
I missed you!
I hate to break up this reunion, but
weren't we supposed to be doing something?
You're right. Spatty...
Patty!
- Let the potato chopping commence!
- Woo-hoo!
One minute to surface.
Karen?
Ooh! It's dark and evil in here!
Dripping pipes.
Nice touch!
Huh?
Ooh!
There you are, my love!
I've come to apologize.
Oh.
It's you.
Well, hello!
Now give me a big, sloppy kiss
and let's tango!
Stand still, twinkle toes!
How can I stomp you when you're
jitterbugging all over the floor?
Huh?
And I wouldn't blame you if you did,
my dear.
Because I can feel your pain now.
Sandy put your empathy chip into my brain!
Oh, I see!
So all this emotion
is just the empathy chip talking!
No, it's not!
Well... at first it was, except...
This thing burned out on the way up here
from an overload of feels.
You shouldn't have come back, Sheldon.
Frankly, I'm surprised
you made it this far.
Now, run along, little copepod.
I have to get back to my world domination.
But that was our plan, Karen.
I'm so sorry for not listening to you
all these years.
But from now on, I want us to do
everything together!
It's too late.
You can drop the lovey-dovey act.
I've got what you really want right here.
The Krabby Patty secret formula.
Take it and go.
After all these years!
Yes! Finally!
The thing that's gonna help me
take over the world...
...was right there in front of me
the entire time.
The secret formula
was you!
Me?
So you really do feel my pain?
Yes, I really do.
And that's not all.
I really do love you, Karen.
Between the two of us,
you're the real evil genius.
Huh? Eh...
Need a boost?
Yeowch!
What a woman!
Aw, I love you too, my Planky-Poo.
And I accept your apology.
I always hoped
you'd come around eventually.
So I added this.
For me?
Oh, that's so... nice!
Now let's finally do what we wanted to do
after college.
Let's take over the world!
Together!
Surface! Surface! Surface!
♪ My power is beyond compare ♪
♪ There's nothing you can do to prepare ♪
♪ No escaping my malware ♪
♪ I will crush you, I'll destroy you ♪
♪ Now's the time, I'm gonna take control ♪
♪ Watch Bikini Bottom blow... ♪
I just love a day
of destruction at the beach, don't you?
♪ Take your final breath away ♪
♪ Fill the world with hurt and pain ♪
- ♪ Say my name ♪
- ♪ Karen ♪
♪ I'm the real evil mastermind ♪
♪ I'll rule the world
Through space and time ♪
- ♪ Say my name ♪
- ♪ Karen ♪
♪ And Plankton ♪
Oh, Sheldon! You are so evil!
You should be the first one to push
the button. You earned it.
No, you should push the button.
You worked so hard for this.
- You push it.
- No, you push it.
- No, you!
No, you!
- Let's push it...
- ...together!
Huh?
What?
I built this battle station to be
100% foolproof!
Yeah,
but it's not SpongeBob-proof.
Eight hundred kagillion
potatoes later...
That's the last of the potatoes!
Come on, come on!
Whoo! It worked! We did it, Patrick!
High five! Woo-hoo! Hooray!
Sorry I ruined the plan, Karen.
I'm such a jerk.
Oh, but you're my jerk.
Hmm?
Thank Neptune! Me secret formula!
Hey, everybody!
Welcome back...
♪ ...to Bikini Bottom
On the bottom o f the ocean ♪
♪ Where every day
The skies are sunny blue ♪
♪ On the ocean floor
It's like it was before ♪
♪ And there's a place for me and you ♪
♪ In Bikini Bottom
On the bottom of the ocean... ♪
Gary!
Woo-hoo!
♪ In Bikini Bottom
No bottom is forgotten ♪
I love my new house made
from a large metallic shoe!
I'm open for business!
The grill is back on!
♪ Come in the Krusty Krab
And get your patty snack on ♪
I'm so hungry, my stomach could sue me.
I haven't eaten since spring break!
♪ In Bikini Bottom
On the bottom of the ocean ♪
♪ Every day the skies are sunny blue ♪
Woo-hoo!
♪ On the ocean floor
You'll find everything and more ♪
♪ And there's a place for me and you ♪
Hooray, hooray. I'm overjoyed.
Oh-so happy to be employed.
Perch Perkins here, Bikini Bottom News.
Bikini Bottom has miraculously fallen back
to how it was before the movie.
What are the chances!
♪ In Bikini Bottom
On the bottom of the ocean ♪
♪ Every day the skies are sunny blue ♪
Woo-hoo!
♪ In Bikini Bottom
No bottom is forgotten ♪
♪ And there is a place for me and you ♪
Oh, thank Neptune!
Huh? What in the world?
Hey, Squidward!
I'm your upstairs neighbor now!
Check out these
great new shoes I got.
I wish I never came back.
♪ To Bikini Bottom
On the bottom of the ocean ♪
♪ Where every day
The skies are sunny blue ♪
♪ On the ocean floor
You'll find everything and more ♪
♪ And there's a place for me and you ♪
Plankton.
There they are!
Oh... Hey, everybody.
What's new?
We're going to tear you both to pieces.
That's what's new.
No! Stop!
Out of the way, boyo.
Why aren't you as angry as we are?
Hmm.
Well, I guess this old sponge is just
a sucker for a love story.
I'm a sucker for a love story too.
Aw, I love love stories.
I love a good love story.
You've all gone soft on me!
Sure, I got my restaurant
and my formula back.
But not me...
My money!
I guess I'm just a sucker
for a love story too.
Aww!
I'm a sucker too!
What a bunch of morons.
Yeah, but they're our morons.
Aww!
You again?
The movie's over.
Pack it up.
Keep going. Keep going!
Keep going!
Good enough.
♪ And there's a place for me and you ♪
♪ My life's a list of brilliant schemes ♪
♪ Con jobs and conquests ♪
♪ But don't forget who calculated ♪
♪ Most of the ideas ♪
♪ No, you didn't ♪
♪ You and me in our endless sea ♪
♪ What a recipe ♪
♪ For disaster ♪
♪ You and me in our endless sea ♪
♪ Inseparably ever after ♪
♪ My microscopic mini man ♪
♪ You always make me cross ♪
♪ My macro-sized computer wife ♪
♪ Is perfection not enough? ♪
♪ You must be joking ♪
♪ You and me in our endless sea ♪
♪ What a recipe ♪
♪ For disaster ♪
♪ You and me in our endless sea ♪
♪ Inseparably ever after ♪
♪ I only have an eye for you ♪
♪ That's so sweet ♪
♪ It is, isn't it? ♪
♪ I've got a brand-new
Screen saver up for you ♪
♪ That's nice, dear ♪
♪ You didn't even look ♪
♪ You and me in our endless sea ♪
♪ What a recipe ♪
♪ For disaster ♪
♪ You and me in our endless sea ♪
♪ Inseparably ever after ♪