(Based on the WEBTOON Series)
( SingNsong)
Hello, Author.
My name is Kim Dok-ja.
I read the last episode
which you uploaded today.
Your web novel, TWSA,
"Three Ways to
Survive the Apocalypse"
began publication
when I was in third
year of middle school.
Mammals include humans, bears...
I still remember
the first sentence.
"The subway car stopped,"
"in the middle of Dongho Bridge."
Planetary system 8612's
free service has ended.
To punish fallen humanity,
the gods sent down
intolerable hardships,
and as the world neared collapse,
the hero Yu Jung-hyeok
and his companions
overcame these trials.
At first, TWSA was quite popular.
But as the story went on,
people called it too
extreme, or unrealistic.
Many stopped following.
Hey, what's this?
Give it.
- Let me see.
- Give me my phone!
You want to die?
Still, during my school days,
this story was everything to me.
With every update,
I'd reread the last two
episodes to keep the flow.
On weekends, I re-read
the entire week's episodes.
And yes, when the views fell to 1,
I was the only reader.
Why read a novel for 10 years
when no one else was reading it?
Yu Jung-hyeok...
I envied him.
(Geumho)
Yu and his companions
brought vicious
enemies to their knees,
and they never backed down
while fighting monsters.
Lee Hyeon-seong!
But as his companions
fell one by one,
to survive,
Yu Jung-hyeok resolved
to become stronger.
So he got stronger and stronger,
but as I entered high school,
I stayed the same.
Now you two are going to fight.
The loser will be our doormat,
but the winner gets freedom.
What, can't bear to
just save yourself?
Whatever, don't do it.
But I told you for sure
what happens if you win!
"If only I could get stronger,"
"like Yu Jung-hyeok..."
That's what I wished then.
I went to a mediocre college,
worked at some mediocre jobs,
then joined this company.
On a temp contract.
Today the novel ended,
and so did my contract.
Good work, Dok-ja.
Call if you're in the area,
I'll treat you.
Thanks.
I appreciate your hard work
running this story for so long.
But still,
why'd you make Yu Jung-hyeok
the only survivor at the end?
What's the meaning of
an ending with one survivor?
Yu Jung-hyeok once said,
"I can't help it"
"if others are
sacrificed so I can live."
Is that the novel's theme?
I can't accept that.
Sir, your novel is
the worst.
The train for Daehwa
is approaching.
Listen to you sigh.
Hi, Sang-ah.
Your last day, too?
I knew they'd never
hire me full time.
No use fighting for
what can never be yours.
Just need to move on
and find a job that suits me.
Thank you.
You've found a new job already?
I'm going to a part time job now.
Need to survive this month.
You know how I designed
the characters' costumes?
That work really suited me,
so I want to make real clothes.
Later, I'll launch
my own brand, open a shop.
Nice, huh?
You're so impressive, Sang-ah.
Sang-ah, fancy meeting you here!
Hello, Mr. Han.
I told you I'd buy dinner tonight.
I need to be somewhere.
I'm so sad that
our Sang-ah is quitting.
If you'd given me a chance,
I'd have fought to get you hired.
Not at all, my skills
weren't up to it.
Let's get off this train
and have dinner.
I know a nice place in Apgujeong.
I have a part-time job.
Hey, no excuses.
I'll pay for the hours you miss.
That's really okay.
I'm going with someone.
Your friend?
Hello, Mr. Han.
I'm Kim Dok-ja from
Map Development.
So you two have had
something going on all this time?
My, what a shame.
This stop is Apgujeong...
Apgujeong.
The doors are on your right.
Enjoy your dinner.
Sure, Sang-ah.
I'll see you around.
What a jekr he is.
I couldn't even report him
for fear of getting fired.
You did well.
Holding back is winning.
It's not winning,
it's being an idiot.
But even knowing that,
I can't say a word.
Like an idiot.
You know how annoying that is?
(Dear Dok-ja, this is
the author of TWSA)
(Thank you for reading my novel)
Just a minute.
(You are really the author?)
(This story was
able to reach its end)
(thanks to you)
The doors are closing.
(No, thank you
for all your efforts)
(I regret what I wrote
in my email, please...)
Your girlfriend?
No.
(So I'll do a special epilogue)
(based on readers' submission)
(If you don't like the ending, )
(try writing your own)
(The service will
start soon, at 7 PM)
(Then show me)
(the ending)
(that you want)
(tls123 has left the chat)
The ending I want?
- What does that mean?
- Next stop is Oksu.
Thank you.
Readers' submissions at 7PM...
But I'm the only reader.
Does that mean I can
change the ending?
Are you okay?
Planetary system 8612's
free service has ended.
This is the start of paid content.
I repeat.
Planetary system 8612's
free service has ended.
This is the start of paid content.
Can this really be...?
"An announcement
echoes through the air."
"Planetary system 8612's
free service has ended."
"This is the start
of paid content."
(This fellow, who
I'll call a dokkaebi…)
What? A dokkaebi?
I'm so damned busy,
what is this crap?
Is someone playing a joke on us?
This is just like
the start of the novel.
Hello?
The Korean language
patch is working now.
People, can you hear me?
Damn it!
What the hell is going on?
Yes, I understand.
I know you're all busy,
but please listen up for a moment.
Get the train moving!
This is outrageous.
Come now, quiet down.
You need to listen to
what I'm about to tell you.
Cause I'm going to say
something super important...
Shut up and let's get moving,
before I rip you to shreds!
I'm busy as hell
and these jerks stopped the train?
Bunch of stupid...
I said quiet!
Humans, I want
you to listen closely
to every word I say.
High up there, those lofty beings
far greater than any puny human
have at last come to a decision.
That humans,
the most vulgar, greedy,
self-centered
race in the universe,
must all be punished!
Channel BI-7623 has opened.
Constellations are entering.
Welcome, dear Constellations!
Some super interesting
things are about to happen,
so come and watch!
From this moment on,
all you humans will
be given a Scenario.
How you solve that Scenario
will determine your fate.
The first Main Scenario
is starting.
Since this is your first time,
I'll explain it nicely.
Kill one or more living organisms
in this subway car.
Within 10 minutes.
Succeed, and you
each get 300 coins.
Fail, and you end up like him.
Simple, huh?
Our dear Constellations
will be watching it all,
so pay no heed to laws or ethics.
Just show it to us.
The true nature of humanity.
The phones don't work, right?
No, they won't.
Are you alone?
Are your parents with you?
Are you going to kill me?
Oh my god!
Yu Jung-hyeok?
I need to get a grip.
A novel that only I know
has become reality.
That means I know the future.
Wait, then next...!
First I have to
clear this Scenario.
Let me think.
One or more living organisms,
one or more living organisms...
(Kiil one or more
living organisms)
Sang-ah.
Hold onto this.
I'll go save those people.
Where are you going?
Are you crazy?
You'll die if you go there.
I know this.
What?
I know how to solve this.
Listen up a minute!
People, listen to me for a minute!
Hold on!
The first kill in this area
has taken place.
The killer receives 300 coins.
What? Hey, you.
How did you do that?
It says each person must kill
one or more living
organisms, right?
It said living organism.
It didn't say human.
Don't come closer!
I'll kill them all.
Wait! Wait!
How many ants have you got?
Tell us that first.
Well...
Not enough for everyone.
Hey mister!
If there's not enough,
you should've said so.
Why'd you kill one
before saying anything?
Then how will we decide?
Can we give it to the kids first?
Hey lady!
Everyone's life is the same!
Is only your kid's life important?
Everyone calm down!
I wish we had enough
for everyone, but...
Then what'll you do?
There's no time, hurry!
Hold on! Hold on!
I'm this guy's boss at work.
Just a minute.
Look, why are you
making the call on this?
People with more life
experience should do that.
So give it.
Mr. Han, that's true,
but people here...
I'm saying, I'll do it.
Give it here.
Don't push!
Okay, okay!
Dammit, why won't you die?
Are you insane?
You want to die?
Here.
Both you and her can live, okay?
I've got my own bug. Here.
A pathetic, useless bug.
In the novel, Kim Nam-woon
was part of Yu Jung-hyeok's team.
Was he always like this?
Hey!
Dammit.
Then I can just kill you instead.
Sure, if this is
just like the novel...
Spend 300 coins on strength.
300 coins spent on strength.
Strength is increased.
Son of a gun, now you're dead.
Kim Nam-woon has activated
the Grimdark Awakening skill.
In the novel, Nam-woon was first
to receive
the Constellation's Support.
Why a guy like him?
Wow, I've got skills,
this is cool as hell!
Want to save that old lady?
Then you die.
Are ants' eggs
living organisms too?
One organism killed.
300 coins paid as a reward.
Spend 3,000 coins on stamina.
Spend 3,000 coins on agility.
What the hell?
Why can't I hit you?
Mister.
Okay, I won't hurt the old lady.
- Give me an ant.
- I changed my mind.
We don't need you in this story.
What the hell are you saying?
Hey, get out of the way!
Out of the way!
Get away from her!
Time is up.
The Scenario has ended.
Granny.
Please wake up, okay?
Dok-ja...
Are you okay?
Ta-dah!
Congrats to the 17 humans
who cleared the first Scenario.
You were originally
supposed to kill each other,
but well, using the ants
isn't against the rules.
The Constellations said this car
was more fun than the others,
so let's move on for now.
Now it's time
for Supporting
Constellations to determine
who will receive
the Constellation's Support.
The Constellations'
Support is a tremendous gift!
If you choose well,
it'll be a big help in
clearing future Scenarios
Thanks to your actions,
the following Constellations
wish to give you their Support.
What's this mean?
Support? Constellations?
The Constellations watch
over all the Scenarios
from out in space.
They enjoy laughing
at the struggles of
humans trying to survive.
If you're chosen to
receive their Support,
it can be helpful.
But someday,
that debt must be paid back.
(None of the Above)
Quick!
Come to this side!
Lee Hyeon-seong!
Another character who
fought with Yu Jung-hyeok.
Listen, don't rely on strength.
Use your skill.
My skill?
How do I do that?
At the bottom
right of your vision,
there's a skill window.
If you just think
about your skill,
it should work.
Lee Hyeon-seong has activated
Great Mountain Push, Level 1.
Out of the way!
As soon as you get out,
run across the bridge.
Fast as you can!
I'm Lee Hyeon-seong.
I'm Kim Dok-ja.
Go on out.
Damn.
What are you doing?
Hurry, you need to go.
We need to go, come on.
Don't cry. Time's running out.
What's your name?
Lee Gil-yeong.
Gil-yeong, can you run fast?
But my ant farm got
destroyed because of you.
Really? I'm sorry.
- But we really...
- No, apologizing isn't enough.
You should take responsibility.
A Sub Scenario has arrived.
Cross the severed bridge.
Why call it a severed
bridge when it's not?
Cause it will be!
This is so thrilling,
don't just stand there!
I'll raise the difficulty level.
Dok-ja!
I just thought of that.
It was only a thought,
then the bridge's been...
I'll go first, Sang-ah!
Hyeon-seong!
Sang-ah!
You chose a sponsor, right?
Your sponsor is helping you.
Let's hurry!
Soon, poisonous gas
will start to spread.
We need to get
underground quickly.
And be sure to collect coins!
That's most important.
How do you know all this?
First, let's get to
the subway station.
Geumho Station is the closest.
If we take the subway
line Yu took, it'll be safe.
Wait.
But at Chungmuro Station...
Early in the novel,
Yu died at Chungmuro Station
fighting the Fire Dragon.
Yu used his Regression Skill
to go back to
the story's beginning,
but in a world without a hero,
everyone disappears.
The hero must not die.
But with the tactics I know,
one can't defeat
the Fire Dragon alone.
This is so tedious.
What if I tell Yu Jung-hyeok
those tactics?
And if we fight together?
Dok-ja, hurry!
Wait, I'll come in a second!
Hey, Yu Jung-hyeok!
What are you?
Huh? Well...
Kim Nam-woon
shouldn't die this soon.
Did you do that?
No, it wasn't me...
Yu Jung-hyeok has activated
the Lie Detection skill.
What, you already
know how to use coins?
It's not that...
Mr. Dok-ja!
Are you okay?
I'm fine! Stay there!
I'm really fine! Don't come!
And you know Lee Hyeon-seong?
- I met him today...
- I'll ask again.
What are you?
If I say I read this in a novel,
he'll never believe me, right?
I'm Kim Dok-ja.
In a few days you'll die fighting
the Fire Dragon in
Chungmuro Station.
Even if you Regress,
it'll take a long time
to clear this Scenario.
But if we go together,
you can defeat the Fire Dragon.
I know the tactics.
Yu Jung-hyeok has activated
the Lie Detection skill.
How do you know those tactics?
My personal skill is Prophecy.
So if you take me with you,
you'll have no problem
with Scenarios.
Let's cross the bridge.
You'll go via
Geumho Station, right?
- Hey, Kim Dok-ja.
- Yes?
Why are you doing this?
Tell me the tactics.
We can just go together
and clear the Scenario!
I can't stand taking
along other people.
If I tell you, you'll drop me.
I'll drop you anyway.
Wait a minute, wait!
Mr. Yu, I have
a terrible fear of heights!
This isn't right!
First, let go... no, don't let go!
Your last chance.
Why'd this happen to the world?
Why are humans being punished?
How would I know that?
Survive and come to Chungmuro.
Then you'll know.
I'll let you know then
if I'll fight with you.
Yu Jung-hyeok, you jerk!
In a few days,
Yu will die fighting
the Fire Dragon.
But for me to live,
the hero must not die.
But before that,
I'm going to die.
A Hidden Scenario has arrived.
Kill the ichthyosaur
and escape its stomach.
(Hidden Scenario:
Commander Slayer)
Kill it to escape?
But I've got no items.
Huh?
He's alive? He's alive!
Constellations, as you see,
a human has entered
the ichthyosaur's belly.
Sure, if I get on
the dokkaebi's good side
it can help me get
coins or an item.
And the thing a dokkaebi
likes most of all...
Am I right, Constellations?
Hey, get over here.
The human's talking to me!
I'll go closer.
You lowly human.
You were quite a sight,
playing God with that ant farm.
And you were a real terror.
Shooting people down
with your little laser.
Speak with some respect.
If you don't like it,
just shoot me.
How dare a foolish
human talk this way
to a great dokkaebi.
Hey, Bihyeong.
You're doing a Star Stream, right?
What? You know my name?
And how do you know
about Star Streams?
Your channel must
be exploding now.
Who else is as
entertaining as me so far?
The Constellations
must be so curious
what I'll do next.
If you kill me now, can
you handle the blowback?
But how do you know all this?
Close your channel
for a sec, and let's talk.
Constellations, let's break
for a quick advertisement!
Now talk.
How can an ordinary human
know about Star Streams?
Ow, that hurts.
That's not what matters here.
What? You told me to close it!
Bihyeong, you need to be clever.
How long will you keep panhandling
as a lowly 9th grade dokkaebi?
What are you saying?
What does a dokkaebi do, anyway?
Let Constellations
into your channel,
and show them
stories about humans.
Get a lot of donations,
and you'll be
a 1st grade dokkaebi.
But I can guarantee my story
will be incredibly fun.
Sign an exclusive
contract with me,
and you'll be dokkaebi king.
Wow.
You should know your place.
Why sign a contract with someone
who's about to die?
Why do you think
Constellations watch
the Star Streams?
Cause it's fun
watching humans
struggle to survive.
That's why they donate too.
Right!
Then suppose we sign a contract.
In the subway I used
ants to clear the Scenario,
and I fought Kim
Nam-woon using my skills.
I was eaten by an ichthyosaur,
but if I escape,
then keep clearing every Scenario
after getting out...
How many donations do you think
our channel will get?
How can I believe
that you'll do all that?
Go see how many
donations you have now.
Look at all this!
How many zeros?
I can't believe this.
Okay, let's sign a contract!
We split the profits 50:50, okay?
- Oh, it's started!
- Damn.
Constellations,
the ichthyosaur's stomach acid
has started to flow.
How will he escape this?
Bihyeong, open the Dokkaebi Shop.
Huh? The Dokkaebi Shop?
How do you know all this?
(Dokkaebi Shop)
He purchased an item!
Let's see what he'll do with it.
Yu Jung-hyeok was trapped
in an ichthyosaur's
stomach once, too.
If you block all
its stomach acid ducts
with thorns, it'll die.
But the problem is,
there are so many of them...
In a few days you'll die fighting
the Fire Dragon in
Chungmuro Station.
Even if you Regress,
it'll take a long time
to clear this Scenario.
But if we go together,
you can defeat the Fire Dragon.
This Scenario is
a battle of endurance.
The last one!
You've cleared
the Hidden Scenario.
9,000 coins paid as a reward.
What is this?
Dok-ja, you defeated
an ichthyosaur!
- Amazing!
- Out of the way!
What?
That's the Ichthyosaur's Nucleus!
How'd you know where it was?
Put this on
the Dokkaebi Shop auction.
Not to sell. I want a 1:1 trade.
And I'll only trade
it for Ether of Faith.
Put up a notification window
when there's an offer.
Dok-ja, you're
starting to scare me.
Killing the ichthyosaur
is one thing,
but to know how
to find its nucleus,
and wanting to trade
for Ether of Faith!
Ether of Faith is so rare!
I doubt anyone in the
early Scenarios will have it.
Let's try to find it
as soon as we can.
And when I call you,
come right away.
Open your Dokkaebi Shop
for me sometimes, okay?
I'll do my best, Dok-ja!
And it's nothing big,
but here's a gift to
celebrate our contract.
You'll need it when you go out.
Oh, a Starter Pack?
(Starter Pack for Novice)
Nice.
The Constellation
Hunter of the Dark Moon
admires your endurance,
and wishes to sponsor...
The Constellation
Bringer of Dark Light
wishes to be your sponsor
and join you on your journey.
Constellations, you're
enjoying this, huh?
Hey Bihyeong!
Turn off all notifications
related to Constellations.
Yes, sir.
But where'll you go now?
Geumho Station.
Need to meet someone.
You mean that tall fellow?
Don't do that.
He's got tons of items
and his level is off the charts.
We just signed a contract,
what'll I do if you die?
I'm hungry.
Hey.
Hey! Can you hear me?
Try to wake up.
Can you stand up?
Did you say exit 1?
Wait!
Wait a minute!
Dammit!
Hey, are you okay?
- Over there.
- What's this?
It's really true!
Jeong Hui-won, you're alive?
- Jeong Hui-won?
- I thought you croaked.
I'll kill that lowlife.
Hey, mister!
Why drag her back here
after we've finished with her?
Don't be a nuisance.
This chapter in the novel
was particularly boring.
The characters were
such stereotypes.
Bang Cheol-su?
What's this?
You know me?
What are you waiting for? Come on.
Spend 1,500 coins on strength.
1,500 coins spent on strength.
Holy crap, he's using skills?
Hey, you should've told me!
Bang Cheol-su is
blessed by his sponsor
Monarch of the Small Fries.
Why choose such a crappy sponsor?
Right, chest, right.
This guy never changes.
Boss!
Kill that idiot!
Now!
Bang Cheol-su!
What's going on here?
Damn...
Hey, let's go.
Wait, who was this guy?
Huh?
Dok-ja!
People say they've survived here
thanks to that congressman.
He persuades high-level
people to go out and hunt,
then shares it with the residents.
It's done. You'll heal in no time.
Gil-yeong!
I told you to stop that!
Why? They're my friends.
He's been acting weird
ever since that day.
He says he can talk to bugs
with his hands like that.
I'm not weird. I like doing this.
But Mr. Dok-ja,
why did that man on
the bridge drop you?
What?
Oh, him?
I've known him since I was young.
He's always been
hard to get along with.
Didn't he cause a scene here too?
No, he wasn't here.
He hasn't been here?
He crossed the bridge,
and even when the gas came out,
he just walked on
his own to Namsan.
Yu Jung-hyeok didn't
come to Geumho Station?
That can't be.
Wait, so you haven't cleared
the Geumho Station Scenario?
Some people went into the tunnel
trying to clear it,
but no one came back.
Damn, if we can't clear it,
we can't pass the barrier
and get to Chungmuro.
But why are things
different from the novel?
Listen up, residents!
The survival fee
payment is due in 3 hours.
The Search Party
will leave in 5 minutes,
so be ready.
Let the elderly stay,
and healthy men
who want to go out...
The Geumho Station Scenario
exacts a survival
fee on all residents
until the monsters are defeated.
100 coins per day.
Residents desperate for coins
went out on dangerous hunts,
and those who couldn't pay
died on the spot.
Hey you!
You, the newcomer.
They say you grabbed
all the coins for yourself,
is it true?
What?
You earned coins
by hunting monsters
in this district, right?
Then share the coins.
How can you just keep quiet?
Give them to the Congressman
so they can be shared.
Think only you have it hard?
Right!
I think there's been
some misunderstanding.
I've never gone out hunting.
Don't lie to us!
You fight so well
because you earned
coins while hunting!
No really, I've never hunted.
And even if I did, wouldn't
the reward be mine?
Listen to him!
Here at Geumho Station,
we've survived up to now
by pooling our strength!
Oh, right.
You must have.
But who told you that
I have a lot of coins?
Why does that matter?
Go to the office and turn them in.
We're desperate here.
So just tell me.
Then I'll give you
each 100 coins, okay?
Who told you?
Bang Cheol-su?
I told them.
With such abilities,
I assumed you were rich in coins.
But those with a lot
are least willing to share.
I hoped you'd understand
our situation here.
With everyone so desperate,
we acted a bit rude.
If you were offended, I apologize.
No, I'm not offended.
Mr. Kim, 20 people can't afford
the survival fee today.
I want to save our residents
by any means possible.
Please help us, I beg you.
Wait, now I remember.
I know who he is...
You want my coins.
That's not going to happen.
You don't care
if our residents die?
Even if they live today,
what about tomorrow?
People are dying right now!
How can you say that?
That's enough.
Stop this, okay?
Stop!
Will you?
I thought you were
a good person, Mr. Kim.
But I read you wrong.
All right.
I'll help.
But even if I give you coins,
you'll need more tomorrow.
So instead...
"Pass through the tunnel"
"and neutralize all the monsters."
I'll clear this Scenario today.
Okay?
Cheon In-ho of Geumho Station,
who sold himself
to the Constellations,
who gave up his
humanity to become
a monster.
Ant eggs instead of humans?
That was allowed?
If a man like you
was beaten by him,
the rumors must be true.
Kim Dok-ja has
the highest abilities
and most coins in
Geumho Station now.
If he's that strong,
can he clear the Scenario?
How many times must I tell you?
As long as I'm here,
no one will clear that Scenario.
Ah, yes.
You're right.
Of course, you're right.
It's human nature to bow
down before the strong.
A weakling like him
who suddenly gains great strength
will run wild, thinking
he's a big shot.
It's reckless gallantry.
In this world,
guys like him die first.
Then if he dies,
we better collect his coins.
How much do you think he has?
I heard it's tens of
thousands of coins.
Is that true, Mr. Han?
Yes, it's true! Sorry.
I saw it clearly.
Help yourself.
I'm not going.
Why go? We'll die.
We won't die. Come along.
I'll go, mister!
I want to fight monsters, too.
Look at him saying
he'll fight monsters.
No way.
Mr. Dok-ja, if you
have extra coins,
why not just share them?
Exactly!
Why do we have to go this far?
I mean you, not we.
Even with coins,
people here will die.
To stop the deaths,
we must target the cause.
Isn't that so, Hui-won?
In the novel, Hui-won
rebels against Cheon In-ho,
loses her friends
and dies in the convenience store.
Now, all she has left is rage.
You say that congressman
is the culprit... how?
When I found Hui-won,
it wasn't monsters
that had attacked her.
Bang Cheol-su's gang
is on his side too.
They recruit a Search Party
to go out looking for coins,
and after hunting,
they quietly kill everyone.
My friends died trying
to stop them with me.
Why would they kill people?
When you die,
your coins all fall out.
That jerk Cheon In-ho
is not human.
It's too dark here.
We can't even
walk, let alone fight.
Gil-yeong, can you help?
Me? Can I?
What are you talking about?
That thing you
thought of, show me.
Hey Gil-yeong, don't you
dare call cockroaches!
Wow, Lee Gil-yeong!
They say monsters are coming.
Make use of your sponsors.
You know how to increase
your abilities with coins?
Spend all your coins
on strength and agility.
All my coins?
Shouldn't I save some
for the survival fee?
Maintain this formation.
Don't fight on your own,
help each other.
Gil-yeong, keep
the fireflies steady.
I'm going to fight too!
Stay behind me.
I'll go!
If we follow that one...
Mister, if we go this way,
there'll be a really
strong monster, right?
The fireflies told me.
What?
I don't know.
But you always
know a ton of stuff.
You're like a god.
Would I be doing
this if I were a god?
If there's a god,
it's that author.
Sang-ah!
Are you there?
Dok-ja! I'm tied up here...
What's that?
You've entered
The Ground Rat's Shrine.
I'll go first!
Do I need an item to
defeat a demon species?
Mr. Dok-ja! I'm coming!
Hyeon-seong! It's no use!
What the... Can he do that?
The Warden of the Dark
has activated an Illusory Prison.
Illusory Prison?
The Illusory Prison traps the body
and wrecks the mind.
If you're caught in it,
you relive awful memories and die.
Run, Hui-won!
What was that?
Just a second.
Gil-yeong! No!
Over there!
Hui-won! Buy me some time!
Hey Bihyeong, you watching?
Yes, what do you need?
Open the Dokkaebi Shop.
White Star Pure Energy.
It's 50,000 coins,
you're 1,000 coins short!
50,000 coins paid.
You have bought
White Star Pure Energy.
Your weapon can now deliver
a One-time Critical Hit.
Hyeon-seong!
He's awake.
Are you okay?
Sorry. I must've fallen asleep.
Just a minute.
If you rest, you'll feel better.
The Hyeon-seong in the novel
was wracked by guilt
for not saving someone,
so he could not make
use of his abilities.
The Lee Hyeon-seong
here is exactly the same.
Nice work, everyone.
I saw some treasure
chests back there.
Let's each go open one.
Two swords for Hui-won,
an arm protector for Hyeon-seong.
What about Gil-yeong?
With this, I can hear
the insects' words better.
Ta-dah!
Nice, huh?
It seems this'll make
me able to fight well, too.
Then I'll open up mine.
Huh? Yours is defective.
Why does the one who
worked hardest get that?
It'll have some use, I'm sure.
Let's go.
This is it. The Broken Faith.
Now if I can just
find An Ether of Faith,
the weapon will be complete.
Huh, what's this?
Mister, I found
this here, what is it?
If you eat this, those
white hands will come out,
and you'll have scary dreams.
Keep away from it, okay?
All right.
Dok-ja.
How do you know all this?
What?
Putting stuff on the knife,
and you seem to know this place.
It's like you've already
lived in this world.
It's true, right?
It's not just me who thinks that.
What is up with you?
About that...
I have no sponsor
or special skills,
but it seems I know
a bit about what will happen.
A kind of prophecy.
You really know what'll happen?
Prophecy? Dok-ja, that's awesome!
Then do you know what
will happen to the world?
Shouldn't you know that, too?
The world can go
back to how it was.
Really?
When? When can I go home?
That'll take some time.
What do we have to do?
We have to clear up
to the 99th Scenario.
The 99th? Who can do that?
There's one person who can.
A hero who can clear all Scenarios
and save the world.
It's not... you?
The two of you saw him,
back on Dongho Bridge.
Yu Jung-hyeok.
That man?
He's so good-looking.
The problem is,
tomorrow he will die
fighting a monster.
What happens if he dies?
Then this world is finished.
It can never go
back to how it was.
He'll be at Chungmuro Station now.
Once we clear this Scenario,
the barrier will be lifted,
then I'll go there.
I'll try to stop it somehow.
Wait.
Didn't we just
clear this Scenario?
There's one monster left.
10 minutes until
the survival fee payment.
Prepare your payment.
I heard people in the Search Party
are being killed for coins?
My husband isn't back yet!
Goodness, you're annoying!
I killed him. So what?
- You didn't!
- What are you going to do?
Annoying idiot.
I told you I'd kill you.
Sweet dreams.
Ms. Jeong Hui-won!
If you went to clear the Scenario,
you should do it or die trying.
What's all this?
I'm here to clear it.
There's one monster left here.
Don't just stand there.
Kill them and take their coins.
In the novel, Jeong Hui-won
wasn't that famous,
and wasn't used much in the story.
Perhaps that's why
I cheered for her
more than anyone.
Hui-won, in this story,
you are the hero.
The Constellation
Demonic Judge of Fire
approves use of this skill.
Time of Judgment
has been activated.
Hey, wait!
Miss!
You're not really going
to kill him, are you?
You may not know this,
but we don't clear this Scenario.
If we clear it, the next
one gets even harder.
At a nearby station they
opened the next Scenario
and all got massacred.
It's better to just pay
100 coins every day.
Hold on!
What's with you people?
Why didn't you say that sooner?
We spent all our coins
to fight those
monsters and clear it.
Well, everyone who
tries to clear it has died.
So we assumed
that you would, too.
You saw how coins
come out when you die.
The congressman
collected and shared them.
Who knew you'd come back alive?
Exactly.
Why'd this happen to the world?
Why are humans being punished?
Is this what Yu Jung-hyeok
was talking about?
Kim Dok-ja!
That means you
don't have any coins
to pay the survival fee!
3 minutes until
the survival fee payment.
Humans within this district,
prepare for payment.
1 minute until the
survival fee payment.
Everyone prepare for payment.
Hui-won, you need to
catch him now!
Why so surprised?
It's the barrier.
Didn't you know
you have to clear
the Scenario to pass?
Except for me,
you killed all the monsters
at Geumho Station.
Time's up.
Wait!
That reckless gallantry of yours
is always the problem.
That's why you will die.
Take cover!
All monsters have
been neutralized.
The daily survival
fee will be lifted.
You have cleared
the Main Scenario.
Who the hell are you?
Hey, what's with your attitude?
Looks like I saved you,
shouldn't you thank me?
Since I killed him,
you don't mind if I take these?
Don't be scared.
I can tell you're just beggars.
Still, thank you.
She looks scary. Let's go.
Where are you going?
Need to clear the Scenario.
Ah, we just cleared the Scenario.
That's for your district.
But you just stepped over here.
What is this?
We're blocked again?
Just so you know,
the Scenario here isn't one
where you band together.
It's everyone on their own.
You just going to stand there?
You really should run.
Lee Ji-hye...
(Main Scenario #1:
Prove Your Worth)
In the novel, at
the first Scenario
when everyone was panicking...
Ji-hye, what do we do?
Lee Ji-hye
survived on her own.
Day 4 of the Chungmuro
Station Scenario is starting.
10 minutes before monsters appear,
Green Zones will be created.
Take refuge in
a Green Zone to survive.
Current survivors: 104 people.
Number of Green
Zones for today: 52.
Find refuge in a Green Zone.
10 minutes left!
If you want to live,
750 coins per person!
It's safe in here!
10 minutes left!
There aren't many empty spaces!
Not many spaces left.
Closing in 10 minutes!
How much in cash for just me?
He said cash.
Look.
We don't take cash. Bring coins.
I don't have any coins,
but I'll give you as
much cash as you want.
- Mister.
- $20,000? $30,000?
Get lost, will you?
Can't you read?
(1 night 1 person, 750 coins)
- Damn it.
- Can't you take this?
This is $100,000.
Please!
I said get lost! Forget it.
Hold on a sec!
Where'd you get $100,000 in cash?
I passed through
Myeongdong Station yesterday.
A guy there was
offering $100 per coin.
You never know when the world
might return to normal,
so I exchanged it just in case.
Did I do something wrong?
That's from my safe!
I'm rich in coins
thanks to fools like him
who still love paper.
My goodness, a young
guy like you, so clueless...
You'll die broke!
Intruder detected.
But why do those beggars
fight so hard to live?
The ones with no
money will all die anyway.
We haven't even started,
do we have to fight
like this every day here?
At midnight, monsters
will rush into the station.
You can live if you go
inside the green tiles.
We'll split up and look
for empty spots, but listen.
There may not be
enough spots for us five.
If you find one,
protect it at all costs.
Then at least one of us will live.
Got it?
(Main Scenario #3:
Green Zone (Day 4 of 5))
(Survive each night
in a Green Zone)
No spaces left in
Chungmuro Station.
To live, we must take
away someone else's space.
You're that prophet?
I heard it from Master.
Since you made it this far,
I guess it works for you.
Where is Yu Jung-hyeok?
He went out already.
This Scenario isn't at his level.
But why just stand there?
If you're a prophet,
you'll know where the bonus
Green Zones appear.
What?
Can't bear to just save yourself?
Master said to tell you this.
He'll take your offer,
so leave the others
and survive on your own tonight.
Can't bear to just save yourself?
But I told you for sure
what happens if you win!
Hey,
let's go.
What did I say?
I told you they'd do it!
You give up.
At least one of us should live.
Get out of there!
6-1, 6-1...
5 tiles back from the 6-1 mark.
Dok-ja!
Dok-ja, we looked all over,
but there are no empty spots.
Gil-yeong, over here!
Is there anywhere
else we can look?
Everyone, listen up!
I'm Biryu the Dokkaebi,
in charge of this Scenario.
Less than a minute left,
but I don't see your desperation.
After a few days, are you tired?
Should I free
the monsters right now?
So I'll raise the tension a bit.
Those who don't have a spot yet,
this is your last chance.
One minute before starting,
some Green Zones will vanish,
and Bonus Green Zones will appear.
Dok-ja, we need to move...
Is this prophecy too?
In this Scenario,
it can't be helped.
At least take those spots.
If we push them out,
won't those people die?
If you want to live,
it can't be helped.
Can't we just fight like before?
How many monsters are there?
That's not how it works.
Without a spot, you'll die!
The teleport has formed.
Monsters are entering.
You need to take a spot!
You can do that!
Why don't you find one?
This is driving me crazy.
Wait up!
Go towards the teleport.
And over there!
Isn't it more dangerous there?
All Scenarios are designed
to entertain the Constellations.
As long as it's entertaining,
the rules can change.
Green Zones can appear
in the most dangerous places.
Hurry!
This doesn't seem right!
Huh?
There's one!
But mister...
Later, I'm busy!
You could've just stayed there,
why'd you come back?
There's this novel I know
where only the hero survived.
But that hero was a real jerk!
Yu Jung-hyeok?
Hey, Yu Jung-hyeok! Move over.
You don't need a Green Zone.
Want to fight
the Fire Dragon with me?
This is my condition.
Leave the kid, and come in.
Otherwise you'll die.
Hyeon-seong, grab this!
- Gil-yeong, stay here.
- What about you?
If I eat this,
I'll be trapped in
the Illusory Prison.
I knew it.
The Illusory Prison is activated.
He hit him!
Time's running out, hurry!
Die, you prick!
Stop, stop!
Hey, I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
Wow Dok-ja, you're so cool!
Dear Author,
Yu Jung-hyeok once said,
"I can't help it"
"if others are
sacrificed so I can live."
Is that the novel's theme?
I can't accept that.
Sir, your novel is
the worst.
Yesterday, Min-seob died.
I'm trying to find
out the details,
but for now,
just try to focus on
today's mock exam.
(Science - Chemistry)
Author,
once I caused a friend to die
so that I could live.
In the novel, Yu Jung-hyeok
seemed to be telling me
it's not my fault.
That it couldn't be helped.
So I cheered for Yu Jung-hyeok.
Until I read the ending today.
For me, this ending is terrifying.
I'm scared it could
happen to me, too.
Sir, I wanted a different ending.
The ending I couldn't have,
when whatever sacrifice it took,
the hero survived to the
end with his companions.
Don't be ridiculous.
Yu Jung-hyeok is using
the Dream Conversation skill.
Then you should've
fought that bully and won.
I know what you want to do.
But helping each other and all?
Humans just aren't born that way.
I used to think like you once.
But after losing
so many colleagues
in hellish battles,
it becomes easier to fight alone.
Then
what do we do now?
Why do you think you
have to do something?
After all, you were nothing.
His wounds are too deep,
he's not recovering.
Dok-ja, are you okay?
I worried you'd be down
like that the whole day.
What happened to everyone?
What's wrong with Hyeon-seong?
Mr. Dok-ja, good to see you awake.
Hyeon-seong pushed
himself too hard.
Sang-ah also strained
herself trying to heal him.
You're really okay?
Yes, but...
Did you fight
the monsters all night?
Because of me?
Time's up. We need to
go do the next Scenario.
My companions survived
outside of the Green Zones.
By pooling their strength.
Perhaps the way to
clear this Scenario...
Hyeon-seong and
Gil-yeong can't fight today.
Secure two Green Zones for them,
and we'll hold out on the outside.
But today, Yu Jung-hyeok dies.
On the last day of the
Chungmuro Station Scenario,
a Fire Dragon comes out.
Yu Jung-hyeok will
fight with it and die.
You said if he dies,
this world ends.
To be precise,
if the hero who can
save this world dies,
in minutes the world
will be destroyed.
To prevent that,
someone else needs
to fight the Fire Dragon.
If that's us,
it means one of us has to die?
I'll do it.
Besides,
if it weren't for Dok-ja
I would have died then anyway.
What should I do?
No.
There's something else
you must do, Hui-won.
I'll do it.
Wait.
That guy Yu Jung-hyeok
has a really high level,
on a totally different
scale than us.
If a person like that will die,
what about you?
Last night you all protected me.
Thank you.
Thanks to you, I now know
what I need to do today.
Current survivors: 57 people.
Number of Green Zones for today...
We have an announcement.
Everyone, listen up!
As you know, this Scenario's rule
is everyone for themselves.
The concept is to
survive on your own.
But last night,
some of you survived
outside of the Green Zones.
Helping each other, no less.
Our dear Constellations
are very upset.
So today we'll be
raising the difficulty.
Current survivors: 57 people.
Number of Green
Zones for today: 1.
What? You can't do that!
Quiet down!
I'll decide myself who
gets that Green Zone.
Who should get it?
The kindest human?
The most unfortunate human?
Or the smartest human?
But I hear in your world,
being rich is best?
Then we'll do that.
A Green Zone has appeared.
If you want to live,
rise up and take this spot.
But even if you do,
it's only one spot.
Wait a minute.
Ji-hye, would you help me?
Why should I?
I'm going to take that space.
Join us instead, okay?
If you'd just stayed in that Zone,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
Everyone's going to die
because of your stupid courage.
That's why I need your help.
I've got an idea,
so if you'd only...
I said no!
You saw who got the Green Zone!
In this world, it's always
the strong who survive.
I think it's great.
It's simple and fair.
If you don't want
to die, just win.
It isn't enough
that you killed your
friend to survive?
Even as she died,
she didn't even
reach a finger to you.
I couldn't help it.
I know you couldn't help it.
But you know what happened
when you tried to survive alone.
Bihyeong, you there?
Dok-ja, wow!
Just as you said,
our channel is going crazy!
The Constellations
love this story,
and donations are pouring in!
Let's cash in those donations now.
How much?
All of it.
When I tell you, shoot it all out.
Hold on, let me convert it.
Hey mister!
Gong Pil-du!
What does this bum want?
Hey, want to do some work for me?
What?
I'll hire you for the day.
How much will it cost?
I thought you were a bum,
turns out you're a madman.
Will 100,000 coins be enough?
100,000?
Sure, if you've got that much,
I'll do what you want for one day.
You've got the coins?
Of course I do.
Bihyeong, now!
Here it comes, 113,000 coins!
The Green Zone is
being re-generated.
My spot!
That crazy son of a gun!
Hey!
Hey, don't do that!
I'll shoot you!
Go ahead and shoot!
I know you couldn't help it.
But you know what happened
when you tried to survive alone.
Hey!
Damn you.
That madman really broke it.
Out of the way.
You jerk, what about my land?
What will you do now?
Monsters will enter in one minute.
The teleport is forming.
From the very start!
If those Green Zones didn't exist,
we all would have fought them.
We might all have survived.
100,000 coins have
been transferred.
What are you doing?
I bought you for today.
Keep your word!
What do you want?
I don't want a single
resident here to die!
I counted everyone!
Hey!
I won't charge you for today,
so those who want to fight, fight.
Those who can't,
come onto my land.
Hurry!
Guess I'll earn bucket
loads of coins today.
The Constellation Defense Master
gives emergency
defense to Gong Pil-du.
Gil-yeong and Hyeon-seong
can't join us today.
We need to fight for them, too.
Don't die, you two.
Die, you jerk!
Pil-du!
I'll stop that one.
You keep blocking the entrance!
Go quick!
Hey, Yu Jung-hyeok!
If you fight, you'll die.
I'll do it.
With that sword?
It was 4 days ago
you predicted I'd die?
Watch this.
There's a human in this area
with abnormal abilities.
With all the
Constellations' consent,
the difficulty
level will be raised.
What?
This wasn't in the novel.
Sang-ah! Pull him out quickly!
Then what about you?
This'll protect me from
the flames, at least.
Now!
Gil-yeong!
Gil-yeong.
What about Dok-ja?
Gil-yeong, stop.
I'm okay. I can do it.
Gil-yeong, that's enough. Stop.
Stop it Gil-yeong, please!
Lee Hyeon-seong's
attribute is ready to blossom.
Sang-ah!
Lee Hyeon-seong has activated
Great Mountain Push, Level 4.
I'm coming, Hyeon-seong!
Ms. Hui-won!
I'll face the Fire Dragon somehow.
Listen closely.
In the dragon's chest
there's a round shell
with a core inside.
If we pierce the core,
we can defeat the Fire Dragon.
The problem is,
whoever breaks that
shell is sure to die.
If I break the shell,
I'm going to die.
Then Sang-ah should bind its arms,
and Hui-won must pierce the core.
If you defeat the Fire Dragon,
you'll receive a special ability.
Just once,
you can revive someone who died.
You get what I'm saying?
We need to trust each other.
This is the only way
that we can all live.
Dok-ja...
Hui-won! Now!
Hui-won!
The core's shell is re-forming.
What do we do now?
The only way to end this fight...
The core is pierced.
Now Yu Jung-hyeok will die.
Just like in the novel.
Kim Dok-ja, what now?
The hero has died.
I couldn't do anything.
Activating Yu Jung-hyeok's
Regression skill.
All matter in the present world
will cease to exist.
(The Ichthyosaur's Nucleus)
(has been exchanged
for Ether of Faith)
(Trade initiated by: Tls123)
(If you don't like the ending, )
(try writing your own)
(Then show me)
(the ending)
(that you want)
Hey Bihyeong!
Send me the item, quick!
Dok-ja, the world is
disintegrating now!
Just send it!
Broken Faith has transformed
into an Attribute Weapon.
There's still a chance.
Hyeon-seong!
Ms. Hui-won!
Sang-ah!
The Green Zone
Scenario has been cleared.
10,000 coins paid as a reward.
As an additional reward,
you receive
The King of No Killing.
Kim Dok-ja revived Yu Jung-hyeok
using the King of No Killing.
Yu Jung-hyeok.
Are you okay?
I didn't think you could do it.
Nice job!
Wow, we defeated that?
Dok-ja, what a sword!
Guess it wasn't defective.
Hyeon-seong, your skill
back there was so cool!
I should have acted sooner.
All of you did great.
I, who was nothing,
lived this story, and
met new companions.
Together with my companions,
we will write a new
ending to this story.
(Omniscient Reader: The Prophecy)
(Written and Directed
by Kim Byung-woo)
(Ahn Hyo Seop)
(Lee Minho)
(Chae Soobin)
(Shin Seungho)
(NANA)
(Kwon Eunseong)
(JISOO)
A new Scenario is starting.
All of the barriers are lifted.
Help!
Someone help!
Mr. Han?
Those idiots!
They killed everyone
at Geumho Station!
Children, the elderly, everyone!
Don't just sit here!
They're on their way here now!
So soon?
They're coming! They're coming!
(Current location:
Chungmuro Station)