No way.
That's so crazy.
No, you have had Snapchat.
I'm not on there. Are you on it?
No.
No! There's no way...
- I'm so jealous! Yeah.
- ...she posted that.
She'd be so embarrassed.
No, the fact that
she's trying to be you, but...
...she's like a millennial!
Yeah, she genuinely is.
Hey, are you guys going to the city?
Yeah.
You meeting some friends there?
Why?
Piper!
You were supposed to wait for me.
I don't know who this is.
- Such a pedophile.
- I'm not... What the...
I'm her brother.
Uh, stepbrother.
Um, Kimmy.
- Let's go.
- Oh, thank God.
Okay.
Come on.
They didn't like me, did they?
"Are you guys
going to the city?"
No, no, they liked you.
- No, they didn't.
- No, they did, they did.
There was three of them
and they all had sort of dark hair.
And they were nice.
They didn't dress very well, though.
Where's your cane, Piper?
It's in my bag. Shut up.
All right. Jeez.
- You ask me all the time!
- Okay!
How was goal ball?
Uh, we lost.
- Andy!
- Hmm?
- Yeah?
- Andy!
- What?
Dad?
Dad, can you answer me, please!
- Andy!
- Here, here, here, here, here.
Dad, I'm gonna come in, okay?
He always answers.
Uh, okay, we're coming in, Dad.
Not answering!
Dad?
What's happening?
Andy?
Andy!
What's happening?
Dad?
Dad!
Andy!
Yeah. Now, take a breath.
He'd just finished chemo. He was...
He was supposed to be better.
Okay.
And, Piper, did your brother
try to help you?
No?
He didn't want me in there.
Okay.
He told me Dad would be okay.
Okay, that's okay.
That's okay. You've been so brave, Piper.
Lift it up a little bit. Just...
Hmm.
It says here you're partially
sighted. Is that right, Piper?
I can... I can only see shapes
and light. That's about it.
I've talked to an amazing foster mum
called Laura. You're gonna love her.
And, Andy, we're gonna put you
in your own supervised unit.
- What?
- Wait, hold on,
you're splitting us up?
But I look after her.
You can apply for guardianship
when you're 18.
Okay, I really don't want her
to move in with a stranger.
She needs me.
Why can't he just come with me?
Laura's had issues
with troubled kids in the past, and...
What?
Nothing.
Grapefruit.
I got into trouble when I was younger.
But it was ages ago. I was, like, eight.
Can you, um...
Can you talk to her and just tell her
that we are not splitting up?
If she agrees, can you behave
yourself for three months?
Oi.
You hear that?
That's Dad going to heaven.
Shut up.
No, seriously though, that's...
That's what happens.
You don't get burned or buried, you just...
Catch a plane.
You don't have to make everything
nice for me, you know.
Yeah, I know.
The room still smells like him.
Oh, Pipe.
You could take some of his clothes.
They're washed.
Don't smell like him.
His pillow, then.
That's not been washed yet.
Subtitle | www.movieddl.me
Uh, we are... here.
Shit!
Thought I was the blind one.
Oh, shut up, Piper.
Smells like Mum's garden used to.
We're not here for long, Pipe.
Come on.
- Hello?
- Come in!
- What?
- The door's open!
Just let yourselves in.
♪ Can't you help me see ♪
Excuse the music!
Whoo!
♪ Loving every minute ♪
♪ 'Cause you make me feel so alive ♪
♪ Alive ♪
♪ Loving every minute ♪
♪ 'Cause you make me feel so... ♪
Oh, here you are!
Oh, my God.
- Look at yo use! Look at you!
- Say hi.
Oh, gorgeous. Come in!
Oh, welcome to your new home!
Mi casa, your casa!
- I'm Laura and you're...
- Hi.
- Piper?
- Yeah.
And ...
- Andy.
- That's right.
Hey, you know what we need?
A photo. Yeah? Shall we get a photo?
- Yeah?
- I think so. I'd love that.
- Smile.
- Here. Yeah. Yeah.
Aah!
Hey, that's great.
That's lovely.
Look at that.
Oh, someone...
needs to meet Pompom.
- Oh, who's Pompom?
- That's my dog.
Yeah.
Come here.
He's a bit shy.
He's stuffed, Pipe.
Yeah, no, he's dead.
I know I'm a weirdo.
Row-row, Piper! Row-row, Andy!
Hi, Pompom.
There's a house cat
around here somewhere.
Junkman.
Haven't stuffed him. Yet.
But I will do.
Where's your cane, love?
Oh, I don't like using it.
Oh, how come?
Uh, don't want people
treating me different.
How do they treat you different?
People start to baby me, so...
Oh, yeah, no.
People can be judgmental.
But you know what my nan used to say?
"Fuck off, you fat fucking fuckers."
She did!
She was always swearing. I never swear.
I loved her.
Is this for Piper?
Oh, no.
My daughter's blind.
Oh, is she here?
No, she's passed.
Sorry.
No, it's all right. You didn't know.
- It's not your fault.
- How'd she die?
- Piper!
- She's okay.
She drowned.
Oh, who's calling?
Oh, it's Wendy.
She is so needy.
- Hello, Wendy?
- The kids get in?
- Yeah, no, they just arrived.
- You know the drill.
Yeah, no, all good. Yep.
Make yourselves at home. Wendy says hi.
- Hi, Wendy.
- Yeah?
Okay.
- Does she have a backyard?
- It's a bit inconvenient.
- She does have a backyard.
- Don't worry.
Do you wanna see it?
That's all right.
Oh, bloody hell.
Oh, if you're going outside,
don't let the cat out.
Oh, fuck.
- Idiot.
- Piper!
Right, wait here.
LAURA. Yeah, no.
Oliver! Excuse me.
Oliver! No.
Give me the cat. Give me the cat.
Let him go.
Got you. I got you.
- Let him go, Ollie.
- Andy.
- Careful.
- I got ya.
What's happening?
Um...
The cat got in the pool.
Laura's sorting it out, though.
I think her kid's...
holding it.
Yep.
Yeah.
It's your new sister and brother, Oliver.
Piper and Anthony.
Andy.
Handy Andy.
Oliver lost his family,
just like you guys.
Needed someone that could
give him special care.
You're done, darling.
Oliver?
Oliver.
Yep, quick as you can, darling.
Good lad.
Here you are.
Oliver's been mute, selectively mute
since we lost Cathy.
So we try not to overwhelm him.
Isn't that right, darling?
Taking one step at a time, aren't we, hmm?
Okay, you're done.
It's your turn.
Quite tall, aren't you?
What's he look like, Andy?
Oh, he's cute.
He's smiling at you.
- What color's his hair?
- Red.
Yeah, and curly too.
He's a beautiful boy.
There we go.
Good girl. And there's a wall
on your right.
And straight down to your bedroom.
Just watch out for this step, Pipe.
Yep, old news, Andy.
- Okay.
- Straight ahead, love.
There you are.
It's Cathy's room.
You okay, Pipe?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Grapefruit.
I'm all good, Andy.
Yep, sorry, uh, your room's in there.
It's just up there.
- Okay.
- Okay, great.
Fuck.
Not much of a room.
Oh, no, no, it's fine.
Wendy tells me you're applying
for guardianship. That right?
Yes, yeah, in, uh, three months.
When I'm 18.
I'm supposed to report
how safe and reliable you are.
So stay safe.
Stay reliable, yeah?
Yes.
Oh, girlfriend?
Oh, no.
Boyfriend?
Just a friend.
So what are you talking about?
Nothing.
Your dad?
- No.
- Hey.
Hey, I'm a counselor.
People pay to talk to me, you know.
Oh. That... That's cool.
So you don't have
to be so defensive, Andy.
Am I ... Am I being defensive?
Oh, come on, look at you.
Arms crossed.
Clutching onto your phone
to tell me you want me to go.
Hey,
I think I can hear you guys.
Can you hear me?
Yeah! Yeah, um...
- Yeah, yeah, you okay?
- Yep!
- She all right?
- You need anything?
Yeah, uh, a better brother?
Okay.
Hey.
Laura! Get off my phone!
What are you doing?
Sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
- No, I'm... Uh, I'm sorry.
No, you're all right. It's my bad.
I just don't like people
going through my stuff.
Absolutely, it's just you had a message.
I didn't mean to yell.
Cool.
So Oliver's a fucking weirdo, is he?
No.
Oh.
Excuse me.
Oh, fuck.
Wait in your room.
Up you get!
Ugh.
Oh, you ...
Dad.
I wanna come too.
Andy!
No, please!
Please!
Hey, Ollie.
We're going out for a little bit.
You'll be all right?
Good.
What's he look like?
♪ We were swimming out so far this time ♪
He looks good.
Grapefruit.
He looks good, Pipe.
♪ Pretty intimate so far ♪
♪ So I ♪
Goodbye, Dad.
Thank you.
- Sorry for your loss.
- Thank you.
Andy, sorry.
Mm.
Andy, I can't let you do this.
What?
Leave without saying goodbye.
Okay? It's the last time
you'll be able to look at him.
You didn't look at him?
You said he looked good.
Pipe.
I said, "Grapefruit."
I didn't want to see him like that, Pipe.
It's better than
how you saw him last.
Look, some people believe
the spirit stays in the body
for months after death.
If that's true, then he's still in there.
You see?
He's so peaceful.
Yep.
You should kiss him goodbye.
No.
Kiss your father, Andy.
It's a custom.
There we go.
His lips.
Yeah. It's custom.
- It's not.
- It is, darling.
It is.
Let me help you.
Come on.
- I can't.
- It's okay, it's okay.
- I can't do that.
- It's okay, I've got you.
I've got you.
Yeah?
Don't worry, you're in good hands.
Oh, come on, it doesn't
have to be like this.
Seriously, a funeral isn't
supposed to be all misery.
It's supposed to be a celebration.
Let's have some fun, huh?
Piper, what do you do for fun, eh?
Kick Andy in the balls.
Yes!
What about you, Andy?
What do you like to do?
Huh?
I don't know. Get hammered.
Hammered? Okay.
Well, let's get hammered.
This one?
♪ Now, listen ♪
So, the game is called Odds On.
You've got to pick a number
between one and ten.
- Yep.
- You got one?
Seven.
Well, no, you're not meant
to say it out loud yet.
- Oh!
- Yeah, keep it in your head.
Now, on the count of three,
you do say it out loud ...
and then if I guess your number,
- you have to drink.
- Got it.
Piper, hit us with the countdown.
Mm-hm. Three, two, one.
Seven.
- Why'd you say it again?
- Bloody cheater!
- All right, it doesn't matter.
- That was so stupid.
- I can take a shot.
- Okay.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Oh, no!
All right, I'm sorry.
All right, Piper, Odds On.
- Really?
- Yeah!
With the whiskey?
Say four.
Three, two, one...
Four!
Oh, calm down, muscles,
it's just one drink.
One little drink.
All right, but you're not
going to like it, Piper,
- I'm telling you.
- We'll see.
Do you like it? Yeah?
Oh, it's good, right?
Oh, that's disgusting, you drink that!
Yeah, I'm more of a vodka slut, eh?
You go for it. I hate vodka.
One for Dad.
- Yeah, okay.
- Hm.
- Piper?
- Yes.
All right, but last one.
First one.
Cheers.
Piper, come on, I need back up!
- I need back up, Piper!
- Come on!
- Piper, get over here!
- This is it!
- Yeah!
♪ Tell me ♪
♪ Where the freaks at ♪
♪ Freaks at, freaks at ♪
♪ Tell me
Where the freaks at ♪
Okay.
Oh, my God!
- Bedtime, young lady. Yes!
- No!
- What's next?
- Andy, play Dad's song!
- Yeah, play Dad's song!
- Oh!
♪ What about me? ♪
♪ It isn't fair ♪
♪ I've had enough
Now I want my share ♪
♪ Can't you see? ♪
♪ I wanna live ♪
♪ But you just take more ♪
♪ What about me? ♪
Piper, sing it!
No! Sing it properly!
Sing it!
Sing it, Piper!
- You've still got one left.
- Yeah.
Whoops!
Thank you for today, Laura.
It's okay, Andy.
I've been through it.
Don't you want to talk about him?
Yeah, but it's...
- I don't know, it's hard.
- Well ...
we don't have to look at each other.
Yeah, you can...
ask me something.
You can ask me anything.
How did you, um...
How did you cope...
with Cathy being gone?
Oh.
I didn't.
When we buried her, I, um...
I didn't want to leave...
'cause it felt like I was abandoning her.
You know?
Mmm.
How could I go home without my daughter?
How could I sleep in a bed
when she was in the ground?
I used to stay at the cemetery for days...
just so I could feel close to her.
Yeah.
I'd give anything to hear her
call me Mum one more time.
Just one more time.
That's all.
You know, we'd only, uh ...
we'd only ever talk if it was about Piper.
Because she was the favorite, huh?
Yeah, how could she not be?
Is that why you hit her?
- Who told you that?
- Oh.
Wendy.
Were you jealous of her?
When my... When my dad ...
married her mum...
...it felt like he finally found the family...
he actually wanted.
I used to get in trouble at school
just so that he'd notice me
and he... he hated me for it.
He'd turn on the shower
so Piper couldn't hear and he'd ...
He used to hit me so hard ...
I'd wake up and...
I wouldn't even know where I was.
That's awful, Andy.
And you know what?
He never touched her...
once.
You awake?
Andy?
I know you're hungry.
You just have to wait a bit longer, okay?
Are you in there?
Is this part of it?
Did I do it right?
How can I believe you're in there
if I can't see you?
Oh, fuck!
- Oh.
- Andy!
- Is that dirty?
- Morning, Andy!
I'm putting a wash on before we head out.
- No, I'll come back.
- I'm not wasting water, Andy.
- No...
- Let's see what you've got.
Andy's hungover!
- You going out?
- Yeah, girl shopping.
- Sorry, just the two of us.
- Yeah, no boys allowed.
- Oh, keep Ollie in his room.
- Mm-hm.
He's mucking around
and doing my head right in.
Yep.
Oh.
Piss.
I don't know what... what happened.
Andy, seriously?
Hey.
Why don't you try and take a shower?
Okay.
Um...
- Sorry.
- You're all right?
Oh, your brother's
not very well, I don't think.
I'm quite concerned.
Became quite aggressive last night.
I'll tell you about it in the car.
She lock you in, Ollie?
You hungry?
How long you been like this,
mute, or whatever?
You wanna write?
I think you should, actually.
So then, uh ... then I can ...
then I can talk to you.
And you can talk to me.
Okay, well, Ollie, this fruit is not free.
It's gonna cost you some writing.
There we go.
Here.
Careful. Just take the fruit, Ollie.
Okay, I'm gonna get you a plate.
I don't want Laura yelling at me...
...for making a mess.
Ollie!
Ollie! Ollie!
Hey, hey! Ollie, Ollie, Ollie!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Fuck! Fuck!
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Hey, come on! Ollie! Ollie!
What are you doing?
We need to go to the hospital, okay?
Come on, just follow me. It's okay.
Just come on! Ollie! Come on!
Shit!
Hey, look at me.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Hey, hey. Hey!
Fuck, Ollie! Hey, hey, hey.
Breathe, breathe, breathe!
Ollie.
Help me.
What's going on?
Why is he outside? No, no, no, no!
Get away! Get away!
Why is he outside?
Get your sister inside now!
- Piper, come inside.
- Andy. Andy!
- Piper!
- What the heck is going on?
- Just take her inside now!
- He hurt himself.
- What?
- Why is he outside?
Andy, what happened?
What did you ... Andy!
Why is Laura screaming?
Do I call an ambulance?
Piper, no!
I can fix this!
It's okay, it's okay.
Shh, it's all right.
You're okay. You're okay.
Andy, we can help you.
Laura wants to get you help.
What?
You're all right.
Where am I?
Who are you?
- What?
- What do you want?
- Shh!
- Please! No!
It's all right, Ollie, it's all right!
Let's get you bandaged up!
You're all right. Shh!
It's okay. It's okay,
it's okay. It's okay.
Help!
You're all right!
No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's all right! No, no, no, no, no!
Stay. Stay!
You're all right, love. You're all right!
No, no, no, no, no.
You're all right. You're all right.
You're okay.
You're okay now! Shh! You're okay.
Shhh.
Laura?
There we go.
Is Oliver okay?
You're all right.
Laura?
Hey, Laura!
- Laura?
- Laura!
He said he needs help.
Should we take him to a hospital or...
So you broke into my room?
Respect my fucking privacy!
Come on, love. You're all right.
Please don't be too mad at him.
Will he be okay?
Yeah, he'll be fine.
Got to him just in time.
Is he sick?
He'll be all right now.
It's Junkman I'm worried about.
Think your brother let him out.
Junkman!
Rain.
She'll die in the rain.
Dad.
Nice deep breaths.
Focus on the light. That's it.
Just breathe
normally. That's it.
Two...
Now, this time,
I want you to push on my hands
with your feet as hard as you can, mate.
What...
What's that sound?
I need ... I need to go home.
- I need to go home!
- Hey, hey. No, mate.
Hey, hey, it's all right.
- She's...
- Nurse, nurse!
- She's gonna die!
- Nurse!
- Yep, yep.
- My sister's gonna die!
- Hey, hey.
- Fuck. Give me the fuckin'...
- Get off me! Get off me!
- Andy.
- Andy!
- Calm down.
Message: Laura said
you don't want visitors.
Hope you're okay. Miss you.
Miss you less than three...
- Laura?
- Hey.
I'm worried about Andy.
I couldn't sleep.
Me neither.
Come in, love.
Follow my voice? Straight ahead.
I've got you.
Sit here.
You all right?
- Oh.
- You're upset.
Yeah, it's the rain. Cathy loved it.
The sound, the smell.
That her on the T.V.?
Yeah, that's her.
- Can we keep watching?
- Yeah, sure.
The first
cat-witch ever to swim.
You're okay, you're okay.
Can you describe her?
She's 12 here.
Long brown hair.
Freckles.
God, she's beautiful.
-Here, look at your ears!
- Oh!
I'm sorry.
Look at my new earrings
Mum bought me.
It's all right.
Thank you.
Yeah, ah, Ollie? Ollie! Ollie!
-Yeah?
- Get her cane.
-Okay, Aunty Laura.
- Thank you.
- Hey, Andy.
- Mm?
Handy Andy.
Mmm.
- Hey.
- Where's... Where's Piper?
She's at home with Ollie. It's okay.
Look, they need to keep you in
for another day.
You have a concussion.
You just need to rest.
What?
Yeah, they need to check
your brain isn't leaking or something.
Where... Where's Piper?
Where...
It's okay.
Yeah?
Shh. Shh.
Oh.
Brought you a present.
Piper got you this.
Your body spray.
You can't let her out, Laura.
- What's that, love?
- You can't let Piper out,
not while it's raining.
Something could happen.
Like what?
I saw my dad in the shower.
He said something.
What'd he say?
Andy?
He said, "She'll die in the rain."
You don't think it's 'cause your dad died
in the shower when I killed him?
What?
Your dad died in the shower.
What...
You're associating rain with that.
What is happening to me?
Hey, don't worry.
I'll keep her inside.
I'll keep her inside, I promise.
I promise.
You can take it.
It's just water!
Cathy? Cathy!
I'm filming you!
Piper!
I want to show you something.
This was Cathy's favorite.
Oh!
You like it?
Uh-huh. Thanks, Laura.
Hey, you can call me Mum, if you like.
Um, maybe.
Hey.
She always used to...
wear her hair back like this.
She didn't want her hair
sticking to her face
or getting in her mouth.
There you are.
Hey, you like living here with me?
Yeah.
Yeah, you're really nice.
You think you like it enough
that when Andy turns 18
you maybe want to stay?
Stay here when Andy goes?
Yeah.
I was...
I was looking forward
to getting our own place.
But we'd still visit you on weekends.
Okay.
Who's that?
It's just Ollie.
Hi.
Not just yet, my darling.
I want to show you something else.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
This way.
That's it, straight ahead.
Oh, it's cold.
Yeah, it's a freezer, love.
Feels crusty.
What is that?
Oh, my God, what is it?
Just meat.
This is unbelievable!
You had a psychotic break
and they just let you go?
Piper's worried, too.
It's honestly dangerous.
God forbid something happens.
What are you doing in there, Andy?
Bit creepy, isn't it?
It's only when you've just woken up.
Enough to hold the soul.
Well, here he is.
Anything you want to say?
Huh?
Show him, love.
Oh, Piper, what happened?
Huh? What happened?
Someone hit me.
- You hit her?
- Don't be ridiculous.
So Ollie hit her?
I put her to bed and then
you went into her room.
Didn't you?
Huh?
You can't even remember.
Piper.
Who did this?
I don't know.
But I smelt you.
You're abusive, Andy.
Just like your dad.
He hit you, so you hit her.
What do you mean, Dad hit him?
Yeah, he abused Andy.
That's why he didn't save him.
That's not true.
- He hit you?
- No, he didn't.
I've tried to help you, Andy, but I can't.
You've butchered Oliver's mouth.
You've been seeing your dead dad.
I hate to think what you've
done with Junkman.
Stop, Laura.
You're the only one strong enough
- to leave that kind of mark.
- Laura, stop.
You take those steroids
or hormones or whatever.
It's creatine.
Well, your testosterone is out of control!
Laura, you'd better
fucking stop right now.
Or what? You're gonna hit me too?
Please guys, enough.
Andy?
The fuck happened to Ollie?
- The fuck happened to him?
- Andy.
Andy, no.
No, no. Andy, look at me.
- Hey!
- Laura, what's happening?
- Give me that! Give me that!
- Laura!
No!
- Wait, what's going on?
- Get off me!
- Andy, what did you do?
- He attacked me!
She's hurt, Andy!
She's not fucking hurt!
Come on, we're leaving now.
- You're dangerous.
- Fuck off!
I'm not gonna let you hurt her again.
- I have to protect her.
- Oh, what,
like you protected Cathy?
Get off!
What the fuck do you fucking ...
No!
- You fucking ...
- Come on, then.
Fucking what? What?
Andy, stop!
Please, Andy, stop.
Please.
Come on, Pipe, we're going.
Grapefruit, Pipe.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. Shh.
Fuck me.
You're okay, love.
You're all right.
You're okay.
Yes, I got you. I got you, darling.
I need to see Wendy, now.
It's urgent.
Um, if you take a seat,
I'll let her know you're here.
All right, let's go.
Grab your bag.
I don't really feel like playing.
Oh, it'll be good to let off some steam.
Come on. Here's your bag.
That's it.
I could be a few hours, darling.
Call the cops.
Laura told me...
you hit your sister and attacked her.
Oh, she's fucking lying!
She's full of shit, Wendy, I swear.
You've been wetting the bed?
Oh!
Would you say your grief
over Dad is getting better
or worse?
It's not about my fucking Dad!
Laura kidnapped a fucking child.
I mean, did you do
any fucking checks on her
before you sent us there?
How do you even know who the fuck she is?
'Cause she worked here
for nearly 20 years.
She was the best counselor we had.
And believe me, love,
she would never hurt a child.
Ollie.
No.
Not yet.
Ollie, it's me.
It's me. No!
No, Ollie, stop!
Ollie!
Get off! Get off!
Get back! Get back!
Get away! Go away!
No!
Get back!
Get away! Go away!
She calls him Oliver.
That's her nephew's name,
the red-haired kid.
Yeah, but he doesn't
have red hair. It's him!
- Who are you calling?
- Laura.
No, Wendy. No.
She might hurt Piper.
Let me take you there. Please.
- Quiet, please!
- Quiet, please.
Play!
I'm sorry, Pipe.
I know you think
that Dad was great, but he...
He hurt me bad.
But only when you were asleep,
or when you weren't home.
You couldn't see how much he hated me.
And I lied because...
because I didn't want you to know
how ugly the world was.
And when I was eight...
uh, I hit you.
And I regret it more than anything, Pipe.
I'd never do it again.
But I just need you to understand that
that bruise on your face
right now, that wasn't...
wasn't me.
It was her.
She's bad, Pipe. She's hateful.
And just like Dad, she's not
gonna let you see it.
I didn't tell you then
but I'm telling you now, Pipe.
There's something wrong with Laura.
She kidnapped Oliver,
and you're in danger.
You're probably not fucking
listening to this, but...
I love you, Pipe.
Grapefruit.
Don't worry,
I'm gonna sort this all out.
Fuck.
Play!
- How's my ball taste?
- Piper, relax.
Wait in the car.
Why?
You are this close to getting
a restraining order.
- All right?
- Fuck!
- Shit!
- Laura!
- Yep, coming!
- It's Wendy.
- Laura!
- All right!
- Hi, love.
- Hi.
So he's brought you, has he?
Yeah, he's been saying stuff.
I've gotta check it out, love.
Yeah, I know.
- You know the drill.
- I do.
- Excuse the mess.
- Oh, don't worry about it.
Yeah.
Oh, there's no one in there, Wendy.
- I just had a shower, so...
- Okay.
- Kids' rooms are this way.
I told her she could have it
any way she wanted,
but she loves this.
Lucky, the kid's blind.
- What's that?
- Oh, nothing. It's lovely.
- Want to see Andy's room?
- Yeah.
Does the weights when he's angry.
Not that it's helped.
Oh, sheets are dry for a change.
- Ready?
- Um...
Can you have a look at this for a sec?
This is the kid that Andy's
been banging on about.
You seen him?
Ollie?
So, I'm guessing you want him out.
Oh, hate to split 'em up
but you know, I've got
to think of Piper now.
Don't worry, we'll take care of him.
Oh, cheers, Wendy.
I just hope he gets better, you know.
I'm sorry for interrupting your shower.
Oh, no, no, no, it's all good.
You're all right.
You're bleeding.
Are you okay?
Wendy!
Don't.
- Please, Wendy. Don't.
- Laura?
Don't... Don't go out there.
- I'm doing something.
- What are you ...
I'm doing something for Cathy.
We're good friends, aren't we?
How long have we known each other now?
It's okay, love. Let go.
It's Cathy.
- We can bring her back.
- What?
- Wendy!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Where are you?
- No, shh!
- Listen, listen, listen.
- What have you done?
- Listen. Listen!
Piper... needs to go...
- the same way Cathy did.
- Jesus.
We always used to fill the hole...
- Let go.
- ...with rain.
- Wendy!
- Let me go, love.
I didn't think it would work,
- but it's working.
- It's okay.
- It's working!
- Let me go.
He's gonna bring her back!
- He's gonna bring her back!
Let me go!
- Let me fucking go!
- I don't have anyone.
What the fuck?
...fucking pullover. Let me go!
Hey! You need to come outside!
Now!
- Here.
- What's going ...?
Oh, shit! Go!
- Fuck, go!
- Run!
- Let me get in the car!
- Come on!
Lock the door. Jesus!
Andy.
You're okay.
Shh, it's okay.
You're okay. Shh, shh, shh.
You're okay.
Righto, darl, let's go.
You ready to go? Come on.
- What's wrong?
- Hey, Piper. Come on.
You're all right. Thank you.
Bye, Piper.
- Bye.
- Did I leave my phone at home?
- I didn't notice.
- Are you Laura?
- Yeah.
Laura, hi, we spoke on the phone earlier.
I wanted to ask you about Piper's eye.
Yeah, no...
- Yeah, what happened?
- Not now, all right?
Have you heard from Andy?
In you go. Quick.
In you go, love.
Whose phone is that?
Mine. Changed the ringtone.
- You like it?
- Oh, can you call mine?
Yeah.
Piper.
Andy?
♪ How did I get my face ♪
♪ To look so wonderfully divine ♪
♪ Why do I appear so picture-perfect ♪
♪ All the time ♪
Piper.
Andy?
Why are you in here?
Can you smell that?
Piper...
Andy?
Hey.
What are you doing in here, love?
I heard Andy.
Oh, no, he's down here.
He's come to apologize.
Come on.
Who is this?
It's just Ollie.
- But I heard...
- Come on, love.
I'll take you to Andy, come on.
I got you.
He'll be fine.
Ollie'll be fine. This way.
Just, um, this way.
What color's Ollie's hair?
Red. Thick and curly.
Why?
Hey.
You okay?
Where you going, love?
Piper! No!
Piper, what's wrong?
Come on.
Open the door, sweetheart, come on.
Don't be silly now, come on.
What's wrong? Huh?
Piper.
Piper, open the door, love.
Come on, don't be silly.
Open the door.
No.
No, Andy!
Andy, come on.
Grapefruit. Please!
Come on, Andy!
Get up, grape...
Grapefruit!
Andy!
Please!
I'm sorry.
Hey.
What's wrong, love?
What happened to Andy?
He had an accident.
Listen.
I've got to tell you a secret.
Something I've been scared to say
because I didn't want to frighten you.
I've spoken with an Angel.
It's a beautiful Angel.
It does beautiful things.
I've put him inside Ollie.
And now...
he's going to put Cathy inside you.
Because you're just like her.
Just as incredible...
and just as perfect.
What are you going to do to me?
I'm going to drown you
in the pool now, love.
Don't!
- Please let me do this!
- No, stop, please!
Let me do this!
Please, Piper, please!
No!
More rain!
Hold on. Hold on.
Please hold on!
No! No!
Mum!
Mum.
Oh, no!
Piper!
I'm so sorry!
Are you okay?
Where did you come from?
Cathy.
Cathy?
Sweetheart?
Hey.
Hey, gorgeous.
There you are.
Are you all right?
Here we go.
Stop!
You're probably not
fucking listening to this, but...
I love you, Pipe.
Grapefruit.
Hey, guys! Over here!
There's a boy!
We're here to help, mate.
We're here to help.
Get a blanket!
- Hey.
- Kira, call ambo.
- Help me.
- Hey, it's okay.
Request ambulance, we've got a 117.
It's okay.
Can you tell us your name?
I'm...
I'm Connor.
Connor Bird.
So brave. Connor, hey, hold onto me.
Hold on to me. It's not
going to be long, okay?