"THERE IS A BRIDGE CALLED SIRÁT
THAT LINKS HEAVEN AND HELL".
"THOSE WHO CROSS IT ARE WARNED"
"THAT ITS PASSAGE IS NARROWER
THAN A STRAND OF HAIR,"
"SHARPER THAN A SWORD".
All right.
Here we go.
Come on.
Careful.
Let's go.
Thanks.
Try to fit it in.
Okay, easy now.
Hello.
Thanks a lot.
Come on.
If you see...
You think she's here in Morocco.
We think, yes.
- Your daughter?
- Yes.
- Your sister?
I'm sorry.
- We'll look. I keep the paper.
- Take the...
- Okay.
- Keep it with you.
Good luck.
The number is this number.
- Thank you.
Give it to me.
I’ll keep going for a bit, okay?
Sure?
Get some rest.
Esteban, what are you doing, kid?
What’s going on?
What?
I followed you.
I was looking for you.
Come on, let's go.
I’ll ask them.
Hello.
You know this girl?
You can speak Spanish if you want.
She’s my daughter.
It's been five months
since we heard from her.
We were told we might be able
to find her here, at this festival.
Have you seen her?
Her name is Mar.
Doesn’t ring a bell, sorry.
No?
Do you know her?
I don’t know her at all.
Look,
there’s another do in the desert.
Another do?
When this ends, there’s another.
She might be there.
Are you going?
To that do?
Maybe. Dunno. We’re not sure.
Perhaps.
Beat it! Get lost!
We have orders to evacuate this place.
As of now there's a state of emergency.
All Europeans are ordered
to get into the vans.
This is a restricted area as of now.
Please!
Come on, please!
Please, it's for your own safety.
Approach the vehicles
in an orderly fashion.
Stop! Hey, stop!
That's enough now!
We don't bother anybody!
We're only dancing!
Get out of here!
What are you doing?
That’s enough!
No.
- What’s wrong with you?
- Out of the way.
Calm down!
Where're you going, madam?
- Just for a wee.
- What did I say?
Get lost!
It's all right, be cool.
What? You're going to shoot me
for taking a piss?
You're just a kid.
Get in the van.
Take it easy.
- Get in the van.
- Take it easy.
Isn’t that the girl from before?
Get going, please.
The one going to the do.
All right, drive!
Let's get out of here! Come on, hurry!
Please!
Go, dad!
- Come on!
- Follow them! Dad!
Wait, let me think!
About what? Drive!
Go on, Dad, drive!
Excuse me! Sir!
Wow, fantastic!
Wow!
We've done it!
It's all right, they're coming.
Let's go!
Very good!
Come on!
Are you following us?
What?
Well... Uh...
Yes. We want to go
to the do you’re heading to.
Not a good idea, as you know.
We want to find my daughter.
She might be there.
What does he want?
He's looking for his daughter.
He wants to follow us.
Follow us? Is this a joke?
The car won’t make it.
It’s all we got.
I don’t see it, man.
The paths are treacherous.
You'd best stay away.
Please, we have to.
Shit.
Fuck, they want to follow us.
I don’t think you understand
what you’re in for.
It's the desert.
What if there's trouble?
Right. We’ll follow you anyway.
We have no choice.
You do. You could turn back.
Please, let us come.
We have to find her.
explosions in various cities
through the country.
Attacks are ongoing
on at least four fronts.
Last night, war broke out.
The military airport was attacked.
There are clouds of smoke.
The situation is extremely chaotic.
Bombings have been reported both
in the east and the west of the country.
Endless lines of civilians head
for the borders. Nobody is any longer...
This is crazy.
Things must be getting out of hand.
Let’s keep going.
It’s impossible here.
Come on!
Let's hope there’s petrol
at the next one.
Inshallah.
It won't do. It's not enough money.
- This isn't enough.
- No.
You'll have to pay more.
- Help us please.
- It's very expensive.
- It's steep.
- Yeah.
I get it, but otherwise
it's not worth it for us.
What you have here
is only enough for one can.
- One can?
- Yes, one.
No! We need three.
But it's not enough for three.
No, keep the money.
We’re screwed.
- No...
- They want more money...
- How much?
- Don’t know.
I’ve got...
Here.
I’ve got this, look.
- Is this okay?
- Come on, Afaque.
- Three hundred.
- Offer it to them.
Don't say anything. Give me the money.
I think it's enough with this.
Is it now?
All right?
All right, very well.
Thanks.
- You're welcome. Come on.
- Thanks, many thanks.
Come, give me a hand.
Thanks.
Should we start filling them?
What’s your name?
Luis.
Will this get us there?
I don’t think so.
Is it that far?
That’s life.
Leave it here, Luis.
Give me a hand.
Like that. Okay, now can you put...
Look, grab it there.
That’s it. Not that one.
This one?
There. That’s it.
That goes there. Hook it.
I asked for more photos of the daughter.
Let's see.
She looks a lot like Esteban.
She looks sad.
A little, yeah.
- The door?
- The door’s there. It’s this.
- It should line up with the van.
- Sure.
Okay. It's this one. Got it. This one.
Can you picture them in the desert?
I was thinking...
- What?
- Yesterday,
you snored louder than Pipa did.
Both of you snored.
- Yeah.
- Really?
You snored super loud.
I was out like a log.
Both of us.
You both snored.
You were like a duet, you know?
- A musical duet?
- You went...
With you, we were a trio, right?
I didn’t.
Me, if I get going,
our friends in the bus
wouldn't sleep all night.
- Let’s see.
- You’ll break it.
- It's touching the ground, it won't do.
- Calm down. We’ll see.
Hey, stop!
Did you see the road up ahead?
- Did you see how steep it is?
- What do you want me to do?
Tell me! What do I do?
Calm down, Luis.
I'll fix it for your car. Hang on.
Now it'll work.
Step on it.
Go, Luis, okay? Come on, easy does it.
Out of the way.
It's happened to me before.
And your stupid mohawk?
Don't you like it?
Isn't it pretty? Isn't it cute?
- Hideous.
- You don't like it?
It's sweaty.
- Take it off.
- I will.
- It's nice.
- Your sheep mohawk.
Fuck. I see your tan line.
- Here. There's a tan line?
- Just there.
- A pathetic punk.
- Shit.
All right, sweetie?
Looks like a hyena.
She's a punk star.
Our little hyena.
If only she could sing.
Hey!
Where do I cross?
I’ll check further up. Or what do I do?
To cross here?
- You drive, Steff.
- Come on, Lu.
Bigui, let’s go.
Hey!
They’re leaving!
Fuck!
I knew it!
They ditched us!
Fuck, I’m such an idiot!
What do we do now?
This makes no sense.
We shouldn’t have come.
What do we do?
The thing is...
How do we get out of here?
We're lost.
- But really...
- Dad.
They’re over there.
Hey, Luis!
It was hard to turn around.
What, can't you swim?
Hello!
Keep going.
Go, go!
Go, go, go!
There you go.
Esteban!
Esteban, come here.
Give me a hand.
Pipa.
Come here.
Any dessert?
Maybe. Pick a hand.
- That one.
- Hop!
Nice, an orange!
Tac! This one’s mine.
Hand it over.
For you.
What’s wrong now?
Do you want the orange?
- No, it’s all yours.
- What then?
We could share with them.
The chocolate?
Yeah.
Nope.
We don't have a lot of supplies.
But you always tell me not to be stingy.
It’s not about being stingy,
it’s about being prepared.
But we can still give them a little.
Esteban,
it's going to be a long trip, you know?
We’ll need it.
All right, but let's be nice.
They gave us some food.
Sometimes you're a real pain.
Good evening.
- Evening.
- This is for you.
Okay. Can you put it on the table?
I mean, in the kitchen.
Come on in.
- What's that?
- Sit down for a bit.
All right.
This one blew out at the do.
When that happens, they just toss them.
But I love how it sounds.
I recycle everything.
They all sound equally noisy to me.
All of them.
All right. Have a look.
It's never the same sound, see?
You never know
if this is the last sound it produces.
You can't hear anything.
What?
You can't hear anything!
Sure. You don't listen to it.
You dance to it.
My daughter says the same.
What?
I said, my daughter says the same.
Have you been looking long?
I'm sure she's fine.
Pipa?
Pipa!
She isn't here either.
- Pipa!
- Hey!
I found her!
- Jade, bring some milk!
- Pipa. What happened?
- Pipa.
- Are you okay?
- Where was she?
Pipa, wake up. Pipa.
- Pipa, love.
- Pipa.
- Easy, calm down.
- Pipa! Pipa, sweetheart.
- Pipa.
- Pipa, wake up.
- What's the matter?
- Let's see.
- Pipa, please. Pipa.
- Pipa.
- She smells of poo.
- What does that mean?
- Pipa.
- What happened?
- She probably ate poo with LSD.
Whatever, mate.
- Poo with LSD?
- Pipa.
She ate Bigui's shit.
Pipa.
How would you know that it was mine?
I know 'cause I shat
in my truck last night, mate.
Drop it!
- I'll give her some milk.
- I'm sure it's yours.
- It could even have been Josh.
- There, very good.
Stop lying! You had a shit last night.
Bury it at least
or put a stone over it.
Pipa, easy.
Right. You shit
in your truck in the desert?
Stop lying, Bigui.
You know it was yours.
Bury it next time. You never do that.
You think you are the Desert Queen.
This is nuts.
- And you call me a liar.
- That's what you are.
I swear it wasn't me.
I swear I didn't shit in the desert.
Will you shut your gob, please?
Take it easy, Pipa.
- Pipa, easy.
- There, very good.
Wake up, Pipa.
This happens a lot, okay?
She'll be fine.
- She's just sleeping.
- Yes.
She's taking a siesta.
Yes, easy. Stay calm.
Let her rest a little.
- Poor Pipa.
- There.
She'll be fine.
We are witnessing
a moment of great confusion.
The nations are aligning
with either of the sides.
The latest events will have an impact
on the world as we know it.
With me is the representative
of the NATO Secretary-General,
Mr Schulz. Hello.
Mr Schulz, is there still hope
at this critical stage?
What a bastard!
Yeah!
Come on!
You daft bugger.
- Come on!
- Come on, Bigui!
You bastard!
Come back!
What's up, Tonin?
- You also wanna play, don't cha?
- Attack!
- Did birdie take flight?
- Don't mess with Bigui!
Enough. It's going to get bumpy!
Motherfucker!
They want to play.
Come on.
They're so cool.
Pipa!
Do you have any siblings?
Yes. Tonin, Jade, Josh and Steffi.
But don't you miss your old family?
Not a lot.
I like my current family better.
I think it's very beautiful
that you look for her.
You mean Mar?
Yeah. Why did she run away?
She didn't run away.
Mar is an adult. She left.
I think she'll be happy
when she sees us.
Hello, dear friends!
I have a song for you.
Dear Mr President
I wrote a letter to you
Perhaps you'll read it
If you have the time
I've just been called up
To go to war
By Wednesday evening
Dear Mr President
I don't want to go
I'm not here on earth
To kill poor people
I'll have to...
Oh shit.
I don't say this to upset you
I have to tell you
My mind's made up
I'm going to desert
It'll look tight.
Where's the do?
In the south, close to Mauritania.
I like Mauritania.
- Why?
- Because of the seals.
Seals, in Mauritania?
All they got is camels.
No, they have seals.
They're called monk seals.
Only very few are left.
I came to ask if I can have some petrol.
Are you out?
I have a quarter tank left,
but I'd rather have some now.
Do you drive with the air con on?
No.
How about food and water?
All right.
We've still got some reserves.
It wouldn't be bad
if you made them communal.
Communal?
We keep all the food in the 911.
Bring yours. We'll have a common pot.
Come on, Luis.
They're not transporting civilians now.
What are they doing?
No idea, but it doesn't look good.
I'd stay on the mountain road.
We'll be less exposed.
We just passed this place.
Check, check, check.
Now we're taking this road.
All right.
But wouldn't it be easier
if we drove through those gorges?
No idea. We're southbound either way.
So, has World War III broken out?
Is this
what the end of the world feels like?
No idea what it feels like, Bigui,
but the end of the world
started long ago.
Careful, Josh!
Hold on!
Step on the gas!
Shit!
Are you all right?
What happened?
No idea. Have a look outside.
I think I fell into a sinkhole.
I can't see a thing, mate.
Fuck!
I know nothing about this stuff.
Have you seen this?
Hey, don't laugh.
Try it with this.
- There's only one on this.
- It's all I have.
Let's see.
- Enough?
- Yeah, a bit more.
Pipa.
Esteban!
Don't go that close.
Get back to the car!
Wait in the car.
Jade, pass the hammer, please.
It's here, here.
Where is it? Look, it's here.
Come on, straight, straight ahead.
Go! Keep coming, hit the gas!
More gas!
Come on!
Go! Come on!
A little more. We're almost there.
Tough, eh?
Fuck!
Dad!
- Esteban!
- Dad!
- Esteban, pull the brake!
- Esteban!
- Dad!
- Luis!
- Esteban!
Esteban!
- No way, no!
- Luis!
Esteban!
- Esteban!
- Luis!
No!
Luis.
We have to go down!
We have to go down to get him!
We can't go down, Luis.
- Let me see him!
- You can't.
- We have to get him!
- We can't go down!
- Let me see him!
- No, all right?
- We'll get help.
- Let me see him.
- Let go...
- Not too close, Luis.
Luis...
Let's go.
What are we doing here?
No! Fuck!
We can't do anything.
I saw him down there, totally crushed.
We have to get help, Jade.
He was down there.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Who's going to tell him?
I can't.
What is this place?
There're cars here.
Anyone here?
Hello!
Hey!
Fuck!
Anybody?
Salam alaikum!
- Help!
- We need help!
We need help, please!
Anybody? Is there anyone there?
We need help.
There's some left.
Look. Luis.
When he's comes out of shock,
it'll be grim.
Hey, sir!
Salam alaikum, sir!
Brother, wait!
We need help.
Help.
Please help us.
Easy.
Help us. Wait!
Brother. Please, friend.
Hey, wait!
Don't be afraid.
Wait, brother!
We need to find a village!
What about Luis?
Someone has to show up who can help us.
Nothing but dust here.
It'll do us some good.
It's a good plant.
It'll help us.
Go on, turn it up till it explodes!
Up till it explodes!
Jade!
No!
- No!
- Jade!
- Hey!
- Tonin!
- No!
- Jade!
- Tonin, no!
- No!
Fuck!
What the fuck was that?
We are in a minefield!
Jesus, I'm so high.
I can't think straight.
We're here, Bigui.
There, Bigui, there.
I keep seeing Tonin exploding
in my head.
I've always wanted
to go out in a blaze of glory,
but that...
Hey.
Do you know
what my father said before he died?
What?
"Fuck, it's getting serious."
I couldn't say goodbye to my father.
Jade said,
"Make everything explode."
Typical Jade.
"Pull the brake".
"Pull the brake"
are the last words Esteban heard.
Tonin saw Esteban's body
when he looked over the edge.
We didn't know how to tell you.
I don't want him to stay there.
No idea how we didn't explode earlier.
It must be full of mines here.
We have to reach that mountain.
No mines in the rocks.
Shit.
Let's go!
Not that way!
Go the other way! The other way, fuck!
Follow the truck's path.
No.
Steff?
It's all that's left.
Doesn't matter now.
How many meters to the rock?
Sixty?
Eighty.
Luis!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Luis!
- I'm coming, Luis.
- Bigui!
You can do it, Bigui.
Luis!
Bigui!
Nearly there, Luis!
No. No!
No!
No.
Bigui!
How did you get across?
Bigui followed your steps.
But he exploded.
How? How does this work?
I don't know.
I crossed without thinking.
Like this...
Come on, Josh.
We're going with closed eyes.