Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
GIRL: Mommy is...
stretchable.
WOMAN: What do you mean
by stretchable?
GIRL: Daddy's hard.
You can't move him.
He gets mad, and that's it.
Mommy gets mad too,
but she's more like putty.
WOMAN: Mm.
- (SCOFFS LIGHTLY)
- And she gets sad too.
That's when it's
the most stretch.
WOMAN: Putty, um... I wonder
how is it that you stretch her?
GIRL: You just--
Can I...
Can I talk now? Please?
WOMAN: Um...
- Is it okay if Mommy talks?
- Yep.
WOMAN: Okay.
I'm not stretchable.
I'm not putty.
WOMAN: Well, that's her
experience of you.
That isn't true.
I try very hard to be in
control of her and everything,
but, um, may as well not even
be there at all.
WOMAN: Well, perception
is reality, so--
Also, I don't get sad.
WOMAN: You seem sad right now.
GIRL:
You do seem sad right now.
We're here to talk about
how to get you better.
All we do is talk about me.
I can be sad. I mean,
I'm allowed to be sad, right?
WOMAN: Well, of course.
(CHUCKLES)
But, um, you must know that
this is all tangled up together
and you of all people
should know--
I know. I know, but, um...
this...
this isn't how things...
(VOICE SHAKING)
...are gonna get better. Um...
GIRL (VOICE WAVERING):
Mommy, please don't cry...
No, no. I--
- ...because then I'll cry.
- WOMAN: Sweetie.
- She...
- Sweetie, it's okay. It's okay.
(CLEARS THROAT)
We want the tube removed. Now.
- GIRL: No, you can't kill me!
- And to do that, we need...
No, she won't do what
she has to do
because she knows
that she has this safety net.
WOMAN: Things are not
stable enough right now to--
It's clear that we have
different goals.
You want her to get better
before the tube can be removed.
I think the tube needs
to come out,
and then she can get better.
WOMAN: We all have
the same goal here.
(DRY CHUCKLE)
WOMAN: But what I'm learning
as we're talking all together
is that you and I need to spend
some time, just the two of us,
without her here...
...to talk about some
serious issues.
(LOW, RUMBLING HUM)
(MUFFLED) I'm gonna need you to
restart the tube feedings
at night
and I need you
to start doing...
- (VOICE FADES)
- (RUMBLING BUILDS)
GIRL: Did you get the kind
with no cheese?
I can't explain this to you
every time, sweetie.
They would just laugh at me
and say it's bread, okay?
I'll take the cheese off
when we get home, of course.
GIRL:
Is it the kind with the little
green and black things
in the sauce?
It's the same kind
we always get.
That kind has the things
in the sauce.
I can't... I can't eat it.
Like, can you scrape it off--
Do you even want the tube out or
is it just me who wants it out?
You have to be...
(GIRL GASPS)
LINDA: Jesus.
(GIRL GIGGLING)
LINDA: Oh, poo.
- Oh...
- (GIRL GIGGLING)
- You got your wish. No cheese.
- (LAUGHING)
- Did you will that to happen?
- Yeah.
Are you some kind of
witch or something?
(GIRL LAUGHING)
Hey, straight to the table.
Actually, no.
Wash hands first,
and then straight to the table.
I don't have to go
to the bathroom though.
No one's making you
go to the bathroom.
I'm just asking you
to wash your hands, please,
like we always do.
GIRL: Is Daddy coming?
Where's Daddy?
LINDA: Uh, he said
maybe bedtime.
GIRL: When does he go again?
(CHEWING) He just got back,
so... in a month?
GIRL: Mommy?
Yeah.
I did have to
go to the bathroom.
LINDA: Okay.
GIRL: This might take a while.
(SIGHS)
(CHAIR DRAGGING)
(SIGHING)
GIRL (FAINTLY): Mommy?
(CHEWING) Yeah?
GIRL: The bathroom
has water in it.
Okay, well, that's good.
No, I mean on the floor.
Come quickly!
GIRL: Are you coming?
- (WATER SPLASHING)
- Mommy!
Oh, my God. What?
Why didn't you tell me
as soon as you came in here?
I just noticed...
because I had to go
to the bathroom so bad.
(WHINING) I don't like how it
feels on my socks.
Where's it coming from?
How deep is it?
Are we gonna die?
Is the house gonna
fall on top of us?
Mommy?
Can you lift me up
and carry me out?
LINDA: Yep, just
stay there, okay? Hold on.
Mom, why are you leaving me?
Where are you going?
Just please stay on the toilet, okay?
No.
(WATER GUSHING)
- GIRL: Can you please come...
- (MUFFLED EXCLAMATION)
GIRL: Can you come now?
(MUFFLED) Oh, my...
- (WATER POURING)
- (GIRL CONTINUES, INDISTINCT)
Oh...
...my fucking God.
Mommy!
Mommy, you're not
telling me what it is!
Mommy!
- What's going on?
- What?
What's happening, Mom?
Are we gonna die?
(LINE RINGING)
- DAD: Hey.
- Hey, yeah.
We just got home,
and you would not believe--
(SHRIEKING)
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
(YELPS)
- (GIRL SCREAMING)
- No, no, no! Do not come here.
Do not come in here!
Right now, go, go, go!
Right now! Right now!
(SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Go, go, go, go!
Go! Oh, my God!
(CONTINUES SHOUTING FAINTLY)
(SPLASHING FADES,
GROWING MUFFLED)
(FADES TO LOW RUMBLE)
(LOW, CREAKING RUMBLE)
(RUMBLING CONTINUES)
(CHILDREN SHOUTING FAINTLY)
LINDA: Nothing is familiar
or real.
Ever.
Every time I feel this way
I get further and further away
from being in myself, and,
like, I can never get back.
MAN: When you think about time,
how do you see it?
LINDA: How do I see time?
Um...
Time is a series of things
to get through.
Each goal is a cliff.
There's nothing
at the end of it,
but then it comes,
and there's just another cliff.
GIRL: I'm so mad at you!
(SHRIEKS ANGRILY)
(RHYTHMIC BEEPING)
(SNORES LIGHTLY)
(GROANS)
- (BEEPING CONTINUES)
- (MACHINERY CLICKING)
- (BEEPING STOPS)
- (MACHINE WHIRS)
(CLICKING CONTINUES)
(BEEPING, WHIRRING
CONTINUE OVER MONITOR)
(VEHICLE PASSING)
(GIRL MOANING SLEEPILY
OVER MONITOR)
("HOT FREAKS" BY GUIDED BY
VOICES PLAYING OVER SPEAKER)
(MOANS LIGHTLY)
(GIRL MOANS FAINTLY)
(EXHALES)
(THUNDER RUMBLES FAINTLY)
(EXHALING)
- (ASH SIZZLES)
- (GASPS)
Oh, shit.
MAN: Yo, you know about
holotropic breathing?
WOMAN: Mm-mm.
MAN: Yo, this shit is lit.
Basically, you trick your brain
into thinking it's dead,
and you see
the fucking universe.
You know what I'm saying?
So you won't feel paranoia
and guilt if something's wrong.
(SONG CONTINUES OVER SPEAKERS)
WOMAN: I've got a friend who
does Reiki and shit like that.
MAN: Nah, see what I'm saying?
This is like hyperventilating.
When you die, they say
you let off this chemical.
And when you're dreaming,
you let off the same chemical.
It's sort of like that,
you know?
You make your brain
think it's dead,
but being brain-dead
is still alive.
- WOMAN: Holographic breathwork?
- Holotropic.
WOMAN: Tropic. Holotropic.
- Is that real?
- What?
- The... the dead brain thing?
- Oh, yeah.
I mean, shit.
I guess anything could be real.
I mean, anything
could be bullshit too.
(CHUCKLING)
You know what I'm saying?
(LAUGHS WEAKLY)
But you know that feeling
like when you're not...
Yeah.
Oh, you're making fun of me.
- Miss, I don't even know you.
- Right.
Okay. Um, yes on these,
but no on the wine.
Why?
The law prohibits me from
selling you this wine right now.
But it isn't even 2:00.
It's 1:58.
Right, but--
By the time I ring these up,
it will be past two.
Huh. Um...
I'll just get
the peanut butter cups.
You can put them on my room.
Will do.
(BEEPING, WHIRRING
OVER MONITOR)
(LOCK BEEPS)
(SWITCHES OFF MONITOR)
(BEEPING CONTINUES
FROM OTHER ROOM)
(WATER RUNNING)
LINDA: I can't talk
about this anymore.
I'm telling you. Please.
DAD: Hey, hey. Look, if that's
what Dr. Spring thinks is best,
then we have to listen
to Dr. Spring.
There is no "we" though.
It's just me. I... I'm...
- It's not fair. I'm telling you.
- Whoa!
Fair? Listen,
I'm working, all right?
I'm dealing with a lot of
assholes. You have no idea.
And I cannot do anything about
what's going on there
from here.
We need to be a team.
You have to go there today
and check in and let them know
- that this whole thing is not--
- I know. I know.
The problem with that logic,
though,
is that I'm not a housewife.
- I work too.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Mommy,
this hotel food is gross.
- MAN: Good morning.
- This is disgusting.
Wow.
You guys look just like twins.
Anybody ever tell you that?
Uh, no.
You're the first person
to notice and/or say that.
(CHUCKLES)
- (SIGHS)
- GIRL: Everyone says that.
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
- Hey, cutie. Wanna see a trick?
- GIRL: Yeah.
GIRL: Whoa. How'd you do that?
Mommy?
You should take it.
She's never gonna eat it.
(PHONE CONTINUES BUZZING)
Okay.
GIRL: Am I gonna throw up now?
- Yeah?
- DAD: You hung up on me.
Look, I know you have
a lot on your plate,
but she's getting better,
and the rest of it
is totally temporary.
The ceiling will get fixed,
I promise.
The sky is not falling.
None of this is your fault.
- I love you.
- I'm sorry. I love you too.
What's so bad about
a hotel anyway?
And while you're there,
take advantage of the pool.
They got a pool, right?
You always said you wish
you had a pool,
so now you have one.
Why don't you go? You can
do some laps, lounge a little.
Get a floatie. Kick back,
get a couple of margarita...
Okay.
GIRL: Did you know that you can
train hamsters to love you?
No.
You can train them to love you.
Well, I would love if you would
finish your bacon.
That way I can tell everybody
you got 100% on breakfast.
And once they love you, you can
get them to do everything
including tricks.
Let's start with one bite.
LINDA AND GIRL: ♪ Ring, ding
Ring-a-ring-a-ling-dang ♪
♪ Ring-a-ling-a-ding-dang-do ♪
♪ Ring, ling
Ring-a-ling-a-ding-dang... ♪
♪ Keeps him from lovin' you ♪
(MIMICS DOG BARKING IN SONG)
(GIRL BARKS, LAUGHS)
(BOTH SINGING
NONSENSE SYLLABLES)
GIRL: Is the parking guy gonna
get mad again?
Double-park! Double-park!
Double-park!
- Okay.
- (HANDBRAKE CLICKS)
Gotta be fast. You know
what happened last time.
(FAINT CHATTER)
You've missed the last few weeks
of family sessions.
Yeah.
I told you what happened.
Our entire ceiling fell down,
and with all that chaos,
and we're living out
of the hotel--
So we need to schedule something
as soon as possible
to talk about her goals
and the treatment process.
Yeah. Yeah, okay. Yeah.
Duh. (FORCED CHUCKLE)
Yeah.
- Mm-hm.
Oh, you meant now?
Okay. All right.
Um...
Well, uh, let me look
at my schedule.
I should probably do that...
I know that you already
know this,
but you can't start letting
feelings of guilt and control
about this illness
and treatment affect you.
It's no one's fault.
That's right.
That's what I keep hearing.
Also, I really need you to
start taking care of yourself.
Right. Yes.
No.
Put my oxygen mask on first.
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
I'm just gonna have
to get blunt here.
So she needs to reach her
weight goal in the next week.
If she does that,
then we can put tube removal
and discharge dates
on the books
but if she doesn't do that,
I'm gonna have to reassess
the level of care
because obviously something
is not working here,
and this is what
I need to talk to you about.
When can we sit down properly?
Yeah, fine. Uh, September 7th.
It's September 15th.
September 20.
I mean, September...
(HORN BLARING)
MAN: Hey!
(HORN HONKING)
Hey! I told you not to do that,
and the next time
I will report you
to the building.
You have no authority
to report me.
You won't be allowed in the lot.
I'll have you towed!
Oh, sure! Call them!
I'm not in there long enough
- for them to even come!
- (ATTENDANT SHOUTING)
Whatever!
Asshole.
LINDA: The apartment is
a 30-minute walk,
but it might as well be on Mars.
And I just, I can't...
Every time I go check,
it looks worse,
and I... I have no control.
THERAPIST: Have you tried
discussing a compromise
with your landlord?
Perhaps they could section off
the room with the hole,
then you could live freely
in the rest of the apartment.
Live freely with asbestos
and 100-year-old dust
and black mold spores?
(CHUCKLING) That's your advice?
It's not advice.
It's a question to consider.
I should really show
you this hole.
It's an entire nightmare
on my ceiling.
When does Charles return?
This is week three of eight.
I mean, you should know that.
Don't you write things down?
It's your job to remember
the boring details
of my fucking life.
We do have to stop now.
We are out of time.
I have another
patient coming, so...
Wait, now?
What about the
ten-minute warning?
Yeah, I just wasn't
paying attention.
You didn't respond to the email
that I sent you about my dream.
I don't respond
to my client's dream emails.
Okay. So, if you
don't bring it up,
then what is the point?
Okay. Uh, you got me.
I had a dream, and I need
to talk about it today,
and I didn't get any time
because you didn't
give me a warning.
We can discuss the dream
you emailed next session.
Well, it's actually
a different dream.
- Well, I don't really--
- About you.
- Okay, quickly.
- Okay.
I was in a hospital day room
or a recreation room
or something,
and I knew my daughter
was also in the hospital
but... but far away,
another part,
and it didn't look like
the hospital
she was in last year, though,
when everything happened.
It was different. It was weird.
And I was waiting for Charles
to come get me,
so we could pick her up
but instead, you were there,
and you wanted to sit
really close to me.
(CLEARS THROAT LIGHTLY)
And I was, like, inching away
from you on the bench
- and you kept inching closer.
- (SIGHS DEEPLY)
And I got my phone
out to text Charles
'cause I was nervous he'd
come in and he'd see
and then you tried
to grab the phone
and then you started
to tickle me...
(CHUCKLING LIGHTLY)
...to try to get me to drop it,
and I was, like... (CHUCKLES)
I was really enjoying it,
but I was so scared that Charles
would come in and he would see.
- (CHUCKLING)
- (GROANS LIGHTLY)
All right.
Okay?
All right. You got to tell me.
We'll talk about it next time.
THERAPIST: Okay?
(GROANS) We won't
talk about it next time.
You know that.
There's no thread.
There's no thread at all.
(EXHALES LIGHTLY)
(MUFFLED PHONE BUZZING)
Yes? (CLEARS THROAT)
What now?
MAN (IN ACCENT):
Hi, yes. So sorry.
Have to leave. Stop work.
Uh, what?
Mother died. I have to leave.
Work is going to take longer.
Uh, okay, uh, just--
(WHISPERING)
I'll be one second.
Okay, what is the issue then?
Can you tell me?
This has been going on
for so long.
Do I need to get
a new contractor?
It spread.
Uh, it's full. It's very full,
you understand? Very full.
It spread?
Not easy to explain.
Not my language.
¡Yo hablo español! Explícame
en tu idioma, ¡lo entenderé!
Sorry, but I don't
understand those words.
How long will you be grieving
for your mother?
I don't say. I don't know.
I can't say.
Look, I need a date, okay?
It needs to be fixed.
Just give me a date. My husband
and I will be returning to--
I'll be back, one week.
Okay, well, fine.
I'm going to be going there
and checking on
what you have done so far,
and I'm going to be
taking pictures, and I--
(CALL CLICKS OFF)
(NOISELESS SCREAM)
Vete a la mierda, el cabrón.
(SETS DOWN PHONE)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
I can see you now.
I'm really happy to hold this
silent space for you but...
...as usual, I am curious as to
what you might be
thinking about.
Riley.
That's all I can think about.
Tell me what's going on.
Well, I...
I keep telling you, it's--
It's like I keep saying
to his doctor, he--
He doesn't smile. He--
He looks at me weirdly,
and he's just very
uncomfortable all of the time,
and... and no one will do
anything about it.
You know what I would love
and what I think would be
extremely helpful
is if you could come
to a session without Riley.
I think it would be...
- I know you think you can't--
- No, I can't.
But I think if you got a sitter
who you trusted, who you could--
Did you hear about that nanny
in New York?
The mom came home from work,
and the nanny had stabbed
both of her kids to death
in the bathtub.
That is real. That happened.
A situation like that is
very, very, very unusual, okay?
Most people have caregivers
- who can trust that...
- I can't. (GROANS LIGHTLY)
Well, I... I believe you can.
I just think you don't want to
or you're afraid
so let's stick
to some practical--
I need to protect him.
From something specific?
Because something
very bad is happening.
(PHONE BUZZES)
I'm so... Can I just--
One second. I just have to...
This could be about my daughter.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
Um...
Yeah. Look, look, I--
I'm not Riley's doctor
so I can't speak to what may
or may not be going on with him.
We can only talk
about your feelings
about what you perceive
is going on with Riley,
which is why I do believe
medication can be--
I'm not perceiving it.
It is happening.
And I feel awful about it.
Okay, listen.
When you're having
these feelings of deep panic
at home with Riley,
just put him in his crib or
carrier or somewhere safe...
...and draw a bath.
Just breathe until your
heart isn't racing anymore,
come out and get dressed,
start the day over again...
...put on some real clothes.
These feelings that
you're experiencing
they are...
they're very, very, very scary.
Okay? And very dark.
And that's why
you need to keep moving.
You need to keep going.
You need to be busy.
You can't sit inside the fear
and doubt
and scariness.
Breathwork is a deep healing
in the nervous system,
where we hold trauma
and trapped emotions.
We can't talk our way
out of trauma.
The body needs to process
unprocessed emotions
within the body.
And this is why breathwork
is so powerful.
If you're looking for deeper
ways of healing
and you're searching
for alternatives,
don't wait any longer.
Let's connect and schedule
your first breathwork session.
REPORTER: Directly before the
judge read Ortega her sentence,
she begged for forgiveness
for her unspeakable crime.
She stated she was sorry
for what the judge had called,
"Pure evil."
She then spoke about how
untreated mental illness...
- (RAPID KNOCKING AT DOOR)
- Fuck.
- The judge was not convinced.
- Shit.
She will be serving life
in prison
with no possibility of parole,
saying that--
(STOPS VIDEO)
(CLEARS THROAT)
You would not believe
what I have been through today.
Okay, so, I don't
know if you recall
but there was this pair of
absolutely davoon-ianca,
davoon, gorge leather gloves
that I saw on The RealReal.
I wake up this morning, banned.
Banned. Yeah. I know.
CHARLES (OVER PHONE):
Hey, my love!
So you been keeping up
and eating,
and doing all the right things?
GIRL: Yeah, I ate
some cheese today!
- LINDA: Mmm.
- CHARLES: Cheese!
That's fantastic.
I love cheese!
- Daddy, can I get a hamster?
- No.
I already told you,
you're not getting a hamster.
No, no. You know what,
let's see, okay?
Maybe when we get
back to the apartment...
No, no, no, no, no.
She's not getting a hamster.
Daddy,
when are you coming home?
She's not getting a hamster.
What, where are you?
I can hear something weird.
Oh. Yeah, that.
I'm catching a game.
- A game?
- Yeah.
Yeah, we got here this morning,
and there's a
minor league team here
on the island where we go.
It's a little loud, so...
Oh, it must be nice, huh,
doing things for yourself.
- What's that like?
- Hey, hey, hey.
You wanna switch places?
You don't know
what I'm dealing with here.
All right,
I'll go sit on my ass...
- GIRL: Daddy!
- ...all day in therapy...
I'm sorry. Ha-ha.
I mean, "sit on my butt"
listening to people whine,
and you can captain this fu--
Uh... this stupid boat, okay?
Listen, I'm allowed
to do things on my time off.
- Jesus Christ!
- Time off? Oh, okay, um...
Daddy has to go now,
and, uh, we have to drive,
- so say goodbye to Daddy, okay?
- No. I don't have to go!
- Look, they're in the middle...
- Jesus.
I told you, it's a rodent,
and just something
to look after for no reason.
Please, please don't ask again,
and don't ask Daddy things
I already say no to.
But Mommy, it's not fair!
(MACHINE BEEPS, WHIRRING)
LINDA: Dr. Spring said this
is a big week.
- Did she tell you that?
- GIRL: Yeah.
LINDA: I think you can do it.
GIRL: But I'm already doing
it my best.
LINDA: I know, but you have
to do a little better
then we can
get rid of this thing,
and everything will be okay.
GIRL: I'll be better.
Okay. Well...
...it's not up to me.
It's up to you.
What book can I read
you tonight?
GIRL: I'm too tired.
Just a song.
LINDA: Okay, what song?
- The dead whale one.
- Okay.
♪ Sit beside
The breakfast table ♪
♪ Think about your troubles ♪
BOTH: ♪ Pour yourselves
A cup of tea ♪
♪ Think about the bubbles ♪
♪ You can take your teardrops ♪
♪ And drop 'em in a teacup ♪
♪ Take 'em down
To the riverside ♪
♪ And throw them
Over the side ♪
♪ To be swept up by a current ♪
♪ Then taken to the ocean ♪
♪ To be swallowed by
Some fishes ♪
♪ Who were eaten by
♪ And swallowed by a whale ♪
♪ Who grew so old ♪
♪ He decomposed ♪
I don't mean to say
we're all robots,
but I wonder
if you had been raised
the way your mother
had been raised.
I mean, she had a father
who just took off,
didn't come home.
Then another man
entered her mother's life,
and she became attached to him,
and he bailed out.
WOMAN:
I know what you're saying.
I did have that same one.
Very similar.
DONAHUE: But...
Okay, well, my question is
if you had been raised
as your mother had been raised
do you think
you probably would've
knocked your kids around too?
WOMAN: See how many
you catch in your mouth.
WOMAN 2: Okay.
- Okay, open.
- (BOTH LAUGH)
WOMAN (WHISPERING): Wait. Shh.
Fuck.
This fucking drunk bitch...
Put this on my room, please.
It's definitely before 2:00.
(BEEPING OVER MONITOR)
I'm gonna need to see
your ID, ma'am.
You've never asked
me that before.
Ma'am, I'm gonna need
to see your ID.
(LAUGHS)
You really want me to go
all the way back up to my room,
get my ID, and come
all the way back down here?
It's the rule. Aren't you only
on the second floor anyway?
When is this the fucking rule?
I have been in here
every single night...
Maybe I cracked open
the rulebook
and found some shit out.
Well, maybe you should
find my ID that's behind...
MAN: Ladies, ladies, ladies...
- It's the rule, ma'am!
- MAN: Ladies!
- Ladies!
- I'm not going back!
- Ladies, whoa, whoa!
- (BOTH YELLING)
- Ladies, calm it down, bro.
- WOMAN: I'm fuckin' chill.
It's not that deep.
WOMAN:
She fucking barking at me.
Just use my ID for it.
- I can't do that.
- MAN: Why not?
I can't use your ID
for her wine.
Well then it's my wine,
she's just paying for it.
She fucking took it.
MAN: Hey!
(FAINT MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKER)
What?
The name's Jamie, by the way.
Got a light?
(SIGHS) I'm not interested.
- In what?
- I need to be alone.
Rude as hell.
A motherfucking thank you
would've been nice, miss.
(BOTTLE CLATTERING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES FAINTLY)
(BEEPING OVER MONITOR)
(MONITOR SIGNAL FADING)
(SIGNAL CRACKLES, FADING OUT)
I'm, uh, at the hotel.
I'm outside just getting
some fresh air.
CHARLES: I don't like it when
you leave her there by herself,
even for a second.
It isn't safe.
I'm just outside for a minute
getting some air.
The windows don't
open in there. (LAUGHS)
To stop everyone from killing
themselves, obviously.
All right. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
but what if she wakes up
and she's scared or--
Well, she never wakes up,
and anyway,
I have someone at the hotel now.
- A babysitter.
- Really?
Where'd you find a babysitter?
Who is it?
His name's James.
His name is James?
He's a male babysitter?
Did you call just to call
me a bad mother, or what?
You have no idea what it's like
not to be able to go outside
even for a minute, by yourself.
You can go outside
whenever you want to.
You can go
wherever you want to.
The machine
doesn't fucking stop...
and there's nothing to do in--
Hey, I am over here
working my ass off!
Oh, my God! Who is the one who
went to a baseball game today
and who is the one who filled
her bag with gloop 500 times,
saw patients, picked her up,
had to do dinner where
she only got 20 percent,
and then had to
try to convince--
Can we please
not do this?
Look, I gotta go.
The reception's really bad here.
Everything's fine.
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
Did you go to the apart--
- (SCOFFS)
- (LINE CLICKS)
Yes. Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
- (PHONE BEEPS)
- Here are pics of hole.
Forgot to send today.
- I went during lunch.
- (PHONE BEEPS)
(STAMMERS) What is movie...
...babies, zombies,
'80s, mothers eating babies?
FEMALE PHONE VOICE:
Here's what I found.
A court has reopened...
- (LOUD CRASH)
- (BREAKING GLASS)
...nine-week-old baby really
was taken and killed by a dingo
24 years after Meryl Streep
portrayed the Australian mother
wrongly jailed
for killing her child.
Chamberlain has
always insisted...
(GLASS CRUNCHING UNDERFOOT)
What?
(WHISPERS) Mom?
(WHISPERS) Hello?
- (LOUD BLARING TONE)
- (CRYING OUT)
- (TONE STOPS)
- (PANTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CHILDREN CHATTERING FAINTLY)
(VOICES SWIRLING, OVERLAPPING)
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
(CHILDREN CHATTERING, YELLING)
WOMAN:
Wake up, Mom. Wake up. Okay.
- (LINDA BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (FAINT LAUGHTER)
WOMAN: Mom. Mom. You hear us?
(FAINT, ECHOING)
Come on, Mom. Snap out of it.
("CANDY SHOP" BY
JAE RAE PLAYING ON RADIO)
GIRL: ♪ If you wanna know this
If you wanna know that ♪
♪ Come to my sugar shack ♪
Hey. Hey, you know
what would be super fun
and like a really, really
big kid type of thing to do?
GIRL: I can't hear you.
I said, you know
what would be super fun
and a big kid
type of thing to do?
GIRL: What?
If I drop you
in front of the door
and you just go in by yourself.
Oh, my God.
- That would be so cool of you.
- No.
- Why not?
- All the moms walk you in.
You're a mom. You have to walk
me in. You have to sign me in.
Eva! Eva!
Can you walk her in today?
Please, please, please?
- I cannot deal with the parking.
- (HORN HONKS)
Of course. No problem.
- No problem.
- Thank you.
Okay. Exciting news.
Guess what? Guess what?
Eva will walk you in!
Go, go, go.
ATTENDANT: Let's go!
- Mommy, Addie scares me.
- Come on.
She only eats Nutella.
I need you!
- To be with you!
- Honey, please. For Mama, okay?
- Please? Please?
- You are my mom.
We'll go look at hamsters
today if you do it.
"Look" at them?
I'll get you one, okay?
Just go. Go!
(DELIGHTED SQUEAL)
Okay, see? I love you!
I love you, okay?
Everything's gonna be...
Shit.
- Hi.
- GIRL: Hi.
- Shit! Shit! Shit!
- (HORNS BLARING)
I'm the worst.
I'm the fucking worst!
And then you told me
that if you touch a baby bird,
the mama bird will not come back
if they know you touched them.
Hm. That must have been
some dream.
- Do you--
- I'm not done.
You kissed me.
I said, you kissed me.
Yes. I heard you.
In your dream, I kissed you.
Yeah, and then the
next day, I felt...
...crushing guilt.
And I knew somehow
that your husband
had called me an asshole.
You know, Stephen,
we can talk about these feelings
apart from your dreams.
But...
(SIGHS SHARPLY)
I can't help it if in my dreams
you always want to kiss me.
What's the difference
between going outside on hotel
property when she's sleeping...
...and going all the way home?
In one, I guess
I'm just a regular mom
making a shitty choice,
and in the other,
I'm a... I'm a...
a straight up shitty mom.
Well, it's not my role
to decide whether you should
or whether you should not...
- That's not--
- No, no, no. I shouldn't.
I know I shouldn't.
I shouldn't even leave
her for a second.
(BITTER LAUGH)
I mean, it is your job to say.
Just tell me not to do it.
Just tell me what to do.
I don't think you want me
to tell you what to do.
You know what to do.
No one will tell me what to do.
I'm supposed to know
how to fix this.
how to fix her.
What is it you think
it's your job to fix?
She has to weigh 50 pounds
by next week, Dr. Spring said.
That's a gain of 2.5
pounds, right?
Each day's supposed to be
2,500 calories in
compensating for her resting
rate at 1,800 calories burned.
That's gotta be at least 80%
of each meal for seven days
plus the tube, and that's
if she just lays still all day.
And if it doesn't,
then something about
not getting the tube out
and reassessing
the level of care.
- What do I do?
- Tonight...
I would like you
to get a good night sleep.
So would I,
but I'm asking you a thing.
An actual thing, a problem to
fix, and I need help with this.
Am I supposed to just sit
around and watch her fail
and this is just gonna
go on forever? What do I do?
Okay. That means
there's no drinking.
There's no drugs. There's no...
Are you listening to me?!
Can you hear me?!
I'm asking you what
I'm supposed to do!
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
Why don't you like me?
(BREATH TREMBLING)
Why don't I like you?
I know you won't answer me.
Just forget it.
That is incredibly unfair.
Why is this so important to you
right now?
(SNIFFLES)
I just want someone
to tell me what to do.
No one will tell me.
GIRL (FAINTLY): I love him,
I love him, I love him.
- When we get home,
he can live a happy life there.
- (HAMSTER SQUEAKING)
(LOUDER) And we're gonna have
him forever, and ever, and ever,
and ever, and ever.
I love him. I'm gonna kiss him,
and I'm gonna hug him.
Oh, my God. Maybe
his name should be S'mores.
That's really nice.
I said, don't open the box.
I just wanna see him.
He's been scratching.
He doesn't like being
in the box.
He's trying to get out.
Can you hold it closed, please?
And keep it closed.
He's scratching me!
He's supposed to love me.
Close the box.
- I can't.
- (SCREECHING)
Mommy, he's getting out.
Just hand it to me.
Hand it to me.
He's gonna jump out.
- He hates us.
- Give it to me. I can't see.
- Give it to me.
- (HAMSTER SQUEAKING)
GIRL: I think we got
the wrong hamster.
Shit.
- Ow! Shit.
- (GIRL CRYING)
- We're gonna die.
- No, we're not gonna die,
but I have to pull over.
Ow! Shit!
- Maybe this isn't S'mores.
- Oh, my God.
- It's out. It's out! Shit. Shit.
- Oh, my...
Mommy. Oh, my God. It's out.
Why aren't you
putting that back in?
- Just put it back in.
- (HANDBRAKE CLICKS)
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
Please! Put him back in!
I don't want it.
I don't want him anymore.
- He's bad.
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
- (CAR CRUNCHING)
- (GIRL SCREAMING)
- Okay. Okay, hey, hey, hey.
- (GIRL BREATHING HEAVILY)
You're fine.
You're fine, and I'm fine, okay?
Nobody is hurt.
- Let's...
- (UNSNAPS SEATBELT)
GIRL: Take it with you!
Take it with you!
- I'll be right back.
- It's gonna hurt me!
I hate my hamster!
- Hey, man. What are you doing?
- Hey, hey, hey.
Oh. You're lucky
there's no damage.
We don't have to
exchange information.
What? My kid is in that car.
Do you hear her crying, huh?
You scared her to death,
you dick.
Hey, Mom.
It was barely just a tap.
Don't fucking call me Mommy.
She thought we were gonna die.
Don't fuck with me
about my child's safety. Huh?
- Give me all your information.
- What the fuck is that?
- What?!
- That! That!
GIRL: Mommy!
- (SHRIEKS)
- MAN: Oh.
(GIRL SCREAMS)
Mommy, what happened?!
Mommy!
LINDA (CHEWING): I love you.
I miss you. Come back here.
- (PHONE BEEPS)
- Everything is under control.
(GROANING)
GIRL: Stop.
Do you know that I love you
and I think you're the best
and so proud of you
for everything,
and you can do it,
and you're almost all better.
- You're so good.
- Mommy, stop.
What? I can't stop.
I just love you too much.
You smell like wine.
(PHONE BUZZING)
- (SNIFFS, CLEARS THROAT)
- Hello?
Hi, it's... it's Caroline.
Caroline Primm, your patient.
I'm sorry it's so late.
Um... Oh.
Is this an emergency?
Because, um,
if this is an emergency,
you need to hang up and--
It's not an emergency. I just--
I forgot to call you yesterday.
What?
Well, you told me
to take Riley for a walk
after I took a bath
and calmed down
and I did it, and I
forgot to call you--
Oh. Okay, yes. Um...
Well, uh, that's good,
and, um...
Uh, I-- I do feel though that I
should tell you that this number
is really for emergencies
only, okay?
Oh. I'm sorry. I just...
I just couldn't sleep
thinking that you were worried.
I wasn't worried.
You... You weren't?
You weren't thinking about me?
I said that you could
call me if you...
I said you could call me
if you couldn't calm down
not that you had to call me.
But, um...
but are you safe, Caroline?
Are you...?
I'm... I'm sorry.
I... I misunderstood.
Yeah, I'm so dumb. Um...
Yes, I'm safe.
Okay. Well, let's talk about
this in session, okay?
(VOICE SHAKING) I'm sorry.
I'm obviously bothering you.
It is not your fault, uh...
and I will--
I'll see you next week.
Well, can I come in tomorrow?
It's just waiting
until next week seems too long.
Uh, well, let me
check my schedule,
and I will text you a time, okay?
Okay. Um, I'm sor--
You've gotta be fucking
kidding me! Shit!
("LIFE'S DEBT" BY MUGSHOT
PLAYING ON RADIO)
Hello?
Hello!
Hello! Is anyone here
doing their job?
Shit.
Want some help with that?
I know a trick. Got a knife.
Sweetie?
Little Bear, open up.
It's Mommy.
JAMIE (UNDER BREATH):
What is she doing?
Whoa. Whoa, whoa.
- What the fuck's your problem?
- What? Whoa.
What, you're obsessed with me
or something?
What are you talking about?
Don't flatter yourself.
Well, why are you looking at me?
What? What do you want?
I don't want you just sitting
outside and by yourself.
Some creep might walk past
or something.
What creep?
How the fuck do I know, lady?
There's creeps
all over this place.
- Don't call me lady.
- My bad, miss.
Don't call me miss.
Don't. Just don't.
- Ma'am.
- (SCOFFS)
- Frau?
- Yeah.
- Slag.
- Oh, my God.
Your thottiness?
Housewife? (CHUCKLES)
At this point, I don't even know
what to refer to you as.
I'm gonna just call you female.
Yo, crazy pants.
I was gonna partake
in surfing the web
for some things that I'm into,
if you catch my drift, and
I'm just putting it out there,
you more than welcome to join.
No pressure. Just saying.
(MONITOR CLICKING, BEEPING)
What kind of stuff?
LINDA: Is that like
the dark web?
Like where you can
buy people and stuff?
I don't know.
Never bought a person, so...
But you could? Or sell one?
I mean, I guess so, but
I don't come on the dark web
searching for that
kind of shit, so...
Aren't there places on there
where people, like, show
each other videos of murders
and people they're
holding captive?
Can we change the subject?
Let's buy drugs.
- Let's get some...
- (PATS LEGS)
...some shit, right? Come on.
What do you want?
What are you into?
I don't know.
Do they have, like...
cocaine or something?
When was the last time
you tried cocaine?
What do you mean?
It's a very popular drug.
I like it.
All right. Well, I'm getting
molly, so we'll get both.
See, the thing is,
I don't get paid till next week,
so I need you to cover me.
Oh. Oh, I'm-- No.
No, no.
I see what this is about.
- Where you going?
- I'm going back to my room.
For what?
You don't even have a key.
Besides, your daughter's
passed out.
Front desk lady's
definitely in a coma by now.
Calm down. Come sit down.
Let's order. Jeez.
I could put it on my
credit card, I guess.
What? No.
The 400, I could put
it on my credit card.
No, no. See, man,
it can't be traced back to you.
It has to be anonymous.
Well, then how do you
pay for the stuff?
All right, what we could do is
we could go to a pharmacy
or something real quick
and put it on one of
those gift cards
or maybe you got bitcoin, or
crypto, or some shit like that?
No, I don't have
any of that stuff,
and I can't get in a car
and leave my daughter alone
in the middle of the night.
You leave your daughter alone
all the time.
No, I don't. That's just
if I go in the field.
Ha! I literally seen you leave
your daughter alone myself
with my own two eyes.
- What's the problem this time?
- What are you?
You stalking me or something?
I'm a concerned citizen.
I mean, takes a village, right?
(GIRL MOANING OVER MONITOR)
What?
Sweetie! Sweetie! It's Mommy!
- (GIRL MOANING)
- You locked me out. Sweetie!
Sweetie! Open the door!
Little Bear, open the door!
GIRL: Mommy...
Just wheel the machine over
and open the door!
Little Bear!
Open the door!
I locked myself out!
It's Mom! It's Mommy!
GIRL: Mommy?
Are you there?
I'm not sure how we can
talk about anything helpful
if you won't even look
me in the eye.
You asked me for this
extra session.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
I can't.
You must be so mad at me.
Mad? Oh, because you called me?
No, no, no. I'm not mad at you.
Let's move on. Please?
You have a daughter.
(SNIFFLING)
Why didn't you ever tell me?
Well, this isn't about me.
But now I know that you know.
You know.
(STAMMERING) I don't know.
You need to tell me.
It's not your fault.
But it is mine.
Okay, you know, Caroline I think
that it may be time that we...
um...
...that we consult with someone
about some medication for you.
Well, I can't take medication.
I'm breastfeeding.
- Do you want me to kill my baby?
- Of course not.
I just think if a doctor thinks
it could be beneficial,
then maybe we need to...
prioritize your... your...
health over breastfeeding.
Just right now.
You know, you need to take
care of yourself
so you can take care of Riley.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Um, well, we only have
15 minutes left.
I have to go now.
Okay, well, can you wait
till after the session?
No?
(SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(RILEY COOING)
(RILEY CRYING)
Oh... Oh.
Shit.
Oh. Okay, okay. Okay.
(RILEY CONTINUES CRYING)
Okay.
Caroline? Excuse me.
Caroline?
(RILEY CONTINUES CRYING)
It's okay.
Caroline? Excuse me. Caroline?
I need you
to help me out here. I...
Okay. I know. I know.
Caroline?
(RILEY CONTINUES CRYING)
Okay. Okay.
Caroline!
Yeah. I know.
What is going on here?
I'm in a session.
So, my patient,
she has this baby
and she said she was
going to the bathroom
and then she left the baby
with me and I...
- She's gone. And now I can't--
- I'm with a patient.
Please, I need your help.
I really need your help.
I'm with a patient.
Plus, also,
I'm not your supervisor.
This is a professional issue.
This is not a treatment issue.
Are you joking?
This is an emergency!
Whatever's happening in here
is not as important
as what I'm going through here!
- Okay, no.
- I need your help!
- Goodbye.
This is an emergency.
- You can come back later.
- Absolutely not.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
No!
(RILEY CRYING)
Okay.
(LINE RINGING)
- MAN: Hello?
- Hello?
Hello. Hello. Yes.
Hello, I am
your wife's psychotherapist...
Stop, I can't...
and she left today in
the middle of her appointment.
I cannot hear you.
I cannot hear you. Who is this?
Okay. Yes.
This is your wife's therapist.
She left in the middle
of her appointment today...
- All right. You gotta stop.
- And...
You gotta stop. I have no idea
what you're even talking about.
Who is this?
Is your wife named
Caroline Primm?
And you are, um...
Your baby's name is Riley?
And you are Nick Primm?
- Yes.
- Okay, yes, right. Well--
My wife doesn't have
a therapist.
Okay, well,
she has been my patient
at The Center for
Psychological Arts in Montauk
since she was about
six months pregnant
with Riley, and today...
Well, this is news to me.
Mm. Well, whether... (CHUCKLES)
...you knew that she
was my patient or not,
what I'm trying to say to you
is that this is an emergency,
and I really...
She left your baby here with me,
and I need you to come
and pick him up.
What do you mean?
What do you mean,
what do I mean?
She left the baby?
She's not answering her phone...
She's probably in the bathroom
or by a fucking
vending machine.
Okay.
I suggest that you call her.
Maybe she would pick up
if it was you.
I'm gonna text you my address
to come and get the baby.
Oh, Jesus Christ!
I'm sure she's okay.
I cannot even believe this.
I'm sure she's okay. I'm sure--
You know what? This is
so fucking typical of her.
Okay. Well, she probably
just needed some space.
I'm gonna text you
my address where...
- so you can come and get her.
- Okay, look. Listen to me.
- Him.
- Listen to me.
I'm at work right now.
I am at work right now.
That's why she's supposed to be
taking care
of the fucking baby,
- so I can work, okay?
- (RILEY CRYING)
Here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna text you my address.
I'm in Amagansett.
You can drop the baby off
at this address, okay?
Okay, well, I can't do that,
and I am actually very
concerned about your wife.
This is an emergency, and she--
You know, you've used
that term twice now.
This isn't my emergency.
I'm not the one
who lost my fucking wife!
I need you to come down here
and get your baby immediately,
and if you're not here
within a half an hour,
I'm going to call the police.
I will text you the address.
- Thank you very much.
- Oh, Jesus--
(BELL CHIMES)
- Yes?
- Hi, it's Stephen.
(DOOR LOCK BUZZES)
(RILEY QUIETS DOWN)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
May I come in?
(RILEY RESUMES CRYING)
I'm expecting a patient.
He just buzzed in.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Would you mind waiting
in my office
down the hall
just a few moments?
Your office?
Who are you, the boss?
No. Just another therapist.
I have an office.
It's down the hall.
Door is open. You'll see it.
This is my time.
She's mine right now.
You can't make me wait, okay?
This is an emergency situation.
You can either wait in my office
or you need to
leave the building entirely.
Is that a baby?
Is that your baby?
You have a baby?
I mean, do you guys
have a baby together?
Okay, this situation
does not concern you, okay?
Make a choice.
Okay, I'll be in your office.
But I won't wait that long.
(WHISPERS) Okay.
(WEAK CHUCKLE)
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
Wow.
Can you believe that
I got talked into getting
this fucking hamster
after all of that? My God, I...
(CHUCKLES)
She's right. I really am
so stretchable.
- It's disgusting.
- You know...
when I was in medical school,
I had to do a stint
in a medical experiments lab.
And we were testing
the efficacy of a drug on rats.
Oh, I... So cool.
And the way it worked is
we'd take the rats,
and we'd drop them
in this guillotine thingy,
chop their heads off
individually,
peel the skin back
and then look at their brains
under a microscope.
(EXHALES) I'm just so curious
about the process with that.
I wonder--
The rats would claw
and bite you...
...when you put your hand
in the cage to pick them up.
So they gave us
these steel chain mail gloves.
They're German.
They're beautiful.
So you put on the glove and
you put your hand in the cage,
and the rats would just
attach themselves to the glove,
clinging for dear
life, you know?
(LINDA CHUCKLES LIGHTLY)
And then when you got
to the guillotine box,
you had to shake them off.
Really shake them.
I was always worried
that the rat would get hurt
when it hit its head on the
guillotine, you know?
But their brains
were always fine
when we looked under
the microscope.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh.
Rodents are
resilient creatures.
(LAUGHS)
Mm-hm. Yeah.
I'll tell Stephen
your session's cancelled.
You have to take care
of this, okay?
I love you.
(DOOR SHUTS)
Just tell me, was she suicidal?
Homicidal?
No. Mm-mm. No.
No, she was obsessed
with protecting the baby...
And, uh, yeah.
She wouldn't hurt the baby.
And she didn't talk
about suicide.
She wouldn't abandon Riley.
She just did abandon him.
Right, well, you know,
I mean, um...
you know, permanently. Forever.
Is that it?
I have another patient waiting
who really needs my help.
It's fine. It's more common
than you think.
A woman tries to run away
from all the responsibilities.
- Yeah.
- Everybody gets all upset,
then they come back with
their tails between their legs.
Okay. Okay.
- Thank you, Officer.
- (RILEY CRYING)
PHONE MESSAGE VOICE: When
you have finished recording,
you may hang up or press one
for more options.
- (PHONE BEEPS)
- Hi. Hi,
it's, uh... it's me again,
your tenant from
22 Algonquin, unit one.
You know, the one with the giant
fucking hole in the ceiling!
Your repairs guy ran off,
and it's getting worse
and I want to know why
you're doing nothing,
and why you're happy for
my daughter and I to be staying
at a flophouse full of freaks
while I continue
to pay you rent!
And I have a very, very,
very important patient
that is a prominent lawyer,
and I am not afraid to--
(PHONE BEEPS)
Fuck!
I was after some
Visa gift cards.
Uh, what denominations
do you have?
Do you have a minute to talk
before the children come out?
- Mm-hm. Sure.
- Okay, come.
(SIGHS)
So, I've noticed that you still
haven't made the appointment
for family therapy like
we discussed the other morning.
I know. It's just been
so crazy at work.
Right. So I can't stress to you
enough how important this is.
I'm on your side here.
Yes. Yes. Yes, I understand.
We need her off the machine.
Yeah, so do I.
Okay. I'm gonna be frank.
We need her off of it as soon as
possible for her to remain here.
And to do that, she needs
to gain faster.
Okay. Well, but we have
until next week, right?
- The 50 pound goal.
- No.
The way things are going, uh,
she's not gonna make that goal.
What are you saying?
We do weigh-ins every morning.
She's not gonna make the goal.
Because the goal you set
was impossible.
We were set up to fail.
- It's unrealistic.
- No.
We're gonna have to reassess
the level of care.
What does that mean?
Well, we can discuss
it in our meeting.
You know what I would love,
and think would be so good,
is if we could get a date
on the calendar for the surgery.
A concrete goal that we can
all work towards.
It's not... it's not a surgery.
The tube removal? Well, uh...
procedure, whatever you call it.
It's not a procedure either.
Uh, when it's time to remove it,
the doctor just pulls it out.
Pull it out?
Yeah, it just slides out.
They could just...
really just pull it out?
Yeah, it's that simple.
Oh. But what happens
to the hole?
It closes up on its own.
Oh.
It's kinda like when you
get a cut on your tongue.
It wants to close up.
Oh.
Yeah?
Oh, hi. Uh, is James here?
Who are you?
I'm his neighbor.
I'm there, in that room there.
He is not here.
Oh, uh, do you know when
he'll be back?
I just have something
to give him.
Give it to me.
- I'll see he gets it.
- No, no.
I have to give it
to him myself. It's, uh...
It's of value.
Of value?
Uh, yeah. Of value.
(RHYTHMIC BREATHING)
(SHARP, RHYTHMIC BREATHS)
WOMAN ON PHONE:
Relax your body.
(LINDA CONTINUES
RHYTHMIC BREATHING)
Center in with yourself.
Right now, your only
job is to breathe.
We're in the work phase
of this...
The more you relax
your body right now...
...the easier it gets for you.
(BREATH ECHOING)
Recognize we're accessing
the body's wisdom zone.
Let your mind go.
See if you can find
your attention
within the movement
of your breath.
(VOICE GROWS CLEARER)
Start noticing
any sensation in your body...
(BREATHING CONTINUES)
...and see what catches
your interest
or your curiosity,
and hold the space
in a way you want to be held.
You'll probably notice
any intensity
builds up in your body.
That's okay.
Rather than trying
to control anything,
see if you can just allow...
the intensity to...
(SWIRLING CHAOTIC VOICES)
(GIRL SCREAMING)
WOMAN: You're not helping!
Hold her legs that way.
Hold her legs down.
(WOMAN CONTINUES, INDISTINCT)
WOMAN 2:
We might have to restrain her.
- WOMAN 3: Mom!
- WOMAN: Hold her down!
WOMAN 2: You're here
to help us, come on!
That's not helping at all.
(URGENT VOICES OVERLAPPING)
(GIRL SCREAMS)
Mommy!
WOMAN: Try to help.
Try to help.
GIRL: Mommy!
(TONE BLARES, THEN STOPS)
(GASPING FOR BREATH)
(WOMAN ON PHONE
CONTINUES, INDISTINCT)
Make yourself feel safe.
If things are getting intense,
recognize you can hold the space.
You can love yourself
right now.
(MACHINERY CLICKING,
BEEPING ALARM)
Don't avoid anything within.
Don't abandon yourself.
Stay connected to yourself.
See if you can honor yourself
in this moment
of reconnecting to yourself.
(DEVICE BEEPS, ALARM STOPS)
(WOMAN ON PHONE
BREATHING RHYTHMICALLY)
(MACHINE BEEPS STEADILY)
WOMAN ON PHONE: Use your voice
and imagine your emotion.
Allow it to be...
Maybe you can even
do it tonight.
(WHISPERING)
Down here. This way.
(EXHALING)
(WHISPERING)
It's in here. Here.
Okay, we gotta be quick because
I have to get back, but...
I just... I just had to show
someone what's going on in here.
Okay.
So, a room filled
with plastic tarp everywhere.
Nice.
So, is this your kill room?
No. Come on, I told you.
The fucking ceiling fell down.
What the fuck is that?
LINDA:
That's it. That's the hole.
That's why I'm at the hotel.
JAMIE: That's why you're
staying at the fucking hotel?
Oh, my God. Come on.
You could've slept on your couch
for a couple of weeks.
What? Look at it.
It's been two months,
and they refuse to fix it.
There's dust and...
and mold everywhere.
JAMIE: Mm.
(BLOWING)
(FAINT CRACKLING)
Yo, what is up there?
LINDA: They've been
renovating forever.
- They said a pipe burst.
- Oh, shit.
It's right there. There you go.
I did the... that... you know,
the thing, the breath thing.
What?
(WHISPERS)
And I think it took me here.
- I think maybe I...
- Oh, man...
That's why I wanted
to come to see it.
Man, you need guidance
with that shit.
You can't just be doing that.
- What are you doing?
- Man, they lied to you, sis.
It ain't even no pipes in here.
Maybe you shouldn't
get so close to it.
Shh. Look. Come see.
It's a clean break.
I'm telling you.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. What the fuck?
Man, my cousin Craig
is a general contractor.
He knows somebody
that knows somebody that can
- fix this shit in a jiffy, yo.
- Oh, my God.
It look like you got some
motherfucking debris
on your furniture.
(VOICE GROWING MUFFLED)
You know, I can reupholster it.
It's gonna cost you.
(CONTINUES, MUFFLED)
WOMAN: Let me go!
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING, INDISTINCT)
- (GIRL SCREAMS)
- (DEEP RUMBLING)
- (OVERLAPPING VOICES CONTINUE)
GIRL: Don't touch me!
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTS, CHATTER)
(INDISTINCT VOICES)
Mommy! Mommy! I don't want it!
- You are doing such a good job.
- GIRL: No!
No! Mommy!
WOMAN: You gotta hold her
a lot harder than that.
GIRL (SCREAMING): No! No!
- (PEOPLE BARKING ORDERS)
- (GIRL SCREAMING)
(WOOD SPLINTERING)
(LINDA SHRIEKS)
(JAMIE SCREAMING IN PAIN)
(MOANS)
JAMIE: What the fuck?!
Oh, shit!
Oh, fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
(PAINED BREATHING)
Fuck! Oh, fuck!
- James?
- (SHOUTING IN PAIN)
- (JAMIE PANTING)
- (GROANS)
Ah! Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck!
Oh, fuck!
- (RAPPING ON WINDOW)
- (YELPS)
(LICKING FINGERS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Everybody settle. All right?
Get started.
Hand out these, please.
Thank you.
All right.
So the topic today is something
that's so fundamental
that it's actually
a little silly to talk about.
But it is so important
to your child's recovery,
and more than that,
to your ability
to help your child recover.
Can anybody guess what it is?
Blame...
- ...and, anybody?
- WOMAN: Shame.
- DR. SPRING: Yeah, thank you.
- (SCOFFS)
(CHALK CLICKING ON BOARD)
So, as parents, a lot of times
we look too
closely at ourselves, right?
And we start to ask ourselves,
is this my fault?
Could I have done anything
differently?
What if this? What if that?
But all it does is create
a thinking trap.
(WOMAN CRYING)
And that does not
help your child.
So what I'd like to
do, if we look...
Melanie...
do you want to put some
words to your feelings?
(CRYING) Yeah.
I...
Sometimes, I just think
that it is all my fault.
(LINDA SCOFFS)
(MELANIE CRYING)
Do you have something
to say to Melanie?
(STAMMERING) No. Whoa, no.
Never mind. Don't mind me.
No, no, no. I want to hear
what you have to say.
Uh...
I just-- You keep telling us
that it isn't our fault.
- DR. SPRING: Yeah.
- Mm. But... but it is.
Excuse me?
I mean, if it isn't our fault,
then we're really super fucked.
We're just walking around
pretending
we have power
to change something
that we don't even understand
because it's not our fault,
but we know how to change it,
even though it's not our fault.
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- No, this is actually good.
This is actually good because
now we have a lot to unpack.
No, no, no. I know.
- I can't do this. I have to go.
- (MELANIE SOBBING)
- Please sit down.
- No, no, no. It's our fault.
It isn't fair,
but it is our fault.
That's how I see it. That's it.
That's what this whole
thing is, is our faults.
- Stop and sit down.
- No, no, no.
No, I don't want
to talk about it.
I already know it,
and I don't have to meet you
because I know what
you're going to say,
- which is that she's failed...
- I need you to sit down!
...and that I failed
because you set us up to fail.
No one tries hard
if they have a safety net.
- Sit down.
- Nobody, okay?
And you should know
that, Dr. Spring.
I'm gonna be here
for the rest of my life
pouring shit down that tube.
- Every night until I die.
- Do not leave that door!
And none of this is helping
any of us. None of it.
Come back!
(MELANIE SOBBING)
CHARLES (OVER PHONE): Hey!
Hey, why are you calling?
Isn't a parent group
going on right now?
LINDA: I couldn't sit there.
I'm in the car.
I'll pick her up later,
but I can't stay there.
CHARLES: What do you mean
you couldn't sit there?
LINDA: I can't do it.
I can't do it.
She's gotta get better, but
she's not gonna make the goal,
and I-- I don't know
what's gonna happen now.
CHARLES: You need
to get back in there.
LINDA:
The hole is getting bigger.
CHARLES: What hole?
Her tube hole?
- No! No, the apartment hole!
- You told me--
The goddamn hole!
Why can't you just keep tabs
on those guys?
Because the guy's gone
for a week.
There's no one working on it.
What?! A week?! When
were you gonna mention that?
I'm telling you now.
It's very complicated
to explain over the phone.
Look, look, look. No, no, no.
Just-- just
- send me pictures...
- No!
...and I'll have somebody
take care of it.
No, no, no. No more pictures.
I'm not going back there.
I'm never going back there.
And I talked to Roscoe...
- What are you talking about?
- ...and he's so full of shit.
He's not doing anything.
And by the way,
I think he has a deal with the
motel because there's another--
Okay. Stop, stop, stop, okay?
Let me just get this straight.
You aren't going into
the program anymore,
and you aren't going
into our apartment anymore?
- That's right.
- Why?
How do you expect anything
to get back to normal then?
It won't.
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
What are you talking about?!
It won't!
All right. Are you...
are you in your right mind now?
Are you done?
Also, there's a woman missing.
What? Who? What are you...
Who's missing?
My patient. She's missing.
She left and she's not picking
up her phone, and she's--
Oh, okay. Okay.
Yeah, let's take a deep breath.
- Start from the beginning.
- No, no, no.
I can't talk to you about this.
Why aren't you going
back into the group?
I'll just talk to
my therapist later. I-- This--
This is fine.
Everything's fine.
Hey, hey.
Slow down. Slow down.
Everything's fine.
How many times a week
do you see that guy?
I just looked in the bank
accounts. How often--
- Every day. Every day.
- Every day?! Come on!
- Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
- That's costing us a fortune!
No sitting idle in vehicles.
Please move the car or yourself.
I have a right to sit in my car
without you harassing me!
- What
- Yeah.
Are you talking to somebody?
Yeah,
there's this creepy asshole
who's harassing me
every fucking day!
He harasses me.
He's obsessed with me.
He's back at my window
wanting something!
What are you talking about?
Are you going to leave
the parking lot
or get out of your car!
Oh, my God! Are you serious?
- I will call the police!
- Oh, my God! Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Call the police.
- Move!
Call the police. Yeah, I'm gonna
call the police on you!
ATTENDANT: I never want
to see you here again!
Oh, my God!
You're harass--
This is harassment!
Anything in particular
keeping you silent right now?
The fact that I want to be
silent is keeping me silent.
- I think--
- This isn't about you.
What I mean is I--
I mean, I pay for your time.
(CHUCKLES)
Right? So I can do
anything I want with that time,
and right now...
I just want to lay here
without you talking.
Well, you did not have to
come here for that.
Go lie on your own couch.
Do you wish I lied on my own
couch instead of coming here?
All I'm saying is
you chose not to be alone.
(SARDONIC LAUGH)
Oh, I'm alone.
No, you're not alone. I'm here.
But no, you aren't. Not really.
- What we can do--
- Can we just not?
Seriously.
Okay.
Do you know what?
Did I ever tell you
that I was pregnant before?
Like, I've been pregnant twice.
I never tell anyone this.
It was when Charles and I
were first dating and, um...
I got an abortion
right away, like...
I took a pregnancy test
and then just went to
a random clinic the next day.
I got the surgical kind
with the vacuum thing.
And it...
hurt really badly, like...
A nurse held my hand.
And for some reason,
I didn't realize
how badly it would hurt but...
(VOICE TREMBLING)
...it really did.
Yeah, it was almost
20 years ago.
I'd have a kid in college
by now if I hadn't done that.
(SOBBING)
Maybe I got rid
of the wrong one.
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
Why won't you say anything?
I can't breathe.
You don't get it.
You don't see.
You... you love to tell me
I don't get it.
What is it you think
I don't get?
What is it you're so sure...
I can't help you with?
I'm one of those people that's
not supposed to be a mom.
I'm not a mom. I'm not.
This isn't supposed to be
what it's like.
This isn't it.
This can't be it.
Will you say something?!
Not everyone can do it.
I can't...
Do you have any kids?
Do you have a kid!?
(FURIOUS GROAN) Hello!
Why won't you talk to me?!
Why won't you help me?!
I know what you're doing...
...and I can't have it.
What am I doing?
This isn't working.
What do you mean?
We can't see
each other anymore.
I got here early.
You'll have to wait outside.
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
(MOUSE CLICKS)
CHARLES: Uh, look,
I don't know why
you aren't answering your cell,
- but Dr. Spring called and--
- (BEEP)
It's Dr. Spring.
You cannot bring your daughter
here for further treatment
- until we have--
- (BEEP)
CHARLES: (GROANS)
You are too much, you know?
- You are... I'm gonna--
- (BEEP)
MAN:
Hey, thanks for checking in.
In case you forgot,
my wife still happens
to be fucking missing.
You know, I don't know
what kind of number--
(CELL PHONE CONTINUES BUZZING)
What the fuck?
INTERVIEWER: You...
You mentioned
an aphorism from the Bible
about a millstone.
Would you say what that is?
That it's better to tie a stone
around your neck
and throw yourself into the sea
than to cause anyone
to stumble-- stumble.
INTERVIEWER: All right, let me
make sure I'm getting that.
It's better to tie a millstone
around your neck
and throw yourself in the sea
rather than to do what?
YATES: Cause someone
to stumble. Stumble.
INTERVIEWER: To cause
someone to stumble? Okay.
What were you trying
to accomplish there
when you did take your
children's lives?
(YATES CONTINUES,
INDISTINCT, FADING)
YOUNG WOMAN: ...all women,
all Gen Z group think.
Like, what are your thoughts?
And?
Hello?
Yeah. Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
Mm-hm.
YOUNG WOMAN: That is totally
unbelievable, right?
That's completely unbelievable.
All of it.
- GIRL: But Dr. Spring said--
- I don't care what she said.
I'm telling you,
I had a work emergency
and I couldn't stay.
I had to leave.
It isn't my fault.
I came right back to pick you up
when I was supposed to
like I always do.
I just-- I just--
I just couldn't stay
for the group, but, you know...
I work with
a lot of very sick people,
- honey, and sometimes they are--
- GIRL: Sicker than me?
Sick in a different
way than you.
- But Dr. Spring said--
- I told you,
I don't care what she said.
I'm your mother.
She loves me though.
She said so.
She said that?
- She loves all of us. The kids.
- (LAUGHS BITTERLY)
She has no right to
tell you that. She's a doctor.
- She doesn't have a right--
- It's true, though!
You know, I don't think we need
the program anymore.
- I'm better?
- Yeah. I think maybe, yeah.
Maybe we...
we just do it, you and me.
What would happen?
(EXHALING) Uh... So many
wonderful things. You would...
You'd be able
to get the tube out,
and you could go back to school
and you'd be eating everything
delicious in the whole word.
Wouldn't that be great?
You can do that?
Do what?
Make me better?
I won't need the machine?
(VOICE SHAKING) Well...
I'm better? They said that?
I think, maybe.
You know, and...
And if not, then
we'll just do it, you know?
You're better than you were,
and Dr. Spring's
not the boss of us.
Mommy?
LINDA: Yeah?
GIRL (CRYING): I'm really
sorry, but I'm not better.
Please don't be mad or sad
that I said that.
(GIRL SNIFFLES)
(MACHINE WHIRRING, BEEPING)
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(WHISPERING) Hello?
FRONT DESK WOMAN:
There's someone here
who wants to see you
in the lobby.
What? Who?
Won't say. Come down or don't.
(LINE CLICKS)
Thanks for checking on me.
Oh, you would not believe
the day I had, honestly.
After you just left me
all alone,
abandoned in your
spooky-ass apartment,
with my bone sticking
out my leg.
I called you an ambulance.
No big deal.
What else did you expect me
to do?
It's really painful.
I had to get back here
to my kid, okay?
Mother of the fucking year.
I almost forgot.
I don't care.
And what exactly
am I supposed to do
with your brick of cocaine?
- Flush it.
- (CHUCKLES) Okay.
It must be nice.
Why didn't they give
you any crutches?
- Fuck them crutches.
- (DOOR SLAMS)
(MACHINE BEEPING OVER MONITOR)
(TECHNO PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
(BELL CHIMING)
LINDA: It's... It is you!
You-- you're here.
I hope that's okay.
I accidentally followed you
this one time, and...
You live here?
Are... are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Okay. Okay.
Where did you go?
I just...
I-- I had to get out of there.
- Okay, I understand. So, let's--
- Do you?
Do you really,
really understand?
I think so.
Oh, shit. No. This is...
This is a mistake.
This is a mistake
because I thought...
I thought that you understood,
and that
I wouldn't even have to say--
Let's calm down.
I think what we should do
is get in a car right now
and go straight
to the emergency room.
A hospital?
- Yes.
- Why? Why?
Because
it's just a safe place to go...
Why? Why? No, I'm fine.
...if you don't feel ready
to go home.
Well, what about your daughter?
- My daughter?
- Where is your daughter?
She's upstairs. She's sleeping.
I don't want to go
to a hospital.
I don't want to
go to a hospital.
Okay.
I want you to help me.
I'm trying to.
- I am trying to help you.
- Please help me.
No, no, because you
don't understand.
You don't see it.
All of their faces.
Their little faces.
They look at us,
- and there is nothing there.
- Okay, you need to calm down.
- No! No!
- You need to calm down.
No, I am fine! Okay?
- But I just need you...
- Let's just breathe.
- No, but you don't know...
- Just breathe.
In and out, Caroline.
Just take a breath.
- Just breathe with me.
- Stop.
Just start with a breath.
- (HARD SLAP)
- (GASPS)
(DOOR SHUTS)
Caroline, wait!
(BEEPING CRACKLES ON MONITOR)
(LINDA PANTING)
LINDA: Stop!
(MONITOR CRACKLING)
(MONITOR CLATTERING)
(PANTING HEAVILY)
Caroline!
THERAPIST (OVER PHONE):
If this is an emergency,
hang up and call 911.
Otherwise, call back
during normal business hours.
(LOUD WHISPER)
Okay, call me back.
Call me back tonight, okay?
Please? Please, you said
that you could help me.
Please. Please, just
call me back, okay?
I need you. Bye.
(MACHINE ALARM BEEPING)
(GIRL MOANING FAINTLY)
(GRUNTING)
(LINDA EXCLAIMS)
(MULTIPLE ALARMS
BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
- (BEEPING STOPS)
- (MACHINE POWERS DOWN)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
GIRL: Mommy?
(SHUSHING) Go back to sleep.
Everything's okay.
My tummy is wet.
Sh-sh-sh. It's okay.
I made it better, okay?
Go back to sleep.
(FAINT, PULSING THROB)
(LOW, WET GURGLING)
(PANTING)
(HEAVY, SHUDDERING RUMBLE)
(GASPING HEAVILY)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(DOOR OPENS)
(YELPS)
(RESPIRATOR HISSING LOUDLY)
(COUGHS) Hello?
Hello?
(HOLLOW THUDDING)
(HEAVY RUMBLING)
(YELPING LOUDLY)
CHARLES: Oh!
Why are you here?
Are you okay?
Where...
When did you get here?
Why are you here?
Where is she?
(GASPING) She's asleep.
- With the babysitter?
- Yes.
Look, I just...
I couldn't think.
I couldn't function.
I couldn't do anything.
All I was doing was thinking
about you,
and her, and the apartment
so I had to come back.
I was scared.
- I wanted to help.
- Wait, wait, wait. Wait, I--
CHARLES: What? You just gotta
know how to talk to these guys.
That's all.
Did you look at it, the hole?
Did you see it?
Did you see anything?
Oh, yeah. No, it, uh...
It was not fixed.
Now it's fixed.
Okay. Okay, I think we should
just... Let's just go now.
CHARLES: I just don't see
how it got so bad.
How did it get so bad?
Are you trying to blame me?
No, I'm not blaming you.
I just...
I just want to get out of here.
- It was a huge hole.
- I want to get out of here.
Do you love me?
Yeah.
(CHARLES EXHALES)
- Hey, hey. Wait, wait, wait.
- What?
What's the rush?
You were the one who was
in a rush to get back here.
I don't want
to be here anymore.
We are here, all right?
Let's relieve the babysitter.
I'm exhausted.
I want to get to sleep,
and I'm excited to see her
even if she's sleeping.
I know, but why don't
you go downstairs
and get us some wine
or something
and I can relieve the sitter
and then you can come
back up and then we can...
What's going on?
There's nothing going on.
Open the door.
- Me?
- I don't have a key.
Right, yeah. Okay.
Oh, God. Don't tell me
you left her here
- without having a key. Come on.
- No, no, no. No.
Of course, I have a key.
What do you think I am?
Hey. I'm her dad. I'm Charles.
Nice to meet you.
You must be the babysitter.
- Babysitter?
- Yeah, James, right?
- Jamie, right.
- Oh, thank you for...
Oh, hell no.
I'm not doing this
shit with you, yo.
Not doing what?
What are you talking about?
I'm not a fucking
babysitter, dude.
Excuse me?
Your daughter woke up
and was crying, scared shitless.
So I pounded on the fucking door
till she finally opened it.
I had to tell her
I was a friend of your wife.
Bro, it took me forever
to get her to go to sleep.
And by the way,
I had to give her a Band-Aid.
She has some shit oozing
from her stomach or something.
Hey. Okay, okay, hold on.
Hold on.
- Listen, who the fuck are you...
- Watch the leg, man.
...and what the hell
are you doing in my room?
- Your room?
- Yeah. This is my wife.
That's my child.
- GIRL: Mommy?
- My room.
JAMIE: I just fucking told you
who I was,
and you need to ask your wife
why I got this cast on my leg.
- LINDA: It's-- I don't...
- Who is this guy?
- He's the babysitter.
- He's not the babysitter!
He just told me
he's not the babysitter.
I don't know
what he's talking about.
- Who the fuck is he?
- She's awake.
Can we just go inside?
She can hear everything
you're saying.
Can you even explain to me
why her machine is off
and the tube
is outside of her body?
GIRL: Daddy! Are you out there?
- I ain't in this shit, man.
- GIRL: Come see me!
- LINDA: Let's go inside.
- Daddy! Daddy!
Hey. Hey. Lookit. Yes, hi.
Daddy's home!
Mom said we didn't need
the program anymore.
CHARLES: Oh, my gosh.
Look at you! You're beautiful.
But I didn't believe her
because Dr. Spring said I do.
- But look, she was right!
- What? What are you saying?
- Look! No tube!
- What?
The tube is garbage now.
- (CHARLES EXHALES)
- I can go back to school!
CHARLES: Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God.
- But Daddy...
I still don't want to
eat food...
What...
- ...because it's too squishy.
- CHARLES: What's going on?
(PANTING)
GIRL: Will you take me
to the playground tomorrow?
CHARLES: What did you do?
What did you do?!
GIRL: Mommy!
(SIGN HUMMING)
(DISCORDANT TONE BLARING)
(DEEP, THROBBING RUMBLE)
(THUNDEROUS CRASHING)
(CRYING OUT)
(GASPS, COUGHING)
(WATER RUSHING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(LOUD GROAN)
(SHARP GRUNT)
(GIRL SCREAMING)
(MUFFLED RUMBLING)
- (FAINT, RUSHING VOICES)
- (LINDA'S LUNGS SPASMING)
(PANTING)
(HEAVY, EXHALING YELL)
(FAINT, MUFFLED VOICES)
(INDISTINCT SCREAMING)
GIRL: Don't touch me!
(SWIRLING, MUFFLED SHOUTS)
(GASPING FOR AIR)
(WAVE CRASHING)
(SHUDDERING BREATHS)
(SHARP, RHYTHMIC BREATHS)
(BREATHING CONTINUES, ECHOING)
GIRL (FAINTLY): Mommy!
Mommy!
(BREATHING FADES SLIGHTLY)
(PULSING RUMBLE)
GIRL: Mommy, I'm here.
Mommy, please!
Mommy!
(RHYTHMIC BREATHING CONTINUES)
GIRL (CLOSER): Please!
- (VOICES SWIRLING)
- (RUMBLING CONTINUES)
GIRL (SINGING): ♪ Sit beside
The breakfast table ♪
- ♪ Think about your troubles ♪
- (OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
- ♪ Pour yourself a cup of tea ♪
- (HEAVY RUMBLE)
(RUMBLE STOPS)
♪ Then think about
The bubbles ♪
Mommy?
(WAVES HISSING FAINTLY)
I'll be better. I promise.
I'll be better.
(WAVES BUILDING)
(CRASHING)
(SEA FOAM HISSING)
(WAVES CONTINUE ROLLING GENTLY)
GIRL: ♪ Sit beside
The breakfast table ♪
♪ Think about your troubles ♪
♪ Pour yourself a cup of tea ♪
♪ Then think
About the bubbles ♪
♪ You can take your teardrops ♪
♪ Drop them in a teacup ♪
♪ Take them down
To the riverside ♪
♪ And throw them
Over the side ♪
♪ To be swept up by a current ♪
♪ Then taken to the ocean ♪
♪ To be eaten by some fishes ♪
♪ Who were eaten by
Some fishes ♪
♪ Swallowed by a whale ♪
♪ Who grew so old ♪
♪ He decomposed ♪
♪ Doo-doo ♪
♪ He died and left his body ♪
♪ To the bottom of the ocean ♪
♪ Now everybody knows ♪
♪ That when a body decomposes ♪
♪ The basic elements ♪
♪ Are given back to the ocean ♪
♪ And the sea does
What it oughta ♪
♪ And soon
There's salty water ♪
♪ Not too good for drinking ♪
♪ 'Cause it tastes
Just like a teardrop ♪
♪ So they run it
Through a filter ♪
♪ It comes out from a faucet ♪
♪ And it pours into a teapot ♪
♪ Which is just about
To bubble ♪
♪ Now ♪
♪ Think about your troubles ♪
(WAVES RUMBLING FAINTLY)