Hi, I'm the narrator.
I'm here to provide facts
about Ella.
But first, let me give you
what she would call
"full transparency."
I've worked for her ever since
she finished law school,
so I'm not exactly neutral.
I'm nuts about her.
I am.
2008. The middle
of the Great Recession.
But, you know, in a way,
a better time.
We all still liked each other.
At just 34 four years old,
Ella is the third youngest woman
to ever hold her office.
Sounds great, right?
The thing is,
we all hide our... our...
Oh, forgive me, "crap"...
until it wins or we do.
ESTELLE (VO): With Ella,
the crap started at age 16.
WOMAN: Let's go, girls.
ESTELLE (VO):
Not to be a downer,
but you're one of the lucky ones
if you've never experienced
other people's totally normal,
happy families
as a small stab in the heart.
Think we're all going to have to
leave soon, Mr. McCay
ESTELLE (VO):
Destiny can be a sneaky thing.
EDDIE: My speech.
Your overcoat pocket.
ESTELLE (VO):
Our lives can turn on a dime.
Or a single word.
Wait.
Nobody's gonna say anything?
(GASPS)
(CHUCKLES) What do you think
there is to say, kiddo?
Hey, Case, could you go get me
a glass of water, please?
CASEY: Okay.
(SIGHS)
Go ahead, Ella,
say what you want.
Thank you, Aunt Helen.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I don't want to act as though
you were just retiring today
as hospital director,
when really you're being forced
to leave because of multiple...
...sexual relationships
with women who work there.
That is one
legitimate point of view.
What do you mean?
Is there another?
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(GASPS)
Um, could you go put some ice
in that, please?
No.
Uh...
Okay. Fair enough. Uh...
You know what?
I-I promise
to read you to sleep
for the next six weeks.
The books with no pictures
and lots of words
that take long to finish.
What if you don't?
Have I ever said I'd do
something and not done it ever?
EDDIE: Another view, kiddo,
is that all three women
wrote letters of support.
(WHISPERING) You're married.
Look, part of what
they require from us today
is to show up as a family,
because of the...
Can you just not...
Oh, I don't know.
Mom?
(WHISPERING)
Don't make us go, please.
CASEY: I want to go.
No. Well, no, you can't go.
Do you know what
a traumatic experience is?
Sure.
Case, don't ever pretend
you know something you don't.
'Cause finding out
is easy and fun.
And the only way in the world
you can not learn something
is to pretend
you already know it.
Okay.
"T." Okay. "Trauma:
a psychic injury
caused by emotional shock,
the memory of which is repressed
and remains unhealed.
An injury to the brain."
That's what could happen to us
if we go.
Do you still want to go?
No, thank you.
Okay.
NASH:
Mr. McCay, we're real late!
I'll never forgive you.
I love you.
Call me for anything.
ESTELLE (VO): Six weeks later,
the other shoe drops.
- HELEN: You have some options.
- Really?
I don't see
that I have a choice.
- I don't.
- HELEN: Okay.
But I just don't think I can
be here when you tell Ella.
Tell me what?
Well, honey, it's, uh...
Your father has a...
a really great business
opportunity in... in California.
And your Aunt Helen
will visit regularly.
No, Mom, I... I can't.
I'll lose more
than a year of credit
on all four of my AP courses.
And that will mess up
my college applications,
and I'd lose that internship
that took all those interviews
and essays.
And there have been
these sort of really...
I guess... I don't know,
hopeful things happening for me
lately at school.
Like that sociology paper
I-I worked on forever.
I just got it back.
And the teacher said that I...
He said that...
(SIGHS)
It's right here.
I can show it to you.
But your Dad wants a fresh start
for all of us.
(SIGHS) Another fresh start.
Mom?
Can you please try
to explain to me...
...why it is you keep
going back for more?
I truly want to understand.
I still love him.
Well, then please, God,
spare me love.
- She does not mean it, God.
- (SIGHS, SNIFFLES)
- Just gimme a second, okay?
- Mom.
(SIGHS)
- He's gonna do that stuff again.
- Maybe. Possibly.
Probably. (SIGHS)
Your Aunt Helen says that...
maybe you should, uh,
stay with her for a while.
Until your father and I
are on firmer...
At least until
the end of the school year.
And then you'll be off
to college anyway, right?
What?
I can't let you
walk into my mistake.
- (ELLA SNIFFLES)
- Hey. Hey.
Don't you dare blame yourself
for any of this, Mom, okay?
Don't you dare.
Um, Aunt Helen,
are you sure you're okay
with my living with you?
(MOM SIGHS)
Yes. Ridiculously.
(MOM SOBBING LOUDLY)
- (DOOR OPENS)
- ELLA: You still up?
Is Mom crying?
- ELLA: Yeah.
- Why?
Because she hurt herself.
I'll stay with you
till you fall asleep, okay?
(SIGHS)
(WHISPERS)
Do I ever love you, kiddo.
Say it back.
(LAUGHS)
ESTELLE (VO):
This is how it started.
Those three days
that changed everything.
I knew it the minute I read it.
And my stomach knew it
before I did.
- Good morning, Estelle.
- Morning.
This reporter guy
isn't going away.
- What did he say today?
- Lots of last warnings.
This time he put
"I really mean it" in caps.
Ella, you should talk to someone
about this.
Just to hear yourself
think out loud.
Yeah. Yeah,
I know, you're right.
Thank you.
(SIGHS)
(SNIFFS)
(PHONE RINGS)
- Morning. Helen's.
- ELLA: Good morning, Aunt Helen.
- Ella, hi.
- Hi.
I-I was just wondering if
I could, uh, come by in a bit.
HELEN: Sure. Of course.
Everything okay?
Uh, yeah, fine. Just, um...
I just need some perspective
on something, is all.
Uh... Kind of a long story.
I'll tell you when I see you.
- (EXHALES SHARPLY)
- ELLA: On my way.
All right, love you.
Love you, too. Bye.
Ma'am, the governor
wants to see you.
He's across the street
in the phone room.
Okay, thank you.
ESTELLE (VO):
Ah, The phone room.
(LOUD CHATTER)
ESTELLE (VO): These noisy rooms
exist because elected officials
are not allowed to use
government offices
for fundraising.
Good morning.
Sorry to be calling you so
early. This is State Senator...
(CLICKS, DIAL TONE)
ESTELLE (VO): So their party
rents phone rooms,
where they're expected
to put in at least seven
solid hours a day
asking for money.
WOMAN: You contributed
2,000 dollars in the last cycle.
ESTELLE (VO): And yes...
I'll put you down
for five dollars.
- ...that's crazy.
- Thank you.
- MAN: ...for 50 dollars.
- WOMAN: Never been more crucial.
WOMAN 2: Asking for
your continued support.
WOMAN 3: ...35 dollars.
Hi, it's Governor Bill Moore.
ESTELLE (VO):
Governor Bill Moore,
known affectionately
as Governor Bill.
He and Ella go back a long way.
She was his chief of staff
when he was known affectionately
as Mayor Bill.
I'm just calling to thank you
for the...
...500-dollar donation.
Yes, ma'am.
- How's, uh...
- (CHATTER CONTINUES)
WHISPERS: Who's the husband?
...Jerry doing? You still...
still okay over there?
Excellent.
And you got those two
strapping sons? Do you have...
Daughter? Colleen.
Of course.
Who could forget Colleen?
She's gotta be, what, four?
Medical school.
All right, I'm gonna let you go.
Thank you.
Sorry for the mix-up.
We are all fools here.
You see what I spare you from?
I keep telling you
I'm glad to do it.
I like talking to voters.
Yes and that's
why you're terrible at it.
You were taking, like,
45 minutes a phone call.
Walk with me.
I want to tell you something.
Stop the world.
- Whoa! Whoa!
- (TIRES SCREECH)
- MAN: Keep it up, Governor Bill!
- (BILL CHUCKLES)
MAN 2:
We love you, Governor Bill!
So, what I'm gonna tell you,
you can't tell anyone.
Okay.
It's happening.
The Cabinet.
Secretary of the Interior.
- I made the short list.
- (GASPS) Oh.
I should hear any time now.
And you should prepare
to maybe replace me.
Congratulations.
Something wrong?
- Well...
- With what I've got pending,
if anything is wrong, I really
need not to know it, okay?
- Goodbye.
ESTELLE (VO):
What was wrong
is that politics
is the only profession
where people can drown
in puddles.
And Ella was stepping
into something
a lot bigger than a puddle.
- HELEN: Hi.
- ELLA: Hi.
Why are you waiting out
in the cold?
Why did you need to see me?
I have a... (CLEARS THROAT)
seriously ridiculous,
ridiculously serious problem,
and you're the only one
I can tell.
What's going on?
I'm about to add
to your problems, Ella.
Your father's here.
- In there? Now?
- Yes.
- Why?
- He wants to see you.
(GASPS)
But, you know what? We can just
go to the apartment if you want.
- Yes.
- Or... Or...
Or you could just pop in for
a second, just as a favor to me.
I mean,
I hate to put it that way.
It's just the best manipulation
I can think of at the moment.
Okay. Can I have a minute?
Oh, yeah, of course.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I...
- HELEN: No, no. Yeah.
(EXHALES)
ESTELLE (VO): Sixteen years ago,
the worst day.
Her mother's funeral.
HELEN: Thank you so much.
It means a lot.
(CHATTER)
ELLA: Who's that woman?
HELEN: I don't know.
Stop thinking the worst all the
time. You're not always right.
- EDDIE: No, oh...
- But I'm here for you.
(HELEN SIGHS)
Your mother was a lovely woman.
But thank the Lord
you have your father to lean on.
- (SCOFFS LOUDLY)
- Thank you for stopping by...
and very possibly meaning well.
- Come on, let's go.
- WOMAN: I am so sorry.
- ELLA: I'm sorry. Excuse us.
- Hey.
ELLA: Sure missed you.
Yes, but you don't have to
write me so often.
What does that mean?
'Cause then I have to
write you back,
and there's always
so much schoolwork.
You don't have to write me back
each time I write you.
It feels like I should.
To me it feels right now like we
should cry together about Mom.
I'm not going to cry.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I really need to.
(SIGHS)
Can you just stand there
and not let anyone in?
Not even Aunt Helen.
- Yes.
- (SNIFFLES) Okay.
(SOBBING)
(SOBBING CONTINUES)
(SNIFFLING)
(BOTH CRYING)
(SIGHS) Okay.
Okay.
Don't let him get to you.
Don't be sad. Don't be mad.
"Don't be sad. Don't be mad."
What does that leave me with?
Bulletproof.
(LAUGHS)
Hi.
Okay.
Uh, if it's all right with you,
I'd rather not discuss
our old issues right now.
Sure. I don't think
we can dive into old stuff
when we haven't seen each
other in... (SCOFFS) How long?
(ELLA CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES)
You don't know either?
Thirteen years.
(INHALES)
What I never got a chance to say
about dating
that friend of yours...
Wha... That's what you wanna
start this conversation with?
- Those two friends. Yes.
- Friends of yours.
- Well, any man in my position...
- You know what, Dad?
- I know, I can understand...
- No.
I can understand how,
since we haven't done this
in a while,
you may want to sort of
reconnect or whatever.
But really, please, really...
no more apologies.
HELEN:
Eddie. You said you understood.
You promised not to be yourself.
Your aunt wanted me
to just break the ice today
and wait till later on
to get around to why it is
I needed to see you.
But you're too smart for that.
No, you're too dumb for that.
Okay, you saw each other.
It went great.
- Yeah.
- Big sis, please.
Look, I-I...
I'm a different person now.
- Can I tell you why?
- No.
- Really?
- Eddie, no.
No, no, I'm interested.
Please, go ahead.
I met... an incredible woman.
- No!
- (HOOTS)
She's a psychologist.
- HELEN: Come on.
- Berkeley. PhD.
And she made me realize
how vital it is
that I make amends
with my children.
- No, no, no.
- Ella.
I-I can't let Olympia get away.
I have never in my life felt
this way about any other woman.
Jesus, Eddie!
No... I-I wasn't counting
your mother!
She's in a completely
different category!
- ELLA: He dyes his hair.
- I think they're plugs.
It took me this long
to make him irrelevant.
- You get how sorry I am, right?
- And he just walks in...
I know. I know. I know.
Listen, we shouldn't even
discuss it.
Let's just concentrate
on why you're here.
What happened?
Okay. (CLEARS THROAT)
Aunt Helen...
Please try not to judge things
I tell you right away.
Just listen till you hear
all of it. Okay?
I'll try.
I made a promise to myself
that I wasn't going to
let my marriage suffer
because of my job.
To a fault.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Go on.
And given that my work
never has a finish line,
and I was coming home
exhausted every night...
Anyway, there's a one-bedroom
guest apartment I discovered
under the Capitol dome,
just sitting there unused.
So, there were times
during lunch, when...
Ryan and I
would meet there, and...
you know,
we'd get to be alone and...
Mmm.
(WHISPERS) ...be together.
Sex!
Sex every day?
- Not every day.
- Okay. Ella.
- Ella. Ella.
- Uh. Yes?
Maybe you're just trying
a little too hard
to be responsible
for everything.
And who cares?
Well, one of the security people
who was fired recently,
and was somehow able to see
through closed doors,
has told a reporter,
who has since contacted me
and wants to leverage what
he knows for special access.
Sweetheart,
you can't get in trouble
for having sex
with your husband.
- That's what I thought.
- You can't.
Turns out, there is a...
very specific law...
which I was unaware of,
which precludes wrongful use
of government property.
And if this comes out at
the same time as something else,
which is imminent and
I can't even tell you about yet,
but will draw
extreme attention to me.
So that... (GASPS)
Oh. Stop it. Stop it, Ella.
(TRILLS)
I suddenly sound pathetic
to myself.
(SCOFFS) I just... Scrap that.
I, uh... I'm just gonna go back
to the office,
shut up, and hold
my own darn hand. (CHUCKLES)
I let myself become rattled.
That won't happen again.
Sorry, Aunt Helen.
Wow, that was interesting.
I love you.
(SIGHS)
- Ella, wait.
- Yeah?
I'm worried about you.
(SIGHS) I'm fine.
Save it for Casey.
He's gone silent on me again,
and I'm... I'm worried about him.
You know your brother.
He's just doing his
"leave me alone" thing.
(SCOFFS)
(KISSES)
ELLA: Okay.
You promised to take it slow.
Eddie, I forgot what it's like
dealing with you.
You blew it!
I'm really angry. Go!
First of all, I have never been
less full of shit!
And...
uh...
...maybe she blew it.
Olympia says it's a given
that Ella would be much
better off once she forgives me.
Oh, you know what?
Tell Olympia that forgiving you
requires you stop messing up
long enough
for people to catch up.
What is it gonna take to get
people to realize I've changed?
Castration.
- Too far.
- (SCOFFS) Not even close.
(PHONE BEEPS, RING TONE)
(BEEPS)
ELLA: Case, it's...
it's me again.
Hi.
(CHUCKLES) Um...
No pressure, but, just...
Just let me know how you are.
Thanks.
- (BEEPS)
- (SIGHS)
(SIGHS)
NASH: Ma'am?
It's just...
Families, huh? Hmm.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah. Absolutely.
What?
Oh, um...
My mother, you know, she, um...
She's... What's the word?
Dotes. She dotes on...
I'm sorry, I can't hear you.
Do you mind repeating that?
Um, my mom, she...
she dotes on me, you know?
- ELLA: Uh-huh.
- Like big time.
- Like I'm the golden child.
So, she visited me
a little while ago.
And the motel she's at
has a pool.
- Uh-huh.
- So, I went to pick her up,
and she's floating in this,
like... floaty-bubble chair?
- Oh, yes. Nice.
- In the pool, you know?
And, uh, she sees me...
Immediately gets up to
let me sit. Muscle memory.
- ELLA: Not true.
- I swear. Big splash.
- That can't be true.
- I swear. And I love my mom.
- But the scream she made?
- (LAUGHS)
It was the funniest sound
I've ever heard in my life.
- I can ima...
- It was like... (GROANS) Like...
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(GROANS, LAUGHS)
Immediate family legend.
(BOTH LAUGH)
ESTELLE: Oh, good.
Bill's in there
just waiting for you.
He's not taking any calls.
He's just sitting there.
- Quietly.
- (EXHALES)
Okay.
BILL: Yes, come in. Come in.
Hello. What's going on?
It came through.
I'm in the Cabinet!
Wow! Wow. Wow.
- Right?
- That's...
I'm resigning immediately to
get ready for my confirmation.
So, for the next 14 months,
anyway, you're governor.
- Congratulations.
- (WHIMPERS)
And, uh, you really couldn't
have gotten this any other way.
- Well...
- Oh, come on.
You couldn't do the bullshit
needed to fund a campaign.
And I wouldn't have gotten
this appointment
without your policies.
So, look at us.
What's more beautiful
than two people
who owe each other everything?
(CHUCKLES)
Thank you, Ella.
Thank you.
Wait. Wait. Uh, sorry.
(CHUCKLES)
Uh, before you go,
you promised to get us
those three additional votes
for the Mom's Bill.
Swore. Your word, not mine.
This is the big one,
the Healthy Start program
that gives expectant mothers
prenatal counseling
at a time when
depression and anxiety
are really common. And...
Bill?
It also includes home visits
to monitor
one-to-three-year-olds'
well-being.
Everybody's research shows that
that period of life
is the most crucial...
Which in turn,
relieves court calendars...
Ella! You have
to let go of this.
There's nothing I've worked
harder on for the last year.
It simply and substantially
increases
these kids' chance
at a better life.
I am not breaking my back
over a controversial bill
as I'm walking away.
No, no. Just breaking
your promise.
(CHUCKLES)
Your word is your what, Bill?
Ooh. (CHUCLKES)
Jesus!
What is the matter with you?
Nobody on earth can
throw their ass
over a high horse
quicker than you.
This could and should have been
up and running last year, okay?
- And by the way...
- Stop! Let it go.
Oh, God.
Let's use this as a learning
moment for your new job.
Go ahead.
BILL: The way
you're coming on right now
is why some of the people...
m-most of the people...
(WHISPERS) ...well,
all of the people around here,
find you so annoying that
their ears clog when you talk.
In this job
it's not enough to be smart.
To get anything done,
you have to make
dumb people feel less dumb.
Our own party's legislators
move in the other direction
when they see you coming.
And unless
you do something about it,
you will get zip done
after I leave.
And all those juicy brain cells
and all that work
and all the pulling of all those
moralistic all-nighters
will be one
stinking landfill of you.
(SIGHS)
Hats off, Bill.
That one hurt.
Come on, we've been here before.
That's what makes us good.
But do you see how that was
just a little patronizing?
- Mm-hmm.
- (KNOCKING)
MAN: Governor Bill!
BILL: Word is out.
New governor first.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Any last minute advice?
Don't take Ambien
more than three nights in a row.
- (CHATTERING)
- (FLASHES CLICKING)
(REPORTERS CHATTERING,
GASPING)
(APPLAUSE)
Congratulations.
How do you feel about the...
This is Ella's day.
ESTELLE (VO):
Like almost everyone,
I will never be
in a public spotlight,
but I can really understand
why some people who
are new to it just plain wilt.
And why others were born for it.
Governor!
ESTELLE (VO): Because
they're like butterflies,
who need heat in order to fly.
REPORTER:
Here comes First Husband, Ryan.
Owner of a chain
of pizza restaurants.
- Okay. Stop.
- (FLASHES CLICKING)
ESTELLE (VO): He was her
high school sweetheart.
- So, 17 years ago...
- (OBJECTS THUDDING)
...boy meets aunt.
(DOG BARKING)
Hey!
- Hey! Hey! No. Hold up.
- RYAN: What the hell?
- No. Just hold up!
- Are you nuts, lady?
Are you nuts?
- What the hell...
- (GRUNTING) Stop! Stop!
Okay.
Stop!
(PANTING)
Why were you just sneaking
out of my house?
(PANTING)
I am not gonna
say anything, right?
But... But you can really move!
- (CHUCKLES) You...
- (PANTING)
I'm gonna call your mother.
Ma'am.
You don't know my name.
(CAR DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
Come on, come on, come on.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
- (CAR DEPARTS)
- Oh, God.
HELEN: Ella?
Ella?
- Ella.
- Morning, Aunt Helen.
HELEN: Did he sleep here?
Who?
No.
When did he get here?
- A few minutes ago.
- I didn't hear the bell.
That's 'cause I saw him coming
from my room, so I let him in.
But, why was he running away?
I don't know. 'Cause
he had to be someplace, I guess?
- HELEN: Okay.
- (SIGHS)
What's his name?
Because?
Because names allow us
to differentiate
human beings one from another.
Um, you're gonna call his house,
aren't you?
Yeah.
Yeah. Well, I...
I'm sorry, but I can't tell you.
Did you have sex with him?
I'm sorry? Are you kidding?
You didn't say no.
Why would you say that?
- Why would you even think that?
- But you still didn't say no.
No! No. No. All he did was...
I don't want to hear another
word unless it's the truth.
I'm late for school.
So go to school.
- (EXHALES)
- But...
I-I want you to think
about seeing me tonight
and whether you do or do not...
...tell me truth about that boy.
But the alternative...
is that you,
maybe for the first time...
...lie to me?
And... And, honey...
We would lose a closeness
of a kind.
He really likes me.
It's actually strange how much.
(INHALES)
He sort of gets a kick
out of how hard I work,
instead of putting it down.
And likes that I'm so serious.
And he loves to talk about
all the things
he believes can happen for me,
which are nuts by the way.
And...
I don't know, he comes
from a normal family.
You know, where they
have this great family business,
and they talk every night,
and hang out and play games
around the dinner table.
And, and...
They vote on family vacations,
you know?
I love you.
I love you, too.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Did he wear a Johnny?
A what?
A condom!
(YELPS)
I don't know how long it'll be
before she lets me go out again.
We'll find a way.
I'll... I'll wait.
I'm excited about us.
And what happens
when I go away to college?
The reality is we're gonna end
pretty soon anyway, right?
That's what happens.
Come on, I do so much better
when I face things.
(KIDS CHATTER ON FIELD)
Then face me.
(CHEERLEADERS CHEERING,
INDISTINCT)
I've never met anyone
like you before.
- Oh, my God.
- No. No.
And you, you are going places,
and you don't even know where.
But wherever that is,
I'm showing up.
(CHUCKLES)
ESTELLE (VO):
Ryan was persistent.
Even after
Ella went away to college.
(KNOCKING)
ESTELLE (VO): He started
showing up every weekend.
- (IMITATING COWBOY)
- (LAUGHS)
Hi!
Isn't he great?
(SQUEAKING ON GLASS)
ESTELLE (VO):
And, as it often does,
persistence paid off.
(LADIES LAUGHING)
- Uh, Ayden, Ayden.
- Yes?
Could you ask her aunt to come
out here, just for a second?
Just for a sec. Thanks. Thanks.
(GRUNTS, EXHALES)
(HEELS CLACKING)
Hi.
Hi. Hi. Uh...
I know you've had your doubts
about me.
Hell, I... I agree with you.
I don't think anybody's
good enough for her.
But I wanted to say that
nobody's gonna try
harder than me.
Blessings.
I mean it.
Thank you. I mean it.
HELEN: Okay.
(WEDDING MARCH PLAYS SOFTLY)
(WEDDING MARCH CONTINUES)
ELLA: Case.
Oh.
(HELEN WHISPERS) I love you.
I love you.
Gorgeous.
(EXHALES)
Your... Your sense of family,
your confidence,
your optimism,
and the way that you believe
life should be fun.
And make it so.
(EXHALES)
(QUIETLY) It's all a joke
except for us, baby.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
- Oh, my God!
- Okay, thank you.
(APPLAUSE)
That fast! 402 phone calls.
Eighty percent favorable.
And the state police
wants to know
if you want
Bill's security detail.
- Oh, no. No, no.
- Yes.
- Nash is great. Thanks, Estelle.
Okay, that's a no.
What? Something wrong?
That's not a way to take office
during a recession.
People like to see
other people win the lottery.
What you just said has nothing
to do with what I just said.
- And you don't...
- What? What? What?
My being governor
means that reporter
is sure to publish the story.
Ella. The dance.
Turn on the TV. Channel Four.
But I think it's on all of 'em.
Okay. Well, no,
we don't have to do that, it's...
- Yeah, we do. Channel Four.
- How do you...
ANCHOR: Finally, today at noon,
take a look at this.
Our new governor
and First Husband
showing us all how
to celebrate a promotion.
Just makes you smile.
(CHUCKLES)
- (CHATTERING ON TV)
- Okay.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
REPORTER: We'll see you
back here at 6:00.
I'm dumb about this stuff.
Join us then.
That's why you have me.
And, look, can you just forget
about the reporter, okay?
I know the guy. I'll solve this.
- Really?
- Yeah!
Maybe then you can ask him
how he can go with a story
when all he has is a trooper
guessing what we did
behind closed doors.
He didn't tell. I did.
- What?
- (SIGHS) Come on, honey.
Look, don't do this
to yourself, okay?
The guy heard a little gossip
about our lunches,
and he asked me the question.
(STAMMERS)
What was I gonna say?
That we used
the bedroom to chat?
No. Okay?
And this humanizes you.
(WHISPERS) Humanizes?
Wrong word.
Okay, that's the wrong word.
- I just need you to... Come on.
- (EXHALES)
- Oh.
- Honey, sweetheart, look...
I am begging you.
Let's enjoy this.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
Let's take a breath. Okay?
It's us.
Yeah?
MALE ANCHOR: Our new governor
and her husband
provided a lift
to bystanders' spirits
as they danced
their way into office.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(PHONE RINGS)
Hello? Oh! (CHUCKLES)
Oh, my God! You looked adorable.
My body exploded in sweat.
My first happy sweat.
Um...
Hey, do you have a minute?
Sure. Yeah, of course.
Everything okay?
There's simply no one else
I can air this out with.
Ryan just told me
that he was the one
who informed the reporters
about our lunch hours,
and I don't know what to think.
- Hello?
- I'm here.
No... No reaction?
(GROANS)
I'm treading carefully, honey.
Ryan honestly believes I'm just
being too tight-ass about it,
which, Lord knows,
is something I tend to be.
Yeah, well, you know the problem
with being a tight-ass
is you never know
when your ass is right.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
Listen, I have to go soon. Tell
me quick what you really think.
I think what
I've always thought.
That your husband is a ticking
time-bomb in your life.
Okay, well...
I mean, you're suspicious of
anyone who's optimistic, anyway,
so you're not
the right person to ask.
Okay.
And Ryan is still the guy
who gave up college
so he could
send his kid brother.
He's still the guy
who watered his tomato sauce.
You promised to
put that one to rest.
You know what,
it's not so easy to forget
when someone
gets drunk at a party...
Four years ago.
- Four years ago.
- ...and brags... brags...
that his business makes
an extra 300,000 dollars.
Because he altered the recipe
for local taste.
No, because
he watered his tomato sauce.
I don't get your need
to do this right now.
(SIGHS)
Forgive me, baby.
The heck with all of it.
Can we just take this in
for a minute?
Ella, you're 34.
And you just became governor...
...of the state you were
born and raised in.
(VOICE BREAKS) And I just...
- (SNIFFLES)
- And I just... I'm...
- I'm just...
- (CRYING)
Are you thinking about your mom?
Yeah. (SOBS)
Me too.
- (SIGHS)
- Okay, well...
Okay, I've gotta mop up and go.
Clean up on aisle five.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay. I love you. Bye.
I love you, too. Go be governor.
(CHUCKLES) Bye.
Did you get a chance to go over
the amendment to the Mom's Bill?
Yes, I know it's a lot to read.
But there is
a summary available.
All we need are three votes.
Okay, Maggie, bye.
(BEEPS)
(EXHALES)
- Uh, Ma'am?
- Mm-hmm.
I just want to say
how nice it's been
- being on your detail all...
- Sorry, what did you say?
I was just saying I have really
enjoyed my time on your detail.
- Don't tell me you're leaving.
- No, you're leaving.
- Where am I going?
- Well, Governor Bill's security
is now gonna be
taking care of you.
No, sorry, Nash.
I'm simply not letting go
of the only cheerful person
around here.
You're coming with me.
Thank you, Lieu...
Governor.
Thanks back.
(RYAN SIGHS)
ELLA: Gosh.
RYAN: Gosh.
Hmm.
I don't want this to be
our last night in the apartment.
Wait, what? Huh?
Let's keep living here
for as long as we can.
What? Why?
No, it's just I want us
to protect our...
(PANTING)
I want us...
as much as possible... to...
stay the same.
You know, we don't have to move
to the residence right away.
We can stay here.
- It's been done.
- Yeah, sure.
- Okay.
That's... (PANTING)
But...
But I can still check out the...
(IN DEEP VOICE) ...the
Governor's mansion. Right?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Come on,
I'm gonna enjoy this, honey.
- You know?
- Yeah.
This is what's called
a healthy attitude.
(SIGHS)
(BRASS BAND PLAYS)
ESTELLE (VO): Inauguration day.
Which usually means
someone's dream is coming true.
(BAND PLAYS
"STAR-SPANGLED BANNER")
- (MUSIC STOPS)
- (APPLAUSE)
- Thank you.
- (APPLAUSE FADES)
Ope! Yep. Sorry.
You know the facts.
We're in a jam.
I have just 14 months
to serve you.
Tough choices
must be made and quickly.
Each dollar placed in
high-quality early education...
can generate up to
seven dollars and 30 cents in...
Many of our seniors have
lost their pensions
to financial schemers...
And the potential
of our children
five years old or younger...
The threatened teachers strike
would be devastating...
If we do not create
a meaningful preschool
experience for them right now.
WOMEN: Preschool!
Finally...
- Finally?
- ...and most importantly,
in order to achieve this,
we must have
bipartisan consensus.
I... I prefer that word
to compromise,
because it allows
for individual passion
and puts a priority on reason.
Here, here. Pass it down.
Quickly, quickly, quickly...
Our lawmakers need...
Our lawmakers need time
for real thought,
as they make the decisions,
which will impact our destiny.
And that just can't happen
when they spend seven
to 12 hours each day,
raising campaign money
and consequently have no time
to even read the bills
they vote on!
(CROWD GASPING, BOOS)
ELLA:
We must take the time and energy
being spent
on getting re-elected
to do the jobs we were elected
- to take on in the first place.
- Quickly, quickly, quickly.
Or else,
it is not hard to imagine a day
where we simply forget
about elections and just...
And just hand offices to those
who raise the most money,
since they're going
to win anyway.
WOMAN: Thank you, Ella!
ELLA: Government works best
when citizens stay interested
and involved.
Because, as has been said,
"If you do not know
what you want,
you'll probably get
what someone else wants."
WOMAN: That's right!
So please, let's get started.
- Thank you.
- WOMAN 2: We love you, Ella!
- What do you think?
- She's great.
(BOOING)
Come on. You can sit at home.
Let's go. Up, up.
WOMAN: Go, Ella!
(APPLAUSE FADES)
She's unbelievable!
- Not mentioning you.
- No, Mom. Mom. Mom.
I'll handle this.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
HELEN:
Estelle. Was Casey here?
I left him a message.
I'm worried about him.
Do you want me to worry
about him too? I'll take it on.
No. No. Thank you, though.
(PHONES RINGING)
Ella, that was tough.
- You were good.
- ELLA: Thanks.
Uh, what did my aunt say to you
on the steps just then?
- (ESTELLE GROANS)
- ELLA: Estelle?
I promised her not to tell you
and worry you unnecessarily.
But since that ship has sailed?
She just asked if Casey called...
Can you give us a minute,
Estelle?
ELLA: Sorry, just a second.
I'm a little concerned
about Casey here, okay?
RYAN: He's an adult, okay?
You wanna maybe deal
with me here for a minute?
Yeah.
I know I didn't thank you.
You didn't mention me.
Bill sent me a note
to not thank him.
And it threw me. Uh...
If I thanked anybody else,
it would look as though
I were disrespecting Bill.
And I didn't want that.
I-I clearly overthought it.
(CHUCKLES) As usual.
- Yeah.
- (WHISPERS) Sorry.
I have a speech scheduled
for tomorrow.
I'll make it up to you there.
How's that?
By saying what, though?
By saying...
What would you like me to say?
- Is that a real question?
- Yeah.
Okay, then let me
get back to you on that.
- (CHUCKLES)
- (DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
Estelle, what do I have next?
Meet and greet with donors.
- Better get going.
- Can't.
- Casey?
- Yeah.
I know. I'll take care of it.
Do what you have to.
Thanks.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
- ELLA: Casey!
- (KNOCKING RAPIDLY)
(SIGHS)
- Casey! It's Ella.
- (KNOCKING)
- Hi.
- Hey.
(LIGHT CHUCKLE)
ELLA: Hello.
Hi. (EXHALES)
First things first.
So good to see you.
How are you?
I'm, uh...
(EXHALES)
Listen, I'm sorry
I haven't been in touch.
- It's just...
- No, no, no.
It's okay. It's okay.
You didn't want me
"big sistering," is that it?
- (SIGHS) Yeah, yeah. Yes.
- Yeah. Yeah.
So, Aunt Helen says
you're the governor now.
Yeah. (CHUCKLES) Yeah.
Strange, huh?
No. No. (SIGHS)
(SIGHS) Wow.
This is the place, huh?
You're still using your math to
advise people on sports betting?
Yeah, and I'm on deadline.
So I need to...
If I could just...
(TYPING)
Uh...
Can it wait?
Briefly, but, you know, this is
very deadline sensitive stuff.
Understood.
How is everything else?
I mean, how have you been?
Have you...
What happened to
that great girl you said was...
Oh, no, no. I can't. I ca...
I don't wanna talk
about that. That's...
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- That's... No.
Uh... (CLEARS THROAT)
May I get a soda or something?
- Yeah, sure. It's in the, uh...
- Thanks.
(FOOTSTEPS)
Have you been in contact
with Dad at all?
Yeah, he... he keeps
leaving me voicemails.
Really?
Yeah, um...
Today's was...
I'll show you. I'll show you.
(MACHINE BEEPS)
EDDIE: Casey, I just need you
to meet Olympia.
Go ahead, honey.
- OLYMPIA: Hi, Casey.
- (GASPS)
No, no, no.
Don't... don't stop it.
It's gonna get sorta wild.
This is Olympia.
A strange, but maybe
appropriate way for us to meet.
(WHISPERS) Really?
Your dad and I have been
reading about forgiveness.
And I think he's learned that,
as I think one female writer
put it best,
"You can clutch the past
so tightly to your chest
that your arms are too full
to embrace the present."
Let me leave you with that.
And just know that
I'm rooting for your family...
(OLYMPIA CRYING)
Yep.
(WAILING) ...to heal.
- Bye.
- (MACHINE BEEPS)
- Good Lord.
- (EXHALES)
There's been a lot more of those
over the past few days.
I stopped listening,
but that stuff, that just...
It gets to you, you know?
Let me...
Let me take care of this. Okay?
Yeah, that'd be amazing. Thanks.
Ooh.
Can I? Haven't eaten all day.
Uh... Yeah.
You want some?
No, I'm good.
(WHISPERS) Why do you keep
checking your watch?
- Are you expecting somebody?
- (TYPING)
No, it's just,
I just gotta make my deadlines.
And well, I don't really like
to get high before 6:00.
What?
We... We haven't seen each other
in all this time,
and you wanna get high?
Why would you choose to get high
when we haven't talked
in so long?
Just to keep you company.
You didn't check the label?
Lemon extract, sugar.
Six dose... Six doses.
Yeah, so you didn't
read that huge word
"Cannabis" along the side?
You didn't see that?
(GASPS) Oh!
Oh, God!
No!
ESTELLE (VO):
In 2008, only 13 states
allowed medical marijuana,
including this one,
even though
Ella had passionately
campaigned against legalization.
- Am I gonna die?
- You are gonna die. Seriously.
- No, you are gonna die.
- Casey, I'm not kidding around!
Is it... Is it strong?
- It's pretty strong.
- Will I hallucinate?
Sativa. It's pleasant,
stress-reducing.
For me, it eliminates
foreboding, free form guilt,
weight watching,
stuff like that.
Okay. I'm not gonna worry.
(SIGHS)
I didn't have much. It's fine.
CASEY: Oh!
- Y-Yeah. Okay.
- What?
The cookie's stronger.
(RADIO CHIRPS)
DISPATCH: Is Snowbird
still at that address?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Yep.
- (RADIO CHIRPS)
- DISPATCH: We'll send relief.
Can't violate
the no overtime edict.
Shit.
(NEARBY ENGINE STARTS)
Sorry.
I just could have used the extra
money. The divorce is...
divorce is chomping me up.
She's getting what's fair, man.
Yeah.
I think Snowbird wanted us in
particular to stay on the job.
What are you doing?
DISPATCH: We need actual
authorization for overtime.
She is at a very private meeting
and said she didn't
want to be disturbed.
- Stop it right now.
- I am drowning, man. Okay?
We are five minutes away
from overtime.
- That is 79 dollars an hour.
- Absolutely not.
I have six dollars
to my name. Okay?
I... I just...
I... I get the kids Sunday, right?
And they didn't even
want to come.
I pick the youngest one up,
she screams.
I put her down, she screams.
Nothing I try works with them.
So I just want to have
one good day. Okay?
One... One single positive,
like, nice experience
where I take 'em somewhere,
or like, or I get 'em...
get 'em a gift. Something.
Some fond association,
before they end up thinking
that their father is just
like this nothing, zero. Not...
(COUGHING, LIGHT PANTING)
Are you trying to cry?
No.
No, something...
Something's happening.
Something...
Do you see this?
I didn't... I didn't know
this was gonna happen.
- (PATTING SHOULDER)
- (FAKE CRYING)
(FLATLY) There, there.
DISPATCH:
Okay. You're authorized to stay.
Copy.
(EXHALES)
RYAN: Baby? I'm here.
- (RAIN POURING)
- I'm at the Governor's Mansion.
Mmm. I get a staff,
a car, an office,
and my own security trooper,
for crying out loud.
Yes, you do.
- And...
- (GONG RINGS)
...we get to use the helicopter.
No. The helicopter
is for urgent travel
when no other feasible
transportation will do.
There's a piano!
Ryan, look, I'm not functioning
particularly well right now,
so I'm gonna... I'm gonna
stay right here tonight, okay?
Oh, but I did...
I did what you wanted.
I spoke with the guy.
He's gonna kill the story.
- You did?
- Yeah. But only if...
♪ If you agree to give him
Just a little special access ♪
♪ And he needs to know
Within the next hour ♪
No. No special access.
We're being extorted.
- (PHONE BEEPS)
- (LINE BEEPS, DISCONNECTS)
ESTELLE (VO): I sure get it.
Raise your hand if you've ever
fallen for the wrong person.
(SIGHS)
- ELLA: Case?
- (TYPING)
You ever...?
No, never mind.
Do you remember the first time
we got high together?
Which was the only time for me.
When you were at MIT?
(WHISPERING)
And I was so proud.
And I first realized
you were agoraphobic.
It's not agoraphobia if you stay
in place based on free choice
and not a phobia
or irresistible compulsion.
Ooh.
Let's not have that discussion.
I remember how great it was
to not feel like it was up to me
to fix things. (INHALES)
It was like the junkyard
in my brain had closed down,
and I had these great,
clear thoughts.
I never did it again,
of course, but...
it sure was tempting.
(GIGGLES)
Oh, sweet mother,
I think it's happening again.
- No. Ella, please!
- Well, wait, wait.
Let me get the thoughts out
while I can!
- No, Ella, please. Ella, no...
- Okay, one...
is that I've so missed you.
And I really think you're great.
And so what if
you're being agor...
Your having
a smallish anxiety disorder
is part of your being great.
(EXHALES)
And recently, truth be told...
(WHISPERING)
I, too, have been slightly...
drowning in anxiety myself.
But I am not drowning
at this moment.
(WHISPERS) No, sir.
Just between us, I'm...
I am so excited about getting
to do this job! (GASPS)
Even though
I got it by accident.
And...
The rest...
the personal stuff...
(TYPING CONTINUES)
I don't know.
The truth is I worry
that he doesn't love me.
Not really.
(TYPING STOPS)
That he just wanted to...
I didn't mean that.
It's just, uh...
It's complicated when you come
from our background,
and you're with someone from
a normal family, isn't it, Case?
Yeah, personally, I've decided
to stop trying to be normal.
And pick something easier.
(LAUGHS) Oh, Case... I love you.
Can I, um...
I have just one more thing...
teeny, tiny thing to say.
If I may.
(WHISPERING) I've never said
this, even to myself. But...
I know exactly what needs
to be done in this new job.
And, Lord help me,
I think I can do it.
I can make people's
lives better.
Even more than my predecessor.
Who is an adorable person,
and everybody loves him.
But... he doesn't
love them back, not really.
(LOUDER) Not enough
to fight the tough ones.
And sure, I'll never be able
to generate that kind of...
"Stop the world!"
"Hi, Nellie, how are the kids?
Doing good?
Which one? The boy or the gi..."
I don't have
that kind of appeal, okay?
I don't have the chitchat.
And the big guns in the party
don't like me at all!
They don't value my ideas.
Or the work that goes into them!
And they actually resent
my energy, whatever that means!
But I know exactly what needs
to be done in this new job.
Okay? We need to
attract new businesses.
And you can't do that with
substandard roads and ports,
and you can't do that unless
you jack... maybe way up...
license and registration fees,
especially
for commercial vehicles.
And you have to not give
a hot hoot
what that does
to your poll numbers.
Because here's the catch:
You can't be popular
and fix anything!
(PANTING)
Would you like to hear about
my favorite community
health program?
- God, no.
- I found it buried in a footnote
to a bill in Vermont
or Nebraska.
It was one of those states
that nobody's mad at.
"The benefits of tooth tutors."
Say it, Case. Tooth tutors.
- No.
- It's fun to say.
- You should try it once.
- No. I'm not saying that.
- It's really fun to say.
- No, I don't wanna say that.
- Please?
- No.
- Tooth tutors. Tooth tutors!
- No, I'm not gonna say it.
- Tooth tutors.
- Tooth tutors!
- Thank you.
(EXHALES) You go to any
deeply rural county anywhere,
and kids' teeth
are in terrible shape
because of the massive amounts
of soda they drink.
And dentists
are virtually non-existent
because
there's no money to be had.
So they started
this cost-free program,
where local volunteers
go door-to-door,
giving out tooth care kits
provided free
by toothpaste companies.
So like Doctors Without Borders,
they show up, these dentists,
maybe three times a year,
and treat all comers for free!
No, no, don't get excited yet.
That's not the best part.
The best part is that
the social workers
reported that these kids,
who'd been previously
walking around close-mouthed
because of
how their teeth looked,
actually began to smile.
(CRYING)
And... (SNIFFLING)
It seems to be at least
partially responsible
for increased high school
graduation rate
and reduced misconduct
in the classroom.
(SNIFFLING)
Thanks for listening. I...
- Now you.
- Uh...
Casey, do you really
have to work,
or are you just trying to avoid
talking about yourself?
Yeah. Yeah, I gotta work.
I gotta make deadlines, okay?
That's what I gotta do.
I know you got
a lot going on right now.
But, you know... This is. I got...
You know, there's 2,100 people
paying me $1,000 a year each,
and they're waiting
for this stuff,
and this is the first time
I've ever been late.
First time, and you come in here
doing all this stuff, and...
(STAMMERING)
...getting all emotional.
I can't be dealing
with that stuff.
I gotta make these deadlines.
You make
two million dollars a year?
Approximately, yeah.
I'm almost done, okay? Just...
Oh, wow.
And I'm not agoraphobic, okay?
I choose not to go outside.
That's by choice. Okay?
If I was agoraphobic, I wouldn't
be able to do this, would I?
- Watch this.
- Casey?
I'm gonna leave this door
right now.
- Pull it off its hinges, man.
- You don't have to do that!
- ELLA: Point made.
- A choice, see?
- Choice.
- Okay.
And my sociability,
- that's also fine.
- Okay.
How you doin', man?
Good to see you.
Welcome to the neighborhood.
How are you, bro?
Nice to see you.
You know what you wanna do?
You wanna take Detroit Lions.
Plus the points.
Oh, you'll make your bookie sob.
Sob.
ELLA: Look, I can't...
I can't show my face
until I'm absolutely
clear-headed here.
May I sleep here tonight?
CASEY: Uh...
- Yeah, sure.
- Thanks.
- (CASEY SIGHS)
- Wait.
Have I made it clear
how glad I am to see you?
Yes.
Let's not
articulate everything, okay?
Okay.
So what does that bring us to?
Oh, my God.
That's double time.
(CHUCKLES)
So...
You're okay that she's sorry
she forgot to mention you
in her speech
and that now she's going
to mention you.
Mm-hmm.
The first thing I did
when I got married
was to make your father
a full partner...
- Mm.
- ...so he wouldn't resent me,
so he could be a...
I don't know what else
she can do.
She can do
anything she wants now.
Give you any title she wants.
(STAMMERING)
Chief of Staff.
Director of Motor Vehicles.
Anything.
Instead of the husband
that gets...
...mentioned.
Oh, yeah. You get it now.
Your mother's smart.
Now you gotta say whatever
it takes to get what you want
or live with nothing.
Clear, strong, manly.
Or you want to be
like your father?
Huh?
Nothin', doll.
I'm juiced.
Thanks, Mom.
FATHER: Love you.
Love you.
Thanks.
(VEHICLES HUMMING)
ELLA: Hi, Estelle.
Uh, could you get Jen in Legal
on her cell, please?
ESTELLE: Okay, hold on.
(DEEP SIGH)
JEN: Morning, ma'am.
Hi. Good morning, Jen.
Did you find anything out?
JEN: Yes. Yes, we did.
It's government property
and therefore,
- it's unfortunately against...
- So it's questionable?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Okay.
(INHALES) Oh.
- Estelle, are you still on?
- ESTELLE: Yeah.
Yeah. I need to
head something off here.
Can we call a press conference
as soon as I get there, please?
(FOOTSTEPS)
- Oh!
- (YAWNS)
They didn't relieve you?
- Hi.
- Good morning.
I-I...
You said you'd be a while, so we
thought you wanted us to stay.
Or, um, okay, maybe there was
some kind of miscommunication?
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
What miscommunication?
- I-I...
- (SCOFFS)
Well, see, you had said,
"See you."
So we took that to mean
that you were wanting, um...
And maybe it was our mistake.
We thought that that meant
that you were hoping
that we were gonna...
That I wanted you
to violate austerity dictates
and rain overtime on you
when budgets are being shredded?
No.
- No?
- No. Um...
People are living in their cars.
And you sat in there,
chiseling them in yours.
It was wrong.
I'm senior. It was
my responsibility, Governor.
Don't you dare
for a second think
that your owning it
means anything at all.
Damn it, Nash.
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
- What a...
- She was right.
I did it for my kids.
You don't have to spend a dime
to be with your kids.
There are museums, libraries,
parks, playgrounds.
Hide and seek.
Catch, for God's sake!
Yeah! Yes.
Thank you.
Great tips.
Thank you. Helpful.
Just throw them a ball. When
they catch it, say, "Good job."
Yeah. Yeah.
Tic-tac-toe.
I am going to get
straight into this.
(REPORTERS CHATTERING)
(SIGHS)
I am faced with a possible
imminent dissemination
of certain facts
about my personal life.
I felt I should speak first,
so I do not appear reactive
or defensive at some later time.
(EXHALES)
For the past year or so,
in my efforts
to maintain a vital marriage
and ever so hopefully
to start a family,
- despite a 17-hour workday...
- Shush! Shush!
...I have been spending
lunch hours with my husband
in a state
office slash apartment
not directly assigned to me.
We engaged
in marital relations there.
- (PEOPLE GASPING)
- (SHUTTERS CLICKING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
I now understand that
one interpretation of state law
would consider
use of a government room
for matters so
strictly personal, a violation.
Though others disagree
with this interpretation,
I nonetheless have
instructed the state auditor
to place a value on the time
I occupied the office
and will pay whatever sum
she deems applicable.
I hope to soon put before
the legislature and the people
matters far more worthy of
our mutual attention and time.
- Thank you.
- (PEOPLE SHOUTING)
MALE REPORTER: When you say
"marital relations,"
- precisely what do you mean?
- (LAUGHTER)
(ASSISTANT SHOUTING)
Ella, you gotta see this.
- ELLA: Oh, God. Casey.
- ESTELLE: Do what you have to.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Comin' through.
- (DIALING)
- (LINE RINGS)
Where... Where is she?
ESTELLE: She said she won't
be reachable for a bit,
but she'll be checking in.
Okay, okay.
Can you tell her
that I need to see her
the minute she turns
her damn phone back on?
Can I tell her what it's about?
Oh, yeah, sure. It's about
how she ruined everything!
All right! I'll tell her that!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES)
ESTELLE (VO): With crises
sprouting all over the place,
work, marriage
and a troubled kid brother,
the problem becomes
where do you even start?
(WATER RUNNING)
ELLA: Case... Case, sweetie,
are you crying?
- What? No! Crap, are you nuts?
- Sorry.
What, you think
I'm just gonna start crying
telling you about Susan?
- Okay.
- Does that sound like me?
It's been a while. I'm sorry.
You're not gonna cry
about Susan.
Just gonna
let the garbage pile up
and suffer a relapse
of some sort
that is not agoraphobia,
but has you primarily
staying indoors for how long?
- Thirteen months.
- Oh.
- What?
- Nothin'.
(INHALES)
Okay, I may have damaged my life
by pressing Susan too early
in our relationship.
(SNIFFS) And I think about it
many, many times a day.
It's like one of those mistakes
you never recover from,
you know?
And by pressing her,
you mean you proposed marriage?
No.
But I mean, that would have been
appropriate to my feelings.
- Okay. What did you... do?
- What did I do?
Yeah.
- You... you want word for word?
- No.
- Just generally?
- Yes.
Okay.
I said how I believe
timing is almost everything.
And that one
of the timing decisions
I'm always afraid of screwing up
is the one where you say,
"I wanna stop dating right now
and just accept
that I've found the person
that's gonna
make my life worthwhile."
So far,
that's pretty word for word.
And then I said, maybe too loud,
that you know,
she was that person for me.
And I asked
if she felt the same way.
And therefore
would also want to stop
looking for anybody else but me.
And she said
that made her feel... weird.
And then she said "weird"
a couple more times, and...
that was it, really.
Did she say you were weird?
No. No. That's a great question.
She said "it" was weird.
What are you saying?
You saying there's still hope?
And this was over a year ago,
you say.
Yeah, barely.
What happened when you
called afterwards? I mean, did...
I... I didn't call.
I didn't call.
And she never called you?
I don't understand.
Look, I changed my number, okay?
Because
I didn't want to be aware
all the time
she wasn't calling me.
Her not calling me right away
was clear enough.
Oh.
You think I should call her now?
- Yes!
- And say what?
- What should I say?
- How is she?
- You've been thinking about her.
- Yeah? Okay.
- You'd like to see her.
- Okay.
- You...
- Oh.
- You know.
- What?
(PANTING)
I don't want to say this because
I know exactly
how I sound when I do,
but the truth is...
...she lives way over
in the Trent Park area.
You know, that...
that distance for me is
gonna be hard, given my issues.
- And... You know?
- (STAMMERS) Okay.
Well, but...
but, I mean, you know what?
Even saying that was difficult,
and you did it anyway.
- Yeah.
- Case,
you have a great work ethic.
This right now?
This is your work.
Okay.
Call her.
Call me for anything else.
Okay.
You know, I'm almost not sorry
I called you.
(ELLA LAUGHS)
I'll take it.
- (PHONE BEEPS)
- Hi, Estelle. Anything?
One of the news outlets
has started
to refer to you
in a peculiar way,
and it's catching on.
- Want to hear what it is?
- Sure.
"Little Miss Nooner."
Well, let's hope
that nickname doesn't stick.
ESTELLE: But your approval
rating is up two percent.
Huh.
Well, let's, uh... Let's use it
while we can, shall we?
Have full staff
as soon as I get there.
It will be a long session,
and no phones inside.
- Okay. Okay.
- Bye.
- Hey, wait a minute.
- How are you, Estelle?
- You're kidding.
I think I'm peaking!
I'm better than I've ever been
in my life!
Though I may have to
spray for lobbyists.
Who, by the way,
have bombarded me
with gifts under
the ten-dollar limit.
If you need
a refrigerator magnet
or a single rose, come to me.
Ella, this is fun.
Yeah, I feel some of that too.
I-I don't know that "fun"
would be my word.
- Ella, it's fun. It's fun.
- All right. Fine.
Little Miss Nooner, signing off.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
All right. Okay. Bye.
Oh, wait! Wait.
(SIGHS)
Could you get my father, please?
ESTELLE: Okay, Ella. Good luck.
Hi, it's Ella.
Uh, I said I'd see you.
Can we do it now?
Great. What's your address?
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Great that you're here. Come in.
- Uh...
- Governor, huh? (CHUCKLES)
I made you some, uh...
ELLA: Listen, Casey doesn't
leave his apartment as it is,
and those calls you're making
stress him out.
So cut it out.
That's what I came here to say.
Okay. I-I just need him and you
to do one thing for me.
Olympia's going to leave me
unless I can work things out
with my kids.
She says I have to own
all of my...
...misdeeds.
Which I have compiled a list of.
So I can offer you
specific remorses.
Hold on.
I have my acknowledgements here.
Uh, okay...
(CHUCKLES)
This is great we're doing this.
Um... (STAMMERS)
"I'd like to acknowledge
past actions of mine
for which I am deeply sorry
and ashamed.
I... during the marriage, I...
...womanized.
Um, I..."
An expense account thing.
Wrong apology.
"I sent Casey to military school
when he was eight
because I didn't want
the responsibility.
I avoided Ella..." You...
"Whenever I could,
because frankly, you scared me."
(CHUCKLES) Still do.
"And I rarely showed you
affection,
- even though I..."
- Trust me, this list
isn't going to help anything.
You want to mend fences?
Lay off Casey.
And how do I fix things
between us?
- (SIGHS) Fix things?
- Come on! Begin to repair, okay?
You're going to
leave Casey alone.
- Yes? Yes?
- Uh...
- Yes.
- Yes?
- Yes!
- Great!
And as far as you're concerned,
if there's anything standing
in the way of us moving on...
...tell me, please.
There is something...
I wonder about that actually
still eats at me.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Did you cheat on Mom at the end?
Not... really.
(SIGHS, SCOFFS)
I-I mean, what did I say?
I said not really.
(CLICKING, BEEPING)
(WHIRRING)
Yeah.
Oh, I gotta call first.
(LINE RINGS)
Hey, Susan, it's Casey.
You know, Casey McCay?
Yeah, yeah, and how long a time.
So, are you married?
No, no, no. I'm not...
I'm not married, either.
May I just come over?
Oh, okay,
well, when will you be back?
Okay, well,
I'll be there in two hours.
Look who's functional.
(GRUNTS)
ESTELLE (VO):
Verum est difficile.
The rug is right.
Truth is tough, but sometimes
you just gotta face it.
I need to talk to you.
Sure.
- Great. Thank you, everyone.
- Governor Ella,
you have your first
full staff meeting right now.
Thanks, Estelle.
What's up?
You called a press conference.
About our lives.
And you gave it
without running it by me.
(QUIETLY) Right.
I... Yes. I...
It's just that
it was just so clear
that something
had to be done immediately.
But you're right. I should have
run it past you first.
Totally solid point. Okay?
And you decided to make me
sound like someone
who has nothing else to do
but bang my wife
when she has nothing else
to do for lunch.
ESTELLE:
We can hear him out here.
- I swear...
- Yep. Got it.
That's not what I said.
All you needed to do
was check in with me.
And then all this crap
could have been avoided.
You and I need to talk at home.
Okay? This is not the place.
What, not in the throne room!
- ELLA: This isn't the place.
- Heavens, no!
Do you have some goal
in mind here?
Some result you want?
Because if you do, I swear we
can't get there from here. Okay?
So for God's sake stop it,
and we'll talk later.
RYAN: No! Okay?
Ella?
This is all on you.
You know that?
If you had just trusted me
to handle it...
What did you do?
No, don't change the subject.
- What's the subject?
- The subject?
The subject is that
you fucked up.
Don't talk to me like that.
You want... You wanna know
what the subject is?
The subject is that this
marriage isn't working for me.
You did something.
Right? And now you're worried
about what you did?
No. You're worried
about what I did,
which was to pay the guy
to kill the story
that you didn't want out there.
And it's not a bribe,
by the way.
I checked with a lawyer.
There is no law
against paying someone
not do a story.
You actually put money
in an envelope
and handed it to him?
No, not money.
He wanted a check.
- You gave him a check?
- Yes.
And you didn't wonder
why he wanted a check?
Yeah, because
it was 7,500, Ella.
And people don't want
to carry that much cash. Okay?
Why else would it be?
Evidence, Ryan!
(INHALES)
If...
Okay, okay.
How about we talk about us?
Sure. The marriage
isn't working for you.
No, but it could.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Remember what you said to me
about making things up to me
in your next speech?
- Yes.
- Right?
Well, this could be it.
This could fix us.
This...
I think this
could make us great.
Wha... What... (SCOFFS)
(SIGHS, EXHALES)
"My husband will be at my side,
using his experience
in the service industry
for the greatest service of all,
the welfare of all of you."
You wrote this yourself?
Yeah.
I mean, I ran it by the family,
- but... but yeah.
- Okay. (CLEARS THROAT)
"He will be part
of the governance
of the state we both love.
Our solid family values
will now be government values.
I'm happy to say you're getting
two for the price of one."
Mm-hmm.
Uh, this makes it sound like
you're co-governing with me.
Well, you sure can use me, Ella.
Because people,
mmm, like me. Yeah.
And to be honest, they see you...
(WHISPERS) Don't.
Okay, I'm not being funny. Okay?
If I don't get this...
If I don't have a job
with... with a title
- where I run things...
- Ryan.
...then what is
my purpose here, okay?
- What is your purpose?
- Without it, I'm your what?
Husband?
That's a hard thing to put
on a parking space.
(SCOFFS) Oh, my God.
Ella.
Just let me go
to my meeting, please,
- and we'll talk later, okay?
- No, no.
I can't do this marriage,
if I don't get this.
I'm not kidding. I can't.
You know, my mother told me
that you wanted those lunches
so that I wouldn't cheat
like your father.
Well, I am not your father.
Right?
When I'm unhappy,
I don't cheat, Ella.
I walk.
Like, right now.
(SIGHS)
Good!
(STAMMERS)
If you... if you can't do
a reconsider here, now,
then I'm gonna go public,
right away.
And... and it's not
gonna be like,
"they wish each other well,"
or something like that.
It's gonna be a divorce.
A messy divorce.
On top of everything else.
It would ruin your shot
at anything, Ella. Seriously.
Why would you do that
to yourself?
(EXHALES)
Because I don't think
you could be
doing any of this to me
right now if you even liked me.
Governor. Phone.
Yeah. Um...
No one who isn't on the list.
Yes, ma'am.
(APPLAUSE, CHEERING)
Please don't applaud!
(SCATTERED GASPS)
So sorry. Very. Excuse me.
I just need a minute.
WOMAN: Of course. Of course.
(LIGHT CHATTER)
(PANTING)
(VOICE BREAKING) Nope.
(SIGHS)
(SNIFFS)
Okay.
(PEOPLE SHUSHING)
Let's just plunge right in,
shall we?
Hi.
I'm so glad to see you all.
I really am.
(CROW CAWING)
This way.
(PANTING)
SUSAN: Just a sec!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Hi.
I, uh, I should've
brought something.
You know, some flowers
or a small car
with a bow around it.
What?
I'm sorr... I'm sorry.
I thought... I just thought
of saying that on the stairs
as, like, a kidding thing to
you know, maybe make you laugh...
I didn't realize
it was, like, a joke.
No, it's funny.
I laughed. I laughed.
- I'm sorry.
- No, I got it.
- Yeah.
- (CHUCKLING) Good to see you.
- Thanks.
- Um... You look, um...
- What? Thinner?
Uh, sure.
But I was gonna say
you look like...
Tense?
Um, no.
I mean, well, maybe.
I don't know.
Sorry, I'm not... I'm just...
I'm not letting you finish
your sentences, and I'm just...
You're not. But that is okay.
Um...
Also, we haven't even
left the doorway. So...
- Sorry.
- Nope. All good.
- Do you want to come inside?
- Yeah.
Oh. Okay, yeah.
(SIGHS)
Um, I was, uh...
Uh... (EXHALES)
- What? Case.
- Really? You wanna know?
(SLOWLY) Sure.
Well, okay, then.
Well, last time I was here,
I got in trouble for saying
something you thought,
possibly correctly,
was excessive.
Remember? I'm just... I'm not...
I'm not tryin' to jump
in your thoughts.
Could we catch up more slowly?
Slowly. Yeah. Okay.
(BLUSTERS)
SUSAN: Right. Okay.
Um... There is
a really great restaurant
a few blocks away from here,
and I think
you'll like the food.
So let's go there.
You'll like it.
It's not really like I remember
exactly what happened
way back then anyway. So...
Wh... Really?
You really don't remember?
Would it help
if I repeated the key parts
- of our last conversation?
- No!
No, it actually...
It would not... help. Um...
I think I thought
today would be a little more,
(BRIGHTLY)
"Hey, how things been?"
(IMITATING CASEY) "Really
normal. I've been so normal."
(BRIGHTLY)
"Oh, my gosh. Me too."
I'm actually not sure
I can do that, Susan.
You know,
I've given a lot of thought
to what I wanna say
about last time.
And I know I can't just pick up
on a year-old conversation.
- Okay.
- Great.
- Fine.
- Cool.
Cool.
Listen. I'm gonna get my coat,
and you're gonna
like the place. Cool?
Mm-hmm.
(EXHALES)
You know,
you don't get to act like this.
You're the one that
changed your number.
You did that!
Yeah, because
I didn't want to be aware
you weren't calling me. Okay?
(GASPS) You wouldn't have known
I changed my number
- unless you called.
- Yay, genius.
What were you gonna say
when you called?
What were you gonna say?
That I was very worried...
At the time.
Can we please stop? (GRUNTS)
(EXHALES)
(PANTING)
(WHIMPERS)
Okay, um...
I think we cut our losses.
This is weird,
a-a-and I am drained,
and you are still...
(EXHALES)
...screwy.
So, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I think I know what you mean!
All you asked for
was a little time to adjust,
and I couldn't do it for you.
Y-Yeah.
I still can't, Susan. I...
...still can't.
Okay.
(SIGHS)
But, but, but...
Hey, hey, hey.
There's a "but," okay?
There's a "but."
I think you've lost the thread
of the conversation
we were almost having.
Well, we were talking about
how last time I was here,
I asked you a question
in a very complicated way.
And I, you know, I know you'd
rather not deal with that again.
I strongly believe if I could
just ask in a more simple way,
you know, it'd clear the past,
and we could go out,
and you know,
we could go eat and...
Hey! We could have some fun.
(SIGHS) Could you just...
come here please?
Please?
(GROANS)
I was gonna, maybe...
maybe sit down in the...
(SUSAN EXHALES)
CASEY: I, uh...
Well, uh...
You know, maybe
instead of talking about it,
I'll just, uh...
Yeah, I'll just do it, okay?
Okay.
Well, the, um, question
I actually
wanted to ask way back then
and, uh...
just as much now is, um...
Susan,
would you be my girlfriend?
(QUIETLY) Case...
(SIGHS)
Yeah?
Um...
I... I almost envy
the way you just don't, um...
No, uh...
Okay. Well, listen.
You know,
a lot of time has passed.
And... and
we've had other experiences
a-a-and been with other people.
Um... Or not. I didn't... That's...
As a hypothetical, maybe.
Um...
What I mean is...
You know,
if you had asked me back then
the way that
you just asked me now,
I mean...
Would things be different? I...
I mean, I don't know. Maybe.
You're giving a very
complicated answer, Susan.
Just...
Just tell me, you know?
Yeah. Yeah. Simple is better.
Okay. Yeah.
I-I think
I'll be your girlfriend.
You...
(STAMMERS)
Okay. Um...
I'm gonna be honest. I'm just
as surprised as you are.
But that's
the way things are now,
so can we go eat, please?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Great. Thank you very much.
Okay.
(CHUCKLES)
- I'm stoked.
- (GIGGLES)
Okay, yeah. This... This'll...
- This'll work. Yeah.
- Yeah.
GUARD:
Proceed in an orderly fashion...
- (THUNDER RUMBLES)
- REPORTER: Hold on. Slow down.
Calm down!
REPORTER: Ryan, could you
add anything to what you said
at your press conference?
Uh, well, my wife was the one
who thought
a payoff would be
the way to handle it.
And... it was her decision
to end our marriage.
I'm sorry.
And did you all discuss...
I think that's all
I'm gonna say.
- (PHONES RINGING SIMULTANEOUSLY)
- Thank you, Ryan.
(RINGING, VIBRATING CONTINUES)
Who is helping
the local community ed boards?
Who on our side
is at their side?
- (LIGHT SNORING)
- I have a document to show you
on the secondary education
system in Oregon,
which is, I mean,
absolutely fascinating. It...
Good grief!
(SNORING)
I-I lost all track of time.
I'm so sorry. I just...
I just think we have
a really great foothold here.
But, um...
(SIGHS) I just wanna say I'm...
- I'm stoked!
- (SCATTERED GASPS)
I hope you are too.
And if you're not, well, it's...
it's my job to get you there.
- NASH: Stay back!
- (THUMPING)
NASH: Please, stay back.
That's an order!
Get back.
(SHOUTING)
NASH: Governor!
- NASH: We got you.
- (GRUNTS)
Get back! That's an order!
- Get back!
MALE REPORTER: Her husband's
saying that the governor
endorsed the $7,500 payment
and claimed
that it was for, quote,
"public relations counseling."
State Senator Tom Lawrence
is now considering
a bill of censure
against the governor.
Hey! Wait!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
REPORTER: The governor seemed
to be in a state of collapse
when she was helped
from the buil...
(QUIETLY) Damn press.
I... can't hear you.
- (GRUNTS)
- Ooh. No. Uh...
I'm sick of not hearing you.
Be careful, please.
Ooh.
Belt. Belt. Belt.
Seatbelt, please. Seatbelt.
(CLICKS)
(WEAKLY) What did you say?
Um...
Just... "Damn press."
Mmm.
It's too easy
to blame reporters.
They're up against
the same things
hitting everyone right now.
Cutbacks,
extreme work load,
loss of dignity...
(INHALES) ...loss of mission.
Oh, whoa. Whoa.
ELLA: Who knows?
Maybe we're all just hamsters
on the same wheel.
Beginning to worry
that the kid who bought us...
...has started to lose interest.
NASH: Whoa.
That is... heavy duty.
- (PHONE RINGS)
- (BEEPS)
Snowbird.
It's Maggie.
Put her on the phone!
Ma'am, the majority leader
wants to speak with you.
(WINDSHIELD WIPERS CLICKING)
I know how wimpy it sounds...
I... I can't.
She cannot come
to the phone right now.
MAGGIE: You're in the damn car
with her, Trooper.
And you're in
way over your head.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll let her know you called.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Governor,
I'm taking you to the ER.
No. No.
What that would turn into.
Ma'am,
I was a paramedic before this,
and you're exhibiting signs
of a small concussion.
(SIGHS)
All I need is a place to think.
That's it.
Please.
(MUFFLED LAUGHTER)
- Can you do it?
- (LAUGHING)
- That's gross.
- Ready?
(MUFFLED CHATTER)
Thanks! (SIGHS)
Of course.
(PANTING)
You did this
under my instructions.
So, no worries.
- Don't worry.
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
Okay?
- Hi.
- Thank you, God.
- Hi. Come in. Come on.
- Okay.
Let's... Let's get you
dried off...
- Hi.
- ...and... and in a shower.
And there's some clothes
from previous weights of mine
in the back closet.
Soup. Soup?
I'll get you some soup.
Are you okay?
- Okay.
(RAPID FOOTSTEPS)
(WHISPERS) I'm okay.
Yeah, well, prove it.
Say something other than,
"I'm okay."
(SIGHS)
I feel strange.
I keep thinking of this thing
I once read.
An avalanche victim.
This woman was almost
completely buried alive.
And, uh...
Lost the thread.
- Avalanche victim.
- Right.
And she could only
move two fingers.
So she dug with them for hours
to clear a tiny pocket
around her mouth
just because she needed
to hear herself scream.
You can use a scream, Ella.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Yeah. Go on.
Do it.
- (WHISPERS) No.
- Do it.
Come on. Just scream.
All right.
Let's go!
Okay!
(INHALES, SIGHS)
(HELEN SIGHS)
(ELLA INHALES DEEPLY)
- No.
- (SIGHS)
No. I might not be able to stop.
That's too bad,
I was gonna join you.
(LAUGHS)
(SIREN BLIPS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(SIGHS)
- Hi. Ella here?
- No.
- Hi, Bill.
- Oh, look. There she is.
Oh. Hi.
This is a terrible hiding place.
I'm Helen McCay. Please excuse
the way I talk or act.
Okay.
Look, I got the whole
leadership with me.
The time bind
we're in is killer.
Uh, how many people is that?
What?
- Fifteen, twenty, thirty?
- What difference does it make?
Because then we should
do this at my bar.
On the corner. Helen's.
Okay. Don't tap me.
(DOOR CLOSES)
BILL: Let's go!
ESTELLE (VO): Oh, boy,
were they waiting for this.
They were finally
about to get rid of Ella,
who was a constant reminder
that their recurring night sweat
self-doubts about themselves
were maybe just plain true.
Why so many of them?
Dear God.
- MAN: Right this way, for two.
- WOMAN: Over here.
(SIGHS)
We are so tight on time
since your husband
decided to do his...
...moment.
What did he do?
He went public with
the fact that you two split up.
And he gave the reason why.
And the reason was?
Can I just do this with Ella?
No. And the reason was?
And the reason was?
He said he was the one who
wanted to preserve the marriage,
but it was you
who wanted to end it.
Even though you admitted to him
that you couldn't
do the job without him.
(SCOFFS)
And he said you agreed to claim
the 7,500-dollar payout
was gonna be used for some
bullshit
public relations advice?
Fuck his shit heart!
(PATRONS GASPING)
I'm sorry. I've never...
I've never said that before
and ever will again. I'm s...
So...
...that makes me someone who
can't make her home life work,
- so how could I possibly govern?
- Govern.
That's exactly
what your instant polls say.
Let the majority leader
go into this with you.
- Maggie!
- Yeah!
Okay.
- Hi, Ella.
- Hi, Maggie.
Okay. Let's do this quick.
We'd like you
to resign immediately.
If not, we'll censure you
for general incompetence,
which would make you
just a figurehead
for the next 14 months
of your term.
It's a lot to take in.
But I also knew
you wouldn't want any bullshit.
And, um, sorry, sorry, sorry,
but we need you
to decide this news cycle.
Right now, actually.
(SIGHS) Hmm...
Bill?
Hmm?
Would you come outside with me
for a second, please?
One minute.
Remember your promise, Bill.
- Your promise?
- I don't know what she means.
Hey!
Help her or go to hell.
Nice input.
We have to wrap this up quickly.
I can't trust my brain
right now.
I understand.
Unemployment or impotence.
It's a tough choice.
If it helps,
there's no cherry on either one.
(SIGHS)
It's the tiger or the tiger.
But either way, they're
gonna call you Governor forever.
And that's a...
that's a nice thing.
Am I making a fundamental
mistake here? About us?
What's the mistake?
(SIGHS) Are you my friend, Bill?
Well...
Under the circumstances,
that's an extremely
complicated question.
Okay.
Yes, I'm your friend.
I'm your friend.
Hi, friend.
But I've got a side here, too.
With the confirmation, this
is the only hand I can play.
Yeah.
My promise to them
was to stay out of it.
But it doesn't mean I can't
think of some advice out loud.
What they want you to do, Ella,
is exactly what you should do.
Get out while the going's bad,
because if you don't,
they'll joyously
make it worse for you.
Joyously? Why joyously?
Because you do the worst thing
a person can do to them.
(STAMMERING) You're poking
them in their limitations.
I'm telling you, Ella,
they will make
the next 14 months hell...
hell... as payback.
So, unless you're
a humiliation junkie...
I'm not a humiliation junkie.
Well, then go in there now
and resign.
- No. Bill, I can't do that.
- Why?
(WHISPERS) I love the job.
They will not let you do shit.
They will not let you
take a pencil home.
Okay. I'm done.
I really...
I gotta get outta here.
If, uh...
If anybody asks
what we did out here...
Goes without saying.
Go get confirmed.
Thanks. Goodbye.
BILL: Ella?
I... I think I'm allowed to make
one very intelligent observation
for you to mull.
When this many people show up
to make you do something,
you're holding better cards
than you think.
Use that as you will.
Nice.
I didn't let
you down completely.
(CHUCKLES)
Good luck, El.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES,
ENGINE STARTS)
(CAR DEPARTS)
(SIGHS)
- I'm staying.
- (PATRONS JEER)
- Are you kidding me?
- What?
MAN: Oh, no, no!
Can you try not to be
a roadkill do-gooder
and be a politician
for a second?
Let's talk. Maybe we can come
to some compromise.
Oh, sorry. "Consensus."
Sure.
For starters,
don't stand over me like that.
This isn't personal.
I'm just doing my job.
Oh, it sure feels personal,
Maggie.
(INHALES, SIGHS)
Go for it.
If I don't get what I want,
I will not only stay in office,
but run again as an independent
against whomever you nominate.
(LAUGHS)
Yes, I will lose.
But get what? How many votes?
My approval rating
has a floor someplace.
Little Miss Nooner
has some fans, doesn't she?
Even if I just get
eleven percent,
there's no way the party wins.
You know that.
(SIGHS)
Or...?
Or...
I will leave.
If...?
ESTELLE (VO): Yeah. Gotcha.
If...
ESTELLE (VO): There would be
two ways of looking
at Ella's governorship.
That it was an embarrassment,
primarily marked
by a silly personal scandal...
or the way I see it,
and love it,
that given just
three days in office...
I feel good about this.
...she left
an extraordinary record
of legislative accomplishment.
(MAGGIE SIGHS)
Oh, the, uh, dental stuff,
I'm afraid there's no room
left in the budget for...
Hardly anything needed.
The Dental Association
is footing the bill.
They could use some public
pats on the back
to keep them motivated.
Pats, I got.
Thanks, Maggie.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
EDDIE: Ella...
I lost my ticket to a good life.
Not right now.
No, Ella. Ca...
Can you make this the minute?
The one that's always
been there, waiting for us.
The minute you need.
Can you forgive me?
(SIGHS)
Not really.
(FOOTSTEPS, DOOR OPENS)
ESTELLE (VO): I get all that
good stuff about forgiving,
but aren't there times
when never forgiving
can also set you free?
Just asking.
HELEN: I simply cannot
contain my anger at Ryan.
I have never been this angry,
where it is unbearable.
You... you can't imagine
what it feels like. You can't.
I need to act on it.
You're wrong.
I can imagine how it feels.
(SIGHS) I...
(STAMMERING) You're...
Sitting on it.
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
That must be very frustrating.
Correct!
Well, that's what not screaming
will get you. Hmm?
So, listen, Ella.
- I do have something...
- (SCREAMS)
(SIGHS)
- (YELPS)
(STIFLED LAUGHTER)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(SUSTAINED SCREAM)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(LAUGHTER)
Well, we should do that
every afternoon.
Yeah, we should.
(LAUGHS)
Tremendous, tremendous feeling.
(GASPS)
I, uh... Wow!
- Ella.
- Yeah?
I...
I've been avoiding something.
There is a slate that needs
to be cleaned.
What...
My problem is,
I am unable to move past
what Ryan did.
I understand that you have
a different way of, you know...
processing his douchiness.
So?
So, I did something.
Okay...
Ella, I put something in motion.
But I'm worried that I...
that I should have consulted
with you first.
ELLA: Hmm...
(INHALES DEEPLY) Well...
For me, it's easy.
I am just going to go
with what I've always believed.
Aunt Helen knows best.
(CHUCKLES)
Thank you. Love you.
ESTELLE (VO): We kid ourselves,
but most endings in life
are inevitable.
Whether you earn them
or had it coming.
Are you a moron? Are you?
(STAMMERING)
Are you a moron?
'Cause I can just rip this down.
It means nothing.
What the hell
are you smiling at?
- The next second.
- What do you mean, the next...
Do you...
I'm just talking with...
Ooh, resisting.
- I...
- Let's go.
You have no idea
who you're dealing with.
Guys, guys.
OFFICER: You assaulted
a public official.
Come on. Let's... Let's
just have something to eat.
Resisting.
I know what you like.
I remember, it's pepperoni...
- Okay, yeah.
- Extra cheese...
And you're Hawaiian?
Hawaiian.
- I'm sorry. I apologize.
- Attempted bribery.
- I'm sorry! I'm sorry.
- Love it, love it, love it.
You guys, I thank you
for everything you do,
but this is
completely unnecessary!
- This is...
- (INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
I'm... I'm sorry.
ESTELLE (VO): Sometimes
"I'm sorry" comes way too late.
It took a while, but Ella
got exactly what she fought for,
passage of the Mom's Bill,
and one of the few pieces
of policy that's fun to say.
Tooth Tutors. Tooth Tutors!
Tooth Tutors!
It's fun! Come on, admit it.
MAN: Legal Aid/Tenants Aid,
how may I help you?
ESTELLE (VO):
Another phone room.
But this one is all Ella's baby.
So there's one big difference.
No one's asking
for anything. Except...
WOMAN: How can we help you?
MAN: (LAUGHS) It's our pleasure.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
WOMAN 2:
There's no charge.
MAN 2: Absolutely,
they can't raise the rent...
WOMAN 3: Would you like
a ride to our offices?
We can pick you up.
WOMAN 4:
God bless you, too.
ESTELLE (VO): Yes, government
can help folks.
But, in the end,
for any grand plan to work...
humans help humans.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
This is for her.
Hey.
You should do it.
I told you.
You did. You did.
Um... (CLEARS THROAT)
Hey, everyone. Hi, um...
I just found out
that we have prevented
3,022 evictions so far,
which means that we have kept
a roof over the heads
of 9,080 families so far.
- So, congratulations!
- (CHEERS, APPLAUSE)
You did great.
Thank you.
ESTELLE (VO):
One last thought.
There is no opposite word
for "trauma."
But "hope" comes close.