Hey, Rick.
Hi. I made it.
Phillip.
The culprit is here.
We must capture him.
That is our challenge.
How did you know?
Your face.
Yeah?
I hope you have
a clean black suit.
Morning, Sonia.
I got you a gig today
at 10:00 a.m. in Saitama.
I know it's kinda far,
but can you make it?
Of course.
What's the production?
They didn't give us
too many details,
but pays pretty well.
- What's my role?
- Sad American.
The fuck?
Guess that means
no zombies.
Nope.
Anyway, you've got 15 minutes.
Until what?
The next guest will arrive.
And he won't be getting up.
Nothing about that was fake.
Especially to Mr. Daito.
The man in the box.
Well, what would you call it,
then?
You know?
I might be able
to use you for something
more than a sad American.
All right.
I knew you would come.
So what do you think we do?
You, if I have to guess
you, um
you sell people.
- No.
We sell emotion.
Oh.
How?
We play roles
in the clients' lives.
Thanks.
But...
you can't just,
you know,
replace someone in your life.
Yes and no.
But people are willing
to take a leap.
The actor, the surrogate.
You don't have to be
that person.
You just have to help clients
connect to what's missing.
- Like what?
- Well,
could be anybody
from their life.
Or a feeling they once had.
Parents, siblings, boyfriends,
girlfriends, best friends.
We play it all.
Well, they could just
get a therapist.
It's not that easy here.
Mental health issues are
stigmatized in this country.
So people have to turn
to other things.
Like us.
Well, what do you need me for?
We need a token white guy.
It's a niche market.
And I need someone
to fill the role.
Just token white guy.
Um, I'm... I'm just an actor.
I don't know how to help people.
But you know how to perform.
I've seen the résumé.
Look, what I'm offering here
is a chance to play roles
with real meaning.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate it.
It was nice...
Nice meeting you.
Eh?
Huh?
Nice to meet you.
- How you doing?
- I like this commercial.
- Thanks.
- How long ago was that?
Seven years?
That's what brought you
to Japan, right?
Well, I'm sure you have plenty
of acting gigs to go back to.
Or you can give this a try.
Because you are Canadian
and you got a job at home.
Here. Your name is
Brian Callahan.
Okay.
Are you sure
that I'm not too old for you?
No.
An older man feels
a little more responsible.
How are your parents
taking all of this?
Thank you
for doing this for me.
Of course.
Can't she just
leave her family?
She can't. She loves them.
What about the truth?
Well, sometimes the story
we tell ourselves
becomes the truth.
To her parents,
you are her husband.
Memorize everything
in the folder.
Every word. Every detail.
- Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Brian?
- Brian?
- Shit.
Phillip?
What's going on?
Nothing. Just...
I need a moment.
How long's a moment?
A moment, you know?
A moment.
We need you downstairs now.
Aiko, listen. I'm sorry.
I can't go through with this.
Listen.
All you have to do is sip sake.
That's it.
No. It's... It's a lie.
I'm messing with people's lives.
You cannot do this to me.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
This is not a lie.
It's an opportunity.
The parents get
the memory they want.
The bride gets her freedom.
If you don't go through with
this, you will ruin her life.
Do you understand?
Get out.
Phillip.
Come on!
Go. Go.
Welcome to our family, Brian.
That was
a beautiful wedding.
Yes.
Nice room.
Very.
I got it.
Phillip?
Congratulations.
I got married today, Lola.
No, it was for work.
Well, it was...
It was terrifying
and exhilarating.
And I haven't felt something
like that in a long time.
And I know that it was fake,
but there were moments
that it felt real.
Already?
Hmm.
I give you ten more minutes.
It's your wedding night.
But
if you wanna keep this job,
I need to know that you're
committed moving forward.
No more hiding in bathrooms.
That won't happen again.
I am, I promise.
- Huh?
- A father?
Later.
This girl needs a father
in order to transfer
to a private school.
You can't be a single mother?
She's been denied once,
and her mother
doesn't wanna risk it again.
Oh, I get it.
So I just play her dad
for the interview?
Actually, no.
The mother thinks
it'll be better
if her daughter believes
you're her real father.
Why?
Well, she's been
feeling down, lately.
And her mother's hoping
that meeting her father
would give her
the confidence she needs.
Also, the mother
doesn't want her daughter
to have to pretend
during the interview.
So, your relationship with her
has to feel authentic.
Listen, I didn't grow up
with a father,
so I don't really know
how to be one.
Now is your chance.
How long is the commitment?
Well, you will meet with her
regularly.
At least up till the test,
which is in three weeks.
So, you need to
get to know her right away.
What if she finds out?
She can't.
You have to trust yourself.
Hey.
Can you give me
just five minutes?
Why?
Come on. Please.
Can I get you
something to drink?
Nope.
You knew the situation.
You knew we were
her last option,
and you still nearly backed out.
- But I didn't.
- But you would have.
See, you're just a...
You will never understand
how things work here.
- You're right.
- I am...
But Japan is my home now. And
I want to try to understand.
Why do you do this?
- What?
- This job.
You're so passionate
about it. Why?
It's the way
these people look at you.
Like they've been waiting
for you their whole lives.
Despite everything Tada says,
these people stay with you.
Sometimes all we need
is someone to look us in the eye
and remind us we exist.
Hello there, Mia.
My name is Kevin.
I'm your father.
Hi, Mia. I'm your father.
No, that's way too formal.
Hi, Mia. You've grown so much.
Look how big you are.
I'm Kevin. I'm your father.
I missed you.
Hitomi-san.
Hi. Thank you for coming.
Please take this.
It's a backpack.
She's been begging me for it.
Perfect.
So, she doesn't know
she's meeting you today.
Oh.
She wouldn't have come
otherwise.
Okay, no problem.
Thank you.
Hello, Mia.
Here. Look,
I got you something.
I hope you like it.
- I hate it!
- Mia!
You can't bribe me.
I'm sorry that
you feel that way, Mia.
And I know
that I have not been here...
Mia!
Hey. Mia!
Stop following me!
I know her! Hey.
Go away.
Wait up.
Please, stop. I can explain.
Did you think
you can just show up?
Your mom said that you need me
to get you into school.
That's the only reason
why you're here?
No, no, no. It's not.
I've been wanting to see you,
and there hasn't been a moment
when I haven't thought
about you.
Why did you leave us, then?
Because I was stupid.
And I can see,
you're very angry with me.
And you probably
shouldn't forgive me,
but I'm here now.
Mia.
Yes. We need him.
Let me be some use to you.
Fine.
But lock it and swear
you'll never leave us again.
Okay.
I... I swear.
Sorry.
How's it going, dad?
She hates me.
That's what being a parent is.
No, I am serious.
She hates me.
She doesn't hate you.
She hates
the man you're playing.
Listen to what they want,
and feed them what they need.
You're just acting.
Acting. I know. Just acting.
Anyway,
I've got a new client for you.
You know the actor,
Kikuo Hasegawa?
Of course.
Well,
he thinks he's been forgotten.
So his daughter wants
someone to interview him
to honor his legacy.
Wow.
This is a really
impressive collection.
Classic. Mingus,
"Myself When I am Real"?
Do you play?
No, I don't, unfortunately.
Um...
But I admire.
My father, he, uh,
he played bass.
Never thought
of it that way before.
Let's get
some air.
Okay, let's do that.
What do you want to know?
Everything.
There's nobody like you.
You can record my voice,
but please, no video.
- Hi, Mia.
- Thank you for being here.
Mia.
Sorry.
I should be done by 1:00 p.m.
All right.
So what are we gonna make?
Can you be his dad too?
Of course.
What... What is that?
Okay.
Well, you're
gonna have to show me how.
Thanks for helping Shion.
Meet me at the karaoke box.
You're going to be
a cheerleader today.
I love video games.
Yeah, count me in.
Nice room.
One more time.
Yeah!
Kaori-san.
Right this way.
My name is Takashi.
Hello. How are you?
Good to meet you.
Did you trim your beard?
It looks good, man.
Wow!
Well, this is amazing.
It's cool.
But it's fake.
But isn't it real
to the person who made it?
You know, sometimes
it's okay to pretend.
I gotta take a quick call.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
- Hello?
- Hey!
So, you remember
the detective series
you auditioned for last month?
- You got the part.
- Really?
- Congratulations, Phillip.
- Wow.
They're shooting in Korea
and want you there right away.
I am so happy for you.
Well deserved.
It's good. It's great.
Oh, I have a really good
feeling about this one.
Hello?
Hey, listen, um...
I'm gonna have to go.
Let me get back to you.
All right?
Call me back soon.
There you are.
Are you coming?
Yeah.
Heaven on your tongue.
You try.
Is everything
all right with your daughter?
"The man on the screen."
Do you regret it?
Not at the time.
Do you have any children?
I have a daughter.
No.
No. But I would like to be.
Mmm.
- Are you my mother?
- No.
Oh, shit.
Kikuo-san. Kikuo-san!
Hey, hey! Stop, stop, stop!
Kikuo-san!
Hey, where are you going?
Listen. It's me. It's John.
We were eating together.
And I'm writing a story
about you.
Yeah. I think it's time
to go home.
Yeah.
We're gonna go in here
and get your shoes. All right?
I can't hear you.
So, what do you do?
I'm a computer engineer.
What's your nationality?
American.
My great-grandparents were
from Ireland.
I'm part Irish?
Yes, that's right.
You are.
Wow, that's cool.
Where were you born?
Sit.
Let's say this is, um,
Japan right here.
And, over here, way over here,
this is America.
Sort of like that.
And right in the middle
is a place called...
Minnesota.
Is that
where my grandparents live?
Uh, no. My mom did.
My dad wasn't around that much.
Do you talk to them?
No. They're gone now.
Do you have anyone left?
I have you now.
I have an idea.
Type in your number.
- Okay.
- Here. Here.
Okay...
♪ Meow meow meow! ♪
Now, I can message you.
And you won't feel alone.
I'll race you to the sweet shop.
Oh.
Wow.
- Hi.
Yes.
Mmm!
Mia.
You got that right.
Well, what do I owe you?
For you, it's on the house.
No. No, I...
I owe you, Natsumi.
Whoa.
- Bye.
Yeah.
"Do not open
until you get home."
Hey, Sonia.
Hey, I was about to call you.
Listen, I... I'm gonna pass.
What? Why?
You're joking, right?
No. I'm not.
I don't understand.
You told me
this is what you wanted.
I know. Please tell them
that I'm very grateful,
but I made a promise to someone
and I need to keep it.
Phillip, you know,
this could literally
change your career.
I... I can't do it.
Are you sure?
I mean, you've waited
so long for this.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for everything
that you've done.
We'll talk soon.
I'm... That's... I got it...
Hi, Mia.
I don't wanna take the test.
No, it... Your mom says that
it's one of the best schools
in Japan.
What if I get bullied?
Well, then I will put you
in karate classes. Hi-yah!
Okay, listen,
you're gonna be great.
You're almost at the end,
and I just know
you're gonna impress everyone.
- I hope so.
- You will.
I believe in you, Mia.
Thank you. See you soon.
- Shall I?
- Sure.
Okay, there should be three
to five teachers
at the interview.
When you speak, hold eye contact
for no more than five seconds.
And our answers?
Short and to the point.
- Should we hold hands?
- No.
You can show some emotion,
but don't become emotional.
Yeah.
If they ask me,
I answer,
That's it? I just say, "Nothing"?
Yes.
The school
does not want pressure
from the parents.
Yeah, but it's your child.
How long is she gonna be
going to school there for?
Through high school for now,
but she could go
to their university
if she does well.
Is it normal to determine
a child's future so early?
I'm sorry, but I didn't hire you
to lecture me
on how to raise my child.
I'm not trying to interfere.
Then why are you talking
with her on the phone?
Sending her messages?
I'm just trying to help.
This kid just wants
to talk to her dad.
You are not her father.
I know.
Do you pray?
Not since I was 15.
What happened?
I turned 16.
A little too early
to give it up.
No.
No, I just...
I have these memories
of being made
to go to church, and...
I never saw the point.
"When in Rome,
do as Romans do."
Mmm.
But I also think it means
becoming more than yourself.
Hey, um, what is in there?
Maybe another time.
In Amakusa.
Why?
I left something behind.
And can't Masami go
and get it for you?
Masami cannot know
that we are going.
Why not?
Sometimes,
all a man has are his secrets.
Hey, it's me.
Wow.
How many clients have you had?
Seven or maybe eight hundred.
And you just keep 'em all?
Yeah. As a reminder
of how many people need
our help.
It's growing on me.
You're good at it.
Thank you.
It hasn't gotten too personal?
No.
I don't think so.
Well, the little girl's
mother called.
Yeah?
She wants the next session
to be your last.
What?
Why?
She's getting
a little too attached.
What am I supposed to tell her?
That you have to go back
to the States.
That you will miss her.
Just like that?
That's how this business works.
All relationships have to end.
Then what?
We move on.
There's always someone new.
You'll get used to it.
Okay. Yeah.
Yeah.
Hello.
Hey, John.
What's all this?
Hey, listen. I can't take you.
Sure you can.
What if something happens
to you?
Aren't you a writer?
I am.
Then how can you write my story
if you don't start
at the beginning?
Your daughter wants you to stay.
I'll...
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- No.
Did you study the notes?
Got it.
Do you have any questions?
I'm good.
Okay.
Mia, are you okay?
- I think so.
- Hey. You got this.
You're gonna do great.
Kevin.
No, look, just...
See?
- She's very talented.
- Right?
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Which one is it?
- Honest communication.
Sorry. Americans,
we talk before we think.
Mia has a lot
of individual personality.
Do you think she will
get along with other students?
Individual personality?
We want our students
to excel on their own,
but we need to know
they can work with others.
She has plenty of friends
at her current school.
And she's very thoughtful.
She asked me to be a father
to a little boy
whose parents didn't come
to the class visitations.
Yes,
and if you should choose
to accept our daughter,
please be there for her.
She needs to dream big,
and she needs to be unafraid.
She makes me a better person
every day.
And I'm sure that
she will make this
a better school.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Can we have dinner together?
Mia, he can't.
Why?
I have to go back to America.
For how long?
A year, maybe longer.
But you just got here.
I know.
You work from here?
My friend's dad works from home.
I can't.
They need me there.
You'll be back, right?
I want you to know
how proud I am of you.
I'm gonna need you
to be strong for your mom.
Can you do that?
I'll miss you, Dad.
Mia?
Take care, Hitomi.
I'm really gonna miss that kid.
Her mom did
what she thought was best.
Yeah.
Would you ever use our service?
- You mean hire someone?
- Mm-hmm.
Never thought of that.
Well, if you could hire someone
to play someone in your life,
who would that be?
- You're being serious?
- Yeah.
My mom.
Why?
Because she never judged me.
And it would be nice
to feel that again.
Who would you choose?
Me?
- I don't know.
- Come on, don't give me that.
I don't.
Well, at least tell me
what happened here.
Were you in an underground
Tokyo fight club?
I wish, I mean...
Angry housewife.
It was for a job?
You tell Tada?
Yeah.
It comes with the territory.
You know apologies are
our most popular service.
I'm probably the last person
you should ask for advice from,
but if you ever need someone
to talk to...
Thanks.
Kikuo-san, psst, hey.
Kikuo-san, wake up.
- John.
- You ready?
For what?
Jailbreak.
Yeah. Here.
Put this on.
What is this?
It's your disguise. Go ahead.
Terrible.
I choose my own costume.
♪ Now, I'm wakin'
At the crack of dawn  ♪
♪ To send
A little money home  ♪
♪ From here to the moon  ♪
♪ Is risin' like
A discotheque  ♪
Go!
♪ Lookin' at happiness  ♪
♪ Keepin' my flavor fresh  ♪
♪ Nobody knows I guess...  ♪
♪ Leavin' at six o'clock
Meet in a parkin' lot  ♪
♪ Harriet Hendershot  ♪
♪ Sunglasses on
She waits by this  ♪
♪ Glass and concrete
And stone ♪
♪ It is just a house... ♪
Hmm.
Kikuo-san.
Japan has more
gods than vending machines.
Kikuo-san.
Kikuo-san!
What are you doing?
Okay. It's okay.
What is...
My life
before... my life.
Is that you?
You good?
Hey, I need to make a call.
So, I'll...
- Hey. Um...
- Where are you?
- I'm in Amakusa.
- What? Where?
I'm with Kikuo. He's fine.
How can you be so stupid?
You kidnapped our client!
- I didn't kidnap him.
- You took him from his home.
No, he asked for something,
and I gave it to him.
Isn't...
Isn't that what we do?
Fulfillment.
It wasn't your choice to make.
No, it was his.
If one word of this gets out,
my business is gone.
- Do you understand that?
- You're a hypocrite.
You talk about helping people,
and you act like
you're saving them
when you're actually
hurting them.
- What are you talking about?
- Aiko, the bruise on her face.
Now, that's on you.
How dare you.
Kikuo-san. Kikuo. Kikuo.
Kikuo. Kikuo-san.
Hey, hey, hey. Kikuo-san.
Fuck.
Kikuo-san.
Mia.
You look like shit.
Hey, thanks for getting me out.
It wasn't just me.
What did Kikuo say?
That he forced you
to be his accomplice.
He did?
And he told Masami-san
to drop the charges.
So why did you do it?
I needed to help him.
But why take the risk?
Um...
My father died two years ago.
And, um...
I didn't go to the funeral.
Got on a train
and went to the airport...
I just...
just sat in the terminal.
So I wanted to be there
for Kikuo.
Hey.
I will
see you again, my friend.
Did you say goodbye?
Yeah, I did.
I am sorry for what I said.
I needed to hear it.
Come on.
Hey, Mia.
Congratulations on
getting into school.
Is my mom paying you?
No. But I asked her
if I could visit you.
Why are you here?
I'm just here to talk.
I don't talk to strangers.
I can go, if you want.
Why do adults always lie?
It's because it's a lot easier
than telling the truth.
Sometimes they lie
to protect the people
that they care about,
but your mom never wanted
to hurt you.
You hurt me too.
And you promised you wouldn't.
I know.
I know. And I'm sorry.
We should've been
honest with you.
It's not fair.
I liked you being my dad.
Me too.
You know, you could have
told me you were famous.
I'm not famous.
What's your real name?
I'm Phillip.
I'm Mia.
Where... And how did you
get on that TV show?
How'd I get on a TV show?