[Dramatic music plays]
[High-pitched ringing builds,
stops]
-[Clears throat]
Your Honor?
-Well, this seems to me
to be fairly cut and dry.
The attempts the defense
has made to paint Mr. Holloway
as a man positively filled
to bursting with remorse...
...laughable, frankly.
You stand there,
talk, talk, talk --
"So sorry.
Never do it again."
But you did, didn't you?
Do it.
Again, again, again.
This wasn't just
a one-time thing.
This was all the time.
A myriad of chances to act
on your professed conscience.
None taken.
So...with that in mind...
...with that in mind...
[High-pitched ringing]
...with that in mind,
Mr. Holloway, please stand.
Grant Holloway,
on these eight counts
of sexual violation of a minor,
I sentence you
to 16 years' imprisonment.
[Spectators murmuring]
With a mimit--
With a minimum non-parole period
of nine years.
-[Whispering]
Thank you.
-On the charge
of reckless abandonment...
-[Voice breaking]
Thank you. Thank you.
-...of reckless abandonment --
on the --
-Thank you.
Thank you.
-Where there are no lions,
hyenas rule.
Wouldn't you agree, madam?
-I...
-That where there are no lions,
then hyenas rule?
-Uh, I don't...
-You mustn't thank me.
I don't want your thanks.
You're culpable.
You put your children at risk --
five children.
Helpless, vulnerable.
And you knew.
You knew full well what was
going on, and you did nothing.
Deplorable.
So no, please don't thank me.
Search your soul instead.
You're not the victim here.
Do you understand?
You're not.
There's no excuse.
You're culp--
culp...lable.
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Glass sliding]
Despicab--
[Gags]
[Exhales deeply, grunts]
[Spectators gasping, murmuring]
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Machinery whirring]
[Music continues]
[Velcro crackling]
[Button clicks]
[High-pitched ringing]
[Music continues]
-Ahh.
[Air hissing, monitor beeping]
[Indistinct conversations]
- Ooh! Ooh!
Granddad, did you get
your present?
-Yes. The nice lady's
just getting it ready.
Oh.
Righto.
I see.
[Children laughing,
woman speaking indistinctly]
Tieke, saddleback -- 12:00 p.m.
- It's my turn.
Get out of the way.
Hi, Granddad!
You like your new clock?
[Children laughing]
-You good, Nigel?
You lost?
You need anything?
You're good?
Morning.
You're good.
[Birds chirping, door beeps]
[Door beeps, handle rattling]
Oh, for fuck's sake.
[Chair whirring]
-[Coughing]
-Oh.
Much obliged.
[Man coughs, exhales deeply]
-[Laughing]
Oh.
You want to watch out
for that one.
I reckon he knows
when you're about to...
Kkht.
[Chuckles]
Ah.
-Oh. No.
Thank you.
-Ah. You're...not from around
these parts, huh?
-I'm a judge in the city.
-Oh. What are you doing
in a shithole like this?
-No one's really admitting
people at the moment,
especially from hospitals --
at least within
my price bracket.
-Pour the pension
into the pokies, did you?
-Oh, God, no.
The four most dangerous words
in the investment world are
"This time, it's different."
-[Laughs]
You're still stuck with us!
-No.
It's temporary.
-[Coughs, groans]
[Birds chirping]
Hey, hey, hey. Aah!
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
[Screaming]
-Help!
Help!
-Oh, no!
-Help! Oh!
Help!
[Screaming continues]
[Voice echoing, man snoring]
[Snoring continues]
[Lid snaps, urine trickling]
[Hinges creaking]
[Guitar strums]
-♪ Down at the English fair ♪
♪ One evening I was there ♪
♪ When I heard the showman
shouting ♪
♪ Underneath the flair ♪
[Inhales deeply]
♪ "Terry's got a lovely bunch
of coconuts ♪
♪ There they are,
all hanging in a row ♪
♪ Big ones, small ones,
some as big as your head ♪
♪ Give 'em a twist,
a flick of the wrist" ♪
♪ That's what the showman said ♪
♪ Oh! ♪
Who's next?
-Me.
[Music continues]
-♪ "Olive's got a lovely bunch
of coconuts ♪
♪ There they are,
all hanging in a row ♪
♪ A big one, a small one,
one as big as your head ♪
♪ Give it a twist,
a flick of the wrist" ♪
♪ That's what the showman said ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Stefan's got a lovely -- ♪
♪ Moira's got a lovely bunch
of coconuts ♪
♪ Every ball you bowl
will make me rich ♪
♪ There goes my wife,
the idol of my life ♪
♪ Singing, "Roll a bowl,
a ball, a penny a pitch" ♪
♪ Oh, roll a bowl, a ball,
a penny a pitch ♪
♪ Roll a bowl, a ball,
♪ Singing, "Roll a bowl, a ball,
really roll a bowl, a ball" ♪
a penny a pitch" ♪
[Singing, music fade]
-Stay clear of that lot
over there.
They're nuts.
Given toys to play with
like children.
Some of them think they are,
too.
You here long?
Oh, me either.
Just over Christmas.
My family's gone to Vanuatu
for the holidays.
But they'll be back soon.
Too soon isn't soon enough
if you ask me.
But I'll be gone soon --
soon as Christmas is over.
My family dropped me here while
they're in Vanuatu for a while.
I...I didn't want to go.
I said I'd be all right.
Just waiting for them
to come back now.
Shouldn't be long.
Soon as Christmas is over.
How much longer, do you think?
[Music continues]
-It's October.
Early October.
-♪ Coconuts... ♪
-Up you get.
Up.
-We made it very clear
it was a double-occupancy room.
-Yes, and excuse me.
That may very well be.
But what I'm trying to
make clear to you is
that information
was not conveyed to me.
-Oh, your social worker
should have --
-Well, they didn't.
That's the situation
we're in now.
So please don't prevaricate.
Do you know
what "prevaricate" means?
It means to beat about the bush,
which is to stall,
to evade, to waste my time.
-Uh...
-It doesn't matter what
you think should have happened,
what you want to have happened.
What did happen
is I was misinformed,
and now I want to be moved
to another room.
-All of our medical suites
are double occupancy.
So once your recovery has
progressed, we can see about
putting you on the wait list.
-Wait list?
-But that is going to take
some managing.
In the meantime, why don't you
try engaging with your bubble?
Make some friends.
-I'll be better soon.
Then I'm gone.
-And we can both look forward
to that day, then, can't we?
-Madeleine?
[Man screaming]
-You'll love Tony Garfield.
-Madeleine, we need you.
[Screaming continues]
-Everybody loves Tony.
He played rugby for New Zealand.
-I fear the intersection of our
interests may be a tad narrow.
My exposure to rugby
has largely been limited
to watching its players dodge
rape charges.
Oh, shit.
-Here. Just let me --
-No. I can do it.
-Okay. So if you just get the --
-No. I can!
-Okay. Let's just --
-I can do it.
[Indistinct conversations,
cart rattling]
-Let's try one more, okay?
[Woman groaning]
-Okay?
-[Grunts]
-It's okay. Take your time.
Take your time.
I'll -- Okay.
Um, I'll come back, okay?
Hey, David.
I'm just going to get Jenny Pen
so you can eat properly, okay?
-Yeah.
We just tend to leave that.
[Indistinct conversations]
- The time is 12:35.
-What are you reading?
-I'm not really.
Trying to, but...
I have trouble now.
-Where are we, love?
-The Green Parrot!
-Couple of true-blue lovebirds
you got over there.
-"'Tis times' plague
when madmen lead the blind."
-Righto.
- The time is 12...
-Might have the time, mate, but
you have no bloody use for it.
-[Chuckles softly]
-Josie -- that's my, uh,
third youngest --
she gave me one of those Tom
Clancy books for Father's Day.
Well, I'm not much of a reader,
but it's a real ripper
of a yarn.
This joker, um,
Jack what's-his-face
gets the bloody job done.
I'll tell you what.
It's a real ripper.
Uh, what's it called?
Uh...
Oh, bugger me.
"The Sum of..."
"Sum of --"
-"The Sum of All Fears."
-Oh, you've read it?
-Mnh-mnh.
-It's interesting.
It's all about this --
-I know what it's about.
-But...you never read it.
-All those books
are about the same thing.
-Would anyone like some tea?
Coffee? Tea? Coffee? Tea?
[Woman stammering]
[High-pitched ringing]
[Woman stammering,
sounds echoing]
[Ringing builds, stops]
-When you're ready.
Yep.
Just when you're ready.
-Hm?
-Just when you're ready.
Hand on the table.
We'll just use this one.
We want these muscles
to recover.
That's it.
So slide along the table.
Open up those fingers.
-Mm.
-Really look at
what you're doing.
We want your brain to recover.
-[Grunts softly]
-Open up your fingers.
That's it . Keep going.
Keep going. Keep going.
Reaching out,
sliding towards the cup.
[Man laughing]
[Cup clattering]
-Oh. [Groans]
-No problem.
-[Laughing]
-Okay.
We're gonna go again.
Look at what you're doing.
Reach out those fingers.
-♪ For the tree was born
in a thunderstorm... ♪
-Hand on the table.
Can you hold the cup?
Can you hold it?
[Man laughing, cup clatters]
Can you pick up the cup?
-[Laughing loudly]
-Let's try that again.
Look at what you're doing.
[Dishes rattling]
-Jasmine,
can you pass me a towel?
Jas?
-I'll manage.
-You s-- You sure?
I'll be two tics.
-Stronger than I look.
-Okay.
Um...shit. Okay.
Just...Yeah.
[Door opens, footsteps echoing]
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Water splashes]
[Water bubbling]
[Music continues]
-Oh, my God!
-[Coughs]
-Breathe. Breathe.
Just breathe.
You're all right.
[Bed whirring]
-All right.
Let's stick to showers
from now on, okay, Morty?
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Footsteps approaching]
[Indistinct talking in distance]
-"Cities or towns
beginning with 'U.'"
-Yeah. You got it.
Who's that, then?
Well, if it isn't Dave Crealy.
You out causing mischief,
are you?
Painting the town red?
Seriously, though, mate.
It's time for bed.
-Hello, Jenny Pen.
-Yeah.
Good night, Jenny Pen.
Come on, mate.
Off to bed.
There you go.
Okay.
[Bell chimes]
So, an arty joke.
Sounds like little Arthur
may asphyxiate on his food.
A-something,
T-something, something.
I don't know.
A-something, T-something...
-Artichoke.
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Woman humming softly]
-Merry Christmas.
[Chuckles softly]
Is my family here for me?
I've been here a fortnight.
They'll be expecting me.
-You've been here for years.
Hello?
Anybody home?
-[Snorts, exhales deeply]
-[Breathing heavily]
[Dramatic music plays]
-[Gasps]
[Gasping]
Aah! Aah!
[Exhales sharply]
-[Whimpers]
[Music builds, ends]
-No. No.
No. No.
I will not need that.
Not until somebody --
Oh, finally.
-Let's get back to bed.
I'm here. I came. Let's just --
It's okay, everyone.
Everything's all right.
Back into your rooms, please.
-Everything is not all right.
-Let's just calm down, shall we?
-That's all anyone will say
to me is to calm down,
after what's been done to me.
-I am aware of the situation.
Please lower your voice.
-Then I want to know what
you're going to do about it.
-Well, we're going to
get you cleaned up.
-Oh, I'm glad that's
on the cards,
but that's not what I'm asking.
I want to know what you're
going to do about my assailant.
-Who?
-Dave Crealy.
-Dave?
-Can't --
Can't you confine him
to the dementia wing
-or put him away somew--
-Mr. Mortensen,
Dave is a paying resident here,
just as you are.
-I'm sitting in my own emissions
here, woman.
-Oh, so they are yours?
-My...
-The emissions.
-Yes, they're --
Oh, look. I explained all this.
-Okay.
Well, if he was responsible --
-If? If?
-I'm not suggesting
you made it up...
-Oh, you're not suggesting?
Well, good!
-...but sometimes people
can experience night terrors...
-Night terrors?
-...when they're adjusting
to a new environment.
-I'm not some prepubescent tot
with a weak bladder.
I saw what I saw.
-Sometimes people get confused.
-I'm not confused.
-Right now, people are trying --
-Oh, for fuck--
Ask the st-- the national
treasure, the star witness.
-Tony?
-No idea what he's on about.
That fella starts kicking up
a fuss out of the blue
in the middle of the night.
Scares me half to death.
-Dave's out to it, as expected.
-I'm telling you that
Dave Crealy was in my room.
-Mike, can you please help
get the other residents settled?
-No. No. No.
You listen to me.
-I will look into it
in the morning.
Grace, Jasmine, can you please
get Mr. Mortensen cleaned up
and back into bed?
-Good night, Mr. Mortensen.
-Don't walk awa--
-No. Don't walk away...
from -- from me.
-Lily, back into your bed,
please.
Mike, can you clean up
those pajamas?
The lights are going out
in five minutes, everybody.
- ...time is 12:35 p.m.
-Pumpkin soup Tuesday
is pretty nice, eh?
Pumpkin soup Tuesday.
Yeah.
Oh.
More tea.
[Indistinct conversations]
-Oh, Dave.
You silly Billy.
You know we're not sharing food.
If you want more soup,
I can get you some,
but this one is Olive's.
Cool?
Hello, David.
Oh, no.
Ah. Yes.
It's such a shame.
Yeah. I can get you
more tea or coffee.
Tea?
[Down-tempo music plays]
-All right?
Hi, Mary.
How are you?
[Music continues]
[Music playing, choir singing]
-Here you are, Olive.
It's hot. It's hot.
[Cart rattling]
-All gone.
Ain't that a bugger, Garbunkle?
[Music continues]
-Really?
Is that the best
you could muster?
This man has a rich history
of failure and regret
you can excavate.
Huh?
We can do better.
Let's see.
Tony Garfield.
"Gunner" Garfield, wasn't it?
You know,
they say the best thing
that ever happened to his career
was the knee injury --
because he sat on the bench
and watched.
Oh, and what about the time
when they won the World Cup
and the coach got up and said,
"Thank you, Tony.
We could never have done it
with you"?
Well, I -- I have had
a bit of a stroke.
What's your excuse?
Overmedicated stupefaction?
Softening of the brain, perhaps?
Or have you always been
a stupid cunt?
- The time is 4:21 p.m.
[Music continues]
-I'll see you tonight.
-What's happening here?
Oh! Get Mr. Mortensen
to his room, please.
-Oh, yes. That'd be right.
Remove the weapon.
[Wind whistling]
[Branches creaking]
-Night.
-See ya.
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Clanking in distance]
[Music builds, continues]
-[Breathing heavily]
-[High-pitched voice]
Who rules, Tony?
-Jenny Pen.
-That's right.
-[Grunts]
-Good boy.
You're on Jenny Pen's side,
aren't you?
-[Gasps, groans]
-[Growls]
[Jabbering]
Had enough?
Huh?
Had enough, old son?
[Jabbering]
-You're not allowed to do this!
[Gasping]
-You stay still now, Judge.
[High-pitched voice]
And don't you call out
or you'll get worse.
-[Coughing, breathing heavily]
-[Giggles]
[Door opens, closes]
-Some nights I may have
got away with a slap or two.
That's it.
Now he has a fucking audience.
[Clock ticking]
[Collar jingling]
[Man breathing heavily]
[Hinges creaking, door rattles]
[Gine Pitney's
"If I Only Had Time" plays]
-[Whistling]
♪ If I only had time ♪
♪ Only time ♪
♪ So much to do ♪
♪ If I only had time ♪
♪ Dreams to pursue ♪
♪ They'd be mine ♪
♪ Time, like the wind ♪
♪ Goes a-hurryin' by ♪
♪ And the hours just fly ♪
♪ Where to begin? ♪
♪ There are mountains
I'd climb ♪
♪ If I had time ♪
♪ Since I met you, I thought ♪
♪ Life really is too short ♪
♪ But loving you ♪
♪ So many things ♪
♪ We could make true ♪
♪ One whole century ♪
♪ Isn't enough to satisfy me ♪
♪ Time, like the wind ♪
♪ Goes a-hurryin' by ♪
♪ And the hours just fly ♪
♪ Where to begin? ♪
♪ There are mountains
I'd climb ♪
♪ If I only had time ♪
[Whistling]
[Music continues]
♪ If I only had time ♪
♪ Only time ♪
[Inhaler hisses]
[Whistling]
[Music fades]
[Indistinct conversations]
-Hand on the rail, Shirley.
-All right, Miriam?
-Okay.
We're gonna be turning right.
-Hey, Dave.
Do you mind if we have
a wee chat?
Now, Stefan Mortensen
has told me...
-Hey, where you off to?
Where are you off to,
silly-Billy Steve?
Come on. Back here.
Back with me.
We're just going down
the hallway.
How are we going today?
[Indistinct conversations]
-Monitor syringe drivers
for three palliative patients.
-Frank, what are you doing?
Frank, back with me.
Come on.
Come on. Back in the group.
That's it.
Thank you, Frank.
Thank you for your time.
[Door opens, closes]
-[Sighs]
Oh. Yes, Frankie.
I need you to come and help Joy.
-Yeah.
-She needs some assistance.
-Yeah. Okay.
Cool.
[Spritzer hissing]
-Thank you.
-I just wanted these boys
to come and meet with you.
They've heard a lot of stories,
uh, a lot of local legends.
Um, but none from
the horse's mouth, so to speak.
These boys these days,
they've...
they've got so many
distractions, you know?
Phones, TikTok, girls.
Although I guess girls were
always a problem, eh?
[Chuckles]
I just wanted them to, um,
to get their heads around, uh,
you know, what it takes.
You're living proof, and, um,
if -- if they just focus up,
give it all they have --
it doesn't matter that we come
from a small town --
they can take it all the way.
Aaron C.!
Show some bloody respect.
Gentlemen,
Mr. Tony "Gunner" Garfield, eh?
Round of applause, please.
[Applause]
Thanks, Gunner.
We appreciate it.
Okay, fellas. Come on.
[Indistinct conversations]
Hey, that was great.
Wasn't it great?
Yes.
Good one.
Okay. Twelve, move over.
Aaron C.
So what did we get out of that
today?
Huh?
Attitude.
Head in the game, make sure
there are no distractions.
-Yeah!
-All right. Come on.
Let's go.
Come on.
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Music continues]
[Hinges creaking]
-[Breathing heavily]
[Machinery whirring, rattling]
[Hinges creaking]
[Gasps]
They never really use this one,
so I come here sometimes
when I know he's got it in
for me.
-I'm preparing to lay
an official complaint
if you'd vouch for me.
-Oh, you sure know
how to make a girl feel special.
Why would I help you
if you've been nothing
but a pain in my ass?
-What's his story?
-He strike you as a man
who enjoys swapping yarns
about the good old days?
He was here when I got here.
-I'll be gone soon.
Once I've regained the use
of my legs,
I'll be ascending the stairs
to my home
and getting back to my life.
He'll have you all to himself
again.
How long have you been
letting it all go on?
-You think you got
everyone pegged.
-Enjoy your hidey-hole.
[Chair whirring]
I think yellow
is more your color.
[Bell chimes]
[Bell chiming]
-Okay. That's enough.
That's enough.
Ua lelei, Sonny.
Ua lava lena. Okay?
Here.
[Mid-tempo music plays]
-...do medicine rounds
for 30 regular patients
and attend family members
in one afternoon.
-I'd like to make
an official complaint.
-Oh, Mr. Mortensen.
Perfect timing.
Follow me, please.
-Excuse me.
I said I'd like to make
an official complaint.
Are you deaf?
I'm talking to you.
Oh, is senility endemic?
-Joy, Tobias has lost
his glasses.
-Oh. Are they --
-They're not around his neck.
-Would you slow down for a bit?
-And then do the rounds?
-Dave Crealy was in my room
again last night,
and he assaulted me.
-He bloody well assaulted me!
-Calm yourself, Stefan.
-What? No. I can do that myself.
-I know you can.
-Stop! You don't need to.
Where are you taking me?
-Just calm down now.
-I don't understand.
I'm telling you
I've been attacked.
-We will assess that next, then.
Come through.
There's been a complaint.
-Someone else complained?
-Concerning you.
-Oh. So when he lays a
complaint, you spring to action.
-Dave Crealy
is under the impression
that you have something
against him.
-Well, he'd be right,
because the man's a...
-He says you stole from him.
-He says that --
No. What?
-And from others.
-I...
He...
N-No. That's what I'm
trying to tell you.
He's the menace here.
He's been at me from the jump.
-Dave Crealy's been at you?
-Yes.
-I hear from two staff members
that you assaulted him
yesterday unprovoked.
-Assaulted?
W-- I...
Oh. The pudding. No.
That was...
That was a muscle spasm.
I'm still working
to get control of my right arm.
-And if we search this room
right now,
we won't find anything?
-I...
Uh, I don't ex--
No.
Please don't listen to him.
The man came into this room
last night
and terrorized me
and Mr. Garfield.
And now he's trying to --
Look. I-It's a stitch-up.
-A stitch-up?
-I really don't think
this is necessary.
-Well, Mr. Mortensen,
it seems we owe you an apology.
-Oh, wait.
[Suspenseful music plays]
Oh, shit!
[Music builds]
-Have you been taking
your medication, Mr. Mortensen?
[High-pitched ringing]
[Music continues]
[Insects chirping]
[Match clatters]
-No bastard can see me.
[High-pitched voice]
No bastard knows you're here.
[Chuckles]
[Down-tempo music plays]
[High-pitched ringing builds,
stops]
[Woman stammering]
[Indistinct conversations]
-Want me to chop it up for you?
-Hey!
-Mine.
Mine.
[Music continues,
voices echoing]
- The time is 12:35 p.m.
-[Speaking indistinctly,
voice echoing]
[Metal scraping]
-[Chewing loudly]
Popanovich takes his time.
It's key.
Likes to chew your ear off.
So there's always
plenty of mash left
by the time I'm done
w-with Shaw.
I mean, when you're an --
an observant man like me,
you get to know
the lay of the land.
[Indistinct conversations]
It's share and share alike here,
Judge.
-Communism always has
the greatest attraction
for those with the least.
I will admit to being
a somewhat prideful man.
Nonetheless, I have considered
the potential benefits
of debasing myself
and flattering you,
stroking your ego
with a compliment or two.
Sadly, none come to mind.
[Chuckles]
You do really seem
entirely absent
of any positive attributes.
The human equivalent of a
dried-up husk of dog excrement.
-[Laughing]
[Both laughing]
You, uh...
...go away for a bit just now,
while I was sitting here?
Have ourselves...
a wee blip, did we?
-I don't know
what you're talking --
-Ooh. You watch where
you're steering, Judge.
Those low coffee tables
in the hall, they'll get ya.
-[Exhales sharply]
-Now, what did I just tell you?
You are a clumsy bugger.
Don't worry.
I won't do it again.
-[Grunts softly]
-I feel sorry for you, Judge.
I really do.
You've got a raw deal.
-[Weakly]
Oh? Enlighten me.
-Old Sean Dunn over there.
That's the way you're headed.
I've seen it before
a hundred times.
More.
-[Exhales sharply]
-What's gonna happen
is you'll get worse and worse
till you can't speak...
or even lift a finger.
Till you're so locked up
in your own body
that you're praying for it all
to be over --
that's if you can still think
straight enough
to know what kind of hell
you're in.
-[Groans]
-It hurts me to tell you this,
but it's the healthiest thing
for you to accept it.
That you're gonna be a turnip.
-Come on, then!
Kick me again!
-Hey! Whoa!
-Get off me!
I haven't done anything!
Anybody wish to testify
on my behalf?
I apologize!
Crealy!
He should murder me in my sleep!
Say something!
Do something!
You're all weak!
You're all dead already!
[Hinges squeak]
[Down-tempo music plays]
-Chevrolet.
Zebra.
Honesty.
Have you got that?
-Chevrolet. Zebra.
Honesty.
-Good.
[Music continues]
And the words I gave you?
-Chevrolet.
Zebra.
Honesty.
[Indistinct conversations]
[Lid rattles]
[Voices overlapping, echoing]
Chevrolet.
Zebra.
[Music continues]
-And the objects in the room
that I pointed to?
-Uh, radio.
-And?
Chevrolet. Zebra.
Honesty.
[Music slows, continues]
[Paper fluttering]
-You boys seem a little
down in the dumps tonight.
What's the matter?
[High-pitched voice]
How about a joke, Mr. Crealy?
Ah. Good idea, Jenny.
Got a good one?
[High-pitched voice]
Sure do.
What do you call a Maori
on the moon?
Well, I don't know, Jenny.
What do you call a Maori
on the moon?
[High-pitched voice]
A problem!
What do you call two Maoris
on the moon?
Well, I-I don't know, Jenny.
What do you call two Maoris
on the moon?
[High-pitched voice]
A problem!
What do you call
the whole race of Maoris,
all of them,
up there on the moon?
Well, I don't know, Jenny.
What do you call
the whole race of Maoris,
all of them,
up there on the moon?
[High-pitched voice]
Problem solved!
[Exhales deeply]
Mm.
Who rules, Tony?
-[Breathing heavily]
Jenny Pen.
-Lick her asshole.
Go on.
Want to play, Stefan?
Want to play the game?
Who rules?
-[Weakly] Jenny.
-Not you.
The judge.
Who rules, Stefan?
[Exhales deeply]
[Bed whirring]
[Bed squeaks,
whirring continues]
-[Gasping]
-Which is the bad one?
-[Gasps]
-[High-pitched voice]
Bingo!
-What's all this actually about,
Crealy?
-How's the hip, Garby?
-[Gasps]
Please. Please.
-What demons are we exorcising?
-[High-pitched voice]
Not too good. Not too good!
-Has it helped to dull the sting
of Daddy's belt?
-Had enough, old son?
-[Whimpers]
-Does it sweeten the stench
of the chaplain's breath
as he bent you over the altar?
Or is it more personal?
-Ah.
This is new.
-[Whimpers]
-You've been having issues,
Garby?
-Revenge, is it?
-Who rules, Stefan?
Eh?
Who rules?
-[Breathing heavily]
-I'm not talking
to a fucking puppet.
-Fair enough.
-No, no. No, no.
No, no!
[Plastic stretching]
[Gasps]
[Bag thuds, urine sloshes]
[Exhales sharply]
-[Laughing]
Gonna break you
one of these days, Judge.
[High-pitched voice]
One of these days!
-"The world breaks everyone,
and afterward many are strong
at the broken places.
But those that will not break,
it kills.
It kills the very good
and the very gentle...
-♪ Knees up, Mother Brown ♪
-...and the very brave
-impartially.
-♪ Knees up, Mother Brown ♪
-If you are none of these,
you can be sure...
-♪ Under the table you must go ♪
-...it will kill you too."
-♪ E-I-E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ If I catch you bending,
I'll saw your legs right off ♪
♪ Knees up, knees up,
don't let the breeze up ♪
♪ Knees up, Mother Brown ♪
Hey!
[Wheezing]
What was that bollocks
you were spouting just now?
-"A Farewell to Arms,"
Hemingway.
-He knew a thing about survival,
did he?
-He blew his brains out.
-Not entertaining any similar
notions, are you, Judge?
-You'd like that.
-No.
We're having more fun than
we've had in donkey's years.
Ain't that right, Jenny?
[High-pitched voice] Don't
stick around on our behalf.
[Chuckling]
Ooh. Cheeky.
Who rules?
[Breathing heavily]
[Door opens, closes]
[Dramatic music plays]
[Music builds, continues]
You expecting visitors?
-Is someone there?
Do you think it's my family
come to see me?
-[High-pitched voice]
I think it's your family
come to see you, yeah!
They're waiting for you.
Come on.
We'll show you.
[Door chimes, lock clicks]
-Mine!
[Lock clicks]
-You have people.
You could kick up a fuss.
They'd listen.
Don't be such a damn coward.
-You remember Dudley Palmer?
-Who?
-On television.
-Dudley...
The weatherman?
-They found him floating,
all bloated, down a ways
from the Huka Falls,
a 16-inch pink dildo
sticking out of his fundament.
Turns out he'd been
with a dominatrix.
But this time...
there'd been a bit of a mishap.
Poor girl panics,
calls her boyfriend,
and the two of them decide
to dump the body.
I met him once, you know.
Seemed a good enough sort.
People loved him.
They depended on him for their
picnics, their camping trips.
The nation's fun uncle.
All anyone remembers...
is a giant pink dildo.
My son's youngest, Thea,
she has this way
of looking at me.
I don't want that look
to change.
I don't want her to see me
as something to pity.
[Switch clicks]
[Down-tempo music plays]
-Hey, puss.
[Key jingling]
[Gasps] Mine!
-Look over there.
Your family's waiting for you.
-I...can't see them.
-[High-pitched voice] You need
your eyes checked, lady.
Yeah.
I-I can see 'em.
[Latch clicks, hinges squeaking]
You need to check out now, lady.
[Insects chirping]
[Down-tempo music plays]
You see 'em?
-I don't think so.
-Yeah. They're right there.
They're waiting for you.
[High-pitched voice]
Here! I'll help you there.
[Latch clicks, hinges creaking]
You better hurry!
That's right.
You just go straight.
You can't miss them.
-All right, then.
That's right.
You're on the right track.
[Music continues]
[Voice echoing]
What was your name again?!
♪ A-da-lum, bum-ba-dum, ba-ba ♪
[Humming softly]
[Women laughing]
♪ Ba-da-ba... ♪
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Door beeping]
[Door beeps]
[The Settlers' "Lightning Tree"
plays]
[Music continues,
group vocalizing]
-♪ Down in the meadow
where the wind blows free ♪
♪ In the middle of a field
stands a lightning tree ♪
♪ Its limbs all torn
from the day it was born ♪
♪ For the tree was born
in a thunderstorm ♪
♪ Grow, grow,
the lightning tree ♪
♪ It's never too late
for you and me ♪
♪ Grow, grow,
the lightning tree ♪
♪ Never give in too easily ♪
[Music continues]
♪ Down in the meadow
where the wind blows light ♪
♪ The lightning struck
in the middle of the night ♪
♪ Limbs stripped bare
by the lightning flare ♪
♪ The lightning flare
was a wild affair ♪
♪ Grow, grow,
the lightning tree ♪
♪ It's never too late
for you and me ♪
♪ Grow, grow,
the lightning tree ♪
♪ Never give in too easily ♪
-[Grunts]
[Water splashing]
[Music continues]
-♪ Down in the meadow
where the wind blows cold ♪
♪ The lightning tree
stands stiff and old ♪
♪ Branches bent
where the lightning rent ♪
♪ The lightning rent
from the firmament ♪
♪ Grow, grow,
the lightning tree ♪
♪ Never give in too easily ♪
-[Grunts, breathing heavily]
[Music continues]
[Water splashing]
-♪ Down in the meadow
with the wind in the west ♪
♪ The lightning tree faced up
to the test ♪
♪ Its heart went snap
when it took the rap ♪
♪ The terrible rap
of the thunder clap ♪
-[Groans, breathing heavily]
[Wheezing]
[Inhaler hissing]
[Exhales deeply,
breathing heavily]
[Birds chirping]
-Gary, what's the big idea
of having a paua fritter
inside your footy sock?
- Good evening, and welcome
to the Wellington regional
final of its academic fin--
- And on that note,
we bring "Tawa Talk" to a close
for this evening.
-Hundred and fifty dollars?!
What am I saying?!
- L-I-N-O-L-E--
[Frequency modulating,
down-tempo music plays]
- Across the Tasman Sea
to the green pasturelands
of New Zealand.
- And welcome back,
you viewers at home,
to "It's In the Bag."
-If thy bait offends thee,
put it in.
[Light music playing,
frequency modulating]
-Splitting off from the pride,
the young male strays farther
than ever before
and stumbles directly
into the midst of a hyena clan.
Contra to their reputation
as lowly scavengers...
-[Laughing]
-...hyenas are in fact
consummate predators,
something this young lion
has come to learn.
-[Growls]
-[Laughing]
[Hyenas barking]
[Barking, laughter echoing]
[Chair whirring]
[Gate rattling]
[Chain jingles]
-[Exhales deeply]
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Music builds]
-Stefan, are you with us?
-I've got to get out of here.
-As far as physical
development is concerned,
with the damage to the tissue,
at this stage I'm not seeing
much improvement.
So it's important
that we manage expectations.
And with the latest
development -- uh, the blips...
...it's very important
that we keep a close eye
on cognitive progression.
[Voice echoing] This really is
the best place for you.
Stefan, are you with us?
[Dramatic music plays]
[Detector buzzing softly]
-[Weakly]
Yes, I'm with you.
[Music continues]
-[High-pitched voice, echoing]
What's that, Judge?
[Music continues]
-You're not the victim here.
[Voice echoing]
You're not the victim here.
Was she your first?
She was, wasn't she?
[Voice echoing]
Again, again, again.
-When you really think about it,
not a big splash in the pond.
-[Voice echoing]
I sound upset.
You're culpable.
-She didn't have
really much time left, you know.
-Where there are no lions...
-[Music builds, continues]
-...hyenas rule.
-We just helped things along.
-[Grunts]
-...full well what was going on.
Again, again, again...
-[Groaning]
-[Voice echoing]
Again, again, again...
[Music builds, slows]
[Thud echoing]
"Nothing I cared,
in the lamb white days,
that time would take me
up to the swallow-thronged loft
by the shadow of my hand, in
the moon that is always rising,
nor that riding to sleep
I should hear him fly
with the high fields
and wake to the farm forever
fled from the childless land.
Oh, as I was young and easy
in the mercy of his means,
time held me green and dying...
though I sang in my chains
like the sea."
-Would you shut it?
-I was finished.
-Always some other
dead wanker's words.
Huh?
What are you gonna say
about this shit we're in?
-There was a time when I
would've imagined for myself...
...a room full of loved ones...
grandkids...
...floral arrangements...
...when I thought I deserved
all that as well.
I've been trying to think --
when did I become this?
Bitter, lazy, stupid.
Forgot myself.
Gave up on...
...people.
In the worship of what?
A podium?
And all the while, it appears...
...you were building shrines
to better gods.
-"Look upon my work,
oh, mighty...and despair."
-"Look on my works,
ye mighty, and despair."
[Hinges creak]
[Dramatic music plays]
[Door chimes, lock clicks]
[Music continues]
[Collar jingling]
[Bell chiming]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Bell chimes]
-We've got about 15 minutes,
and then we're gonna have to
move on to Marcus down...
-Oh.
That never gets tired, does it?
[Chair whirring]
[Whirring stops]
-Come on, Dave.
I think we're gonna wash
your hair today.
It sounds like a good idea,
doesn't it?
Okay.
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Door chimes, lock whirs[
And please use the chair.
We don't want you slipping over,
now, do we?
I'll pop back in a few minutes,
and I can, uh,
help you wash your back
if you need some help.
[Humming softly]
[Music continues]
Here we go.
Very handsome.
Okay.
Watch your step.
Now, we'll get you dressed.
[Door chimes, lock whirs]
Here we are, then.
Here's your pants.
And here's your shirt.
Your socks and your belt.
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Indistinct talking on TV]
[Door closes]
[Machine clicks,
record crackling]
- And here she is --
the Cockney queen herself,
Mrs. Jenny Pencarrow!
[Up-tempo music plays]
-♪ I've just been
to a dingdong ♪
♪ Down dear old Brixton way ♪
♪ Old Mother Brown
the pearly queen's ♪
♪ A hundred years today ♪
♪ Oh, what a celebration ♪
♪ A proper la-di-da ♪
♪ Until they rolled
the carpet up ♪
♪ And shouted,
"Now, then, Ma!" ♪
-Hey!
-♪ Knees up, Mother Brown ♪
♪ Knees up, Mother Brown ♪
♪ Come along, dearie,
let it go ♪
♪ E-I-E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ It's your bloomin' birthday ♪
♪ I'll wake up all the town ♪
♪ Knees up, knees up,
don't let the breeze up ♪
♪ Knees up, Mother Brown ♪
Hey!
[Music continues]
♪ Knees up, Mother Brown ♪
♪ Under the table you must go ♪
♪ E-I-E-I-E-I-O ♪
-♪ If I catch you bending,
I'll saw your legs right off ♪
♪ Knees up, knees up,
don't let the breeze up ♪
-♪ Knees up, Mother Brown ♪
-[Wheezing]
♪ Oh, dear ♪
♪ What a rotten song ♪
♪ Oh, my! ♪
♪ What a rotten singer, too ♪
♪ Knees up, Mother Brown ♪
♪ Under the table you must go ♪
♪ E-I-E-I-E-I-O ♪
♪ And if I catch you bending,
I'll saw your legs right off ♪
♪ Knees up, knees up,
don't get the breeze up ♪
♪ Knees up, Mother Brown ♪
-[Grunts]
-♪ Oh, my! ♪
♪ What a rotten song ♪
♪ Oh, my! ♪
♪ What a rotten singer, too ♪
[Cart clattering]
-[Gasping]
[Music continues, echoing]
-♪ Knees up, Mother Brown ♪
♪ Under the table you must go ♪
♪ E-I-E-I-E-I-O ♪
[Music continues,
tempo increasing]
-[Wheezes, groans]
[Door chimes]
[Dramatic music plays]
[Inhales deeply]
[Wheezing]
[Inhales deeply, gasping]
[Inhaler whining]
[Groans]
[Inhaler whistling]
[Music continues]
[Wheezing, groaning]
[Grunting]
[Music continues in distance]
[Gasps]
[Detector buzzing softly]
-[Snoring]
[Snorts, sighs]
[Birds chirping]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Men laughing]
- The giant moray allows
the skunk cleaner shrimp
to comb its skin for parasites,
feeding itself while keeping
the moray free of infection.
This type of mutualism
is common on the reef.
-I suppose everyone
needs someone.
-[Chuckles]
[Dramatic music playing,
water bubbling]
[High-pitched ringing]
-Oh. Excuse me.
That was my...
-[Breathing heavily]
[Rumbling, crackling]
[Rumbling builds]
- The time is 4:21.
[Clattering]
-[Gasps]
-Oh, jeez! What's that?!
[Music playing on TV]
-Oh! No! Hey!
Hey! Hey!
-No running inside!
[Thud]
-Aah! Ow. Oh!
[Static hissing,
frequency modulating]
[Matt Monro's "And You Smiled"
plays]
-Lovely.
-Who is that?
-It's our Georgie.
-What's that?
-Georgie.
-That's right.
It's our Georgie.
-Who is that?
-[Sighs]
Oh. [Chuckles]
Oh!
-It's time for our bath, Mummy.
-Oh. Oh!
[Laughs]
-Comfrey!
Comfrey!
-We've got to get you ready.
-What...
Hey, w-what's going on?
[Music continues]
-Hey, it's all right, Peter.
Just getting Mummy ready
for her bath.
And Uncle Stefan
is gonna help us.
-What's going on, you bastard?!
Get -- Get --
Leave her!
What's going on?!
What is going on?!
What are you doing?
Leave her alone!
-What -- Where's Georgie?
-No, no. No, no, no, no.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Shh.
-Aah!
[Shouting indistinctly]
[Music continues]
-Nearly there, Mummy.
-[Sobbing]
[Gasps]
Aah!
-Aah!
Comfrey!
-My Georgie?
[Sobs]
-You bugger!
I love you, Comfrey!
Comfrey! Comfrey!
Aah!
-Well.
What are you --
Ooh!
[Groans]
-No!
I love you, Comfrey!
-Aah!
-Aah! Aah!
Aah!
You bugger!
You bastard!
-♪ And you smiled
with laughter in your eyes ♪
♪ And the world
seemed to fade away ♪
-No! No!
No! No!
[Shouting indistinctly]
-Relax.
[Music, voices fade]
[High-pitched ringing]
[Ringing builds]
[Beep, ringing stops]
[Intermittent ringing]
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Music continues]
[Cart rattling]
-In my 40s,
I picked up a second shift.
Night duty at the Grand in town.
One night, like any other,
another gathering of bigwigs.
An award ceremony, I think.
I'm busy mopping the floors,
and I notice the crowd is
a little more lively than usual.
So I stop what I'm doing and
I look out the service hatch.
And there you were...
...up at front, at the podium
in your fancy dinner jacket,
holding court.
And you were going over well,
too.
You had that room
in the palm of your hand.
And I remember thinking,
"Now, there's a man who's made
something of himself."
Now, what have I done?
Forty-odd years of diddly-squat.
But you...
you were an inspiration
in that moment, Judge.
Of course,
I still had the dregs of what
you might call hope back then.
[Chuckles] No idea how much
of the same there was to come.
[Exhales deeply]
My whole life...
I've been so bored.
When I look back, it's like
looking into an empty bin.
Lack the will, the brains.
Yeah.
The luck.
But time, it seems,
has awarded me...
certain advantages.
Be a waste not to honor that.
Don't you think?
Claim the richness of experience
that's been denied me.
We all get what's coming to us
in the end.
-[Inhales sharply,
exhales deeply]
[Bed creaks]
-[High-pitched voice]
Why the long face?
Give us a grin.
-[Groans]
-Who rules?
-[Weakly]
Jen Pen.
-[Exhales deeply]
Now lick her asshole.
Go on.
Lick her asshole.
Or I'll do the side of you
that's not already dead.
-[Inhales sharply]
-Now, that wasn't so hard,
was it?
I'm really glad we were able
to spend this time together.
-[Exhales deeply]
-"We don't stop playing
because we get old.
We get old
because we stop playing."
Too right.
And ain't it strange,
in this place, of all places?
Here I am, full of life.
[Dramatic music plays]
[Music builds,
distorted voice droning]
[Music fades, droning continues]
[Carl Coccomo's
"Don't Leave Me Now" playing ]
[Music slowed, voice distorted]
-♪ ...means I'd die ♪
♪ For your love ♪
♪ Ritorna da me ♪
♪ Come back, my love ♪
♪ Don't leave me now ♪
♪ Non me lasciare ♪
♪ Come back to me ♪
♪ I'm yours alone ♪
♪ Don't leave me now ♪
♪ Non me lasciare ♪
[Music ends]
[Door opens]
-You're tougher than you look.
I'll give you that.
[Spoon scraping]
[Inhales deeply]
Ka mate, ka mate!
Ka ora, ka ora!
Tenei te tangata puhuruhuru...
[Wheezing]
...I tiki mai whiti te ra!
A upane...
[Breathing heavily]
Up--
[Wheezing]
Ka upane...whiti te ra!
-Okay. All right, Tony.
Okay.
Come on.
Let's go.
Let's go get you settled.
Come on. It's all right.
[Schubert's "Death
and the Maiden" plays]
[Music builds]
[Music builds, continues]
[Music continues]
[Music ends]
[Dramatic music plays]
-[Breathing heavily]
[Music continues]
[Clattering in distance]
[Machinery whirring, rattling]
-[Gasps]
[Hinges creaking]
[Both grunting]
-[Slurring]
Get his legs!
-[Groaning]
Oh! God!
-[Grunting]
[Muffled grunting]
-[Grunts]
[Muffled groaning]
-[Breathing heavily]
Had enough?
You had enough, old son?
[Sobs softly]
[Machinery whirring in distance]
[Whirring fades]
[Detector buzzing softly]
-[Exhales deeply]
[Birds chirping]
[Indistinct conversations,
down-tempo music playing]
[Woman stammering]
[Music continues]
[Men laughing]
[Indistinct conversations,
man snoring]
-Oh!
Yeah.
-[Chuckles]
Oh, no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Put it there.
[Jimmy Gilmer and the Fireballs'
"Misery Misery Misery" plays]
-♪ To share a love
and see it grow ♪
♪ Was more to me
than life itself ♪
♪ Now that you're gone
and tears, they flow ♪
♪ I realize I am by myself ♪
- The time is...
-♪ Misery ♪
-♪ To love someone
and not be loved ♪
♪ To be alone and forgotten ♪
♪ I'm all alone
and feel so sad ♪
♪ And since you left me,
all I've had is ♪
♪ Misery ♪
-♪ Misery ♪
-♪ Now that you have
put me down ♪
♪ I will search
until I've found ♪
♪ Someone new
whose love I'll choose ♪
♪ To take your place
and end my blues ♪
♪ And misery ♪
-♪ Misery ♪
-♪ Now even though
my love for you ♪
♪ May never really fade away ♪
♪ I must forget my love
for you ♪
♪ Or I will have
another day of ♪
♪ Misery ♪
-♪ Misery ♪
-♪ Oh, misery ♪
[Down-tempo music plays]
[Music fades, ends]