The war is over.
The terms of peace
forced Finland to cede
territory to the Soviet Union.
Four hundred and
twenty thousand Finns
had to leave their homes
and move to the Finnish
side of the new border.
The majority of the forcibly
displaced were from Karelia.
Most of them would
never see home again.
Yeagor Dragunov.
Several missions
behind the enemy lines.
Your team burned
down entire villages.
Killed hundreds of civilians,
including a two-year-old boy, Otso,
a six-year-old boy, Otava,
and their mother, Tuulikki.
"We chopped them into
little pieces with a shovel."
We were saving bullets.
That was the family
of Aatami Korpi,
a Finnish commando,
who took revenge
by killing over 300
soldiers of the Red Army
and became a legend.
Koschei...
the immortal.
This killing machine entered
Soviet Union ten hours ago.
I'm sending you to
clean up your mess.
Destroy the legend you created,
and you will go back
home a rich man.
Passport, Mr. Dragunov.
I think the legend
has been homesick.
That is all that is left
from his life before.
Go on.
Go on!
Keep your eyes open.
This one is a crafty
old motherfucker.
No.
Keep very still.
I fucking told you to keep still.
Unleash hell.
Talk to me!
We found the truck!
Did you find the body?
What about the cargo?
You stubborn motherfucker.
Still heading home
to Finland, aren't you?
Took you fucking long enough.
Hold your position.
We want him alive.
There's no place like home.
Get out.
I have killed so many
women and children
that I cannot remember
any particular person.
I remember shouting, crying.
I remember the begging.
But I cannot recall any faces.
Except for one.
It's stuck in my mind,
like it was important.
A small boy.
Tried so hard to be
the man of the family.
I remember him because he
produced a knife out of thin air.
Almost took my eye.
Otava.
Tough little fucker.
Make any father proud.
He tried hard to protect his
little brother, and his mother.
We chopped them all into
small pieces with an iron shovel.
It was a feast for the... the
homeless, the stray dogs.
They're saying I lit
a fire in you. All right.
I will put it out.
You are a mistake, an aberration.
You are a... a
byproduct of my work.
A fucking weed in my field.
And where you are going...
they will beat the
legend out of you
till there is nothing left of you.
Not even a memory.
And your home...
the logs of your house
will be railroad ties,
buried in the frozen ground.
Like the rest of your family.
And you...
you will learn in
the years to come...
Siberia is a very bad
place to be immortal.
That's not good.
Step aside.
Everything okay?
No.
Yeagor!
If you give me what
I got coming to me...
I would like to be on my way.
You'll get what's coming to you.
But first,
let's celebrate.
To Yeagor.
Yeagor!
This is for you.
And this is for you.
Was that your revenge?
I expected something legendary.
Look at me.
Any last words?
Spit it out!
We thought you
might need some help?
No need to say anything.