(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
(FEEDBACK SQUEALS SOFTLY)
(AMPLIFIED TAPPING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
WILLIAM: Welcome back.
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING
BIZET'S TOREADOR SONG)
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls,
are you ready
to start the show?
CHILDREN: Yeah!
WILLIAM: Are you ready
to start the show?
CHILDREN: Yeah!
WILLIAM: Don't forget to
stay around till the very end
for a great big surprise.
Here we go!
Count with me now.
WILLIAM AND CHILDREN:
Ten, nine,
eight, seven, six,
five, four, three,
two, one.
WILLIAM: Showtime!
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHILDREN CHEERING)
(EXCITED CHATTER)
WOMAN: All right, this one?
CHILD: Come on!
CHILD 2: So close!
(BOY CHATTERS)
Oh, cool!
(CHILD SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
MAN: Hey.
WOMAN: Thank you, honey.
Bye.
(MUSIC FADES)
You seriously just gonna sit
here till the trapdoors open?
Leave her alone. She does
this every time she's here.
Come on.
GIRL: You look like someone
who could use a Freddy Fazcola.
(SLURPING)
Ew.
Tastes like gasoline.
(CHUCKLES)
GIRL: It doesn't come out
for a while.
Why don't you come back to
the table and hang out with us?
They don't
want me there.
No one does.
You just got
a bad roll of the dice.
Things will get better.
She's the only one
I can rely on.
who's always here for me.
That... thing down there
isn't your
spirit parent
or whatever
you think it is.
And it'll still
be there
even if you go have
a piece of cake first.
CHILDREN: (SINGING)
Happy birthday to you
(MANIAC BY MICHAEL SEMBELLO PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS) CHILDREN: Happy birthday!
(APPLAUDING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SONG FADES)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(RAPID FOOTSTEPS)
Excuse me. There's
a boy who needs help.
MAN: Go tell your parents.
Please, there's something wrong.
Go tell your parents!
(PANTING)
Sir, please. There's
somebody who needs help.
Not right now.
Please.
Will anybody help me?
There's a little boy
who needs help.
Please help me. I'm
sorry. Adults are talking.
Run along.
Charlotte! Don't.
(BROODING MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(SOMEONE WHISTLING
TOREADOR SONG IN DISTANCE)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(WATER RUNNING)
(WHISTLING CONTINUES)
(WHISTLING STOPS)
(TAP SHUTS OFF)
(SHUDDERS)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(WHISTLING RESUMES)
(WATER RUNNING)
(WHISTLING STOPS)
(TAP SHUTS OFF)
(WATER DRIPPING)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(BOY GROANS QUIETLY)
(CHARLOTTE GRUNTS)
(RAPID FOOTSTEPS)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(GRUNTING)
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS)
(GRUFF GRUNTING)
(CHARLOTTE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(HEART THUMPING)
(MUFFLED, INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CHARLOTTE'S BREATH
TREMBLING)
(SCREAMS)
(CHATTER STOPS)
(GROANS QUIETLY)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS AND THUDS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(CHILDREN SCREAM)
(PEOPLE GASPING)
(RUMBLING)
(GEARS RATTLING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
(PEOPLE GASPING)
(CLICKING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CRESCENDOS AND STOPS)
(MUSIC RESUMES)
(PHONE RINGING)
(GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BEEPS)
Hello?
MIKE: (OVER PHONE)
Hey, it's me.
Mike.
What time is it?
MIKE: Oh, uh,
it's early. Sorry.
Did I... did I wake you up? No.
I mean, yes, you did,
but, uh...
I had a rough night.
Bad dreams again? Or...
VANESSA: I can't seem
to catch a break.
Mmm.
Anything that I can do
to help?
VANESSA: No, I'm fine.
How is your day going?
Abby off to school?
MIKE: Uh, not yet.
She's, uh...
she's around here
somewhere.
Jeremiah's on his way over to help
me keep painting the new house.
VANESSA: Great.
Um, I just wanted
to see if we were...
we're still good for...
for dinner later.
VANESSA: Yeah. Yeah.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Definitely.
It'll be good to get out.
Um, hey, I gotta run, but
I'll, uh... I'll see you later, then.
Bye.
Okay. Bye.
(BEEPS)
(SIGHS)
So, have you
kissed her yet?
No.
Abs, it's not... it's not like
that. We're... we're just friends.
Then why are you going
on a date?
It's not a date. Then
why can't I come along?
Because you can't.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
That's what
I thought. (CHUCKLES)
Abby!
The Abbittyville Horror.
The Abbster.
Word up.
(BOTH MIMIC EXPLOSIONS)
What's happening?
You're growing like a weed.
ABBY: Uh,
I got to run.
You sure you don't
wanna stay and paint?
I'll trade places
with you.
(CHUCKLES)
Thanks, but I think
they'd notice at school.
Probably.
ABBY: Bye.
See you later.
ABBY: Bryson!
Bryson, wait.
You dropped this.
JEREMIAH: You know,
she's a good kid.
She is.
She's got a really good
heart. (BUS DOOR CLOSES)
So, you still going on that
date with Vanessa later?
(BUS ENGINE WHIRRING)
It's not a date.
Just a couple of adults having
dinner together, you know?
Mmm.
Listen, I wish you two all
the happiness in the world.
All I'm saying is
she's got crazy eyes, Mike.
She's not crazy, okay?
(PEOPLE TALKING INDISTINCTLY
AND LAUGHING)
Ooh, speaking
of crazy.
Ever since your aunt
went around
telling stories about
killer teddy bears,
the whole damn town's
lost its mind.
You know, I'll be happy
when this weekend's over.
All the festival
stuff's done,
and people maybe just
will go back to normal.
Yeah.
People are obsessed
with that old pizzeria.
Yeah, I heard they had your
aunt committed, by the way.
That's terrible.
Yeah, it's a real shame.
Hey, you sure your aunt
just made those stories up,
like, out of the blue?
MIKE: Hey, you know what?
Why don't we just keep it
between you and me that
Abby's even related to her?
You know,
she's been through a lot,
and she doesn't like
that kind of attention.
So then Chica tried to shove
me into a springlock suit.
But then Mike came in,
and he had a Taser,
and he shot her
in the face with it.
I ran for
the dining room
just as Foxy
came off the stage
and started
chasing me down.
Luckily,
Vanessa saved me.
But then
the Yellow Rabbit came,
and he attacked us.
He got Vanessa.
He stabbed her.
She's okay now.
So, what happened
to the Yellow Rabbit?
The springlocks went off
inside of his own suit
and crushed him alive.
They say his body's
still at Freddy's,
hidden in a secret room
that nobody's ever seen.
You're crazy.
Want to sit
with us at lunch?
Sure.
Are you ever gonna
go back?
To Freddy's,
I mean.
I would, but...
my friends...
The animatronics
are broken.
Mike says that he'll
fix them someday, but...
he's been saying that
for a while now.
Wait, so do you actually
believe anything I'm saying?
'Cause I'm pretty sure everyone
else just thinks I'm making this stuff up.
I believe in UFOs.
And ghosts.
So why not
haunted animatronics?
TEACHER: Young ladies,
young men, let's go.
Yeah.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(WHIRRING)
MR. BERG: Everyone,
eyes to me.
I just want to,
uh, remind you
that our robotics
presentation
at the science fair
is this Saturday.
Some of you
have been swept up
in the stupidity
that is this Freddy Fest.
Actually, Mr. Berg,
it's Fazfest.
I don't care
what it's called.
It's a mockery
of everything
that true robotics
stands for.
We're making real
robots here, people.
I want each
and every one of you
to be at that science fair
on Saturday,
whether you're entering
or not.
Or you can expect
a big, fat "F."
"F" for "Fazfest"?
(STUDENTS LAUGH)
MR. BERG: No.
"F" for "fail."
Don't waste your time.
Let's get to work.
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(CLATTERING)
MR. BERG:
Ms. Schmidt.
According to this,
you're planning
on showing
whatever this is,
Saturday, at the science fair.
Certainly, I don't have
to remind you
how important this event
is to the school.
We're defending a
three-year winning streak.
I'll be ready.
Yeah, that...
that's just the thing.
I don't think
you will be ready.
Ms. Schmidt, robotics...
isn't for everyone.
There's no shame
in taking a seat
for the good
of the team.
Now, look, look, look, what's
our... what's our school motto?
"Otters otter help
each otter."
Right.
Be a good little otter.
(CHUCKLES SARCASTICALLY)
He's rough on everyone.
Don't let him get to you.
I'm surprised
you haven't tried
to fix your friends
yourself.
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING)
But I bet you could.
MIKE: Abs, is that you?
Yeah.
All right.
Perfect timing.
You wanna do this for me?
You're hopeless.
(CHUCKLES)
How was your day?
Fine.
Um, anything exciting happen?
Not really.
Okay.
There.
What would you do
without me?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Thank you very much.
Okay. Uh...
Abs, I'm leaving a...
a 20 on the table
so you can...
you can order a pizza.
You remember how
to call and everything?
Of course. I'm 11.
I'm not a baby.
I know. I know.
Anything else you need
from me before I go?
You gonna watch
some TV or what?
Maybe I could go
see my friends?
You mean, like,
your friends from school?
I meant Chica
and the others.
Those friends.
Look, Abs,
we talked about this.
Okay, you can't
go back there.
They're broken.
Now, one day,
I'm gonna go fix them,
but until then,
maybe you could try
making some friends
with some real kids.
My friends
are real kids.
(TV BUZZES ON)
LISA: (OVER TV) We are
in the haunted courthouse.
(EERIE SHRIEKING AND WHOOSHING
SOUND EFFECTS PLAY OVER TV)
(CREAKING OVER TV)
Did you guys hear that?
ROB: (OVER TV) Hear what?
Look, you're right.
Abs, I'm sorry, okay?
It's just that it's...
it's complicated,
but we can talk
about it later.
I have to go.
Yeah.
(EERIE WHOOSHING OVER TV)
LISA: I don't know...
(CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
I love you.
ABBY: Mmm-hmm.
All right, don't... don't
watch too much of that show.
It'll give you
nightmares, okay?
ROB: (OVER TV)
You getting this?
(KEYS JINGLING)
I'll be back later.
(DOORKNOB RATTLES)
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR SHUTS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION
CONTINUES OVER TV)
(GENTLE PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
WAITER: Pardon me, sir.
Mmm. Oh.
There we are.
Thank you.
Hi.
So this is
what it's like?
MIKE: What?
Being normal.
"Normal."
Is that... Are we...
We're normal now?
I think we're doing
pretty good,
considering what
we've been through.
I just have too much
time on my hands.
It'll be better when I
can get back to work.
No, I think
you're doing great.
I mean, didn't you...
You signed up for, like...
like, biking classes,
right? Or... Spin class.
Spin class. Yeah, yeah. I've
been going a couple of weeks.
Okay. I even made some friends.
Friends.
What's that like?
(CHUCKLES)
WAITER: Pardon
my reach, madam. Oh.
They... they love
doing that here.
(CHUCKLES)
Um, you... you look
great, by the way.
So do you.
(SOFTLY) This is a date. What?
What?
Did you say something?
No, I... I said... I said this
is a... a lovely day, a day.
Day. Today's been
a great day. Yeah.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Let me guess,
Abby tie that for you?
She did. Yeah.
How is she?
She's good.
Well, some days are good.
Some days, she, uh...
she really misses them...
her "friends."
And, uh, I don't know
how to talk to her about it.
I know you're trying
to protect her, Mike,
but this story
that they're broken,
that you're gonna fix
those animatronics,
it's only giving her
false hope.
Just be honest.
Honest?
What?
MIKE: Uh, nothing.
So, you wanna... tell me
about your bad dream?
It's always
the same. (CHUCKLES)
We don't need
to talk about that.
Your dad?
Look, Vanessa, I was
thinking, do you remember how
I would use my dreams to confront
what happened with Garrett?
I mean, I admit I probably
slept a bit too much,
but it really
helped me a lot.
I think it can
help you, too.
I...
I... I don't think
that's a good idea.
You're never gonna
be free of your dad
until you deal with some of
the mess he left in your head.
I just... I want us to be
able to move past all of this.
You can do it.
At least try.
Just once.
(KEYS JANGLE)
(DOORKNOB RATTLES)
Abs, I'm back.
Abby?
Abs, did you eat?
(FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING)
Abby? Abby?
Abby?
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
(DOOR RATTLES AND CREAKS)
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
(LIGHTS CLANK ON)
(SOBBING SOFTLY)
Hey.
Abs, I'm sorry. I...
I didn't know
how to tell you.
Where are they?
I mean, there's...
pieces of them here,
pieces of them there.
No, that's not
what I mean.
Where are my friends?
Look, Abs, I, um...
I don't know.
You know, maybe, um...
maybe they're in heaven.
Wouldn't you
want that for them?
Yeah.
I would like that.
I'm sorry I didn't
tell you sooner, okay?
But you know what?
They're always gonna be
right here.
That's really cheesy.
(LAUGHS)
Yeah, it's a little cheesy.
It's extremely cheesy.
All right,
all right, all right.
You know what?
Come with me.
I got an idea.
Okay, young lady,
you have
one million tickets.
What can I get you? Do
you want some, uh... Oh.
What about orange
gummy candies?
No?
Okay.
Uh, we got...
Uh, let's see. Oh.
What about this?
(TOY VOICE HUMMING
TOREADOR SONG) Oh.
Well, maybe not.
(HUMMING STOPS)
What you got there?
It's a... Faztalker.
MIKE: "Realistic
voice interaction device.
"Talk to us anytime."
Is that what you want?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Sold.
One million tickets.
(CHUCKLES)
Now let's go home.
I thought you liked
orange gummy candy.
Well, I did, until I ate that
whole bag at Christmas.
Oh.
And you threw it up
everywhere. Yeah.
That was like an
orange slime waterfall.
It was really rough.
Don't remind me.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(ABSOLUTELY (STORY OF A
GIRL) PLAYING OVER STEREO)
You sure I'm going
the right way?
Uh, yeah.
No, it should
be up ahead.
(SIGHS)How'd you guys
find out about this place again?
Security guard
who works there.
His name is... Mike?
I don't care who he is, as
long as we have permission.
Trust me, we have
VIP treatment this time.
No breaking and
entering required.
Yeah, there.
There it is.
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
ROB: Freddy Fazbear's Pizza.
(CHUCKLES) I used to
come here when I was a kid.
Not this one
you didn't.
You're thinking of
the franchise location.
This is the original.
Nobody's been here
for decades.
This location came
before the other one.
So, what happened here?
Some little girl
got murdered.
Whole thing got swept
under the rug.
ALEX: (IN SPOOKY VOICE)
And now,
her soul wanders
these forgotten halls,
tortured and alone.
(LAUGHING)
(SCREAMS AND PANTS)
Dude.
Uh, sorry.
You startled us.
You must be Mike.
It's Michael, actually.
Call me Michael.
So?
Are you ready
for the tour?
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR RATTLES AND CREAKS)
(LIGHTS BUZZING)
(DOOR SHUTS)
Welcome to Freddy's.
You're cool
if we record everything?
MICHAEL: Of course.
That's why you're here,
isn't it?
(LAUGHING)No way.
They had a boat ride?
This restaurant had
a lot of unique features.
Like the marionette.
You did your homework.
Yeah.
The marionette truly
was one of a kind.
What's
"the marionette"?
A marionette would come
out of this trapdoor on the stage
and direct
the other animatronics
during performances.
MICHAEL: That's right.
Using a wireless signal.
The technology was
way ahead of its time,
but... they never made
another one.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Shall we?
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(METALLIC SCRATCHING)
Whoa.
They look brand-new.
MICHAEL: Freddy,
Bonnie, and Chica.
Uh... what about Foxy?
Oh.
Foxy was involved
in a failed
take-apart,
put-back-together attraction
and was never
quite the same again.
Kids can be so heartless.
(QUIET MUSIC BOX MELODY
PLAYING OVER HEADPHONES)
(MELODY STOPS)
You guys hear that?
It was like...
music or...
Uh, fair warning.
(CHUCKLES) This place will
prey on your imagination if you let it.
Shall we continue?
Hey, I'm gonna
catch up to you guys.
I don't know, I wanted
to look around a little bit.
Well, Mikey boy, let's, uh...
let's get the show on the road.
I'm burning
valuable tape here.
(SIGHS)
ALEX: What do we, uh...
what do we got over here?
(QUIET MUSIC BOX MELODY
PLAYING OVER HEADPHONES)
(MELODY GROWING LOUDER)
(MELODY STOPS)
(LIGHTS CLINKING)
(STATICKY CLICKING
AND WHIRRING)
(CLICKING AND WHIRRING)
(WHIRRING INTENSIFIES)
(SHATTERS)
Shit!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
What the hell?
What kind of kid
would want to come here?
ALEX: "Kids Cove."
(CHUCKLES) Awesome.
You know, I think this might
be our best episode yet.
Yeah. Usually, we gotta
play it up, you know?
(CHUCKLING) We have
to make it something it's not,
but this place is
actually pretty creepy.
(MUSIC BOX MELODY CONTINUES
OVER HEADPHONES)
(MELODY GROWING LOUDER)
(MELODY CONTINUES
QUIETLY IN DISTANCE)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(MELODY CONTINUES
OVER MUSIC BOX)
(CLICKS)
(MELODY STOPS)
(QUIET RUSTLING)
(SOFT, SHUDDERING BREATH)
(RUSTLING CONTINUES)
(RATTLING)
(CREAKING)
(MENACING MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS AND SCREAMS)
(SCREAM FADES
IN DISTANCE)
Lisa?
(CHUCKLING)
What... what did you do?
What did you do?
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SHOUTING) Lisa? Lisa, I...
I'm coming. Where are you?
(MECHANICAL CLANGING)
(SCREAMING)
(MECHANICAL GROWL)
(MECHANICAL CRUNCHING
AND GROWLING)
(THUDDING)
ROB: Hello?
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
(SIGHS)
(WATER SPLASHING)
What the hell was that?
(SPLASHING CONTINUES)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(SPUTTERS)
Where'd they all go?
(BREATH TREMBLING)
Shit, shit, shit.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
No, no, no! (SCREAMS)
(STRAINED GRUNTING
IN DISTANCE)
(MECHANICAL RATTLING)
(LISA GRUNTING)
(LISA CONTINUES GRUNTING)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(CLANKING)
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTING STOPS)
(SLOW, HEAVY BREATHING)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GULPS)
(SHUDDERING)
(EERIE MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(SHRIEKS)
(PANTING)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUTS)
(SCREAMING INSIDE)
Welcome back, Charlotte.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
ABBY: Come on. Please work.
Please work. Please work. Please.
(CLICKS)
(BUZZING, WARBLING)
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS)I miss you guys.
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING)
ABBY: Hello?
Can you guys
hear me?
(STATIC CRACKLING QUIETLY)
Chica, can you hear me?
I need you.
I miss you all so much.
(WHO INVITED YOU?
BY THE DONNAS PLAYING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
INSTRUCTOR: All right, all
right. Welcome to class, you guys.
Today I got a plan
for you all,
so we're gonna get you
guys nice and warmed up.
Whenever you are ready,
go ahead and turn to the right.
Keep pedaling.
I'm glad you decided
to join us again.
INSTRUCTOR:
You can do this.
Feel your core
start to engage.
Another full turn
to the right.
(SINGING) When I see
outta the corner of my eye
"Look who's here"
and "How you doing?"
Why don't you tell me
who let you in?
INSTRUCTOR: Feel
your quads start to activate.
Three, two, one,
turn to the right.
One, two, one, two.
One, two, one two. Again.
This is your moment.
Be here. Be present.
WILLIAM: Faster.
INSTRUCTOR: You can do this.
Push it all away.
WILLIAM: Faster.
(SHUDDERS AND GASPS)
(BIKE WHIRRING RAPIDLY)
WILLIAM: Faster.
Faster!
(GASPS)
(WHIRRING SLOWS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MECHANICAL GROWL)
(SHUDDERING)
(PANTING)
(EXHALES)
(CONTINUES PANTING)
Please. Vanessa, easy.
(GROANS)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
(STATIC DRONING)
(TAKING DEEP BREATHS)
(EXHALES)
You can do this.
(SIGHS)
(EXHALES SLOWLY)
(STATIC CONTINUES DRONING
OVER TV)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(STATIC CONTINUES DRONING
OVER TV)
(STEPS CREAKING)
Dad?
I'm not afraid of you.
I don't need you anymore.
I am nothing like you.
(DOORS CREAKING AND SLAMMING)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(PANTING AND WHIMPERING)
(RATTLING)
No, no, no. Come on.
(BANGING)
Help me!
(SCREAMS) Help!
(BANGING STOPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I'm not done with you.
You can't keep me here.
I'm leaving.
Don't you know
you're my favorite?
that I love you?
Don't you know
that I care about you?
Oh.
(EERIE MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
You are my child.
(ECHOES) You have
a purpose.
(TAKING DEEP BREATHS)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(WILLIAM WHISTLING
TOREADOR SONG)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(WHISTLING CONTINUES)
WILLIAM: Where are you
gonna run to?
(CLANKS)
(POWER WHIRRING)
(YELPS, PANTS)
(WILLIAM GRUNTS)
You will always be mine.
(GRUNTS) No!
(PANTING)
(GUNSHOT)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(THUDS)
You shall
always be mine.
(LAUGHING)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(TOY VOICE STUTTERING)
TOY VOICE: A-B-B-Y.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
Abby, help us.
Chica?
Chica? Chica,
is that you?
TOY VOICE: Yes.
Please help us.
Where are you?
TOY VOICE: Come find me.
How?
TOY VOICE: I will
show you the way.
(RAIN PATTERING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
(EXHALES)
TOY VOICE: Hurry.
We are all waiting for you.
(SIGHS)
Whoa.
(DOOR SQUEAKS)
(DOOR CREAKING)
What is this place?
Chica?
Freddy?
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
Bonnie?
(WHIRRING AND CLANKING)
ABBY: Chica?
Abby, you've come back
to us.
Chica!
I've missed you
so much.
I've missed you, too.
How did you get
this new body?
Do you like it?
It's neat.
But it's... different and
kind of cold. (CHUCKLES)
You said
you needed my help?
CHICA: We do.
But right now, what matters
is we're together again.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
(KEYS JANGLE)
(ENGINE SHUTS OFF)
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
(DOOR CREAKS)
Mike?
(TOY VOICE STUTTERING)
Abby?
(TOY VOICE
CONTINUES STUTTERING)
Gotcha!
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
(ABBY LAUGHS)
Haven't you ever played
hide-and-seek?
First rule is always
check behind the doors.
Right. (CHUCKLES)
Where is your brother?
Getting breakfast.
Do you wanna see
my science fair project?
It's finally done.
VANESSA: Wow.
You made this
all by yourself?
Well, no. Chica helped.
Freddy tried, but his
fingers were too fat.
Pretty cool, right?
Very cool.
(CHUCKLES) You said
Freddy and Chica helped you?
Yeah, in their old house,
last night.
It's so neat. It's got a
play area for little kids
and even a river.
Wait. A river?
(DOOR RATTLES)
MIKE: Abs, I'm back.
(GASPS) Breakfast!
(FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey. Uh, they didn't
have chocolate,
so I got banana
and, uh, blueberry.
What do we got here?
Hey. These are cool.
These are really good, Abs.
Vanessa's here.
Hey.
MIKE: Hey.
We need to talk.
Yeah, we do.
VANESSA: What is this?
I don't understand.
Yeah, neither did I
until I called the number.
Listen, we really need
to talk about Abby.
She said she's been
with Freddy and Chica.
Yeah, it's just
this toy she has,
this new
Faz-speaker thing.
No, she said
she saw them.
She said she went
somewhere. Okay.
You know, Vanessa,
I've... I've...
I've been trying really
hard to... to move forward.
I know, but, Mike...
Um, no, listen.
How can I move forward when
it's one thing after another?
Look, I hear you. I do.
It's just what Abby said...
Abby's just a kid.
And right now
she's hurting,
and she misses her friends, and
there's nothing that I can do to help her.
The same way that
I couldn't help Garrett,
or... or the other kids
at Freddy's.
Other kids
like Charlotte.
How do you...
Her dad made that flyer.
And so I called him, and he...
and he told me about his little girl,
and her
best friend Vanessa.
(SIGHS)
Why didn't you tell me that there
were other victims, other kids?
My father was a
monster. You know that.
Look, all...
all I'm trying to do
is I'm trying
to fix my family.
I'm trying to fix the situation
for Abby. I'm trying to fix you,
and... and I don't...
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Is that what this
has been about?
No.
You're trying
to fix me?
You know what? I
can take care of myself.
You just need
to watch out for Abby.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, Abs, um...
do you think that you
can get set up without me?
You're not coming?
No, no, I'm... yeah,
I'm coming. I just, uh...
I just have to go
do something real quick,
but I... I'll be back
before it starts.
Don't be too long,
though.
Okay.
Hey. You're gonna
do great.
Thanks.
(OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(RUSTLING NEARBY)
(SIGHS)
(MUSIC CRESCENDOS AND STOPS)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
Charlotte?
It's just me, Vanessa.
(SPEAKER FEEDBACK)
CHARLOTTE: (OVER SPEAKER)
Are you here to put me back to sleep?
I know what you want.
You wanna get out of here
so that you can hurt people.
The way that they hurt you.
But I can't let that happen.
CHARLOTTE: I'm out of the box.
But you still
have me trapped here.
Somehow.
It's called
a perimeter lock.
None of the animatronics
can leave.
Not even you.
CHARLOTTE:
But you can fix that.
I'm not gonna do that.
CHARLOTTE: That's okay.
I have another friend
who can help me now.
I don't hate you,
but you need to stay
out of my way.
(RAPID MECHANICAL RATTLING)
(YELLS)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
WOMAN: You're gonna be great,
honey. Don't worry.
(CHATTER CONTINUES)
(WHIRRING)
(BURBLING)
(RAPID BEEPING)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(THUNDEROUS RUMBLING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Excuse me.
Oh, Abby.
Do you know
where my booth is?
Uh, uh, I thought you
decided not to participate.
Yeah, it's a little late
to be setting up.
No, it's not. Look.
I can set up over there.
MR. BERG: Look, uh,
I just don't want you
to be embarrassed, Abby.
Why would I be
embarrassed?
I'm proud
of my project.
Of course you are. Yeah.
So am I. Here, let me...
Let's just find the
perfect place to display it.
(STAMMERS) Oh!
(SHATTERS)
(ELECTRONIC SQUEALING)
Oh! Oh, oh, sorry.
I'm so, so sorry, Abby.
I... I got, uh,
butterfingers. I...
I tell you
what I'll do.
I'll give you full credit
for the class.
And this way, you can
just go home, and...
and I'll take out
this trash.
BOY: You're such
a dick, Mr. Berg.
Who said that?
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
CHICA: Abby,
what's wrong?
ABBY: Mr. Berg, he...
he destroyed
my science fair project.
I'll be
your science project.
You'd do that for me?
Of course.
Well, come on.
We gotta hurry.
But first, I need you
to do something for me.
Remember how I said
we needed your help?
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
There is a secret code that
will let me come with you.
Will you enter it for me?
Okay.
(VANESSA GASPING, CHOKING)
(MENACING MUSIC PLAYING)
(PANTING)
(CHOKING AND GRUNTING)
No. No! No!
If you don't give me the command
to release the perimeter lock,
I will kill her.
(PANTING) Charlotte,
listen to me.
I know you're angry,
but it's not Abby's fault.
I know you. I know
you wouldn't hurt her.
ABBY: What do I type?
Are you willing
to take that chance?
VANESSA: Abby!
(GASPING, CHOKING)
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Four.
A-E...
(PANTING)
Seven-X-C-D...
C-D-One.
Now what?
Hit "enter."
(FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING)
(BEEPING)
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS,
MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(FOREBODING MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(RAPID CRACKLING, BEEPING)
You did it, Abby.
We're free.
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS,
MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
We better hurry if we want to
get to the science fair in time.
I only have my bike.
How are we going
to get there?
(TALKING IN YOUR SLEEP BY THE
ROMANTICS PLAYING OVER STEREO)
(SINGING) 'Cause I hear it
in the night
I hear the secrets
that you keep
When you're talking...
Where to?
(SCOFFS) You again?
You gotta be kidding me.
Kid, get out of this cab
right... (CAR CREAKING)
(CAR DOOR SHUTS)
(MECHANICAL GROWL)
Oh, my goodness!
Oh, Chica, you, uh,
dropped this. (CHUCKLES)
CHICA: Thank you, Abby.
I gotta get a new job.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(DOOR RATTLES)
HENRY: Mike?
Yeah.
Uh, thanks for seeing me.
HENRY: Come on inside.
Honestly, I was surprised
to get your call.
(COFFEE SLOSHING)
The only calls I've
gotten so far have been...
(SIGHS) ...prank calls, kids asking
to order a pizza, things like that.
Sure I can't offer you
a cup, Mike?
Oh, no, I'm... I'm fine.
Thank you.
Um, I don't know
what I'm doing here, really.
I just, um...
I don't really have anyone
else I can talk to about this.
I'm just looking
for some answers.
You know, I...
I wasn't the best father.
I was...
I was obsessed by my work
when I was younger,
and it eventually...
(INHALES SHAKILY)
...cost me everything.
(VOICE BREAKS)
Including my little girl.
MIKE: I'm sorry.
You know, on the phone,
you said that Charlotte died
at Freddy's?
Everyone called it
an accident.
I had my suspicions about
what had really happened,
but it wasn't
until years later
when those five children
went missing that...
that I knew
she was murdered...
by him.
(HENRY SIGHS)
I can only assume that
you lost someone as well.
It's my little brother.
HENRY: I'm sorry
for your loss.
(VOICE SHAKING) It's so easy
to become so blinded by ambition
that even with the best
of intentions
you don't see the devil
sitting right beside you.
And now this Fazfest
business, it's brought it all back.
It's an abomination,
people celebrating
that place.
That's why I posted
those flyers.
People need to know
the truth. Wait, what...
Where... where is this?
What is this?
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
It's the... the river ride.
It was one
of Charlotte's favorites.
But I... I've been
to Freddy's.
There's not a...
a river ride.
There was only one
at the first Freddy's.
None of the later
locations had one.
First Freddy's?
Abby drew this.
Uh, can...
can I use your phone?
Yeah, of course.
It's over there.
(PHONE RINGING)
BETTE: Hello?
MIKE: (OVER PHONE) And
you're sure she isn't there?
I'm so sorry, sir.
Apparently, there was some
sort of incident and she left.
But if you'd like, I can
call the... (CLANKS)
(DIAL TONE DRONING)
(SCOFFS)
What an asshole.
Is everything all right?
I, uh... I don't...
I... I don't know. Um...
I think my sister...
I think she's here.
One-two-five...
two-five...
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I made this music box for
Charlotte when she was just a baby.
The music,
it helped her sleep.
I know this might sound
crazy, but if you go back there,
would you leave it
for her?
Uh, yeah.
Thank you.
(BROODING MUSIC PLAYING)
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(ENGINE IDLING)
Abby?
(DOORS RATTLING)
(SHOUTS) Abby?
(THUDDING)
(GRUNTING AND PANTING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(MENACING MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS IN FEAR)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DISTANT CLANK)
(SOFTLY) Abby?
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER INSIDE)
(CLATTERING)
(CHUCKLING)
(PEOPLE APPLAUDING IN
DISTANCE) CHILD: Whoa! A giant robot.
MR. BERG: Excuse me.
Pardon me.
CHILD 2: Look, it's Chica!
Excuse me. Clear out.
CHILD 3: Whoa. What's
going on over here?
Mr. Berg, this is my new
science fair project.
Mr. Berg, I've heard
so much about you.
Is this a joke,
Ms. Schmidt?
Putting someone in a suit and
passing it off as your own work?
You're an embarrassment
to our class
and to our school,
Ms. Schmidt.
Now, take your
freak-show friend,
and get out
of my science fair,
before you
lose us the title.
I'm sorry, Chica.
There is nothing
to be sorry about.
How about
I go talk to him?
What are you gonna say?
I just want to see what's
going on inside of his head.
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS)
CHILD: Oh, whoa.
No.
I'm on my way.
I... I just left my
keys in my office.
Again.
(BOTH YELLING, LAUGHING)
(MR. BERG YELPS)
This part of the building
is closed!
Now, get out of here...
(BABBLING MOCKINGLY)
...before I have
you both expelled.
(SIGHS) Oh, geez.
(KEYS JINGLING)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(SOFT ELECTRICAL HUM
IN DISTANCE)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING
(LIGHTS CLINKING)
(MUTTERING)
(MR. BERG SIGHS)
(ELECTRICAL HUMMING
IN DISTANCE)
(FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS AND SCREAMS)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(YELLING)
(GROANING AND YELPING)
(GASPS)
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS)
(MR. BERG GROANING, SOBBING)
(GROANING AND WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMS, YELPS)
(GROANS AND THUDS)
(WHIMPERING)
(SOBBING)
CHICA: I would like
to talk to you
about Abby's project,
Mr. Berg.
(ELECTRICAL HUMMING)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(SCREAMING)
I'll give her an "A!"
(WHIMPERING)
You... you... (PANTING)
...you want test answers?
(SOBBING) I'll... I'll give
you answers to the next test.
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
What I want is to see what's
going on inside of your head.
(MR. BERG GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(SKULL CREAKING)
(HEAD SPLATS)
(BODY THUDS)
Just as I thought.
Nothing in there
at all.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Abby?
(THUDDING)
(LOUD THUDDING)
(KNOB RATTLES)
(GRUNTS, PANTS)
Vanessa.
(GROANS)
(WHIMPERS)
MIKE: Are you okay?
VANESSA: (GRUNTING)
I'm okay.
What's going on?
Where... where's Abby?
VANESSA: I don't know
where she is exactly, but...
(PANTING) ...she left
with them, the animatronics.
I just saw the animatronics
in... in a back room.
No, those are just prototypes
used for spare parts.
It's Charlotte.
She's behind everything.
I think Abby
might be in danger.
We need to get
to the security office.
It's the only way
I know how to help her.
Come on.
(VANESSA GROANS, PANTS)
I know you don't want to,
but you have to trust me.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Okay.
(GIRL LAUGHING IN DISTANCE)
Is there another way?
VANESSA: (PANTING)
Come on.
I don't understand. Are...
are the ghost kids here now?
No, there's just one ghost
here... in the marionette.
Charlotte.
After she was killed, I would
sometimes still see her here.
VANESSA:
She seemed stuck
in the last emotion
before she died.
(SCREAMING)
Rage.
But there's this music box
that kept her asleep.
(GENTLE MELODY PLAYING)
(RUSTLING)
(MECHANICAL RATTLING)
I put her to sleep
with this music box, but...
something or someone
broke it.
Wait.
Henry just gave me
a music box.
(WATER SPLASHING)
(GASPS)
Maybe coming this way
was a bad idea.
Hurry.
(YELPS)
(SCREAMS)
Mike.
(BURBLING)
(MENACING MUSIC PLAYING)
Here.
Here. Grab my hand.
Mike!
Come on.
Okay. Come on.
Come on, come on,
come on.
Where are you?
Vanessa, what are we doing here?
How do... how do we find Abby?
I'm trying to pull up
the tracker.
Abby thinks these
animatronics are her friends,
but they're not.
They're being wirelessly
controlled by the marionette.
By Charlotte.
What does she want?
My father killed her,
but she doesn't blame him.
She blames the parents.
All parents.
Okay. What does she want
with my sister?
It seems like
the marionette needs
something or someone
to bond to
in order to move around.
I'm afraid it might
target Abby next.
So there's
four animatronics,
and we don't know
which one has Abby.
They're all out because the
perimeter locks were disabled.
It's a system that drains the
animatronics of their power
the moment they leave
the building.
But we can find them once
we get their trackers working.
MIKE: Wait.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
Did you say
that the marionette
controls them
wirelessly?
Yeah.
Get up. Look, you... you
go... you go into town,
find Charlotte
and just try to buy me
as much time as you can,
and I'll try to disconnect
the signal from here.
Okay. Here.
We can use these.
Mike, I should have
told you about her.
I should have told you
about this place.
I... I, um...
(CHILDLIKE GIGGLING
IN DISTANCE)
Hey, don't worry about that
right now, okay? Just... just go.
Please.
Okay.
Hey, how do I close
the door?
There isn't a door.
There isn't a door?
What kind of idiot
designed this place?
All right, where the
hell are you guys?
(EXHALES) Okay.
Maybe no one
will notice them.
(THE BOMB! BY KENNY DOPE
PRESENTS THE BUCKETHEADS PLAYING)
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS)
Dude,
that costume is...
Legendary.
I don't know.
Seems kind
of fake to me.
Don't be rude.
What?
I mean, it just looks
like a toy, is all.
Hey, we're on the way to the
costume contest. You want to come?
I do, but first,
I have to go pull the heads
off some very bad people.
Right on.
(CHUCKLES)
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS)
He wins.
Yeah.
(MENACING MUSIC PLAYING)
(CROWD CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
Okay.
Here goes nothing.
(BEEPING)
(RAPID BEEPING)
(RAPID BEEPING CONTINUES)
(WHIRRING, CREAKING)
(MECHANICAL GROWLING)
(POWER WHIRRING)
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(SIGHS) Okay, come on.
(BEEPING)
Yes!
Vanessa.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Hey. Any luck over there?
MIKE: I located
the first tracker.
Freddy is at 175 West Elm.
Can you get there?
VANESSA: Copy that.
I'm close.
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
MARGARET: Harry,
come inside.
You're letting in
the mosquitoes.
HARRY: (SCOFFS SOFTLY)
Mosquitoes, mosquitoes, mosquitoes.
(GATE RATTLING)
(LOUD CLANK)
(GATE CLANKING)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
(CLANGING IN DISTANCE)
How is there not a door?
There's no way
that'll work.
Okay.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
Come on. Where are you?
(BEEPING)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(KISSES) Sleep tight.
(MUFFLED KNOCKING)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(CHILDLIKE GIGGLING
IN DISTANCE)
(GASPS)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
CHILD: (IN DISTANCE)
Hello?
MIKE: I hate this place.
(CHILDLIKE LAUGHING
OVER WALKIE-TALKIE)
Mike, you okay?
(STATIC CRACKLING)
(THUDDING ON ROOF)
(SCREAMS, GASPING)
(MECHANICAL GROWLING)
Holy shit!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SCREAMS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(MECHANICAL GROWLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(GRUNTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(METAL SCREECHING)
(YELPS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(HORN HONKING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SCREAMS)
(LOUD CLANG)
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SCREAMS)
(MECHANICAL GROWLING)
(GRUNTING)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(MECHANICAL GROWLING)
(GASPING)
(THUMPING ON ROOF)
(VANESSA YELPS)
(GASPS)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(SCREAMING)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
Please, come on.
Come on!
(ENGINE STARTS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
I'm going to bed.
(SIGHS)
ANNOUNCER: (OVER TV)
You're invited to Fazfest.
Come celebrate with Bonnie,
Foxy, Chica and, of course, Freddy.
Scrumptious snacks,
marvelous merchandise...
Did you leave
a door open?
I feel a draft.
(TV SWITCHES OFF)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(VANESSA YELPS, GRUNTS)
You left me to die.
What? What did we
do? (WHIMPERING)
All of you did.
(SCREAMS)
No!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(CAR ENGINE REVVING
IN DISTANCE)
(THUDS)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(PANTING)
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Here. Here.
You okay?
It's okay.
Is there anyone else
inside of the house?
Just us. And... them.
(WHIMPERING)
MARGARET:
What are they?
We need to get out of here
right now. Come on.
(MECHANICAL BUZZING)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
Whoa! (GASPS)
Please, please, please.
(MECHANICAL BUZZING)
(MIKE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS)
That worked.
I'm Debbie.
What's your name?
My name is Bonnie.
Can we be friends, Debbie?
Sure, we can.
LORRAINE: Debbie,
stop talking to your animals
and go to sleep.
I'm gonna go see
if your mom
will let us
stay up late.
ANNOUNCER: (OVER RADIO) Now,
if you're headed downtown this evening,
you may want to be
on the lookout for bears.
No, the circus
isn't in town.
Tonight marks
the inaugural Fazfest,
the local grassroots, cultural arts
festival celebrating the nostalgic...
(CHILDLIKE LAUGHING)
(GASPS)
(LOUD BUZZING OVER
SPEAKER) (GRUNTS AND GROANS)
(WHIRRING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTING)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(GRUNTS)
(CLANKING)
Oh, no.
(BANGING)
(GASPS)
(MECHANICAL GROWLING)
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS)
(MENACING MUSIC PLAYING)
Okay. Come on, Mike.
Come on.
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS)
It's now or never.
ANNOUNCER: (OVER RADIO) ...long
defunct food and entertainment chain
began last year as a
series of urban legends...
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(SCREAMS)
(WHIMPERING)
Oh, God. No.
(SOBBING) Please don't.
DEBBIE: Stop! (LORRAINE
WHIMPERING AND SOBBING)
Stop. Stop.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
Come on. Where is it?
Oh. Yeah.
(ELECTRICAL CLINKING)
(MENACING MUSIC PLAYING)
(MECHANICAL GROWLING)
(MIKE GASPS)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
(MIKE BREATHING HEAVILY)
Oh, no.
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING
AND CRACKLING)
It's not working.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(MECHANICAL SNARLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I have to disable the signal.
Come on.
Your mom
doesn't care about you.
Please, just stop.
(WHIMPERING) No.
She only thinks
about herself.
Parents are all the same,
and I have
to punish them for that.
(SOBBING) Please,
don't hurt her.
MIKE: I'm in. I'm in.
(BEEPS)
Yes, I'm sure.
(MECHANICAL GROWL)
(POWERING DOWN)
(BEEPING)
Go, go!
Go, go, go.
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
Do you need
some help?
You all need to stay
inside tonight.
Can they go with you? Of course.
You know, it looks like you
might be needing a good lawyer.
VANESSA: (OVER WALKIE-
TALKIE) Mike? (PANTING)
I got it, Vanessa.
They're deactivated.
(SIGHS)
(SIGHING IN RELIEF)
(BEEPING)
No.
No. Wait.
Vanessa, there... there's
one more dot. It's still moving.
That's not possible.
Where is it?
It's at my house.
The marionette.
I'm gonna head there
right now.
(BEEPING)
(BROODING MUSIC PLAYING)
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(RAPID CRACKLING
AND WHIRRING)
(CRACKLING)
Ta-da!
(SCREAMS)
(SCREECHES)
(BEEPING)
(POWERING UP)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
Mike?
(ENGINE REVVING)
They're turning back on.
The signal's been reactivated.
We're outmatched.
We need more help.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
MIKE: I've got an idea.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
I don't know
if you can hear me or not.
I... I don't even know
if you're all still here,
but... Abby needs you.
She needs your help now.
Do you hear me?
If any of you
ever really cared about her,
you're gonna help her
right now!
Please!
Please, I...
I can't do this alone.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
VANESSA: Oh, come on, come on.
Don't die.
(ENGINE KNOCKING, HISSING)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
Mike?
(STATIC CRACKLING)
Mike, are you there?
My radiator's busted.
I don't know what to do.
I... I can't...
I can't get to Abby. I...
(STATIC CRACKLING)
(GROANS AND YELLS)
Vanessa?
Oh, thank God.
Do you need a ride?
I need to go
to Mike's house.
Right now.
Vanessa,
what is going on?
Crazy eyes.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Abby?
TOY VOICE: Vanessa.
Vanessa.
Charlotte?
TOY VOICE: No, silly.
It's me, Abby.
(LAUGHING)
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
VANESSA: Charlotte,
what have you done?
ABBY'S VOICE: Come out,
come out, wherever you are.
Vanessa.
The adults in your life
betrayed you, too.
They don't deserve
your protection.
You don't have
to die with them.
You can help me.
Vanessa.
(LAUGHS)
You really thought
I'd forget
the first rule
of hide-and-seek?
Always check
behind the door.
(PANTS, THUDS)
(WHIMPERING)
Charlotte, listen to me.
Abby's innocent.
Just let her go.
You know, Vanessa,
I've always wondered,
what exactly goes on
inside of your head?
(ABBY'S VOICE LAUGHING)
(MUSIC BOX MELODY PLAYING)
(LAUGHING STOPS)
(SHUDDERING)
ABBY'S VOICE:
No. No.
(SCREAMING)
(ABBY COUGHING)
(ABBY GASPING, COUGHING)
MIKE: Abby.
ABBY: Mike.
Hey. Are you okay?
(GROANS)
I don't know
what happened.
I feel sick.
It's like the bag of orange
gummy candies all over again.
MIKE: All right, can
you... can you stand up?
ABBY: I think so.
MIKE: Yeah? Okay.
Let's get out
of here.
Yeah.
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS)
Come on. Come on.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(ABBY SCREAMS)
(MECHANICAL GROWLING)
(MENACING MUSIC PLAYING)
(MECHANICAL SNARLING)
MICHAEL: Knock, knock.
(VANESSA GASPS)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Hiya, sis.
Michael.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
Vanessa, what the hell
is going on?
MICHAEL: Oh,
let me guess.
She never told you
about me.
(CHUCKLES)
That's my sister for ya.
She always was a little
selective with the truth.
I'm Michael.
Michael Afton.
I am so pleased
to finally meet you.
Leave them alone, Michael.
They haven't done
anything wrong.
I think our father might
strongly disagree with that.
Your father's dead.
Yeah.
But I'm here
to continue his legacy,
just in time for Fazfest.
That was you.
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
Well, your aunt was the one
who rekindled everyone's
interest in Freddy's, but...
(CHUCKLES) I gotta admit,
I did add fuel to the fire.
(LAUGHING)
It's the perfect cover.
I mean... (SIGHS)
...we're all just
gonna blend right in.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Half of this town
will be dead by morning.
You can't do this.
This isn't a game.
Michael.
You can have
a normal life.
We could have
Vanessa, is that
what you thought?
You thought you
could just trade us in?
Betray us? Get
yourself a shiny new life?
You are his child.
You have a purpose.
We will always
be his.
Come home.
I am home.
Hmm.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(GIGGLES) Doesn't matter
to me anyway.
Yeah. Break their bones.
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
Crush them.
(ABBY GASPS)
It's okay. It's okay.
(MECHANICAL SNARL)
(VOICE SCATTING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(THUDS)
(GASPS)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
Freddy?
(GROWLS)
(MECHANICAL SNARLING)
(GASPS)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(CLUNKING FOOTSTEPS,
MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
Abby, you've been
a very, very bad girl.
(WHIRRING)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(THUDS)
(GRUNTS AND THUDS)
(COUGHS)
Where do you think
you're going, jackass?
(RAPID ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
Chica.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(POWERING DOWN)
Oh. What's wrong
with them?
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
Their systems,
they're... they're failing.
(HIGH-PITCHED WHIRRING)
They weren't made
to leave Freddy's.
They're dying?
No way, you can't die.
BOY: We're just
moving on.
We can't stay
in those bodies anymore.
Are you going to heaven?
See you there someday?
But not too soon.
Mike?
Yeah? You should know
that when we leave...
I won't be able
to hold him anymore.
He'll get out
eventually,
and he'll be stronger
than before.
Who?
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(CRACKLING STOPS)
(STAMMERS)
Goodbye.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
MIKE: (SOFTLY) Hey.
Mike? Whoa.
Everyone okay?
MIKE: Yeah, um...
Hey, we got to go.
Okay.
(ABBY SOBBING)
Come on, Abby.
Stay away from us.
What?
I can't trust you.
Mike...
Just stay away.
(SHORT, GASPING BREATHS)
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MECHANICAL CLICKING)
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(MECHANICAL CLICKING)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(IT'S BEEN SO LONG BY THE
LIVING TOMBSTONE PLAYING)
(SINGING) I don't know
what I was thinking
Leaving my child behind
Now I suffer the curse
And now I am blind
With all this anger,
guilt and sadness
Coming to haunt me forever
I can't wait for the cliff
At the end of the river
Is this revenge
I am seeking?
Or seeking someone
to avenge me?
Stuck in my own paradox
I wanna set myself free
Maybe I should
chase and find
Before they'll try
to stop it
It won't be long
before I'll become a puppet
It's been so long
Since I last
have seen my son
Lost to this monster
To the man
behind the slaughter
Since you've been gone
I've been singing
this stupid song
So I could ponder
The sanity of your mother
(SONG ENDS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Why do we have
to do this in the rain?
Because this whole place is
getting demolished tomorrow.
We got to grab everything
we can while it's still here.
Why couldn't we just make
the props for the haunted house?
Come on, they want
the authentic thing.
The authentic
Fazbear experience.
You can't
replicate that.
Just try
looking around.
Anything that might trigger
a little bit of nostalgia.
Ethan! Where are you?
You got something?
ETHAN: (IN DISTANCE)
Back here!
Dude, I... I think I just
found another room.
I'm not joking. I think I
just found another room.
Get back here
right now!
Yes, Ethan!
ROBERT: Okay, okay, okay.
You got something?
I... Yeah.
I think
I found one. I...
(LAUGHING) I think
I found a real one.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
How is this
still here?
It smells terrible.
Yeah, we gotta
take this with us.
Let's see, uh...
Hey, uh, Patrick,
cover it.
Let's get the dolly.
Cover it, will you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
(ETHAN CLAPPING)
(ETHAN WHOOPING)
Hey, guys, wait up!
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(WIND BLOWING)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(DEEP GROANING)
(UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING)
(CASSETTE TAPE CLATTERING)
(BUTTON CLICKS)
(TAPE WHIRRING)
HENRY: Leaving dead space.
Three, two, one.
This message is intended
as a warning.
Mike, I wish
we'd had more time
after our conversation
about Charlotte,
but I'm sending you
this message now in case I...
I can't deliver it in person.
There are things
you need to be aware of.
I was William Afton's
business partner for many years.
And although the equipment I have
left over from that time is outdated,
I can still track
some of the animatronics.
Mike, the marionette...
(RUSTLING)
Mike, get out
as fast as you can.
She's coming for you.
(STATIC DRONING)
(BUTTON CLICKS)
(WHIRRING STOPS)