Downloaded from YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site: YTS.MX
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
We have ignition,
we have a liftoff.
Program is in on time,
and the response is normal.
♪ Go, Johnny, go, go ♪
♪ Johnny B. Goode ♪
♪ Deep down in Louisiana
close to New Orleans ♪
♪ Way back up in the woods
among the evergreens ♪
Move! Move!
Hold on!
Roger that. Full sweep.
Go left.
Careful.
Here they come!
Fucking idiot.
You're welcome.
They're right.
Clear left.
All clear.
Stairs on me, boys.
Donnie, which way?
This should be Fordosa.
Left takes us to
the Aziziyah District,
towards the friendlies.
- Move it.
- Move.
Rhodie! We can't stay here!
Way out on me! Move!
Move it!
- Cover!
- The fuck!?
Come on, fuckers!
Jax, move! Jax!
Move, move!
Let's move!
I got you, man. I got you.
I got it, I got it.
Jax! Let's go!
He's gone!
Pull yourselves up!
Negative, negative!
They're on top of us!
Where's the fucking QRF!?
Jammed up! Five minutes out!
This shit is over in two!
- Go in there and light us up!
- Are you crazy?!
I said go in there!
This is Bravo One Zulu
requesting an ordnance drop.
Our GRID is 07238947.
Yes, I know it's
our fucking position!
Send it! Danger close!
Drop the motherfucker!
Come on.
Are you good?
Solid.
You?
Fuck! Fuck me!
I know, right?
This is tier one bullshit, man.
I just wanna know who to kill.
'Cause someone's definitely
getting blood for this shit.
Jax, what the fuck
is this shit, man?
Stasis resin residue. It
should dissolve quickly.
How do you know that?
I don't know, I just do.
Kelly.
Oh, Jesus, fuck, man!
Oh, Jesus, dude.
What's happening
here, boys? Fucking...
- You calm down.
- Calm down?
I just woke up in a fishbowl
in this goofy house of horrors.
And you want me to calm down?
Yeah, shut it!
Where the hell are we?
Black site.
Black site?
Run by who?
Yeah, I don't know.
Somebody with tech,
somebody with deep pockets.
Maybe Russians?
Chinese, maybe.
Well, this ain't Chinese.
It says our names.
Our unit designations.
How do you know that?
I don't know.
I just do.
Fuck me.
What?
Mags are all topped off.
Mine too.
Same.
Why would somebody do that?
Better yet, who
the fuck would do it?
Yeah.
What's the last thing you remember?
Hasakah.
Gunfight.
Donnie.
And that huge siren blast.
And that electric shock.
Felt like a damn taser on roids.
That's a fucking understatement.
And then just... just nightmares.
- We gotta move.
- Go where?
Whoever did this to us put us here.
They did it for a reason.
They'll be back.
The sooner the better.
Yeah, I'm with you, boss.
Say we get out of here right now.
Heads on a swivel.
Let's move.
Go on.
What are you doing?
I don't know. I just...
felt like that's what I
was supposed to do.
Now what?
Try manual.
Jax!
Okay, on me.
Together.
- Got it?
- Yep.
One...
two...
three...
Easy!
Wants to close.
- Got it?
- Yeah. We got it.
Reyes?
Give me...
Got him, buddy, eh?
Careful, that'll cut
your ass in half.
- Shit.
- Give me one.
Move it.
This one's fucked.
Look. It's bent.
Warped off its track.
Reyes.
You're up. Let's go to comms.
Shit.
I'm at a junction.
I can go up, down into darkness.
Or I've got a little
light just ahead.
Is that the other
side of this wall?
Think so.
All right, we'll check
it out. Be careful.
I'll do that.
Yeah. I'm through.
I'm on the other
side of your hatch.
I'm in a passageway, kind
of like the one that you're in.
Just a little bit longer.
How much longer?
20, maybe 25 yards.
There's an intersection.
And it T's left and right.
Thanks, dude.
- You good?
- Yeah.
Hey, boss?
Take a look at this.
Hey, check out these
gnarly-ass burns.
The impact marks.
Like someone was trying
pretty fucking hard to get in here.
Hey.
This place is like one big maze.
Have you ever seen
anything like this?
No. Never.
It's got to be underground.
More underwater.
Yeah.
I've heard of places like this.
Big old massive prisons underwater.
They keep spooks, HVTs,
you know, stuff like that.
Team buddy of mine,
he said he synced it.
Said they were calling
it the North Atlantic Vault
or something like that.
Said it was a huge
underwater prison.
- Bullshit.
- No.
I swear to God he
told me he synced it,
and I believe him.
That would explain the airlock.
What the hell was that?
Come on.
Wait, we're going to go towards it?
What is it?
Are you good?
What's with the clamp?
Power failure.
This place must be dying.
Hey, on me.
Fuck me.
Oh, shit.
Holy shit, man.
Hold it! Hold the room.
Reyes, Gibbs, on me.
Nash.
Sh, sh, sh, sh. Hey.
It's okay. It's okay.
Got you. Got you.
Pull the lever.
Pull the lever, the last lever.
Pull it, pull it, pull it.
Come on, now. Come on.
Holy shit!
The hell is that thing?
Hey, wait!
Come on.
Well, who the hell is she?
Where's Gibbs?
Fuck.
Kelly...
Run.
Fucking run!
Come on! Let's find a way out!
Hey, give me cover!
Down, down, down!
Hey, find a way out!
And watch her.
Like she's one of my own!
That ain't gonna hold.
You gotta be kidding
me, man. Come on!
Way out, on me.
Go, go, go.
Go! I'm right behind you!
Go.
Go, you go.
Reyes, let's go!
Hey!
Reyes!
Clear!
I'm just trying to help. Come on.
Got you.
Fuck!
- Take my weapon.
- I got you.
Come on.
Where's Reyes?
Fuck. That's my
fucking brother, dude.
Look, I only believe in two things.
Jesus Christ and Dolly Parton.
And those things don't look
like the Messiah nor the Queen.
So can we all please agree
that those are fucking aliens?!
Hey! Enough!
How did you know
how to use that thing?
She says we ain't gonna make it.
Appreciate that, darling.
That's real kind of you.
Fuck!
How is she?
Grazed her. Just hit me.
Cauterized the wound.
- What's she say?
- She said she's fine.
We need to go.
Didn't know you spoke Russian.
Yeah, me neither.
Who are you?
What?
She called us sleepers.
Said she ain't telling us shit.
Hey.
We just saved your
ass from those things.
What are they?
Huh? What?
She said you already told us.
I knew it!
It was aliens! It
was fucking aliens!
I knew the whole time!
God almighty, I told ya!
Okay.
Okay, so...
So where the hell are we?
Kelly.
She said we're on this ship.
A ship?
Fuck.
Like a spaceship? A spaceship?!
What is happening
here, guys? Am I fucking...
Okay. All right. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
All good.
We need to go.
They will be coming for us.
She speaks English.
Hey. Go where?
A safe place.
A safe place?
On a spaceship?!
- Nash!
- Not another fuckin' word.
Guys, I'm sorry.
But we just lost two more brothers,
and I don't want to lose
any more of them, all right?
I'm just having a really
hard time with this right now.
Yeah, we all are.
But hearing you piss
down your leg ain't helping.
I'm sorry.
God. What are we gonna do?
I don't fucking know.
But I know my little
girl ain't gonna grow up
with me being a
picture on the wall.
Uh, hang on, boss. I
don't mean any disrespect.
I'm just gonna say
one more thing, okay?
But it sounds like
you're saying that we
should take over the ship
and just fly our asses
back to Earth, right?
Okay? Okay. I'm
with it. I'm with it.
We'll go with it.
But one of those things almost
wiped out our entire team.
So what do we do?
We find the one nice
one, the one that they give
goop-filled jelly donuts to,
and we ask him, hey,
pal, do me a favor.
Will you fly me back to Tennessee?
'Cause I got some moonshine
buried in my backyard...
Shut the fuck up.
And calm the fuck down.
Hey!
We must keep moving.
Then get out of the way.
Bro, what are we doing?
How do we know she's on our side?
Well, she's been
running from them things
just as fast as we were.
Yeah, but, I mean, what if...
Kelly's got this.
Just gotta trust her, man.
If you say so.
It's okay. It's okay. Cover. Cover.
It's okay.
Give me your name.
Tell me your name.
Ravshana.
Ravi.
Okay, Ravi. I'm Kelly.
The big one with the scars.
Is that the leader?
Yes.
How many has it got?
One is too many.
Dozens?
More.
As big as this place is,
it's not gonna be easy to find us.
No, they'll know where we are.
They have motion sensors.
Yo. Yo. Fuck you doin'?
I got your shit.
What are they after?
A meal.
They're hungry.
Wait, what? She's kidding, right?
I mean, she...
She's gotta be pulling our leg.
What's inside it?
Can't tell. Glass
is all scratched up.
Way too cloudy to see anything.
Hold.
What? What is it?
That's a fucking person.
Sleepers.
God almighty, this is all
sorts of fucked up, man.
We shouldn't be here.
We need to go now.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm with her.
We need to get
the fuck out of here.
Jax, seeing as you're
my best friend and all,
I'd like to share
something with you.
Shit, what now, bruh?
You've been tripping
since we've been abducted.
That's just it. I've
been thinking about it.
I don't think we were abducted.
I think we were raptured.
- Raptured?
- Yeah.
What, this look like heaven to you?
This ain't heaven or hell.
This is the book of Revelation,
brother, and we're living it.
And I don't think those are aliens.
Those are demons.
What do you think?
I think your daddy should
have thought twice before
he started banging his sister.
- Jax.
- Yo.
Bandage.
Thank you.
For what?
Helping me.
I'm sorry for your friends.
Me too.
Where are you from?
Here.
Originally.
My family was from
a place called Sochi.
You know Sochi? Black Sea?
Have you been there?
I haven't. But I
heard it's beautiful.
What about you?
New York.
- America.
- Yeah.
Land of the free.
Home of the brave.
That's been the plan.
What's your daughter's name?
Sara.
What about her mother?
She lives with her.
And the two of you?
This ain't the job for most wives.
Have you always been a soldier?
Pretty much.
What is it you like
so much about it?
Like?
Is it the fighting for something,
or simply the fighting?
What's all this?
Anything and everything
they thought could
be worth taking back.
Relax.
You'll hear them
before you see them.
Kelly.
Yeah?
I've been thinking.
About what?
They know where we are.
They know where we're headed.
It's only a matter of time
before they get ahead of us
and try and box us in.
That's what I'd do.
Yeah.
What?
We'll make a stand.
No, you can't fight
them straight on.
You have to hit and run.
We need some bait.
Fuck that.
Relax, bro.
I'll do it.
You sure about that?
I run a 4.5 with gear.
Any of y'all could beat that?
I got you, boss.
Come on, bro, like...
That should be all right.
All right?
Good.
I got it.
Just be ready.
♪ Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm ♪
♪ California knows how to party ♪
♪ In the city, city of LA ♪
♪ In the city, good ol' Watts ♪
♪ In the city... ♪
♪ We keep it rockin'
We keep it rockin' ♪
Come on, motherfucker!
Come get some!
Come on!
♪ In the city... ♪
Come on, let's go!
Let's go!
♪ In the city... ♪
- Clear!
- Comin' in!
All right, I'll
admit it. I like her.
Too easy.
Nah.
That right there is what
we call our Zip-a-Mall focus.
Did you guys see Scars?
Negative.
Nah.
They don't work like that.
Their leaders are never bait.
Shit.
Move, move, move!
- Jax, move!
- Come on! Come on!
Aah!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Aah!
Let's go! Go, go!
Oh, hell, no!
I got you. I got you, Kelly.
It smells so bad.
It's like... It's like
standing in popcorn.
It's people! It's fucking people!
Holy shit!
Shut the fuck up!
- This is insane!
- Everybody shut up!
That is good advice.
Mama?
Ravi!
Mama!
Come.
Mama? Mama?
Who are you?
Russian fourth guards?
You talk too much.
Come!
What about the sensors?
Stay close.
Only go where I go.
Ravi, show them.
Nash.
Rhodie.
What's a Russian tank
commander doing here?
For the same reasons
special forces are.
How long have you been awake?
I don't know, a few hours.
Hours?
We were ambushed.
Constantine was
carrying the charges.
He sacrificed himself to
give us a chance to escape.
Tell me, where did you wake up?
I don't know. A
room about this size.
Our names stenciled below our pods.
Our weapons and kit
packed conveniently with us.
Not conveniently.
Purposely.
It was a trophy room.
Congratulations.
You're souvenirs.
How long have you been awake?
I can't know for sure.
20, 30 years.
How old do you think she is?
Did she just say 20 or 30 years?
That's right.
You can't be serious.
It's very hard to
track time in here.
She was born after the fall.
Fall?
The invasion.
Invasion?
It's our own fault, really.
We were the ones
who rang the dinner bell.
What the hell is she talking about?
In '77, your NASA sent out a probe.
It had a map stamped on it,
telling whoever found it
exactly where we were.
Admittedly, there were those
who were opposed to
the inclusion of the map.
They called it the Stamp of Osiris,
after the Egyptian god of death.
Okay, tell us more
about the invasion.
I am only a trophy, like you.
I only know what I've
been able to piece together.
But the war...
It's over.
They crushed Earth
in a matter of weeks.
With all the intel we
gave them, it was easy.
What intel?
They collected us first.
The world's greatest
military strategists on air,
land, and sea.
They have a device
which allows them
to hardwire into us.
You... You had nightmares? Yes?
They were not nightmares.
They were war games.
War games to study exactly
how we would fight and
how we could be defeated.
And the strange impulses
you cannot explain.
The gifts you woke up with,
where do you think they came from?
The connection they
made went two ways.
Accidental transfer.
Spillover.
And the ship?
It's basically a giant
shipping freighter
bringing home the spoils of war.
What spoils?
What they came here for.
Livestock.
Their cargo hold.
With all those pods.
Deck 31.
Yes. That entire hold
failed after the uprising.
Ravi's father was with
another group that got loose.
Sabotaged the reactor.
Wait, what does that
mean? Where are we?
I have no idea.
Floating in space?
She's telling the truth.
We don't share with sleepers.
It's how we've stayed
alive as long as we have.
They find you, you will talk
and lead them back to us.
So why share with us now?
I have no choice.
With my team gone, I
need you to help finish.
Finish what?
They are attempting to repair
their communications relay.
And how do you know this?
My gift.
I can hear them.
You can understand those things.
They are almost ready to broadcast.
If the transmission goes out,
their friends will
know where we are.
They will come.
They will wipe us out and
harvest the remaining holds.
We must stop them.
I can't believe this is it.
It's how I go out.
We're never going home.
How are you holding up?
I just realized that
if she's still alive...
she's, like, 40 years old.
Yeah.
I was thinking the same
thing about Beth and the boys.
You know what I
keep thinking about?
I can't get out of my mind?
Cargo hold.
All those people just getting
sucked up into an alien ship.
Wake up and then served
on a platter for evening chow.
So what are we going to do?
You know where the comm center is?
I do.
Top deck.
It's their base, where
they're strongest.
What's the plan?
From what Ravi has told me,
there can be no more
than two dozen left.
Why don't we just
take the fight to them?
Too risky.
Too many.
Got it.
We will use the ventilation shafts.
But once we enter, they
will be on us in seconds.
Unless they have something
else to keep them busy.
You have what you
need to take it out?
Okay.
Lead the way.
It really hurts.
This harness is
pinching my bean bag.
What do they use these for?
For air?
There's no way those big
fuckers crawl through this thing.
Shit.
The comms center is right there.
We will repel in,
plant the charges,
and hopefully make it back to
the bulkhead before detonation.
That's where we come in.
All right, I'm counting
on you to keep them safe.
You got it, boss. I can't wait.
We'll keep them busy, hold
them off as long as we can.
Press here and here
to activate the shield.
Here and here to turn it off.
Anya.
Anya Mitov.
Michael Kelly.
Good luck.
Watch your ass, big man.
Hey, you too, hillbilly.
All right, let's move.
Come here.
That's it?
We wait.
Here we are.
Here we are, motherfucker,
come and get us.
I liked Jax. He was nice.
Yeah, he's the coolest.
So, uh...
Who's Constantine?
He was my best friend.
Yeah, I bet he's
pretty cool, too, huh?
I'm sorry about that.
Me, too.
He's moving.
- What the fuck?
- The hell they going?
They're coming.
Nash, you copy? Over.
Roger that. Over.
Tangos inbound. Get
the fuck out of there.
Get the fuck out of there.
Get out right now!
Fuck me.
Rhodie, they're fucked.
Not if you can get to them.
Rhodie!
Nash, I'm coming to you!
By hook or by crook.
Fuck you.
Ravi. Go.
Go! Go!
Go!
Now you. Go with her.
Keep her alive.
Mama, stop!
Here it comes...
Mama!
Come on. Come on, come on.
Nash, you copy?
Nash!
It's done! It's fucking done!
But I got a heap of trouble in tow!
Hang tight. I'm coming to you.
Shit!
Go right! Go right!
Come on! They're coming!
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Hey, hang on. Hang on.
Get in.
- What?
- Get in!
All right. Good.
Wait. What are you doing?
Whatever I can, sweetheart.
Whatever I can.
Let's go!
Let's do some country-ass shit!
Come and get me, you
big, ugly motherfucker!
Yeahhh!
Come on!
If you can hear me,
boss, it's been real.
♪ In the city, good ol' Watts ♪
♪ In the city, city of Compton ♪
♪ We keep it rockin'
We keep it rockin' ♪
Oh, fuck.
Fuck. Okay, okay, all right.
♪ We keep it rockin' ♪
Nah.
Sara!
Please, please...
Kelly?
- Kelly, are you all right?
- Yeah.
Nash?
And your mother?
Whiny bitch.
How's it hangin', boss?
Get me the fuck down!
All right, hang tight.
I'm on it.
- Where we going, boss?
- To find Ravi.
Here.
Give me that. Hold the door.
- Ravi!
- I'm here!
Back away! Get away! Get away!
We got company!
God almighty!
Ravi! Ravi!
Hey! Are you okay?
Okay, go.
Let's move! Let's move!
Go! Move over!
Move over! Go, go, go!
Nash!
I'm out!
Boom!
We did it.
We fucking did it.
Fuck.
Go!
Come on. Come on, motherfucker.
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
No!
You want me?
I'm right here!