♪ Call on me, call on me ♪
♪ I'm the same boy I used to be ♪
That's hard.
Yeah.
That's dirty hard.
♪ Call on me, call on me ♪
Oh, man!
Remember who we're fighting for,
gentleman.
♪ Call on me, call on me ♪
Bring it on, bring it on! Bring it on!
♪ I'm the same boy I used to be ♪
♪ Call on me, call on me ♪
I like this house. I think we're
gonna take it.
Yes, sir. See you in a bit.
Let us know if there's any changes.
Moving.
Sir, there's a wall up here.
Copy that.
Why is there a wall?
It's, er, two apartments.
Top and bottom floor.
Two houses.
Understood.
Break it.
Let's go. Come on.
Redman 0-6, Profane 5-4.
Er, contact individual headed
north to your location.
Civilian traffic east to west
of your structure.
Er, prox, Profane 5-4-10-8.
Er, Profane 5-5-10-5.
All stations this net,
all stations this net.
Clearance operations are complete.
All friendly units are RTB at this time.
Be advised you have new friendly
location.
Baker Company has moved
north-west of your location.
Two klicks.
Understand. Copy all.
Sir. Baker Company were here.
They're now here.
Two kilometers in this position.
Copy that.
Manchu, stand by for sit rep.
Say when ready to copy. Over.
Frogman, send your traffic.
At 0-niner-7,
we observed people probing
our position from the east.
Section Papa 1-0, building 1-7-4,
east of route Boiler.
At 0-9-1-2,
we saw massing at building 1-7-5
north of route Spartan. Break.
At 0-niner-1-6,
a blue Daewoo with MAMs
north on route Lakers.
How copy. Over.
Yeah, Frogman, repeat everything
after blue Daewoo.
Over.
Manchu, a blue Daewoo
with military-age males
traveling north on route Lakers.
Over.
Copy all.
Do you have any more traffic
for my station? Over.
Negative, Manchu.
How's your signal?
It's good now. Still intermittent.
Cool.
Got eyes on the north-west
corner of building four.
Is that white Hilux still there?
No, the Hilux pulled out, like...
five minutes ago.
But I got a male...
white shirt, dark tracksuit pants
looking at our position.
That sound familiar?
Negative. ID any weapons?
No weapons.
He's gone.
Is he going on the list?
Single MAM, white shirt,
dark tracksuit pants,
building four, north-west corner.
By the way, my, uh... my blue
Nike hoodie
went missing off the base.
If you see somebody out there
wearing it, let me know.
Don't shoot 'em, either. I want it back.
Yeah, I'll try.
We should check that run of
buildings to the West again.
I mean, you could step right
across those rooftops
if you wanted.
Yeah.
Walk right to us, right?
Mmm-hmm.
How's it going, Dozer?
Baker 6 tracking. Baker 6 out.
Huh?
How's it going?
Going well.
Okay.
That's that new guy energy.
Mmm-hmm.
How is it down there?
Cigarettes and tea. You want tea?
No, I'll pass.
What you got up here?
Peekers.
Where?
Corners of building four.
Oh, I gotcha.
I can't see anything.
Oh, he's back.
White T-shirt?
Mmm-hmm.
Alpha Two, this is One.
We might have guys starting
to move on our position.
Maybe because they heard you
sledging through that fucking wall
all night.
We could hear every strike.
Why didn't you use a charge?
I didn't wanna make a noise.
Not sure that worked out for you.
Profane 5-4, this is Redman 6.
Can you slew your sensor
to the east of my position
on one-zero-zero meters
on building per GRG?
Call contact.
Redman 0-6, stand by.
Turning.
Prox 5-5, track OP-1.
Profane 5-5 looking.
Contact, corner, IC personnel.
Hey, er, we got an individual
who was peeking
on the north-west corner of building 4.
He's disappeared to the west.
Do you see anybody hanging
around that corner? Over.
Stand by. Looking.
5-4 contacts.
Just be advised he's been
probing our position.
Do you see any massing
or suspicious activity
that can indicate a threat?
Over.
Negative, 0-6.
Er, you're all good.
Roger that, Profane.
Redman out.
You keep an eye on that for me.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Headscarf, red-green jacket.
Peeking again.
That's the fourth fucking time
he's done that.
Is he peeking or probing?
Peeking with serious intent to probe.
How many times are we gonna
let this guy do this?
I'm gonna relay to OP-2.
Hey, Cowboy, give me a heads-up
if you see this guy come to
your position.
Headscarf, red-green jacket.
Copy. We're getting a build-up
of activity here, too.
I had a pair of guys in
blue jeans probing, twice.
I have two MAMs of that description,
just showed up here.
Blue jeans, one red shirt.
Yeah, that's them.
Well, it looks like they're
getting their Jihad on.
Alpha One, Bravo One, we're in a TIC.
We're getting rockets and small arms fire.
We're all good right now,
but we're pulling air to our position.
Roger that. Check in with BDA
when able.
Wilco.
Alpha Five, this is Bravo Four.
Hey, I think we're gonna need
to pull Profane
to our AO. Over.
Roger that, Bravo Four.
Redman 0-6, this is Profane.
We have been re-tasked.
We're checking off station at this time.
Roger that, Profane.
Hey, is there a reason
they're pulling air from us
and not sourcing it from somewhere else?
I'm on it.
What's up?
We just lost air support.
Pushing to Bravo.
Wild Eagle Base, Wild Eagle 2-4.
Profane 5-4 checked off station
at this time.
I'm looking for any available
air assets. Over.
That's not good.
Roger, stand by.
They're troops in contact.
Aff-irm, Wild Eagle Base.
Standing by.
Hey, Cowboy, we're getting
movement here.
Yeah,
the streets are definitely clearing out.
Yeah, I'm tracking.
Captain Erik.
It's not good.
They say they call on all Muslims
for Jihad.
Jihad to come now.
To kill you.
To kill Americans.
Yeah, that sucks.
Yeah, that does suck.
All right. Go keep lower deck
locked down.
You understand?
Hey. Downstairs. Keep it fucking secure.
Okay.
Do you think they're gonna do it?
I think we're about to find out.
You've been in there for a while.
Yeah, I live in there now.
All right, swap out. I'll relieve you.
Yes, sir.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Hey, Frank. Jump on this a second.
I'm out of dip and I gotta stretch, dude.
Yeah, I got you.
I got a blue Opel moving east to west
towards OP-1 position. Over.
Roger that, blue Opel.
Blue Opel is approaching building three.
Three MAMs just exited vehicle.
Correction, make that four.
Heading into building three.
PKM!
Fuck.
Cowboy, the fourth MAM
had a PKM.
I couldn't get the shot off.
Over.
Weak.
What happened?
I, er... I couldn't get him.
He, um... He ran inside too fast.
Weak.
Yeah, we have definite massing.
Hey, six MAMs just exited
building five in my sector.
I'm seeing the same where we are.
Yeah, building three. I'm gonna
take a piss.
Oh, fuck.
Grenade!
Our position is under small arms fire.
Frank, Tommy, Elliott? You good?
Motherfucker.
Move!
Movement, balcony!
Elliott?
I'm out.
Stand up. You hurt?
Look at me.
No, I'm good,
I'm good. Check on Elliott.
Think our gear's still in there.
Down.
Lift your arm up. Look at me.
How bad is it?
Yeah, we're gonna need a cas-evac.
All right.
Okay.
This is Frogman-6 Romeo.
We are troops in contact
at our last known position.
More info to follow. Stand by.
Wild Eagle Base, Wild Eagle 2-4.
We are troops in contact.
Requesting immediate air support.
Over.
Alpha Two, this is One.
We've had grenades thrown into
our position.
Copy, One. We're in contact too.
Elliott is injured. Are we coming
to you
or are you coming to us?
Fuck.
Stand by.
Hey!
Downstairs. Keep it fucking secure.
Alpha One, we're moving to you.
We'll let you know when we're inbound.
Yeah. All right.
All OPs are under attack.
This is what we're gonna do.
We're gonna collapse to the first deck,
cas-evac Elliott.
Break it down.
Let's get ready to move.
Yes, sir.
Collapse. Collapse.
OP-2, what's your status?
I gotta get the receiver.
Sir, sir, sir, sir!
What are you doing?
I gotta get the receiver.
We're in a TIC, on our way.
Mac, not a good idea.
This is Frogman-6 Romeo.
We need a cas-evac at our last
known position. Over.
Cover me.
Yeah.
Frogman, confirm sector and
building number.
OP-1 location as follows:
Papa 1-0, building 5-8.
How copy? Over.
Frogman, read back as follows:
Papa 1-0, building 5-8.
Good read-back.
Frogman, any amplifying remarks?
Over.
Negative. No amplifying remarks.
Just need a cas-evac. Advise on ETA.
Over.
Copy that. Stand by. Over.
Um, guys, my shit is still in there.
Where is it?
I don't fucking know, dude.
It's in there somewhere.
And my shit's in there too.
All right, I... I got it.
Alpha One, we're moving to you.
We'll let you know when we're inbound.
Copy.
Shit.
Tommy, you see where that gunfire
came from?
Um, I saw a guy.
They shot through the window.
I can't find it.
It's in there, bro.
I can't fucking find it, man.
Frogman-6 Romeo,
cas-evac is inbound.
Callsign Bushmaster on ID 7-5-5.
ETA 1-0 mikes. Over.2
Copy. Bushmaster 7-5-5. Over.
Bradley launched. ETA 10 minutes.
Ten minutes!
All right. Stack up.
Get ready to collapse.
We're moving down.
Yes, sir. Sir.
I still think there's dudes on our roof.
Yeah. We're gonna blow claymores
as we move.
Sam?
Yes, sir?
Alpha Two, be advised,
we'll be blowing claymores.
Oh, fuck, I got a bunch of C4
in my bag.
I gotta get my shit.
Roger.
Yeah, I'm gonna get it.
Sam, Tommy.
Let's go.
Coming. Coming.
My shit's to the left.
His gear's in the corner.
Cover me.
I got you.
I got Frank's shit right here.
God.
How we doing?
Yeah, I'm up. It's cool.
Tommy, on me.
All right.
I got your kit. Med bag.
Thanks, Mac.
That's your kit.
We're good.
Laerrus, give me some hands!
Yeah. Moving.
Clip him in.
Yes, sir.
Tommy?
OP-2, this is One.
We are breaking down,
getting ready to move. Over.
Yo, someone clip me in.
Yeah, Tommy, on me.
There is an M79 in that room there.
Oh, shit, it's mine. Mine. You got it?
Sam, sledgehammer is in front of you.
Lock me in. Lock me in.
I got ya.
Helmet's behind.
You got that?
Who's got that?
Yep.
All right.
Hook me up.
Yep.
Frank, you let me know
when we're up on gear.
Sir.
I need my backpack.
Is there any more gear
in that room, Tommy?
Uh...
Negative.
Okay.
Helmet.
Over here, brother.
Fuck.
All right.
We're all right.
We're up!
Copy.
Go, Mac.
Alpha Two, we're about to blow
claymores.
Blow claymores, Sam.
Roger.
Fire in the hole!
Go!
Last man!
I got the window.
I have the door.
This is Bushmaster.
Your cas-evac is inbound.
We are six minutes from your position.
Over.
Sir, six minutes out.
Copy, Bushmaster.
Okay. Go, go.
Alpha Two, we're preparing
to receive cas-evac platform.
Are you guys broken down yet?
One, not yet.
Check.
All right. Here's the breakout plan.
Mac, Laerrus, you're covering the family.
Yes, sir.
When the tank rolls up, Frank,
you're gonna pop smoke.
Check.
Scouts are gonna lead us out.
It's gonna be Tommy, Elliott, Sam.
And I'm bringing up the rear.
Ray, you're with me.
Once Elliott is in the tank,
we are all coming back inside
the building.
All right. Do it.
No sudden movements.
No talking.
And keep their hands
where these men can see them.
Frogman, this is Bushmaster.
Advise on how to receive you.
Over.
Bushmaster, we'll be extracting
two pax,
exiting out a metal gate directly...
Where's your smoke?
...outside our building,
marked by HC. Over.
Back right pocket.
Copy, Frogman.
Two pax, metal gate.
ETA five minutes. Over.
Copy, Bushmaster.
Five minutes, sir.
All right.
Alpha Two, when the tank rolls
up, we're gonna break out.
Once we get Elliott evacuated,
we're pulling back to our house.
Break.
With me.
What? Why?
Sir, why? What is planned?
We need to cover this door.
Anything we can do
to facilitate your movement to us?
Just don't fucking shoot us
when we roll up.
You cover this door.
Why, sir?
Just do it, okay?
All right.
Hey. Mac.
Are we good in there?
Yeah, we're good.
We're a few minutes out here.
Yes, sir.
All right.
Hey, find out for me
whether the tank is gonna be
left side or right side.
Yes, sir.
Bushmaster, this is Frogman-6 Romeo.
What side of the gate will you
be landing? Over.
How you doing?
I'm good.
Left hand side.
Left hand side. Over.
Left hand side, sir.
Copy.
Yeah, that fucking claymore
rocked me, dude.
Fucking rung my bell.
Do me a favor.
Check on Tommy.
He was pretty close to that grenade.
Yeah.
Elliott, you good?
Good.
I'm good. I'm good.
Okay?
Yeah, bro.
Yeah? Let me see it.
Yeah, I'm good.
Fuck.
We are 10 minutes behind.
Unable to breakout.
Oh, fuck me.
Um...
Roger that.
Cache made aware and ready
to receive wounded.
Three mikes out from your position.
Copy, Bushmaster.
Three mikes out.
All right.
Sir, what's going on?
You are holding security.
Yes.
We are gonna bust out,
go to the Bradleys.
I'm gonna get in a Bradley,
you guys are gonna come back
to the house.
Just like before. Everything is okay.
All right?
Frogman, Frogman,
we are two mikes. Over.
Copy that.
Two mikes.
Two mikes out. Pass.
Mac. Mac.
Frank.
Two minutes. Two minutes.
Tommy, you okay?
You good?
Frank, I hear it. Prep the smoke.
Smoke's prepped.
Frogman-6 Romeo, approaching
your OP now.
One minute out.
One minute.
One minute. One minute.
Tommy?
Sir.
All right, Frank. Smoke out.
Smoke out.
Frogman, we ID your smoke.
Thirty seconds.
Hey, stay in the stack. Stay in the stack.
Ramps down. Ramps down. Ramps down.
We're gonna go.
Breakout, breakout, breakout!
Go. Go.
Hold up.
Go.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Fuck!
Fuck!
Oh, my God!
No!
Ah!
Oh, my God!
Oh, God!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Hey. Get air.
Sir.
Wild Eagle Base, Wild Eagle 2-6.
When platform is available,
push to my pos.
Advise on ETA when...
This is Bushmaster.
We are troops in contact.
We've just experienced a large IED.
We have to RTB at this time.
How copy? Over.
Bushmaster, this is Manchu.
Solid copy on troops in contact,
what's your sit-rep?
Yeah, upon arrival at OP-1,
er, we were ramps down
before the Frogman element
was able to...
Hang in there. (GROANS)
We had a massive IED. Break.
Our gunner took some frags.
We're gonna have to RTB this cache.
On me! One on me!
We're gonna need assistance
off-loading our casualties.
Over.
Solid copy on all, Bushmaster.
Proceed and de-conflict with
medical personnel
at front gate of Camp Corregidor.
Alpha Three, this is Alpha Two.
What's your status? Over.
Wilco. Understand.
Alpha Two, negative.
Er, we're still taking effective fire.
Can you assist?
We're receiving small arms fire.
We got Dash 2 in tow.
Roger. Understand.
Have you sustained any injuries?
Fuck. Hold on, Manchu.
Not at this time.
I got Dash 2 in tow.
We're receiving a lot of
rocket and small arms fire.
Machine gun on rooftop.
Tommy, what the fuck are you doing?
I need you to help me.
Get the fuck out here now!
Hey, can we get some guns up here?
Frogman-6, this is 5. Radio check.
Give me a good base of fire up there.
Stand by.
I'll be sending some guns up to you.
Break. Alpha Three, this is Alpha Two.
We are pushing guys to our rooftop.
Bushmaster, copies all.
Elliott, you're good.
Are you in contact with the Frogman?
Is that situation over there?
That's a negative, Bushmaster.
A-ffirm. We're getting the same thing here.
Understand. Understand. Break. Break.
Alpha One, this is Alpha Two.
Radio check.
Frogman, this is Bushmaster.
Radio check. Over.
Frogman-6, passing in the blind
to your location.
Frogman, Bushmaster. Radio check.
Over.
All elements be prepared to break down.
Zawi, I need you to break down
in approximately one minute.
Over.
Negative on comms with
the Frogman element.
Roger that, we are coming in now.
Will attempt continuously...
Frogman-6, this is 5.
Advise you attempt it on your end.
Over.
What's your status?
Stand by.
Prior to breaking out,
we either gonna blow those claymores
or we gotta swoop them up.
Fuck!
Alpha Two, this is One.
We have taken massive casualties.
We're anticipating coordinated
enemy attack
at our position at any moment.
We need you to collapse to us.
Time, now!
Jake, this is One. Collapse to us, now!
I'm tracking, but where are you guys?
We're by...
We're b...
Look for the blood and the smoke.
We're there!
Two rooms deep!
What was that?
Fuck!
Two rooms deep!
No, no, don't, don't...
Fuck, fuck!
Don't touch!
Go, go, go.
Hang on. Hang on.
Jake, what's your update?
Alpha One, this is Alpha Two.
We're experiencing effective
fire from across the street.
Um, we're looking at trying
to break out of here
once it gets soft. Stand by.
Copy that. Just fucking hurry.
Yeah, wilco.
Hey. I gotta do a blood sweep.
Fuck! Fuck!
Okay. All right. All right.
All right, Elliott. I'm right here.
I'm right here. Just hang in there.
You're not alone, man.
You're okay. Rolling you over.
You're okay. You're okay.
Your back's okay.
You're good. All right?
You're good.
Come on.
All right. You're gonna feel a little bit
of pressure.
Oh, no.
I got you. Sit down.
Hey, you need to sit down.
Get the fuck down!
Stay in the room!
It's coming over your boot
right now, all right, man.
All right. Just hold on.
It's just... Oh, man, your shoe.
It's, uh...
Oh, man, that's not gonna work, okay.
Here's what we're gonna do, all right.
Sir?
Yeah?
Apply pressure.
Like this, down.
Manchu-6 X-Ray, this is Frogman-6
Romeo.
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
This is Manchu X-Ray,
advise on number of casualties.
Manchu-6 X-Ray, this is Frogman-6
Romeo.
We have two severely wounded.
We need another cas-evac
as soon as possible.
Be advised an IED caused
the injuries. Over.
Here's what we need to do.
Okay, all right.
Okay.
Your leg's like a tree trunk, man.
Frogman, you are broken
and unreadable. Say again.
Manchu-6 X-Ray, this is Frogman-6
Romeo.
We have two severely wounded.
We need another cas-evac.
Over.
Hey, who's the severely wounded?
Is it me?
No, it's not you.
...this is Profane 5-6-5-7...
Who is it?
it's not you.
Mission number 3-9-0-1...
It's not you.
Then who the fuck is it?
Two by marine F-18s.
No. Sam.
Who is it?
Don't worry about it.
Checking in as fragged.
Who is it?
We are postured for
a show of force at this time.
Hey. Hey! We got air back.
We can't do gun runs
because the bad guys are right
on top of us.
But we can coordinate a show
of force.
Do you want me to do it?
Do it.
Profane 5-6, Wild Eagle 2-4,
we need an immediate show
of force over our position,
over our position OP-1,
from south to north. How copy.
Over.
A-ffirm, Wild Eagle 2-4.
A show of force, south to north,
inbound 30 seconds.
Fuck. It's bleeding through.
Guys, I need more gauze!
Yeah, yeah.
Here. Here, here, here.
Okay. Okay.
Ray!
Ray, pressure!
Oh, fuck.
What? What the fuck is Frank doing?
Frank! Frank!
Lock the fucking stairwell down.
There's guys up there.
Hey, bro.
I need you to take over
comms for me. You got it?
Got you.
Right, yeah, okay.
Wild Eagle Base, Wild Eagle 2-6.
Requesting relay to Manchu X-Ray.
Uh, we're receiving small arms fire,
grenades.
And we have two severely wounded.
We need air support. Over.
It's bleeding through too much.
Just stop, just stop, just stop.
Please, please. Please.
Fuck.
Sam, we gotta put a tourniquet
on you, all right?
Sir.
Yeah.
Alpha One, this is Alpha Two.
What's your sit-rep over there?
We're treating Elliott and Sam right now.
Be advised, possible multiple MAMs
on our rooftop.
Roger that.
We're taking effective fire
from across the street.
We're 200 meters to your East.
Move, move, move!
Stand by for an ETA on our side.
Roger that.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Fuck!
Hey,
I'm gonna do something that's gonna hurt.
I can't put the tourniquet on.
I need to apply pressure another way.
All right?
No, no, no, no, no,
don't fuck...
Don't touch me. Don't t...
Don't...
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
All right.
I... I need morphine.
Okay.
Uh, morphine.
Hey.
Give me morphine.
Jake, where are you guys?
Hold on.
Alpha One, this is Alpha Two.
We've broke out of OP-2.
Guys...
Sir?
We're now 100 meters to your location
to the east.
Sir, what do we do?
Yeah, we're still on route... Be advised...
I don't know.
We're about two minutes out.
We're looking at a coordinated attack.
Give it to him.
Okay... I don't know where the morphine is.
It's in my bag. It's in my bag.
It's in the medic bag.
What, your, in the medic bag?
It's in the pocket.
Okay, I'm getting it, I'm getting it,
I'm getting it.
Hey, Ray. I need morphine too.
You gotta give me some.
Ray, give it to me.
Okay.
I got it, I got it, I got it,
I got it, I got it.
Give it to me straight.
Shoot!
Shoot.
Sir!
Hey.
You fucked up?
I did it upside down. I did it
in my, uh, in my own thumb.
You all right though?
You good?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Bro, bro, you there, bro?
Yeah.
You gotta get another one.
There's more in there!
Right.
Get another one out.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
We're still pushing to you.
Pushing to your location,
OP-1. ETA, five minutes.
We're taking effective
fire from multiple rooftops.
Okay. It's coming, it's coming.
Hey, man.
Hey. Elliott,
it's in your arm right now, all right?
It's in your arm.
The morphine's in your arm,
it's going into you.
You're gonna feel better any second.
I need more morphine, man.
You can't have more.
It's not enough.
I'm telling you, it's not enough.
I'm telling you, you're good.
You're not even the one
we're worried about.
Okay?
Wild Eagle Base, Profane 5-6,
we are flying to you. We're overhead.
We are contact.
The friendlies, the Frogmen,
moving from south to north.
And tally the individuals,
they are taking contact from the north.
Taking contact from the north. Uh...
Profane 5-6 is, uh, contact several
individuals.
They are using rooftops
along Frogmen's position.
They are using the rooftops
going from East to West.
Uh, we are, uh, contact the friendlies.
They are moving from east to west
as well.
And, uh, it looks like
we are picking up the second element
of Frogmen
to the West side of that, uh, same,
uh, same, same street.
Uh, Profane 5-7, keep your sensors
to the North in vicinity of OP-1.
We are contact the friendlies,
uh, linking up on that street right now.
And, uh, Profane 5-6 is,
uh, tally several individuals
that are just to the north
of the Frogman position.
Just to the north of the Frogman
position,
we have several individuals
setting up in the prone.
Just setting up an ambush
to the Frogman position.
And we are also, uh, contact
several enemy to their east
using the rooftops in vicinity
of their position. Just to...
Profane 5-6, this is 1-0-8.
Be advised, we are reaching
OP-1 position.
Advise on all enemy positions.
AJ! AJ!
Zawi, I'm coming to you!
Fucking bump 'em out,
bump 'em out!
Ready to move!
Three, two, one, move.
Fucking move!
Let's fucking move!
Changing!
0-8,
stand by for sit-rep.
Hold! Hold!
Move, move, move, go, go, go!
Hold!
Move! Let's move!
Driveway! Driveway! Go! Go!
Move! Go, go, go!
One, this is Two. We're coming to you.
We have eyes on you.
We're coming to you.
On the gate!
Come on, let's move, move.
Move left to right!
Covering!
Hold this position.
They're coming to us.
Move!
Go!
AJ...
Zawi, move!
Go, go, go, go! Moving!
On me! Contact rooftop!
Contact rooftop!
One, this is Two. We're coming.
We're fucking coming.
On me!
Frogman-6, Frogman-5.
Prepping smoke!
Smoke out!
Ready?
No.
We gotta move! We gotta move!
Right now, let's go. Come on.
Frogman-6, this is Frogman-5 Romeo.
Stand by.
Right, we're moving, we're moving.
Frogman, Frogman, coming in.
Move, Brock!
Move, move, move!
Ready!
Fucking move!
Last man!
Frogman, Frogman, coming in.
All right, check it out.
We got multiple leg injuries here.
I need morphine. Gauze.
Whatever you guys got.
We got windows in every...
Hey, watch out.
We got windows in every inch
of this house
and we got dudes on our roof.
We need to get these guys
the fuck out of here, now.
Have you called for cas-evac?
I can't punch out from here.
Go, get up there.
Zawi, go.
Can you make comms?
Yes, sir.
Sir.
Has anyone looked at you,
checked you out?
Hey, take a knee, take a knee,
take a knee.
Take a knee.
Has anyone looked at you?
Let me do a blood-sweep.
Manchu X-Ray, this is Frogman-5
Romeo.
Be advised,
OP-2 have consolidated
on OP-1 position.
How copy. Over.
Is the cas-evac platform
coming back here?
What calls have been made?
Dude...
I'm fucked up.
I'm gonna need you to run point.
What's going on up there?
All right,
we got grenades thrown
in this room over here.
We've probably got, probably
got dudes on our roof still.
All right.
This is the external door,
straight ahead, all right?
Yeah.
On me.
Gonna need some ammo, dude.
All right, I'll get it to you.
Let's go.
Go.
Hit in both of his legs and hit
in his arm.
And he's got abdomen wounds,
and, man, he's lost a lot of blood.
Okay.
And, uh,
there's something burning inside of him.
Yeah, that's phosphorous.
It's all over outside.
Elliott, can you breathe?
Hmm.
Yeah. All right. You're good.
You're good.
You guys hit me with that fucking
morphine?
Yeah, I gave you the morphine.
I gave you the morphine, man.
When?
A few minutes ago.
Right before you got here.
Did you do it in my arm?
'Cause I got shitty blood
return in my legs.
I did it in your arm, man.
I did it right in your arm.
Move, move, move!
Move, move! Move!
Let's go, boys!
Let's fucking do this!
Hey! Hey!
I know we're moving fast,
but don't step on anyone's fucking legs!
All right, Sammy. Let's go.
Relax, man.
My man, let's do this!
Come on!
Don't fuck with him!
Stay in there, Sam, stay in there.
All right, guys, listen up.
Everybody shut the fuck up.
Eyes on me.
Start doing a re-org.
Prepare for breakout.
We're gonna get these guys cas-evacced.
Yes, sir.
All right.
Yo, Brock.
Yo, what's up, Frank?
You got ammo for the gunners upstairs?
Yeah, outside pocket.
I want four Bradleys over here.
Two for cas-evac, two for extraction.
I want the cas-evacs on
either side of the front gate.
Brad one will be right.
Brad two left.
Yes, sir.
Hey, lock down the windows!
Thank you.
Go.
Fuck!
We can't make it.
This is Frogman-5 Romeo.
We need a cas-evac from OP-1 building.
Four Bradleys.
Two for cas-evac of two severely
wounded. Break.
Hell, man, get off me!
Stay in there, bro. You're good.
Relax. Hey.
He's fucking good, man.
It's a fucking paper cut!
Hey.
You're a fucking Frogman, Sam!
He doesn't need this!
He's a fucking Frogman!
Let's go! Let's go!
Fuck!
Fucking A.
Frogman, Manchu, you are denied
Bradley cas-evac due to IED,
small arms threat in the AO.
Authorization pending...
Fuck.
...CO approval.
How copy. Over.
Solid copy. Stand by.
Sir.
They're waiting on Brigade approval.
What the fuck?
Because the last tanks got fucked up.
So they won't send a cas-evac
unless the CO gives the thumbs up.
We gotta get him out of here, sir.
You've gotta be the CO.
Sir. Say back.
Radio them right now.
Say you're the CO.
Give them the order to send
the fucking Brads.
Roger that.
Hey, Tommy, lock it down.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
What happened?
I don't know.
Was it an IED, what?
I don't fucking know, bro.
I just wanna get the fuck out of here.
Yeah.
Manchu X-Ray, this is Manchu-6.
I authorize Bushmaster. How copy.
Over.
A-ffirm, Manchu-6. Break.
Frogman-5 Romeo, be ready to
receive Bushmaster on 7-5-5.
How copy. Over.
Wilco. Bushmaster 7-5-5.
Bushmaster is approved
to maneuver to our position.
Mikey, Brian, give me an update
on the roof.
Taking effective enemy fire!
Multiple bad guys on the rooftops!
Bushmaster is approved.
I'll give you a shout.
You okay?
Let me know. You good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Is there a rug in there?
You're good, man.
I'm right here.
You're good.
On it.
Are we all up on gear?
any gear out there?
There's gear in the street.
John, with me.
Fuck!
Collapse, collapse.
Collapse, collapse, collapse!
Collapse!
Fuck!
Zawi!
Bradleys are four minutes out!
You got four mikes.
They're pushing in on us!
We gotta get off this fucking rooftop!
Zawi!
Get back! Get back!
Zawi.
Zawi!
Motherfucker!
What's going on? Cas-evac inbound.
I need a 5W.
Had to suck back.
Unable to hold position.
We got multiple bad guys
trying to get to our position.
Sir. Sir, I'm calling in a show of force.
Profane 5-6-5-7, Wild Eagle 2-6,
requesting an immediate...
When the Bradleys get here,
Mac, Aaron, Tommy...
...show of force over
OP-1's position.
...you grab Elliott.
You guys are gonna go out first.
You're going to go into
Brad one. Right hand side.
Right hand side. Check.
Yes, sir.
Ray, Brock, grab Sam.
Brad two. Left side.
Got it.
Three minutes out! Three minutes!
Wild Eagle Base,
tracking Bushmaster now.
They are en route
to you now, OP-1.
Hey, hey.
Yeah.
I got his legs. You got his arms?
Yeah, let's get him ready.
All right.
Let's get this shit sorted.
Gonna get you out of here.
Get that rug.
All right, we're gonna get you
the fuck out of here.
I got him, I got him.
Come on,
give me your hand, brother.
All right.
Watch his arm, watch his arm!
We're gonna get
the fuck out of here, okay?
All right.
Right here. Right here.
Okay, okay.
Right, now let's fold him, okay?
Tommy, on you.
We're gonna fold him your way.
On my count.
Guys,
if you're gonna move me,
you gotta move me real fast.
Yeah, we will. All right.
All right.
Whoa!
On my count.
All right.
All right, on three. One, two, three!
Come on, come on!
One, two, three!
We good?
Set him down.
All right, you're good, you're good,
right?
Other side, other side, we got this.
All right, Aaron.
One, two, three.
All right, all right. Okay.
Two minutes out! Two minutes!
All right, and at three, two, one.
All right, you're doing great.
You hear that?
Don't forget my fucking arm!
Don't worry, bro, your arm's
still attached.
It's right here. I got it.
Two minutes out! Two minutes!
Wild Eagle Base, Profane.
Bushmaster appears to be
approximately 100 meters out
at this time.
Hey, you gotta get ready, man.
This is gonna hurt.
No, no, no, there's gotta be
another way, man.
There's gotta be another way.
There's no other way, man.
No, don't fucking touch me.
We gotta do it.
Don't fucking touch...
BTF-up, bro!
What side are we getting Elliott out?
Elliott...
Inbound!
Elliott right side, Sam on the left side.
Elliott right. Roger that.
One minute out! One minute!
Tommy, I got Elliott.
Tommy, Frank, you two
are breaking us out.
Check.
Yes, sir.
Gunners, you'll set up security
out on the street.
Frank, you straight?
I'm good.
I'm gonna buttonhook right.
Copy that.
I'm taking the right Bradley.
Frogman, this is Bushmaster.
We are approaching OP-1 at this time.
Frank, Tommy.
We good?
Good to go.
When we break out of here,
eyes on me
and only me, all right?
Ray, Brock,
you good?
We're good!
Bradleys are here!
All right.
Let's get him on three.
Three, two, one.
Two, one.
Ramp down, ramp down,
ramp down, ramp down.
Breakout, breakout, breakout!
Go!
Watch his legs.
Let's go!
I'm stuck.
Right, Brock, let's move.
One, two, three, up!
Move!
Right side! Right side!
Move! Move!
All right. One! Two! Three!
I'm out!
Come on, brother, we got you!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go.
Move, move! Come on.
Changing!
Go, go, go, go, go!
AJ, 1 o'clock!
Fucking good!
Three o'clock! Ramp up!
Collapse! Collapse!
Ramp up! Ramp up! Collapse!
Mac! Mac!
We have to collapse.
Let's go.
Wait, wait!
To the house.
You all right?
Yeah. Yeah.
I just...
Thought you were hit.
I just tripped.
Let's go, let's go!
Last man! Last man!
Hey, come on, man, giddy-up.
I didn't make it out.
I'm stuck in the Bradley.
Over.
Redman 0-8, this is Profane.
We're seeing activity converging
on the rooftops on all sides of OP-1.
We need you to de-conflict
any friendlies.
Profane says the guys
are moving to our roof.
They're telling us to get our
guys off the roof right now.
Do we still have guys up there?
We're the last guys up there.
They're right on us.
Zawi, you hold security
and lock it down.
Check.
Listen up! I'm gonna have
the Bradleys
take out the second floor
of this building!
Gunners, you're holding security
out on the street
for extract.
Yes, sir!
Mac, I want a show of force
for when that happens.
Yes, sir. Sergeant.
Yeah.
Bushmaster 1-1.
Need you to fire into
top deck of our building.
We have enemy on our building
and all surrounding buildings.
Say again. Fire into your building?
We got a full head count.
Fire into our building.
Top deck.
Zawi, get the fuck down here!
Negative, Frogman.
We can't do that.
The top deck is fucking clear.
Fire into it.
Roger that. Stand by.
Going hot.
Suck in!
Find cover!
Let's go!
Get down! Get down! Get down!
We're breaking out hot!
Gunners up! Let's move!
Gunners up!
Frogman, Bushmaster.
Shifting fire, going hot.
Why?
Why? Why?
I'm sorry.
Why?
Inbound! Inbound!
Stand by!
Breakout, breakout!
One! Two!
Three!
Last man!
Moving!
Let's go!
We're out!
Get the fucking ramp up!
You made it. I didn't think
you were gonna make it.
I had a bet.
I lost the fucking bet.
♪ What could I say? ♪
♪ Taken aback ♪
♪ All that you gave ♪
♪ Chasing the line ♪
♪ Tear in the coat ♪
♪ Pierced in the side ♪
♪ Keep in the know ♪
♪ Throw in the earth ♪
♪ Dancing and blood ♪
♪ What could I say? ♪
♪ Taken aback ♪
♪ All that you gave ♪
♪ Wasn't enough ♪