Oh, okay. Hold on, hold on man--
Hey, what's going on? Chill man.
I was here 8 months ago. Can you
please just check your papers?
Okay.
Okay, you're gonna do it or?
Yeah.
Like now?
Just a second.
What do you mean a second,
I've been here like 5 minutes.
Okay.
This isn't my watch.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
No, mine is a Seiko.
And this, is a Casio.
That's the fucking watch
you left here eight months ago.
I know the watch I left,
and it wasn't that one.
Now get the fuck out of
here before I call someone.
Bloodsucker.
-Beat it, loser.
-Fuck off!
Hi, can I help you?
What do you got?
Can you put it in
the drawer, please?
Thank you.
Mid-century French.
Looks like imitation.
Not worth a lot.
Well, at least it's ticking.
Hello?
Argh!
Hey.
You can be all over that,
I know you're not.
Come on, man.
I thought she was jacking you,
to be totally honest.
-Are you kidding me?
-Nah, I'm kidding.
Hands up!
Everybody out! Move! Move!
Get the hell out on the ground!
Move! Get out! Get the fuck
down! On the ground!
There's nothing left!
You have to believe me.
We moved it all to
the headquarters this afternoon.
You don't have to do that.
Last chance.
I'm telling the truth.
There's nothing left!
Left.
I'm telling the truth.
Right.
And...
-center.
-I'll tell- I'll tell--
I'll tell you where it is.
Hurry up.
Oh!
It won't be long before the
Albanians get here. Let's go!
You guys don't even know who
you're stealing from, do you?
You're so gonna regret--
-Hey, hey, hey, what are
you doing? -No witnesses is
necessary.
They haven't seen shit, bro.
Okay.
-Let's move out.
-Yeah.
Mmm. Can you smell it?
Can you smell it?
Woo!
-Start a new life!
-Shit.
With this amount of money,
you could start a whole bunch of
fucking lives.
Problems?
Smooth as silk,
just like you planned.
All right, everybody.
No fuck-ups.
Lay low. Keep to your routines.
Don't meet one another.
Make sure no
one's sniffing our trail.
On the 10th,
we get across to Rez.
And as usual,
-split the money.
-Yes!
Woo!
Mr. Rhodes, just to say
thank you very much for
giving me a second chance to be
a part of this.
Take care of the car.
Boom.
New pilot?
What happened to Finn?
Finn is no
longer with us anymore.
Hmm.
Got the last one.
Come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on.
Easy does it.
Come on, motherfucker, come on.
Shit!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Ugh!
Ah!
Ugh.
Jesus Christ!
How's his temp?
-101.
-Clinic get his meds?
-Not yet
-Keep him cool.
Plenty of water
Honey, 20 years ago, I
brought your fever down.
So don't tell me what to do.
Thank you, Carol.
You're a lifesaver.
He's family to
me. Both of you are.
You know, your grandmother
would have been proud.
Fuck no. She would've killed
me for putting on this uniform.
Half the Rez still wants to.
Forget those bellyaches.
Always complaining.
You're doing good things, Ani.
I know it.
And I just wanted to go at it.
But Jim dives in, chasing after
-Mornin'!
-his favorite hook.
Ugh, fellas, this is Annie.
-Hi.
-She's taking over Tom.
And uh, get this, she's
real Native American.
-Oh, wow. Blackfeet?
-Blackfoot.
Blackfoot. Right.
Hey , well, nice to meet
you. We're just headed out.
-Yeah.
-Lakes closed, guys.
-On whose authority?
-On my authority.
Right. Come on,
cut us some slack here.
We just drove for 75 miles.
And the ice is still blue.
It was clear yesterday.
It'll be gray tomorrow.
Less than four inches thick.
Early thaw.
Climate change, y'know?
Climate's always been changing.
It's called weather.
You can't go out.
And who's gonna to stop us?
You?
She's cute.
-Oh yeah!
-Yeah, boy.
Oh, no. Ani, Ani, Ani. Hey, Ani.
Hey, you can't treat
any tourists this way.
I mean,
they bring in good money.
Are you serious?
They're good folks,
all right? Let's just
be a little bit
more accommodating.
You want me to talk to them?
-No.
-Hey, what the fuck, lady?
Wait, wait, wait! Ho-hold up.
Guys, she's got a job to do,
all right?
But look,
I'm sure if we play nice,
she'll take it off.
Am I right, warden?
The choice is yours.
You're fucking kidding me.
Okay. No fishing.
We get it.
Uh,
Jed Matuzak just called in.
He said his truck's stuck out
there in the middle of a lake,
-about three miles east of
the old mill. -Yeah,
I'll head out there now.
Oh, uh, and by the way,
a bunch of us are headed
out to Slippery Rock tonight
if you want to join.
Little man's sick.
Rain check, then.
We're all sinners.
I was a sinner.
But, uh
the Lord, he forgives a sinner.
Luke tells us that, uh,
sinning is human.
But if you do sin,
then you gotta repent.
Like he said in that
story about the son who
took his inheritance and
then whored and gambled
and did all the wrong things...
He returned home,
prodigal, he called him.
But the father, he
welcomed the sinner son back
and the kid, well, he repented.
And so they threw
a big party for him.
Really, what I'm--
what I'm saying is that...
repentance can
lead to redemption.
For our Lord has space in
his heart for sinners, for sure.
Let us pray.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you.
You have a moment
for a sinner, Father?
No sins I can help you with.
Oh, it's
something you definitely can.
The tracker was tripped, Pen.
Yesterday out on the lake.
That plane disappeared
almost six months ago.
Never made it to the
other side of the Rez.
Twenty million dollars
is under that ice.
So, I'm thinking
the tracking device leads us
to the sunken Cessna.
We have diving equipment.
Go for the suitcases,
and that's it.
Nothing against the law.
Nothing against Jesus.
-Nah...
-You're a native.
So we could use you as a guide.
Help us with
your people on the ice.
My people...
You owe us.
Sirena and Ellis.
Mm-hmm.
Dax is on
the other side of the lake.
We're a team again.
Just like the good old days.
Come on.
That's blood money.
Yeah, well, there's a little
blood on every dollar bill.
Don't you think?
So...
You found God.
He found me.
Is that why you changed
your name to Milcham?
Milcham's a kind of phoenix.
So you rose from the ashes.
Me too.
Check this out.
I've been sober three months.
And all that other shit.
That's great, man.
Day at a time, right?
Proud of you, Ellis.
Yeah, you know, I...
got some projects of my own now.
Need some startup funding.
About ten hours before
this starts melting.
The tracker's moving on the ice.
Could be
the current shifting it.
Or maybe
somebody else is out there.
The fuck
you mean "somebody else"?
Who'd you tell
about the money, Pen?
I didn't tell
anybody about the money.
Come on, man.
Yeah, all right.
Let's move.
Morning.
I hit one of those...
warm
currents.
No worries, Jed.
The ice gave way.
-I can get you out of there.
-Thanks.
How's Martha?
Miserable.
But she is
married to me, after all.
That is true.
Who's that?
It's Harlan.
I passed him a ways back.
You know him?
I've seen him from time to time.
-Hmm.
-He lives off the land.
Looking for his wife.
Yeah.
He's a poacher, then, huh?
-I see you got help already?
-Mm-hmm.
You been fishing?
Yeah.
What'd you catch?
A couple of walleye, a perch.
Got a license for this?
-Gonna take a look.
-It's just fishing gear, and...
Uhh, no, don't--
The fuck is this?
I-I found it.
You found it?
-Where?
-It's-- It was...
-Under the ice.
-Under the ice?
-Okay.
-I was gonna...
I'm gonna need you to
take off your backpack, slowly.
Hands up where I can see them.
Place them on the cab of the
truck. No sudden movements.
Did I do something illegal?
Hands on the truck.
You have any
weapons? Anything sharp?
Knife.
Bow's in the sled.
Hands behind your back. Come on.
Ma'am, I don't understand.
Mm-hmm.
Stay there.
Jesus, boy.
You clean out the casino?
Sheriff Raleigh, this is Ani.
Check.
I just arrested a poacher.
Name of Harlan--
What's your last name?
Fanshaw.
Harlan Fanshaw.
I'm about 40 minutes out.
Just send me your location.
-It's no problem, Ani.
- A whole suitcase full of cash.
Millions.
You said how much money?
Yeah, a real
fucking win on the lottery.
You expecting some more help?
Hey folks, uh,
lake's closed.
Early thaw.
You should turn
around for your safety.
I think you've
got something of ours.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
No?
Okay.
Get on your fucking knees.
Now.
Hey, D.
-Thought you said no violence,
man.- There is no violence.
Search the truck.
-Let's just get the money--
-Search the fucking truck.
Okay.
Who's the prisoner?
Just a poacher.
How we lookin'?
There's one case.
Where's the rest of it?
There's... there's more?
Ah...
You mind telling me?
-I don't know.
-You don't know?
-No? Okay.
-I don't know.
Left. Ugh!
Go!
Ahh!
Ah!
Argh!
Ugh!
Well fuck me, Drake.
I thought you were dead.
Ev--
Everybody in the SUV.
Looks like
the tire got hit by a bullet
You two fix the tire.
Serena, call Dax.
Tell him to get to them
from the north. Yeah?
Fuck!
They said "Where's
the rest of the money?".
Where's the rest of the money,
and who the fuck are they?
There's a plane.
-Plane where?
-Where I found the case.
Under the ice.
There's more money in the plane?
And you're a part of it?
What are they doing?
Drugs? Weapons? What?
I just live on the land.
Yeah, Jed told me some bullshit
about your wife.
I found the case.
I saw the plane. That's it.
I was supposed to
check fishing licenses,
not shoot and get shot at.
I'm not made for this shit.
Hey Sirena.
From the north?
I'm on my way, babe.
Raleigh.
Come in, Raleigh.
Yes Ani, talk to me.
We got multiple shooters
on the ice.
Jed's dead.
What? You're shitting me.
Jed's dead, Raleigh.
Me and the poacher got away,
but they're
coming. Send help now.
Shit, Ani.
Who the hell are they?
The poacher, is he
anything to do with this?
I- I- I don't know. Maybe.
Okay, listen. Uh...
Head for station 11.
I-I'm calling for
backup. I'm on my way.
- I'm coming.
-Copy that.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No. No!
What the fuck!
Fuck, no!
Fuck!
-You got a plan?
-Get to station 11.
-How far is that?
-Two miles.
On foot, that's too far.
We're not gonna make it.
They got wheels.
Any suggestions?
We gotta split up. They
can't follow both of us.
It's not happening.
If either of us go under,
we'll both drown with these on.
Come on.
Got a bullet for you
if you try anything.
Hurry.
Okay, let's go.
Keep 50 feet apart.
Oh, man.
That was bad luck.
Do you believe that bullshit?
A long time ago, five or six
warriors were chased out here by
thirty soldiers from the
1st American Regiment.
Soldiers had guns. The
natives knew the lake .
Warriors pushed them
right out into the center.
When night came, the ice had
melted. The soldiers started
to panic.
In the middle of the night,
God brought
his wrath down upon them and,
they all burned to death.
Their charred bodies found days
later, half frozen in the ice.
You've become
a fucking bedwetter, Pen.
You need to turn
that God shit off.
You see,
I believed in him once,
but there's money out there.
And now that we finally get
a hit on the signal,
you want to quit?
It's not worth it, bro.
The fuck it isn't.
Ready!
You want to leave, be my guest.
Start walking.
But Rhodes is the devil.
And we made
a deal with the devil.
You know the consequences.
People have lived on this land
for over a thousand years.
We know our forest.
We know the ice.
Those murderers have no idea
what they're walking into.
You know how to
walk the gray ice?
The weak stuff?
Some.
We're clear!
Got him. Ellis, start
the truck. Let's move!
Ellis, give us some
fucking gas, let's go!
No, no, no. The ice
will give. Ellis, don't.
-I'm getting out.
-No, you'll sink it.
Ellis, stay still.
Make a line. Hold each other's
hands.
Furthest out on the strong ice.
It's going to sink
and take us with it.
Just do as
he fucking says, okay?
Ellis, now move
slowly to the other seat.
Slowly.
Ugh, ah!
I got a bad feeling about
this, Pen.
Don't worry, stay calm.
We're getting you out.
The Irish say a bullet's made
for each of us the day
we're born.
The Irish are born liars.
I'm tossing
you the belt. You hang on.
We're going to
get you out, stay calm!
-No!
-Don't let go!
Pull! Pull!
Holy shit!
My foot's caught!
Don't let go. You hear
me? Don't you let go.
Ah!
Ahh!
Hang on.
Hang on, you hear me?
Fucking pull.
Grab it, grab
it, grab it, grab it!
Pull!
Hey.
It's this way.
Yes, I'm sure.
Where'd you learn
to speak Blackfoot?
My wife.
So she is real.
We're not going
to reach help in time.
Sheriff's coming.
We're not going to make
it to him either. Listen.
Listen, of
here. I got some gear.
We should head there.
Ice is melting faster that way.
I know, but
if we make it there, at
least we have a chance.
By doing what?
What I do.
Hook.
Come on.
What happened?
They're up ahead.
Hey, they're moving quick.
We're losing a millimeter
of ice every 30 minutes.
Yo, Dax, let's get
the snowmobile down.
-You can get to them faster.
-Put some fucking clothes on.
We'll take the truck around
the weak ice and meet you at
the shore.
The hide's over there. How
many rounds you got left?
I'm out.
What?
Never tell a suspect
you're out of bullets.
Police academy.
Whoa, wait. Shit.
The ice is too thin.
The cars will pull us under.
We're going to have to
go around.
Nah, let's run for it.
Okay.
Okay, you ready?
Is this your family?
Yeah.
I have a son about that age.
He's at home now. He's sick.
Here, hold this.
Where did you get these?
Do you hear that?
Fuck.
I only got that one
shitty arrow,
so I got to get him off
that snowmobile if I'm going to
get a shot.
Get ready to run!
Run!
Ahhh!
Ugh!
Ahh!
Gahh!
Ah! Ahh!
Ah!
Now tell me where
the fucking plane is!
Ahhhh! Ahhh!
Ahhhh!
Ah! Ah! Ahhh!
Okay? Are
you okay? Are you okay?
They're gonna come for us.
Ahh!
Okay.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
We gotta get you someplace warm.
I know a place.
Let's go.
Look at the snowmobile.
Where the fuck is he?
Dax!
Sirena?
Honey!
Honey?
Honey, hey, honey!
Ugh!
What? What?
It's not fucking fair!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey! Okay, okay.
It's gonna be okay.
They're gonna pay for this.
Yo, I think
they went this way. Up here.
I can't feel my fingers.
There's a hide up
here in the forest.
Not many know about it.
Harlan!
The woman!
Not the poacher. We need
him for coordinates.
Fuck!
Come on.
Ellis! Pen! Let's go!
We're leaving a trail.
Come on, we have to lose them.
There, there. Let's go, come
on.
She knows what she's doing.
They're in the water!
That way.
This way! Come on!
Move, let's go!
Wait, wait, stop!
What?
It's a medicine wheel.
Sacred.
Yeah.
This is a hunting ground.
-It's bear country.
-Oh, fuck off.
So what you're saying
is we shouldn't be here.
Hey, I don't give a fuck
about your woo-woo shit.
-Let's go!
-Guys, hold on!
I'm gonna get them and I'm--
Ahh!
Fuck! Ahh!
Sirena! Ah, fuck!
-Fuck! Goddamn it.
-Get me the fuck out!
Ahhh! Ohhh!
-Here, get behind me.
-Fucking help me, guys!
All right, give me your hand.
-Give me your hand! -I need
fucking help or something.
You have to pull your foot out.
-You're gonna have to pull
your foot out. -Fuck you, Pen!
-Hey! Hey! Hey! I'll pull you
out -Fuck, ah, ah! Oh my God.
Ellis, grab her arm.
-Here.
-Okay, okay. Okay.
-You ready?
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
-One, two, three.
-Let's go!
-Ahh!
Okay guys, let's go!
Okay.
Ah!
Fuck, okay.
You good?
I got it. I got it. Ah!
Come on.
It's up here.
Missing fuel.
Watch your head.
Get your clothes
off. All of them.
-No fire.
-They won't find us here.
We're too deep in the caves.
Ah.
Mhm.
Ah, goddamn it.
-Come on.
-Okay, come on.
Mhm.
Fuck!
I got it. I got it.
Whew.
-All right.
-Careful.
-Just figure this out.
-Ah!
Turn the light on.
Do it!
-Alright.
-Fucking do it!
You good? Yeah?
Ah!
Oh God.
Oh, my God. Ah!
Ugh!
-Mhm...
-Almost, almost. Ugh.
Ah. Fuck.
I'm gonna fucking kill them!
We lost them.
They're long gone by now.
Yeah, well, fuck this.
Come on.
Ugh.
Thank you.
Is it true?
-Uh?
-What Jed told me about you?
Looking for your wife?
I'm not looking for her.
She's dead.
Fuck, Drake.
It's on me.
No. Stop with that bullshit.
We're a team.
And we're stronger as a team.
We'll get them.
It was too much money
to keep everyone together
as a team, I mean...
Everyone had
their different plans.
Me and Dax,
We were gonna...
Hey, come on, Sirena.
I don't see
you wiping no babies' asses.
No.
Sure.
She O-- ODed.
It's not like she's a
junkie, you know. She--
We-We lost o-our daughter, Kai.
I wa-was in Afghanistan.
She got some kind of
infection.
Lung.
Her little heart just...
Little heart just stopped.
I-I came home...
It was like Mia
was already gone.
She wouldn't let me touch her.
She stopped talking till
the house was just
just silent.
It was dead.
I mean I-I don't know what
the fuck to do with the pain.
So i-it's like I blow
my brains out or I
drink. So I-I--
You know, I just stayed drunk.
I don't know how long she's
been dead when I found her.
She was already cold.
This place is...
It's the only place where
I feel close to her.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
But for almost fucking drowning
in that car today,
I deserve this.
You think there's a
chance at a second life?
You gotta grab what you
can in your first one.
That's my opinion.
I used to think that.
Until I found God.
Chances are too
high he doesn't exist.
Now, Rhodes, though...
He exists for sure.
Mr. Rhodes.
Thank the heavens you're here.
Look, Mr. Rhodes.
I know how this looks, but
we got everything under control.
She begs to differ.
It's just a game
warden and a poacher.
This was not meant to happen.
They killed him.
They killed Dax.
They will pay for this.
It's quillwork.
It's beautiful.
She said
it contained her love.
She wanted me to wear it
if I went on a mission.
Said
it would bring me home safe.
Some pretty powerful medicine.
Bear.
It's my spirit guide.
Do you know what hers was?
It's a bear, too.
And you've
never felt her spirit?
I mean I--
I-I think about
her all the time.
My people,
we have a cleansing ritual.
Helps us mourn our loved ones.
And then afterwards,
we move on.
We keep living.
You can't bring Mia back.
But you can let go of the guilt.
She wants you to live, Harlan.
And you know that.
You know what I've discovered
over the years of working
together?
Is that home isn't a place.
It's the people.
It's what we have right here.
Family.
And when you have family,
you have no fear.
You can handle
just about anything.
Take our youngest, Ellis.
I found you on the streets.
Took you in.
Taught you everything.
Yes, you're...
you're still
a little young and wild.
Misbehaving at times.
But hey, that's
the privilege of youth.
But then again, loyalty is
expected even from
the cutest puppy.
You can imagine my surprise when
I met that fag friend of yours
in that shithole
village by the lake.
What was his name, huh?
Yes, Ethan.
-Mr. Rhodes. I--
-Shh.
After three fingers,
he admitted that he was
here to steal the money.
From us.
After two more fingers,
he told me that it was you.
That you had planned this.
Mr. Rhodes.
This isn't what
it looks like. I'm sorry--
Family.
Should we forgive
a misstep?
Pen.
What does your God say?
Should one be
allowed to fail, to be weak?
Isn't it truly divine
to condone?
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Hey!
It's all right.
It's okay.
I-I'm sorry.
The answer is no.
Mercy is weakness.
And you're
a piece of shit, Ellis.
You don't deserve to be part
of this group of
wonderful people.
Tomorrow we kill the warden.
And then the poacher.
They'll come to us.
Don't you worry.
You really know
your way around here.
As a little girl, the elders
would teach us how to hunt out
in the woods.
And we'd go back to the caves
and eat and sleep.
You know, life was simple.
I can't believe I never heard
about this place.
Oz!
You come with me.
And you
stay here.
Him. He tried to kill her.
He killed her.
No, he didn't.
And then you take him
here to this secret spot?
-I didn't mean to--
-It's on me to just--
Is there a problem?
Oz...
They've been tracking us.
He says he knows you.
He doesn't like you.
You dragged his niece
out of the community.
-Took her to the city.
-That's not what happened.
-Got her addicted to drugs.
-No, I-I-I--
I-I told you, we--
We lost our child.
I watched Mia grow up.
She was like family.
She was happy.
But you,
you took her away.
I didn't take her.
We loved each other.
If it wasn't for you,
she'd still be alive.
-Fuck you for saying that.
-Stop it.
We do not have time for this.
Oz,
these people are chasing us.
They're trying to
kill us. They shot Jed.
You're kin. You have a duty.
Not to him.
He's my prisoner. He's with me.
You and I share
the blood of our people.
But when this is over...
Come on.
Our people believe
that spirits are in the
sky and in the wind.
And under the water.
Those are
the ones we fear the most.
Hidden in the dark,
away from the sun,
there's a dead
forest under this lake.
Ten thousands years
ago before the Napikwan came.
See that?
It's methane. Explosive
gas in those bubbles.
I, uh,
think I'll go this way.
So watch your step.
You stay close.
What is this place?
Ice shanties.
They call it the Empty Quarter.
I know you have licenses for
all this.
It's our land.
You know,
my grandparents
asked me one time,
how many generations
does it take to lose
your connection with the land?
After looking at you,
I know the answer.
Who are you to say
anything about my connection?
You're a weekend tour guide.
You sold out.
I'm protecting our home.
-I'm protecting what belongs to
all of us.
-Well you lost all of us.
Why don't you help yourself
to some food back there?
Take all you want. We have lots.
And get the hell out.
So, um,
where we going?
Cleaning your mess.
-There you are.
-Hey.
This place.
We could hide out here.
It's way off track.
You know what they call us.
Sellout. Curse.
They don't want us here.
Listen, this
crew that's chasing us,
they're after me because I know
where that plane is.
There's no reason for
you to put yourself at risk.
My land, my people,
made a promise to protect them.
You're on my land, right?
Besides, finally got reception.
Sheriff Raleigh's on his way.
He's 15 minutes out.
We're going home.
Oz?
I'm so sorry.
We got some
unfinished business, aye, Chief.
-Listen I-I wanna--
-How dare you
bring your fucking
poison back here to my land?
Listen, um--
I want you to know that
the crew that's chasing us,
they-they're looking for this
plane that's at the bottom of
the lake.
It's filled with cash.
Millions, probably. And they're
chasing us because I know where
it is but,
I don't want that money.
And I was thinking...
You know, maybe you,
your people, Mia's tribe...
maybe...
So, uh...
you think you can buy us off
and change your luck, hm?
I'm not trying to pay you off.
Trying to do something right.
Ah, shit.
Pen...
life isn't like
a choo-choo train...
where you can get off at any
station and then move on to
your own liking.
My God wants us to
repent and be reborn.
I had an interesting
conversation with Ellis about
that yesterday.
About the
choices in life.
I'd like to forego my share
of the money, Mr. Rhodes.
No.
Please. All I wanted--
Ellis, I loved.
You...
I don't even like.
Only God can forgive me or give
me the punishment I deserve.
Well...
whatever we have coming,
it's coming fast.
Oh,
Pen.
Choo-choo!
Jesus...
What happened here? I've
been looking all over for you.
Five guys jumped us, they--
He play any role in this?
-No, he helped. He helped.
-You sure?
-Yeah, he helped me.
-Alright.
Look, I called it in. Backup's
on the way. But we gotta go.
Okay. How much backup?
Enough.
So, where did it happen?
-They attacked out on
the middle-- -No, no, no.
I mean where is it?
Where's what?
Headquarters wants to
know where that plane is.
How'd you know
there was a plane?
You mentioned it when we
were talking on the radio.
Pretty sure I didn't.
Listen to me.
This is a very important moment.
Alright?
One that you're gonna look back
on years from now and realize
how wise you are in telling
me exactly what I need to know.
Not you, Raleigh...
Come on, we can make
out real good here, Ani.
This isn't like you.
Why are you doing this?
Come on. It's
their money, Ani, just--
We're giving
it back, for Crissakes.
How much are they giving you?
Five percent of
whatever's on that plane.
Five percent. I'd
gladly split it with you.
Yeah, if we give
them Harlan, right?
You're such an asshole.
Hey, hey, backup, backup!
Give me the gun.
-Stand down, Oz.
-I'm the sheriff, alright?
Get in the goddamn
car, let's go!
You too.
Come on.
Nobody try anything.
Give me the bag.
Give me the--
Get in the car.
There's nothing to worry
about here, all right?
Everything's under control.
It's gonna be okay.
Where are we going?
-Where's the plane?
-Fuck you, Raleigh.
You good, man?
Something take the edge off?
Yo, man.
It's methane, you idiot. You're
gonna blow the whole lake.
Methane?
Hey, listen, man.
After we get this money,
everything will be all right.
There.
That's the sheriff.
You got him to bring them here?
Sheriff.
You realize
handing me over to them,
you're giving up
millions of dollars.
Why would you do that? I can
just take you to the plane.
Okay. Where is it?
I'm gonna need your word
that you're gonna let us go.
Yeah.
Yeah, you have my word.
I got a GPS
tracker in the backpack.
It's got the coordinates in it.
It's in the top pocket.
If you're lying to me...
Ahhhh!
Damn it!
Ani, Ani?
You okay?
Yeah.
-You okay?
-Fine.
Look at me.
Okay.
Okay. Shh.
Why'd you do this?
Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey.
Back!
Wait.
You betrayed me, Ani.
Sheriff.
Hey.
You don't want--
No- Nobody...
Nobody's betrayed anyone.
-This can't be serious.
-Don't do anything stupid.
Why?
Fuck! Fuck, come on. Come on.
You shot the sheriff.
Poacher's mine.
Don't kill him!
Okay. Hey, stay down.
Get the fuck over here.
Rhodes!
What do you want me to do?
You,
poacher,
lead us to the plane.
-Oh yeah?
-Now.
And Pen,
kindly dispose of the lady.
-But I thought that--
-Do it.
No.
Do your own dirty work.
The fuck, Pen?
You've killed over a hundred
people, and now your God won't
allow this one?
Fuck you, Rhodes.
Ah!
-Wait, wait, wait, wait!
-Rhodes!
There's a second chance.
There always is.
Ah!
Rhodes!
Your jacket! Your jacket!
Choo-choo.
Ah! Help!
Help! Ahh!
Ah! Ah!
Run!
Get on the ground, Rhodes!
Get on the ground!
Ahh! Ahh!
Argh!
Harlan!
Ahhh!
-Ani?
-Ahhh!
Ani?
Poacher!
All you had to do
was tell us
where that plane was.
New deal.
You lead me there.
And you both live.
You have my word.
Word of a killer.
Best I can do.
Now, where's my money?
Hmm?
Lady? Poacher?
J-J-Just let her go.
Mhm-hm.
-Left!
-Ah!
Wait, wait!
Ahh!
Get up.
Get the fuck up.
-Wait. Listen.
-Look at him.
Fuckin' look at him!
Remember, he's
the one killing you.
-Not me.
-Y-you-you'll get what you want.
I-I'll show you!
Right!
Ah!
Ugh!
The plane, poacher.
Where's the fucking plane?
Fuck you.
Wrong answer.
Ugh!
Ah!
Last chance, poacher.
Where is it?
Where's the fucking plane?
Ughh!
Ah!
He's been out there on
his own for four days.
He's fasting.
Okay, Harlan.
It's okay to grieve.
Aaah!
It's okay.
I heard the Staties
found the plane.
Found four million dollars.
They were expecting 20 million.
That's a lot of money.
Did Harlan give it to you?
You know there's an
old saying that uh,
the earth
does not belong to man,
but man
belongs to the earth.
Hum. Aye.
That's a Facebook meme.
Where'd the money come from for
the new community hospital, Oz?
Oh, ice fishing.
You wanna see my license?
-And this?
-You gotta put this in here.
This. And then it's
gonna be in the water.
And the other fish is gonna
get it, on this reel. Okay?
And the yellow one?
Mommy, mommy!
Look what he gave me!
Look at all the different
baits he gave me!
You okay?
Yeah.
-Let's see what you got.
-So this red one is for
the big fish.
Oh boy! And this is for
the little fish? That's great!
-The blue is for the small ones.
-Oh, yeah.
Can I go fishing
with Harlan sometimes?
Is Harlan teaching you
the right way to do it?
Please Mom, please!