My lord.
The enemy is at our door.
Are the Ottomans so cruel as
to interrupt our love?
And they will pay for it,
my beloved.
Come on!
Mmm-mm.
Is this war necessary?
Can't we all live in peace as
God intends for us?
You are my reason for being,
Elizabeta...
Please take care of
yourself my king...
...my life...
Because I cannot
survive without you.
That's enough, my lord.
War calls, victory's yours!
My men will take you to
Vilmür Castle, to our cousins.
You will be safe here.
Princeps invictus et
iustarum animarum...
...nos in proelio defendamus.
Amen.
This battle will be bloody,
your eminence.
The dead will number
in the thousands.
Are you sure God will this?
Our kingdom is the last bastion
against the Muslims.
- Do you have faith in our lord?
- I do.
I'm ready to die for him.
Then hunt these barbarians
to the last man.
I will fight in his name,
but I ask him for one favor.
I'm listening, my son.
I want him to spare my wife.
If she doesn't survive,
I won't be able to go on.
Everything would lose meaning.
Life would become unbearable.
Calm yourself,
you risk basphemy!
Lord gave you life.
You must honour and serve him.
But he gave me love as well.
He cannot blame me for
being unable to live without it.
If he takes her life...
...he can take mine too.
I will pray for your request.
No. Don't pray.
Tell him.
For the prince!
They're here in the forest...
What is your plan sir?
Let them come...
Go Princess! go!
Run! Save yourself!
Pierce the barrels!
Vlad?! Vlad, the Princess!
Speak!
There was an ambush...
...she managed to escape!
Where did she go?
The forest of wolves.
No!!
My Prince!!
No.
My wife...
...is dead.
We've been praying
for her since you left.
So God is deaf?
Or you did not pray hard enough!
My Prince.
God has his own reasons,
it is not for us to question them.
Perhaps he had
another destiny for her.
She has no other destiny!
She is dead!!
And he didn't even allow me
to say goodbye to her!
I beg you...
...tell God to send her back to me.
It's impossible.
Why?
Why?!
Because God does not perform
reincarnation.
But he can perform miracle,
can he not?
Can he not?
If you pray hard enough,
he will listen to you.
Please tell him.
Tell him!
She... she was a good
Christian and a pure soul.
I'm sure God will take care of her.
And what about me?
I've done everything he has asked.
My soul is stained with the
blood of our enemies...
...whom I have killed in his name.
I don't have the answers, my Prince.
I'm only his humble messenger.
Good...
I have a message that
I want you to deliver to him.
Tell your God...
...that until he brings me
back my wife...
...my life no longer belongs to him.
When did he arrived?
Around ten minutes ago.
Okay.
Where did you leave him?
In the Chapel.
- It seemed most appropriate.
- You did the right thing...
You did the right thing.
Let him finish praying...
Father?
Ah!
- Dr. Dumont, I presume?
- Yes.
You have a very beautiful chapel.
Yes, it's true.
Thank you for making this trip,
Father.
It must have been a long
and arduous journey.
Exhausting, I must admit.
That's why I'm partaking of some
light refreshment I found right here.
I hope you don't mind?
- Not at all.
- You're most kind.
I'm sure it tastes much better than
the beer in my native Bavaria.
I'm sorry to welcome you in such
an ungracious manner, but...
I'm afraid the hospital
administration and diocese...
...don't support your presence here.
I'm used to it.
The church and the scientific academies
don't get along very well.
That's why the Vatican for centuries
has been in the habit of...
...delegating its most
delicate cases to us.
This case is very delicate.
The Queen of England herself
is concerned.
The Queen?
Exciting...
No. No, no...
It's the ceremony of the centenary
of the French Revolution in...
...a few days.
There's a lot of
excitement everywhere...
Go down.
Close the door.
Why so many chains?
Afraid she'll fly away?
She was quite aggressive
when we picked her up.
A real beast.
Even animals are entitled to
a little humanity.
What do we know about her?
Please.
Maria de Montebello,
25 from Bologna, Italy...
...engaged to marry
Henry William Spencer...
...consul, here in Paris, and...
...great-nephew, by marriage...
...of the Queen herself.
That's why this case
is so delicate?
More than delicate...
Sensitive.
Anything else I should know?
From what I've been told...
...it all began during the wedding,
which took place...
...on the family estate,
as Maria objected to a church.
However the groom had invited...
...the bishop of Westminster to
bless the union...
...and at the sight of the
clergyman the bride...
...was seized with hysteria
...and a sexual appetite
beyond comprehension.
Appetites can be a sign of very good
health, can they not, doctor?
Well, certainly, Within limits.
- May I?
- Sure.
Born on the
18th of March, 1759.
It must be a clerical error.
Otherwise it would mean
that she is...
A hundred and 30 years old exactly.
A hundred and...
So you believe this woman
is a creature of devil?
That's a hasty conclusion, doctor.
Very often when a situation
escapes our understanding...
...we see in it the
work of the devil.
Well, the fact that she's old and
allergic to God's representatives...
...is merely a symptom,
not a disease.
It is very important in
cases like this to study...
...to observe without prejudice.
We must follow...
...the rules and laws of nature,
science, mathematics...
...not those of superstition
or the church...
...which I must admit
can be a trifle obscure.
You see, doctor,
we have to approach this...
...like a criminal investigation.
First, we establish the fact.
From there,
we deduce the motives...
...the circumstances, the location.
Could you hold this please?
And the murder weapon.
My order has been studying this
phenomenon for more than 400 years.
I personally, for more than 30.
And I can state for the record,
doctor, you are the first...
...one to have captured
a specimen alive.
Congratulations.
Thank you... I...
What exactly did I capture?
A vampire.
Don't listen to him, doctor.
Help me...
I'll let you do whatever you want.
Smile, please.
The oversize canines could
be a clue...
...but they could also be
a natural explanation.
So we must look elsewhere.
This creature, like any other...
...is definitely the
work of our Lord.
But for some mysterious reason...
...it seems God may have
other plans with it.
Contrary to popular belief,
vampires adapt...
...very well to light in general.
But it is direct rays
they cannot take.
This is crazy.
It doesn't make any sense.
Again, you may be right.
This could be just another
anomaly of nature.
So we have to continue until
we find irrefutable proof.
Well, I think we have
all the proof we need.
Doctor, don't you?
This is beyond science
and understanding.
- Uh!
- That's why I am here.
My dear child...
...may I call you Maria?
Of course.
You can call me as you like, father.
I'm all yours.
Maria, if you answer
my questions nicely...
...I will give you what you want.
You know my desires.
I know your needs.
- Mmm.
- Allow me.
Come a little closer my son.
Science requires sacrifice.
Are you ready to make one?
- I suppose so.
- Good boy.
What are you doing?
A few drops of blood.
A meager contribution to science.
I'll buy you a lentil soup,
you'll feel like a new man.
Uh-uh.
Thank you.
Uh.
Mm.
Maria.
Show me your neck, please.
You see, she's not
a first generation vampire.
So you mean there
could be more of them?
Without a doubt.
For 400 years now,
we've been looking for the source.
- The source?
- Yes.
My master.
Who is he?
What's his name?
Where can we find him?
Oh, don't bother,
he'll find you.
- He's here? In Paris?
- No.
Very soon.
Maria? Maria?
Maria!
Who is he?
He is a prince.
A prince?
He comes for the celebration?
No...
...he comes to find his princess.
His princess?
Who is she?
- What does she look like?
- Mmm.
Very beautiful.
More blood please.
Ah!
You had enough.
More would be greedy.
So, what is your conclusion?
Now we can find a princess
who will lead us to her Prince.
Good luck.
Are we there?
Take this road. It is at the end.
Can you help me with my luggage?
Can't leave my horses alone.
Too many wolves around.
Glad to hear it.
- Do you have a crucifix with you?
- Huh.
No.
Take mine.
Keep it always with you.
Thank you, but...
I do not believe in God.
Then pray God believes in you!
Huh.
Shhh! Shhh!
Indeed.
Hello?
Is anybody here?
Oh...
Excuse me...
I...
You surprised me.
It is I who apologize for my...
Somewhat my...
...dramatic entrance.
Give me this.
Oh, uh.
My apologies sir,
I didn't introduce myself.
Jonathan Harker, solicitor.
You're quite young for a lawyer.
Yes, I joined Phillips Law Office
in Paris earlier this year.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
And, you are?
Vlad the second...
Prince of Wallachia...
...Count...
...Dracula.
Oh?!
Your Excellency - I apologize for
my clumsiness, I was given no...
...physical description of you.
My portrait is not well known.
Except on these walls.
Oh!
Magnificent!
Is that a gramophone?
Yes, it is.
Uh!
I've never seen one before.
- I'm very curious to...
- Later maybe.
Let us dine.
Fine.
Oh, this is so good.
Your appetite is a pleasure to see,
young man.
Everything is so delicious and,
to be honest...
I was starving to death! Huh.
That certainly
won't be the case here.
The upkeep of such an abode must
require countless amount of staff!
Too many.
And yet,
I am puzzled not to have seen any?
They're very discreet.
- You aren't eating?
- Later.
Try this.
Oh?
Nice trick...
Huh.
Fantastic flavor!
It is one of the recipes
I bring back from India.
You travel a lot?
Not anymore. But...
...once upon a time, yes...
...I visited every continent,
and crossed all oceans.
Oh?!
You must have so many wonderful
stories to tell then?
I do.
Were your travels for
work or pleasure?
I handled certain affairs,
it is true...
...but I'm retired now.
I let my...
...associates travel around
the world in my place.
And it's my associate...
...Mr Jenkins, who arranged
for my visit here.
And, once again...
...let me thank you for according me
a moment of your time...
...I have plenty of time.
So...
...what brings you here, young man?
Well...
...among the many properties
that you own in Europe...
...there is one in particular...
...uh an old abbey,
in the heart of Paris.
The county, which we represent...
...wondered, given the
dilapidated state of the property...
...if you might be interested
in selling?
Uh.
I think it's this one.
No, not this one.
Sorry. I must admit, the road...
...was quite chaotic to get here
and my stuff is all upside down.
And what do they
want to do with it?
A hospital, I believe.
The great Paris Exhibition
is coming soon...
...and the city will
receive millions of visitors...
Euh... Not this one...
It's located near
Saint-Germain-Des-Près...
Not too far from
the river la Seine...
...I will... I will show you.
Are you a believer?
Sorry. What did you say?
Do you believe in god?
Not really.
The Coachman gave it to me.
Old superstitions
run deep I suppose.
Uh!
Ah!
Got it!
Enough talking for tonight!
Let me show you to your room.
The castle is well guarded, but I
prefer you do not leave your room.
Under any circumstances.
Forgive me but...
what exactly are you afraid of?
Old castles like this are filled
with memories that might haunt you.
Oh, I'm not superstitious.
That is a pity.
Watch him.
Elizabeta...
Good evening.
How may I help you, Father?
I'd like to speak to
Mr. Henry William Spencer, please.
Yes?
My apologies for disturbing
at such a late hour...
...but I was sent by a friend...
...Doctor Dumont of
the Hôtel-Dieu Hospital.
Oh God.
The hospital where Maria is?
Indeed.
Has something awful befallen her?
Yes! No! I mean...
...she's alive, clinically speaking.
Oh. Thank God. Please come...
...and sit down.
Tell me everything, Father.
I'm worried sick.
Is her health stable, at least?
She doesn't eat much,
drinks reasonably well...
...yet she's bursting with energy.
That bodes well.
Hmm.
That bodes...
...very well,
yet... yet do we know more about...
...this evil thing that's
eating away at her?
We're making progress.
But as you know, the science is
a long winding road that....
...we can only travel step
by tiny step.
You have a very nice place here.
Yeah,
it belongs to the English crown.
Yeah, the crown has always known
how to make good investment.
What can I do for you, Father?
I'd like to visit her room.
May I ask what you're looking for?
Nothing in particular.
It's just important that
no stone be left unturned.
You're a bit like an inspector
on a police investigation.
Precisely.
Except, I'm trying to solve
the case before the murder.
Hmm.
I'll leave you to it...
And if you ever need
any help in any occasion...
...I'm your servant.
Thank you.
That's very kind of you.
There you are...
Princess Elisabeta.
You should not have left your room.
Oh, my God.
Don't utter that name.
He is not welcome here.
Are you the devil?
God. Evil.
Two almost identical entities.
Two minds battling one another
without showing themselves.
And we... we are their playthings.
We are puppets that move
only and dare be haste.
No! No! No!
No! No! No! No!
Do you intend to kill me?
I do.
But not right away.
It is important to wait until
the blood engorges the head.
Who are you really?
I am just a poor soul
condemned by God.
And cursed to walk in the
shadow of death for all eternity.
No!
And sustain myself on fresh blood.
Human blood is recommended.
Ah!
Why would God do such a thing?
He is only love and mercy.
Oh,
I thought you were not a believer.
- I am now.
- No!
You are very funny
Thank you.
What is your last wish?
Euh...
Tell me your story.
My story?
Yes.
Please.
I want to know everything about you.
This is your last wish.
Is to listen to
a story from an old man.
I'm dying to.
You're dying to.
It is very funny.
Let's grant it then.
Lower him down.
Life is nothing but a
long hard road, my friend.
Death...
...is a privilege that God
grants you...
...and denies me.
And yet, I was one of
his most faithful servants.
What happened?
He took my wife.
My princess.
The love of my life.
Leave me alone.
Since then, I've lived
on waiting for her return.
How long exactly
Four hundred years.
That's pretty long.
But how can you
be sure she'll come back?
Sometimes pure souls
can be reincarnated.
And my beloved was
the purest of them all.
Forgive me, but I presume you
don't know when, where or how?
Precisely.
That doesn't seem like
a very good deal.
That I have known.
Sooner, young man, I would
have hired you as my lawyer.
You've been looking for
all this time?
The task has not been easy.
The Black Base spread all
over Europe for centuries.
Nearly 200 million souls
were decimated.
Half of them women.
This made my research
all the more difficult because...
...all the remaining women were
gathered in holy places where...
...I was not welcome.
I was so lonely...
...that I began to envy the
unfortunates that death claimed.
Living without love is the
worst disease of all, my friend.
It is like a fine...
...incessant rain...
...that gradually eats away
at your bones...
...turning you into
a formless sponge...
...unable to stand upright.
And then, after a while...
....no matter how strong
your love is...
...you lose your faith.
And yet they said that
hope is the spice of life.
In my case...
...I would prefer that...
...hope kills me.
To theibiline But, all
of this was of no use...
...because God denied me
the right to die.
Over time,
all desire disappears.
Even the desire to end one's life.
All you are left with is...
...an orderless, charmless...
...melancholy...
...and the hope
that I will find her one day.
But, I couldn't visit every
castle house in hamlet
So, if I couldn't go to her....
...I had to find a way for
her to come to me.
How?
Poison?
Now look at this
who is being dramatic.
It is a fragrance that I
developed for over a century.
I visited the great city
of Baghdad...
...known for its...
....magical gardens of a
thousand and more flowers.
Then I continued my journey
to Kanash...
...in India, where I learned to...
...capture the souls
of the most sensitive flowers.
But it was only back in Europe
that my research came to fruition.
First, to the colorful fields
of Grasse in France, where...
...some flowers have intoxicated
our imaginations for centuries.
And then, finally,
in the heart of Italy...
...in the magnificent
city of Florence...
...which was, at the time,
the capital of...
...all the perfumes.
Sir, I think this is it.
The color is quite pleasant.
Oh, never mind the color.
The city is divine,
and the effect guarantees it.
We shall see.
Perhaps it would be wiser
to try outside.
No, this seems to
be the ideal place.
Oh, mamma mia.
Uh.
This...
...perfume....
...was highly effective....
More powerful than
I could have ever imagined.
I have to admit, this period
was not the most unpleasant.
Indeed.
And then...
...after visiting
every court in Europe...
...I ended my journey with the famous
French court of Versailles.
The king at the time.
Louis, whose number...
...I forget.
This little Buttercup
had the bright idea...
...to bring together all his...
...nobles and his artists of his
kingdom to keep closer eye on them.
There was no doubt in my mind...
...that if Elisabeta had returned...
...she would be here.
I had never been
so close to finding her.
In my heart,
I was as excited as when I began...
- Elisabeta?
- Ah.
Uh-uh, no, I'm not "Elizabeta"!
I'm Isabelle de Touraine.
But I'll change
my name if you insist.
But my task seemed impossible...
...and on this day,
hope left me.
All that...
...effort, time...
...and money spent...
...only served a world...
...of debauchery and artifice,
which left no place for love.
It was now time for me...
...to entrust the task of finding
my Elisabeta to others.
Uh.
How many did you bite?
It doesn't matter.
Cause in the end, my associates
were as unlucky as I was.
So I returned to my Elizabeta.
Uh-uh.
Since then,
I've rarely left this castle...
...with the deluded hope that one day
my disciples will finally find...
...my beloved.
Mmm.
So you seem to know what you're
talking about when it comes to love.
I do.
Then you have to spare me, please.
I too have a beloved,
and you'll separate us forever!
In whose name?
Hm?
God?
No...
In the name of love.
Are you married?
I proposed to her,
just before I left.
And she...
...accepted?
Yes, she did.
We're to be wed
as soon as I return.
That is unfortunate.
If you kill me,
she'll die of grief, I know it!
What does she look like?
The locket,
there, around my neck.
Inside is her photograph.
My prince...
My love.
Elisa... Elisabeta!
No... Mina.
Mina?!
This woman is mine, young man...
...but I will spare your life
for finding her, for me.
Keep him prisoner!
I need to pack my things,
I need to...
Everyone come down!
Come down from there!
Fill this vial! Fill this!
My horses!
Prepare my horses!
I need to be clean!
I need to be beautiful!
I need blood! I need blood!
Lots of fresh blood!
Elisabeta...
I found you...
This is the portrait of the woman...
...our Prince is searching for
in your great city of Paris...
...He's been looking for his
beloved for more than 400 years.
We've been tracking him
for just as long...
But the resolution...
...of his endless wait is about
to happen now...
...right here in the heart of Paris.
She's left handed.
Yeah.
Good observation.
This book contains
all observation...
...my congregation has compiled
over the centuries.
- You speak German?
- No.
Well,
let me read you a little piece.
It is likely that
these creatures are...
...the way they are as
a result of a divine curse.
Göttlich verflucht in German.
If God can give life
then consequently...
...he can also give death.
But he can refuse...
...in cases of great offense
or blasphemy.
Ah!
Then the offender
will be condemned...
...to wander
the earth for all time...
...but even more interesting...
God can forgive
the offender, however...
...in the event of true repentance.
Death will be granted...
...and the curse will be lifted.
Ah.
This mean, if we succeed
in destroying this demon...
...all those who he's bitten will be
freed from the curse.
And euh...
Suppose we do manage
to find this demon...
...how do you intend to
get rid of it?
That's the easy part,
you drive a stake...
...through his heart with a hammer
and cut off his head.
Wonderful.
In another book
It's mentioned that...
...cloves of garlic
will cause it to flee...
...I doubt this method is effective.
Yet more within my grasp.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
First, we have to find this woman.
Because she's the only one
who can lead us to him.
Mmhmm.
Strange...
What?
The young woman in the portrait.
Yes? What about her?
She bears
a striking resemblance to...
...the young woman you asked me
to keep waiting in the next room.
Madam?
Are you Dr. Dumont?
Indeed, how can I help you?
I'm a friend of Maria de Montebello.
I learned that
she's under your care...
...and I came to inquire
as to her condition?
Of course.
To... whom do I have the honour?
Mina... Mina Murray.
I was at Maria's wedding when...
the tragedy occurred.
You knew her well?
Knew?...
...oh...
No, no, no...
please, my apologies...
...no, no, she's very well.
I mean her condition is stable.
Sorry...
Praise be to God!
Indeed my child.
Would you mind if we ask
you a few questions?
It could help her recovery.
Yes, of course.
Are you related?
No, not at all.
I am not from here.
Can you tell us about
your relationship?
Her behaviour?
Ah.
I met Maria...
...a few days ago...
...at a tea party...
...that her
future husband organized.
Henry...
When she saw me, she...
...she took me under her wing.
She never really let me go.
It was as if
she could sense that I...
...didn't really belong.
She took me into her room, and we...
...we talked, we laughed a lot.
It was so nice.
What did you talk about?
She could talk about anything.
She was...
She was particularly fond of...
...discussing love.
I...
To the point of
making me uncomfortable.
But she was so excited.
About what exactly?
About everything...
And then...
...suddenly she just...
...she tore herself apart.
Oh my god!
Why did you attend that wedding?
I...I accompanied my fiancé...
...who knows...
...everyone it seems.
He's from a very respected family
I suppose.
You suppose?
Yes, I don't...
I don't know.
Get some water, please.
My dear child...
...you have before you
a doctor and a Priest...
...both bound by
the strictest confidentiality.
You can express
yourself without fear.
To tell you the truth,
this wedding has upset me.
Like a bad premonition.
My engagement happened
so quickly I don't...
I don't know if I...
If you love him?
I do, of course.
He's wonderful...
...any young woman would be
delighted by such a match.
But you are not any young woman?
I can't help but feel like I...
As if I...
As if...?
As if I don't belong in this time...
I apologize.
You must think I'm
incredibly naive and...
...I'm boring you with
my problems, I...
Absolutely not, quite the contrary.
Could you write down
your address, please?
Of course.
I'm staying at a boarding house
until Jonathan returns.
- You're left handed?
- Yes.
I've often been advised
to become right handed.
Don't change a thing.
- It's very charming.
- Well...
Thank you for your visit.
Thank you for seeing me.
I'll go now to the hospital chapel
and pray for her.
Excellent idea, my child.
Good day.
What is it, my son?
I have no shelter and have...
...not eaten for centuries.
I am cold as well.
I will take him to the chapel.
Please come in.
Come in.
Thank you for the invitation.
Don't move, I'll get you
a hot bowl of soup.
You are too kind.
Who are you?
Count Dracula, at your service.
Thank you for the soup...
...but I require something richer.
Don't worry...
...you won't catch fire.
Your evil spells have
no effect in the house of god!
Oh really?
In the name of the father...
...the son...
...and the evil spirit.
Come, my sisters!
Look what God has made of you.
Hearts of stone in dormant bodies...
...suffocating under
their own thick issue.
Let me free you from this prison!
No!
Come on!!!
Hey!
Ah.
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Master!
Good evening?
The hospital is closed.
I found her Master!
I found her!
You've done very well.
Oh. Thank you, thank you.
You deserve a reward.
Oh, come, come, my little boy...
Come closer.
Here you are...
Sorry for disturbing you Father...
...but doctor Dumont needs
to see you immediately.
Yeah... I'm coming.
If this patient's disappearance...
...could remain
a secret between us...
...at least for a while?
You can count on me.
Here.
- Allez.
- Monsieur.
Hey!
He lost a lot of blood.
I was thinking of giving
a transfusion.
I'm sure he would have loved that.
Oh... Yes, of course, sorry.
He uses a pleasant perfume.
I never noticed.
How could she have escaped
with all the chains?
There was an outside accomplice.
A man...
He was seen wandering the hospital.
- Is there a description?
- Mm.
Thirties.
Elegant and richly dressed.
Blue eyes. Tall and upright.
Mina is in danger.
We must warn her.
Are you cold my child?
No...
I've always loved
the spectacle of fire.
Expecting visitors?
No.
I'll see what it's about.
Tada!
Maria?!!
- But... You're cured?
- Indeed I am!
Oh, It's a miracle! I'm so...
- ...I'm so relieved!!
- Don't worry.
Evil is gone as quickly as it came.
Let's not speak of it anymore.
- But you're feeling...
- In tip-top shape!
And ready to celebrate
my return in grand style.
- Dr. Dumont - he let you go?
- Well...
I have so much energy today...
...I don't think he could
have stopped me!
- And your fiancé?
- In Scotland!
Oh! Look what I have.
- Put your hat! We'll go together!
- Where?
Three front-row tickets for
today's celebration!
You're welcome.
- Three?
- Oh yes, my friend...
...the one I've been telling you
about is in town...
...and he is dying to meet you.
Quickly go change...
Go change!
Ah!
- Bonjour!
- Bienvenue, bonjour.
- Where are you taking me?
- At the Grand Hotel.
They serve wonderful hot chocolate,
you have to try it.
Ah!
Where have you been?
Ciao Maurice.
Well, I know my friend is
very beautiful...
...but I'm a bit offended!
Forgive me...
...your beauty brings light
to this place...
...filled with dark suits
and top hats.
Very true!
Madam, it is an honour...
...and a pleasure to see you again.
Have we met before?
In a dream, perhaps.
I have the strange feeling...
...that we have known each other...
...for a long time.
That's very romantic.
Terribly.
Excuse me.
I seem to have lost my mind
and my manners.
Vlad the second,
Prince of Wallachia...
Count Dracula
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Maria?
You promised me hot chocolate.
Yes, but first we're
going to have a little fun!
- Mm?
- Mm.
Mm.
Sorry!
I am sorry.
Oh!
Un... Deux... Trois...
Oh, let's go.
Allez-y mademoiselle. Un...
Bravo, bravo! Murray.
Ouh!
All right, lets go!
Oh, look at that!
I want to see the exhibition.
Chicken Lady!
Oh my god, it's so beautiful,
look at that.
Oh, wow.
The old lady with the beard!
Hello.
Beautiful!
Look at that.
Mina!
Come! Come!
- You see Mina? It's beautiful.
- Ladies and gentleman...
A little quiet please!
I'm going to feed the beast!
She is beautiful.
The Little animal.
- Oh, this is scary Mina!
- No, no, no, no.
Yeah, let's go!
Maria?
Maria!
This way.
That girl wants to shoot!
Bravo, Mina!
Allez, allez, monsieur!
Allez!
I took the liberty to
have libations prepared...
...while we wait for tonight show.
Excellent!
Maria, It's not really
proper to visit...
...the room of a man
we've only just met?
Don't worry,
I won't let go of your arm.
Tada!
What do you think?
It's wonderful.
I don't know about you,
but I'm starving.
I'm exhausted.
All right, all right.
Oh, you sit here, princess...
...and I'll bring you
a hot chocolate.
Ah!
Oh!
Thank you for accepting
my invitation.
Your apartment is fit for a king.
I'm just a prince.
- Sorry...
- Do you live in Paris?
No, further north.
In the country,
where life is quieter.
- You like the quiet?
- Not at all.
I love nature...
...birds, trees...
...and the wind that
makes them sing.
May I ask, where do you live?
My family home is an old castle...
...at the foot of
the Carpathian Mountains...
...in Romania.
There I know
only winter and loneliness.
I love winter.
With its harsh landscapes.
But my parents dream of Andalusia.
Perhaps the memory of another...
...older life.
I suppose so.
May I show you something?
Yes.
It's beautiful...
...what is it?
It is a music box.
Many people think
it was invented in the...
...18th century by the Swiss.
But I found this one...
...at a merchant's table
in Constantinople.
It dates from the 15th century.
Remarkable.
I gave it to my wife as a gift.
You're married?
Widowed.
- Forgive me.
- You're forgiven.
And it still works?
Of course.
Do you know this melody?
It seems so familiar...
But I trace my memory.
I don't know from where...or when...
Keep searching...
In your heart... In your skin...
In your soul...
Do you feel me... Elisabeta...
What kind of spell are
you putting on me?
None, Mina.
I'm only haunted
by the memory of my wife...
...my one and only love and
you look so much like her that...
...it troubles me.
Her name was Elisabeta...
...and when she wanted me...
...she used to play
this little tune...
...that echoed through the castle.
It was my signal to run to her.
This is all very touching...
I am Mina.
Mina Murray...
...and I am getting married in...
- ...a few weeks time.
- Yes, of course.
Forgive me for bothering you
with my stories.
These are old pains that...
...your presence has
brought back to life.
And I sincerely apologize for this.
Please...
Sir, I cannot accept this.
This is far too precious.
A gift can never be refused.
And maybe this melody
brings back some memories.
Mina! Come!
It's gonna start in ten seconds...
...now you have to come, let's go!
3...2...1!!
Oh, my God!
It's here.
Thank you for the wonderful evening.
It is been an eternity since
I have known such...
happiness.
Has the word become
unfamiliar to you?
My wife took it with her.
Good night then.
Good night.
Jonathan?! Jonathan!
What is happening to you?!
I thought
I will never see you again.
Please, please, It's better he rest.
He's worn out.
What's happened to him?
- Mina?
- Oh father.
Do you know where he went?
No. Not exactly.
To a castle where
he was held prisoner...
...and from which he was
miraculously able to escape...
...at the risk of his very life.
And do you know
who owns this castle?
No.
Maria's very good friend,
Count Dracula...
...the one who's infected her
and many others.
What?
No... no you m...
You must be mistaken. The count...
The Count is charming... and he...
You've met him.
Yes, the count...
He's an absolute gentleman...
...he even walked
me to my door, he's...
...I don't understand.
How did he find you?
I don't know.
It's all happened so quickly.
Maria came here...
...and she told me
you'd released her.
Maria escaped, knocking out
three guards in the process...
...and drained most of
the blood from my clerk.
What?
I... I don't believe it, she...
Take a seat...
...and calm yourself...
...because what
I am about to tell you...
...will be difficult to hear...
...and even more so to understand.
That man is a hematophagous.
It feeds exclusively on fresh blood.
Human blood mostly.
He's a vampire.
Yes. He is.
It bites its victims,
usually in the neck...
...and sucks their blood
until they're dead.
Some of them are, sort to say...
...spared, but they become
vampires themselves.
Oh my God!
Maria is one of them.
I need to make sure
that you're not as well.
Maria... of course not.
He never touched or
disrespected me...
...he behaved like
a perfect gentleman.
He uses a perfume
to seduce his victims...
...a kind of elixir
that annihilates...
...all will and removes
all inhibition.
So you may be under his spell
and not even know it.
How awful.
Yeah... Indeed.
But it's easy to verify.
May I see your neck please?
Ah!
All is well.
It's a miracle really.
Please.
Please. Please.
- This way.
- Ah!
Good evening sir! Father.
Easy.
Quiet, please.
- We have guests who are sleeping.
- Yes. Sorry, sorry...
What are you doing?
Don't take another
step or I'll scream!
Mina. Don't be afraid.
I mean you no harm.
- Yes?
- Miss, I seem to remember being...
...perfectly clear about
the rules of the house...
...which include no music after 8pm.
And it's past midnight.
Please forgive me,
I hadn't noticed the time.
Good.
Now, sir...
...if you are the gentleman
you claim to be...
...you leave this room immediately.
I understand. My regards.
No! Not that way!
Go out the way you came.
What are you doing?
You can't jump - it's much too high!
Mina, I've waited almost
four hundred years to see you again.
So if you want me to leave, I can.
Yes... Now, leave!
No, I forbid you from killing
yourself under my window!
So you'd like me to
die further away?
Yes! No! YES!
Just get off the
balcony immediately!
You lied to me!
Not even once.
You use charm to seduce me,
like you do to all your victims.
You are right...
...it is a perfume.
But I never used it with you.
I'm told you drink
the blood of your victims?!
It's true,
but you are not my victim...
- ...you're my beloved.
- Quiet!
My one and only true love.
Who are you to talk
to me like that?!
I'm damned, Mina.
I'm a dead man condemned
by God's will to live.
Why would God do such a thing?
Because he took you from me...
...so I cursed him and
abandoned him.
And, contrary to popular belief,
I don't like blood.
Even if yours has
a delicious taste to it.
Without it, I would only be
a repulsive old man...
...whom you'd hardly
deign to look at.
These are all just words.
Charming words meant to deceive me!
You're right, sometimes words
can deceive.
Take my hands.
Hands never lie.
I will tell you the
truth about me...
...but also about you.
About who you really are.
They will tell you...
...how much they enjoyed...
...caressing your face...
...and your neck and your hips too.
Remember the last thing
you said to me?
You said: take care of yourself
my prince...
...my king.
My life.
Because
I cannot survive without you.
Oh my love.
I missed you so much.
I missed you too.
I want to be with you forever now.
- Take me.
- I cannot.
Why?
Take me...
I want you to take me!
Now!
You have your all life ahead of you.
And I only offer death.
I want to be your flesh...
...and your blood.
Please.
Please, my husband.
Dumont?
- Yes?
- That smell?
It's the same as in the hospital!
Same perfume.
He's here.
Oh my God!
They're left.
But where?
There's only one place.
It appears Mina's gone missing.
- With him?
- I'm afraid so.
This man is the devil.
He must be stopped
as soon as possible!
Precisely.
But do you think
you'll be able to guide us...
- ...to his castle in Romania?
- Yes.
Father?
We can't just go like that...
...without any preparation,
without any help!
I think I know someone
who could help us.
Ta-da!
Henry William, amore mio!
So you missed me?
Of course, my darling!
I prayed for you every day, but...
- what happened? Is this a miracle?
- It is!
God heard your prayers.
And here I am,
completely healed and...
...ready to love you for
the rest of your life!
Henry...
...I was going mad without you.
When were you discharged
from the hospital?
I...
I asked them to let me know as...
I know, I know.
I left barely an hour ago and
came straight here.
- And... Are you completely cured?
- Of course!
Don't bore me with your questions.
Aren't you excited to see me?
Of course.
Oh Henry.
I missed your arms...
...and these beautiful hands...
and your lips!
Especially your neck.
Maria!
How dare you?!
Jes.. Jesus! What did you do?!
Do not worry, do not worry,
there is an explanation.
We can explain everything.
Oh no my blood!
Oh... what have you done?
Look what you've done!
Oh, it's all over the carpet!
What have you done?!
- My darling, don'...
- Oh, shut up, Henry!
My dear...
Help!
Maria.
Don'... Don't... Aaaah!
No, no!
Welcome home.
My friends.
Princess Elizabeta has returned.
Let me talk to them.
I won't be long.
Master!
They are already on your trail...
...and will surely find you soon.
I think it is time for you to leave.
Thank you for your concern.
But we are finally at home.
There is nowhere else to be.
Take this.
I don't think I will need
your services anymore.
Go in peace now.
Elizabeta.
My prince.
Do you think God will forgive us...
...for loving each other so much?
God is love.
He understands.
And if he doesn't...
...he can go to hell.
They will know what it is
to wake a dragon.
Stay here.
Over there.
That's where he
sleeps in his coffin.
A coffin? That's the last place
I want to sleep.
We all will one day.
Soldiers.
Open the door!
That's him.
He's inside.
Soldiers.
You won't kill him that way.
Leave it to us Father.
He won't get away this time.
I told you I would spare you.
Don't make me go back on my word.
Huh.
So... You are the priest...
...who has chased my people
for so many years.
Yes...
...but rest assured
I didn't come to fight you.
Nor I.
I fight God.
I'm not interested in
his servants.
No...
...you're not fighting God, my son,
you're fighting yourself.
No...
No, no, I fought
and I killed in his name.
We live and we breathe
in his name...
...why would he want us to
destroy his creation?
Man kills in his own name...
...and you're doing it again.
That is all just very fine words,
God sent you here to kill me.
God sent me here to save you.
So...
So God wants to save me now?
After he denies me
the right to die for centuries.
But this is not a punishment,
this is an opportunity.
Repent, Dracula,
for your salvation.
She is my salvation.
But you are her damnation.
I need a little bit more time.
Open the door!
Elizabeta!
Huh!
Elizabeta...
The curse will disappear if I do...
...you will regain your freedom.
But you are my freedom...
...you are my freedom my love.
Where you go, I go.
Dracula?
You believe you love her...
...but you expect her to
sacrifice her life for you!
Please don't go.
Please don't go and stay here.
Your soul still belongs to God.
If you truly love her
let her return to life...
- ...and you return to God.
- My darling.
Dracula!
No!
Oh!
Open the door!
Open the door please my love!
Four hundred years ago...
...I asked a priest that
God spare my wife.
He did not.
Please!
Can he hear my pray this time?
Whether he hears or not...
Only you can change destiny, my son.
Save her...
...and you'll be
in peace for eternity.
My love..
So let it be...
Please, don't leave me my love...
Hurry up before
I change my mind.
Please...
Amen.
Cease fire!
Oh!
Why are you doing
this to me my love?
Because I love you.
I love you too.
Mina?
The spell is broken.
Excellent...Excellent...
Everything is fine now.
Good. Thank you.
- Auf Wiedersehen
- Yes, yes...
Ah!