Oh, oh, wow.
No. No.
No.
You must re...
You must return it.
Another defeat.
What's the use of
Abraxeon seizing my crops
to feed their soldiers
if they're going to continue
to lose ground?
Pretty soon
there's not going to be
nothing left for them
to protect.
How are my children
supposed to survive the winter
with nothing but scraps to eat?
They've already eaten
all my good boots.
Hey!
That weren't meant
to be a jape!
At this point, we might as well
join the scavengers.
Oi! They're the only ones
profiting from all this.
Picking through the corpses
like vultures.
Oh, here comes one now.
Look at this handsome specimen.
He'd strip us bare
before our bodies were even
cold, he would.
Makes me sick.
Oi!
There's not a one among us
who's stared into hell
the way he has.
Leave him be.
Aye. Who is he, then?
I don't pretend to know
his whole past.
They say he was once
a knight in the Queen's army.
The old queen,
before Halgan's ascension.
Before the war against
the Dreadites.
Surgeon with a sword.
That's what's been sung.
And a survivor of the massacre
by Grimvault.
What?
I was told no one survived
that cursed night--
Aye, not a soul.
Yet there he is.
At least his body.
Who knows
what remains of his spirit
as he wanders this realm alone?
No allegiances, no banner.
Few even know his name.
Only the one he answers to.
What name would that be?
They call him--
Deathstalker!
You know why we've come.
Halgan's amulet.
Hand it over!
- Never met him.
- He's lying.
We should eat his legs.
That will make him nice
and honest.
We're hungry, aren't we?
I could eat.
For my food and drink.
And this is for the chair.
What...?
Oh, wow.
You can't run from us!
Show yourself, fool.
Sneaky little bug!
Let me have the first bite, brother.
Two against one.
Not very fair.
Why are we doing this dance?
Master wants the amulet.
And you, dead!
Oh, I hate trolls.
I'm outta here.
Oh, you're
gonna make us work
for our meal, aren't you,
little man?
I want his brains!
You can have them
You need them.
This is what you want?
- The amulet!
- Hand it over!
Go ahead and run,
you fool!
Every assassin will
be after you!
There's nowhere to hide!
That's right!
Come back and fight me!
I'll tear you to pieces!
I'll scatter your brain to
every corner--
Whoa.
Good riddance.
What?
God, it stinks.
I know it stinks.
Calm down.
That's nasty.
Whoa.
Hello?
Ah, Deathstalker.
What terrible curse
has befallen you this time?
This.
I can feel it is bound to you.
I noticed. Now unbound it.
This flavor of enchantment
means it can only
be passed on with the death
of the one who carries it.
Well, do these runes mention
any exceptions to that rule?
They are
beyond my understanding.
So I'm stuck with this guy?
I said they are
beyond my understanding,
not that they cannot
be understood.
Map.
A symbol.
And now the offering.
Nice.
There is a man
who might have
the answers you seek.
That is, if he still lives.
His name is Daedelad,
a member
of the Order of Troxartas.
One of the few mages
left in Abraxeon
who still carries a passion
for the ancient tongue.
Well, where
do I find this wizard?
Patience, child.
Aw, great.
Not the destination
you were hoping for?
Thanks for your help, Toralva.
Something for your stew.
Your offering
warns of danger.
I'm sure it does.
Your door's broken.
The specters of your past are
calling in the darkness.
I see a great evil
on the horizon
of your fate!
You cannot outrun it.
Just once I would like to come
to this cursed place
and not entertain
such rambling nonsense.
But it is you who are cursed,
Deathstalker!
Whoa.
Easy, Calibus.
Wait here, okay?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Calibus!
Damn it!
Holy crap.
What happened here?
I hope you cut
better than the last one.
Someone there?
Sit tight.
Is somebody out there?
Say something!
Whoa.
Oh, hello.
What are you doing
down there?
Oh, shit!
Oh, at last. I'm free!
Are you DaedeWad?
Uh, yeah,
I'm Daedelad Parsaneon,
son of Amax The Wise.
But everyone calls me Doodad.
Look, I hate to break it
to you, Doodad,
we're in a bit of a bind here.
Oh, serpents of Malinax.
I warned those bumbling bandits
what they'd find
if they ventured
too far into these caves.
I have an idea.
Hop on. Come on.
What are you gonna do?
Not die.
Nice one!
-  Ooh!
- Oh...
- Tuck and roll!
- What?
Wait, wait!
Hurrah! We're safe!
Yeah. You're welcome.
What do they call you, good sir?
The name is Death--
Hold still.
Would you stop it?
Okay.
Hold still.
I was close that time.
You were not.
Okay, hey, hey.
So you stole this
from Prince Halgan?
Well, "stole" is a bit strong.
He was already dead.
Well...
on his way out, at least.
- Meaning?
- He was coughing a bit.
But it was definitely
a death rattle. I'm sure of it.
- Sounds like he was alive to me.
- Hey!
I didn't rescue you
to get a lecture on the ethics
of the spoils of war.
Now you keep it up,
and I throw you
back in there
with those serpents.
Well, I suppose
I do owe you my life.
So I'll do what I can to solve
this little riddle.
These runes alone
suggest powerful magic.
But what purpose does it serve?
Mmm!
The runes.
They're not Abraxeon,
they're Asmordian!
Asmordian, huh?
The precursor to the
Abraxeon empire.
Very little record of
them has survived.
Their language
all but forgotten.
- Dead language, huh?
- Dead to everyone but
a fellow member of the Sorcerers
Order, the great wizard Xodan.
Skilled
in all the ancient tongues.
- Hyperion, Atlantean--
- Wait, wait, wait.
So you can't read it either?
Crap.
Where do we find this Xodan guy?
In his crypt, I imagine.
- He's dead?
- Very much so.
But he would be entombed
with his scrolls,
and I'm certain
that one of them
will contain
the Asmordian cipher.
And with that,
you can read the amulet
and reverse the curse?
- I believe so.
- Great.
- We'll head out at sunrise.
-  Oh, no.
I can't go to Xodan's crypt.
With so many assassins
in pursuit of the amulet,
it's far too dangerous.
You go there and get it
and bring it back to me
at Munkar's Tavern.
Hey, if it wasn't for me,
you would still be locked
in a trunk.
Besides, do
you really think
you're going to last
out of here on your own?
- Hmm?
- Eh...
Fine.
At dawn, we'll travel
to Xodan's Sanctuary.
Now pass me some of that meat.
I noticed something strange
with the assassin I slayed
back at Munkar's Tavern.
The marking on his shoulder.
A guild marking, perhaps.
No,
this was something else.
Maybe you know what it means.
Something like this.
That's not possible.
The Sect of Sytor was wiped out
eons ago.
Sytor?
An ancient cult of sorcerers.
Obsessed with the mysteries
of the Outer Realms.
Worlds of dark evil
that no mortal
was ever meant
to understand.
Their leader, Nekromemnon.
He was defeated,
and all records of his teachings
were destroyed.
Or so I thought.
If the markings you saw
are from the Sect of Sytor,
then there are more
sinister forces at work here.
So you're saying the Sect of
Sytor has returned?
That Nekromemnon is back to
finish what he started?
Well, the Dreadites
are rumored to have been
born from necromancy.
But all I know for sure
is that
if the Sect of Sytor
is involved,
your quest is truly doomed.
We should keep moving.
Hop on.
All right.
Someone approaches.
Hide!
Where is he?
Excellent.
We've got him.
He's here.
Find him.
Come on, let's go!
After him!
Hide behind those rocks.
What are you doing?
When it happens,
you'll thank me.
When what happens?
Whoa!
Go that way!
No. That way!
No, go the other way!
How is this helping?
God damnit!
- What is this?
- No, that way!
Go!
What is this? Hey, hey!
- Stop. What is this?
- No!
- No! No, no, no.
- God damnit! Stop!
- Stop it!
- No!
Stop. Stop it. Stop.
- No, not--
-  Pathetic.
Jotak.
Tritus.
I gave up that name
long ago.
Ah, yes.
Deathstalker, is it not?
I knew our paths
would cross again one day.
Fortunately, your cowardice
has set you on a path
back to me.
You see, old friend,
the ritual at Grimvault...
Tritus, Jotak.
Stop those warlocks!
The warlocks
we killed to protect
the might of Abraxeon.
That was the first step
in ensuring his resurrection.
You must resist
the dark enchantments.
My old friend.
Your blade should have ended me
that night.
But what you failed
to realize is that
my fate was in his hands,
not yours.
And now Nekromemnon
has returned.
And this time,
he'll bring the entire world
to its knees.
And I couldn't resist the chance
to take Halgan's amulet
from you personally...
Deathstalker.
Then by all means.
Come and get it.
No!
He's mine.
Goodbye, my friend.
Doodad, let's go! Come on!
After him!
What have you embroiled me in,
Deathstalker?
- Hey!
- This is no mere curse reverse.
If Nekromemnon has
truly returned
from the outer realms, then
Abraxeon
is on the brink of annihilation.
We must decipher those runes,
and quickly.
At this rate, we'll be lucky
if we survive the night.
Survival may have set you
on this path, but I see it now.
Our meeting
is the machinations of the gods.
We have to learn what part
the amulet plays in this plot,
or risk the end of everything
and the beginning of a dark era
I dare not imagine.
Machinations of the gods, huh?
- I like that.
- Huh.
Lead the way, little guy.
Come on, let's go.
Nekromemnon's minions!
On this sacred ground?
Why?
There's no way past those
Dreadites without being seen.
Look. The Xodan scrolls
will be buried with him.
And among them will be
the Asmordian translation.
Oh, that translation is my
my only chance
of deciphering the amulet.
If I could just
get my hands on it.
We have to find a way in there.
I have an idea.
Oh, wow.
The acolytes of Kulthis.
I should have known they played
a part in this madness.
This was a bad idea.
- This was your idea.
- Ugh.
What is this?
This is gross!
- Shh! Quiet!
- Hey!
- They'll hear you. Shut up!
- You shut up.
Maybe both of you
could shut up.
You're not the only one
sneaking in.
Okay?
Could you shush?
Please?
- Sorry.
- Who are you?
- What is he doing?
The ancient rite
of resurrection.
A ritual that can only
be performed
by those who share lineage
with ageless beings
that rule the outer worlds.
So this is
how he makes his army,
by enslaving the corpses
of his enemies.
Of all the graveyards
in all the realms.
- Really, Doodad?
- Whine about it later.
What's the plan here, guys?
First of all, this is our plan,
and it was working fine
before you showed up.
And who the hell are you, anyway?
Who are you?
I don't know who you are.
The path
to Xodan's crypt is clear.
Now's my chance.
Doodad!
Where are you going?
Keep an eye on the acolytes.
I will return.
That's some plan.
- Wait for me.
- Hey!
What the hell?
Gross.
There it is.
- Help me!
-  Just a sec.
What are you after, exactly?
A scroll that translates
the Asmordian tongue.
One of these must be it.
No!
Hey, uh,
I don't want to rush you,
little guy,
but there's only one way
out of here,
and if the freaks upstairs
catch on, we're done.
It's here, I know it is!
I just need more time!
Ah... Not it!
No!
We gotta go.
I need more time!
Ugh. Atlantean.
Okay, you freak.
Let's see what color you bleed.
Well, did you find it?
Just a sec. Hypernian...
Come on, hurry!
- Got it!
- Great, let's go. Come on.
You are the one they call...
Deathstalker.
I will have...
...what is mine.
It's him.
Nekromemnon.
My emissaries
will hunt you
to the ends
of the realm and beyond.
Run while you can.
The further you take
the light of Talon from me,
the greater
my wrath will grow.
Light of Talon?
Soon you will beg
for the mercy of death!
- Here.
- What?
A way out.
Let's go!
Go, go, go!
Come on, Doodad.
- Uh, hi.
- Okay.
They'll be all over
the main roads.
We should wait till dawn
before we go any further.
This looks like a fine spot.
- What's that sound?
-  Ah, don't worry.
Those are just
the Wailing Woods.
Nothing to be concerned about
and should help
mask any noise
we might make in the night.
Well, good.
So nobody's going to complain
if I play a little bit of this.
Hey.
Thanks for your help
back there.
I never got your name.
It's Brisbayne,
thief extraordinaire.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to steal
any of your precious scrolls.
I prefer my treasures to have
a little more sparkle to them.
Well, I'm not worried.
All right, then.
I'll let you know
when I need the amulet.
Just rest.
Hey, Doodad. Brisbayne.
Show yourself.
No!
Aah!
Huh, look at that.
Just rubble.
Let's go. Come on.
This is but a taste
of what was shared with me
from within the abyss.
The child will obey
if you have the strength
to command it.
Your work...
...is not finished, Jotak.
It is the will of Sytor
himself.
Yes.
If I am to possess
the light of Talon,
Deathstalker must die.
Oh, yes!
Your little friend
is a heavy sleeper.
He's not my friend.
I've enlisted him to
lift the curse, nothing more.
Something to do with
that Asmordian amulet?
Look, the talisman
is bound to me,
and I'm looking to unbind it,
and preferably
stay alive in the process.
You really can't stand
the thought of anyone
sticking by you, can you?
You're an easy read,
Deathstalker.
The world is full of people
like you, I get it.
Life is much simpler
when you live for one destiny.
And I suppose you prefer
the camaraderie of
the thieves guild, huh?
I'm not with the guild.
Not anymore.
They found me too...
...impulsive.
You know, I used
to sack the palace
for fun all by myself.
Yeah, but that game
certainly got stale once
the palace's bravest were sent
off to die in this war.
But still, I suppose I am always
looking for my next challenge.
Oh, is that what we are,
the next challenge?
No, no, I already said I have
no intention of robbing you.
But I have been having fun.
Yeah, right.
Huh.
An Abraxeon battle camp.
How exciting.
Do you think these
guys have some food?
Wait.
Hey!
-  Hello?
- Hey--
Oh.
Dreadites.
But they moved on long ago.
Huh. Onions.
Move!
We have you now,
Deathstalker.
Where are you going?
Let's go!
Scarabus'
exploits are legendary.
You really are attracting
the very best assassins
in the kingdom, my friend.
Please shut up.
I'll just use
my magic to protect you.
I don't need
your wizarding ways
getting me killed!
Excuse me?
My powers have been nothing
but helpful.
Yes! It worked!
Oh, sorry.
You cannot escape us.
Yes, I can.
There!
That thing can--
can teleport and--
Okay.
I should thank you.
But I'm not going to.
Let me see it.
Can you stitch me up?
No, I, uh, got something better.
Hold these healing crystals
against your arm.
What are those?
The amethyst is going
to purify the cut.
The bloodstone helps
with circulation,
and the tiger's eye
will help to lessen your fear.
- My fear?
- Yes.
Your fear of dying
from your wounds.
And you think you can read
people like me?
- Aah! Ow!
- There you go.
I never figured a thief
for an alchemist.
Yeah, well.
Unlike you...
my heart is, uh...
a bit more complicated.
What does your heart have to do
with anything?
We all have our own hearts,
Deathstalker.
It's what rules our fate.
I've seen more than
a fair share of hearts
- at the end of my sword.
-  Mh-hm?
And they all look
the same to me.
Ow!
Hey.
I'm glad you stuck around.
Sure.
-  Ah! That's it!
- What?
The runes. I've deciphered them.
What does it say?
Ah...
It's done.
You're now free
from the amulet's bonds.
Oh.
Thank you, my friend.
But wait, there's more.
Behold Talon's prophecy.
This kingdom
was once ruled
by the magic
of two supreme beings.
Talon, the wizard king of light.
Sytor, the
witch-lord of darkness.
Together, these titans battled
over the fate of existence
using the mortals
as their pawns.
As Sytor's power grew
too strong to defeat,
Talon created a weapon
so powerful
that only those that walked
between the worlds of life
and death could wield it.
It was hidden within
this magic amulet,
passed down
through the generations,
until its true purpose
was completely forgotten.
What kind of
weapon does it hide?
A weapon unlike any that has
ever existed
in this world before.
A weapon
known as the Light of Talon.
It's beautiful.
The perfect sword.
One day, a warrior will
rise to wield its four blades
to extinguish
the four hearts of evil,
saving the kingdom from a
never-ending reign of darkness.
Doodad! Come on!
Get out of here. Gah.
Brisbayne?
The amulet.
She took it.
That rotten little...
I slept terribly
last night.
You're going to have
to carry me.
No, don't.
There's too many of them.
I know this path.
We are headed
to the dead swamps.
It's a dangerous place.
If you do not tread lightly,
you'll awaken the ancient curse
that lives below.
Perfect. That's just what
we need right now.
What evil lives in these walls?
I only know rumors. Stories.
Diseased men cast out
from their villages,
absorbed by the earth
and resurrected
into vengeful spirits
that have forgotten
the joys of music
or the comfort
of a brotherly hug.
That is all I know.
No one who has encountered
them face to face
has lived to tell the tale.
What else do you have?
It's empty.
There he is.
The one who got away.
Brisbayne's really proven
herself worthy
by helping us capture you.
And bringing me the most
valuable item in the kingdom.
Halgan's precious amulet.
- Mwah.
- And you brought us here
to give us our share
of the reward, right?
I don't remember
you being so generous, Grendul.
I'm generous to those
who follow the rules
and share the wealth.
These are troubling times,
after all.
We thieves must stick together.
Look at her.
Brisbayne, you're one of us
forever now.
Bravo!
Hooray!
Hey! Stop it!
We're family here.
For a family to get along,
there has to be rules.
You know this.
Did I not warn you years ago
that there would be a price
for not paying us
our proper share
of your bounties?
Yeah, you warned me.
I just didn't care.
Do them fast.
Prince Baldur
expects us to meet him
at Grimvault before nightfall.
Truly despicable act,
I must say.
Robbing a dead prince of his
most precious family heirloom.
I'm sure Baldur will appreciate
its return,
for a tidy sum, of course.
We have a saying in the guild.
If you only serve yourself,
a reckoning you'll be served.
And now, gentlemen,
your reckoning is served.
Wait!
Isn't there another way?
Can't you just...
smack him around a little?
Stick to your flute,
Brisbayne.
Archers!
Fire!
Get them!
Archers!
Fire!
Here, help me out! Untie me!
No! You untie me first.
No! You untie me.
I can't help you.
- Come on.
- All right, fine.
Fire!
No!
They've forgotten
the joy of music.
Or the comfort
of a brotherly hug.
Wait.
No.
That's right.
Oh, no.
Yes.
- Deathstalker.
- Hmm?
We can leave now.
Okay.
Come on. Hop on.
Remind me,
why are we going
to Grimvault again?
The Royal family
is waiting for the amulet
so the forces of good
can summon the Light of Talon.
There's no time to waste.
Well, there
better be a sweet reward
at the end of all this.
Is saving the world
not enough of a reward?
Nope!
I'm cold.
Can you fetch my blanket?
Something wrong, my lord?
It's just...
Oh, my God,
you're going to hate me.
You know, I'm a little warm.
Baldur.
You're not that lady
from the Thieves Guild.
My name is Deathstalker,
and I'm here for the reward.
Oh! Deathstalker!
Mother speaks highly of you.
Your...
...swordsmanship is legendary.
I didn't realize the Queen
held me in such high regard.
Yes, she says,
of all the traitorous parasites
sucking the kingdom dry, you...
are the most handsome.
That is so sweet.
Yeah. Wish she'd say such
nice things about me.
Ah! Anyway.
Sure was a rough road
getting here.
We were pursued by many foes.
You know,
we almost didn't make it.
So many foes.
Hmm?
Poor Halgan.
He always was the unlucky one.
Rocks.
Oh, I had no intention
of paying you.
So these are just regular rocks?
Not expensive, royal rocks
or anything like that?
No, just normal dumb rocks.
Mother will be pleased
when I bring her the head
of the kingdom's most
notorious deserter and thief.
The once-mighty
Deathstalker!
You forgot handsome.
And you know what else
she would really like?
This.
Kill him! Get him!
Dreadites!
Watch out!
I've got it!
Begone foul creature!
Nice shot.
Let's go.
I will, my friend.
I told you this wasn't over.
Before you ask, no.
You can't have your sword back.
Keep it.
Stay back.
Again you hide behind steel.
True power
comes from more than just
the sword.
Your madness
ends tonight, Jotak,
even if I have to do it
with my bare hands.
My eyes have
been opened, Tritus.
The only way you will
know the truth
is in death!
Deathstalker!
Brisbayne!
Hey. I'm so sorry
about what happened.
I didn't mean to--
Who is this?
A friend of yours?
Definitely not a friend.
I said I was sorry!
No!
Let me go!
You vile creatures!
Give it to me.
It's yours.
I don't know what Mother
wants with it anyway.
- At last.
-  There.
You have what you want.
Just free me,
you undead cretin!
Of course.
Oh, wow--
Tonight we ride to
Nekromemnon's fortress.
And to victory!
Jotak was right.
Death does open your eyes
to a lot.
I know what I have to do now.
I have to save my friends.
And they've got a day's
start on me.
How do I get to them in time?
That'll work.
Restrain the wizard.
Bring the thief to me.
Kneel before your master.
The will of Sytor
that brought you before me.
This is your destiny:
to serve us for all eternity.
Thing is, I didn't really like
the last club that I joined.
Well, if you'd prefer...
I could just rip your heart out.
But it sounds like I get
to live forever in this one, so,
that sounds good, too.
All the powers of darkness
will be yours.
Okay, okay.
Uh, hang on a second.
- Where are we going?
- You can join us
in rebuilding this world...
as it was meant to be.
- No, no.
-  In the
image of Sytor.
- I think I'll pass.
-  Yes!
Oh, okay. No, no, no, no!
Oh! Oh.
More, more! Yes!
Oh, yes.
In the hands of a mere mortal
it's quite useless.
But in the hands of one
who walks between
life and death
it could spell our demise.
But no more! No more!
The light of Talon dies tonight!
-  Nekromemnon!
- Huh?
You're mad!
There it is.
It is time.
Abraxeon will fall!
There is no one who can stand
in my way.
Oh, oh, oh.
What the fuck is that?
Here I come!
Dreadites.
Rip him to pieces!
Deathstalker!
Behind you!
Oh! Get up!
Get up, you fool!
Look out there!
Ha, ha! Yes!
- You're alive!
- Doodad, are you all right?
Oh, I'm good.
Just get me out of these.
Oh, it's so good to see you.
What took you so long?
The wraith, it got lost,
and I was in the swamp,
and I got resurrected.
There was a lot going on.
We have to help Brisbayne.
You're too late,
Deathstalker.
What are you doing to her?
Her heart
has joined the dark beyond.
She is now the vessel
of Sytor.
Don't worry.
You can't save her.
It's time
I put you down for good.
Hey!
This ends here, sorcerer.
You say, "Hey" to me?
Oh, dear.
Hey!
The magic you wield
is but child's play
compared to mine.
Your arrogance will be
your undoing, Nekromemnon.
Oh good heavens,
I'm so scared.
Well, come on then.
Let's have at it.
Give it to me!
Goodbye, old friend.
Your aim still hasn't improved,
Son of Amax.
You missed me.
You missed me, again.
Did I?
What's that?
Oh, dear!
Did I Doodad?
Ah! Ah, yes!
Oh, yes!
Sytor is risen!
Sytor, yes!
You've come!
Sytor, you've come!
You've come. You've come.
Come, come, come.
My queen, yes!
Yes, yes! Ah!
Any ideas, wizard?
The light of Talon
has been destroyed!
Sytor will consume us all!
It's over, Deathstalker.
I thought I was a pessimist.
Deathstalker, no!
It's too late!
In the hands of one
who walks between life
and death...
could spell our demise.
Deathstaker! There! Go!
We all have our own
hearts, Deathstalker.
It's what rules our fate.
I've seen
more than a fair
share of hearts
at the end of my sword.
And they all look
the same to me.
Wield the four blades
to extinguish
the four hearts of evil.
Hurry, Deathstalker!
Fulfill the prophecy.
No. I'm doing this my way.
Brisbayne!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Come on. Hey, Brisbayne.
Brisbayne. Come on.
Wake up! Wake up!
She's alive!
-  You're okay.
-  I'm okay.
Of course.
Sytor only had three hearts.
Just like the alignment
of the three moons.
Oh, my goodness,
that was a very lucky guess,
Deathstalker.
I wasn't guessing, Doodad.
Someone once taught me
that we all have our own heart.
So I just avoided the one that,
well...
Looked complicated.
- Come on, let's go.
- Okay.
Get up. Yeah. You're back.
Hey.
You may want to wash that off.
Meh.
You know what?
I think we earned ourselves
a bit of music.
- What? You found it? Thank you!
- I did.
Hey, don't
you understand what this means,
Deathstalker?
You've rewritten the prophecy.
You are
the one that saved the kingdom
from the never
ending reign of darkness.
Yeah.
You could walk
right into the palace now
and take the throne
if you wanted to.
Huh.
It's a perfect sword.
But a weapon like this
should not rule our fate's.
Destroy it.
If that is what you wish.
Ow! Doodad!
Sorry.
Just stay still. Once more.
What do you mean? I'm
standing still.
Hold it high!
Come on!
The sword is here.
Don't move, don't move!
Hold it up.
- I can do this.
- You're doing this on purpose.
I'm not doing this on purpose.
Honestly.
- I'm gonna put it on the ground.
- No. You can't.
- You have to hold it up.
- Why?
The one who fulfills
the prophecy has to hold it.
- Hold it high!
- I'm pointing it far away.
I'll get it this time. Ready?
I swear to God,
if you hit me one more time,
I'm going to spank you.
Okay?
One last chance.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Doodad!
I don't understand you.
Don't hit me!
♪ Born in chains ♪
♪ Condemned and powerless ♪
♪ How the boy
becomes a man of vengeance ♪
♪ And when you're
forced to fight ♪
♪ The blood becomes a friend ♪
♪ Yet a distant cry echoes
on the way ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ With every step you take ♪
♪ When walking that road ♪
♪ Don't look behind you it's
just demons and ghosts ♪
♪ Deathstalker, blood lust ♪
♪ The path you walk for
the rest of your life ♪
♪ Scared at times ♪
♪ Through many
sleepless nights ♪
♪ Living by the makers hand
by design ♪
♪ And when at last ♪
♪ You find the heroes
many crimes ♪
♪ All the lines get blurred ♪
♪ Between what's wrong
and right ♪
♪ Oh, with every step you take ♪
♪ When walking that road ♪
♪ Don't look behind you
it's just demons and ghosts ♪
♪ Deathstalker, blood lust ♪
♪ The path you walk for
the rest of your life ♪
♪ It's not a nightmare, so
just open your eyes ♪
♪ It's in the flesh the
dream is coming alive ♪
♪ Deathstalker, blood lust ♪
♪ The path you walk until
the day that you die ♪
♪ Oh yeah! ♪
♪ Go find my chains ♪
♪ Righteous and reclaimed ♪
♪ On the throne of blood ♪
♪ The crown of gold decays ♪
♪ Yeah! When every step
you take ♪
♪ When walking that road ♪
♪ Don't look behind you
it's just demons and ghosts ♪
♪ Deathstalker, blood lust ♪
♪ The path you walk
for the rest of your life ♪
♪ It's not a nightmare
so just open your eyes ♪
♪ It's in the flesh the
dream is coming alive ♪
♪ Deathstalker, blood lust ♪
♪ The path you walk until the
day that you die ♪
♪ I can feel you've changed ♪
♪ When I look into your eyes ♪
♪ There's something that they
want from you ♪
♪ Like the moon up in the sky ♪
♪ Everything goes quiet again ♪
♪ Leaving the field
of death behind ♪
♪ How does it feel like
to run the rest of your life ♪
♪ With nowhere to go ♪
♪ How does it feel like
to be the only one ♪
♪ You're walking alone ♪
♪ I can hear it call ♪
♪ The darkness of your fate ♪
♪ You've seen a share
of hearts on your sword ♪
♪ A past you can't escape ♪
♪ Everything goes quiet again ♪
♪ Leaving
the field of death behind ♪
♪ How does it feel like to
run the rest of your life ♪
♪ With nowhere to go ♪
♪ How does it feel like to be
the only one ♪
♪ You're walking alone ♪
♪ How does it feel like,
feel like ♪
I want to know ♪
♪ How does it feel like to
run the rest of your life ♪
♪ With nowhere to go ♪
♪ I want to know how it feels ♪
♪ How does it feel like
to be the only one ♪
♪ You're walking alone ♪
♪ How does it feel like
to run the rest of your life ♪
♪ With nowhere to go ♪
♪ How does it feel like
to be the only one ♪
♪ You're walking alone ♪