Good to go.
Charlie Oscar, Charlie Oscar,
Snakebite, how copy? Over.
- Charlie Oscar, Charlie Oscar.
- Snakebite, how copy? Over.
They gotta be monitoring.
Crack the whip!
Oh!
Charlie Oscar, Charlie Oscar.
Snakebite, how copy? Over.
Charlie Oscar Six,
-give me the latest.
-Six, it's Snakebite.
Mission's a bust.
Four down hard.
Requesting emergency extract
from Site Delta. Over.
Is the mission complete?
Six, be advised,
we cannot continue the mission!
We are down to two!
I say again, we are down
to two back--
Where are you?
You motherfuckers!
I take you boys
ain't from around here.
Well, we could tell ya,
but, you know?
- I hear that.
-
Let's go--
I need three guards
to cover that jeep
right now, let's go.
Fan out! Fan out!
You two. I want you both
up on that ridge ASAP.
-Yes, sir.
-Jesus fucking Christ.
We're looking
for a Major Wallace.
That'd be me.
Listen, you fuckers!
You gonna tell me
where the rest of your stash is.
- Yeah?
- Tell me where it's at!
Bill Wallace.
S-2, First Field Force.
You guys must be the field reps
-I was told to expect.
-So, where is it, Major Wallace?
Just when I thought
I'd seen it all.
Follow me.
You guys are what? CORDS?
MACV? SOG?
-CIA?
-Need to know, Major.
Right. And I clearly
don't need to know.
If you told me, you'd have to--
That's the drill.
- Sergeant Jensen.
- Let's go, let's go.
-Let's go to the...
-Would you please get
this kid a lollipop,
or a shot of morphine,
or something?
For Christ's sake, mama's son,
what is your problem?
I told you, I don't understand
a fucking word you say!
- Okay, come with me.
-She said a demon took her husband.
-A feathered demon.
-That's what I heard.
-You speak gook?
-A little.
Comes with the territory.
Yeah. We can have
that territory.
Truck's over here.
Same barrels, Russian markings.
Knew it. What are they for?
Right.
Oh, shit.
-I need to know about that.
My men are out--
-We're done here,
Major, and so are you.
Sir, Six-Alpha is on the phone.
Charlie Oscar,
Rampage, how copy?
I need to talk to the Six.
Wait one, Rampage.
Rampage, Charlie Oscar Six.
What do you got?
One truck, ten barrels,
all with standard markings.
Measure 3.46 on the counter.
Hot as hell. Over.
The NBA driver
is showing early symptoms
of radiation poisoning.
This is number five
since we've started the track.
Yeah, a-- any further word
on Snakebite?
Negative.
We overflew both last knowns.
Nothing but bush and more bush.
All right, big army
is gonna come in
and extract all those civilians.
You just stay tight.
Lock it down and stand by.
- Let's go!
- We're close. I think
-we can pick up
Snakebite's track--
-No, no, no,
n-- no, no. Negative.
That is, uh, too much
of a risk out there.
We are ass-deep
in alligator right now, okay?
We're just gonna mark our time
and-- until I figure
this thing out, all right?
Charlie Oscar Six out.
R4 800.
Make sure Bravo gets out
of the perimeter.
What's the latest on Vulture?
All right,
let's rock and roll.
Go, go!
Get down, get down.
Go, go, go!
All right. Here we go, Logan.
- Clear! Go!
-
Clear!
Rig it!
Sarge, Vulture overwatch.
Touching!
Covering!
Vulture overwatch,
you got eyes on this circus.
Roger that. Got a visual.
Clear to engage. Over.
Twelve o'clock.
Eleven o'clock, left hut.
Breathe. Relax.
Aim. Squeeze.
He's toast, man.
Breathe. Relax.
Aim. Squeeze.
Vulture Six,
clean house here, man.
We're good to go. All right.
-All right.
-Just give me a second, okay?
You're good.
Son of a bitch.
Bingo.
Covering.
- Jesus fucking God.
- Oh, no--
- Hey.
- Leon!
Hang in there.
We got you, we got you.
We got you.
Vulture Overwatch,
two friendlies
on the north side perimeter.
Call the birds and then join us.
Watch out!
- Hey, Sergeant,
find anything?
We checked all the other huts.
-No joy. Looks like these two
are all we gonna get.
-We'll take it.
We'll get you outta here,
fellas.
Get you back to your families.
Oh.
- Too late.
- Easy, easy--
-Fuck.
-Shit, man. You're bleeding.
Ah, shit.
Fuck, man.
We going home, boys.
Vodkas and T-bones for everyone.
-Yeah!
-Courtesy of your favorite
Uncle Samantha.
-Oh, yeah!
-And the rocks pretty crew
from Vulture Squad.
-Whoo!
-Look after him!
- ...going home.
- Get some beers,
- boys. We earned it.
- Oh--
-Yeah, you found me.
-New order, Sarge.
Supposed to get you
and your guys
loaded into the Huey
-and out to the sea--
-Wait, wait, wait.
Who the fuck ordered this?
Some colonel named Jericho.
All I know, Sarge.
Well...
we're not getting any beer.
Ah, shit.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Who the fuck is Jericho?
Jesus!
You recons look like
a sack of hampered assholes.
-Where's Baker?
-What are you doin' here?
More importantly,
what are we doin' here?
Because we all made
some poor life choices, Baker.
The old man would love
to discuss
the consequences with you.
No rest for the weary.
-Miller, get that arm
checked out.
-Whatever.
I'm good, Sarge.
I ain't asking!
Hey.
-Sir.
-I heard you got two.
Nice work, Baker.
It is not bad
for a sorry ass LURP team.
Yeah, yeah. Well,
you gotta remember,
I let you choose that team
of degenerates and fuckups,
so, you know,
maybe you were right after all.
Yeah, you gotta be a lunatic
if you're gonna be a Vulture.
- Well, maybe so, but I'm
gonna tell you something.
Let's see what you guys think
of this next mission.
-Sir.
-Mm-hmm.
Have a seat, everybody.
Smoke 'em if you got 'em.
There he is, Razor.
There we go!
You hungry there, Razor?
- Oh, man, I bet you are!
You deserve it.
I got so much respect
for this guy. You know why?
Because he doesn't beg
like a little fucking dog.
- He's an apex predator,
top of the food chain.
Took on a whole platoon
of my men and it wasn't
even scared.
Now it's sitting in there,
he's all chained up,
and he's waiting
for an alpha male to feed him.
And so it goes.
RT Vulture.
Yeah, you did one shit hot job
on that POW snatch.
Brought two live ones back.
We ain't seen that yet
this side of the Z.
By the way, you managed to do it
without even pissing me off.
- First time
for everything, Colonel.
Yeah, nothing succeeds
like success.
Y'all ready for your next
kick-ass mission?
Bring it on, Colonel.
All RT Vulture needs
is an Indige rucksack
and half a shoulder
to carry it on.
Yeah, maybe bring it on
after a night's sleep, Colonel.
You got it.
Zero dark thirty,
we're gonna drop you
in right here.
Three days ago,
we sent a MIC team in here,
ODA 225 at Van Gent.
They were sent over here
to investigate
some heavy lift transports,
new, uh, construction bunkers
-and that sort of shit.
-Green beanies get lost
in all that bush, huh?
-Leon.
-They did not get lost.
Radio fucking silence
and we could see nothing
from the air.
There is something
going on out there
in that valley.
Y'all are LURPs, right?
Reconnaissance is
your fucking business.
Let's get after it.
What's the end game, Colonel?
Assuming we find 'em,
do we round 'em up,
-call for extraction?
-That is negative.
I need you to find 'em,
identify 'em, call it in.
We'll take care of extraction.
And what's so special
about this valley, sir?
Fuckin' new guy.
Classified.
Seems kinda Major League
for trolleys, sir.
Sounds more like NBA.
Or PLA, you know, right?
We can theorize
about that shit forever.
Y'all stay in your fucking lane.
Keep your head
on a fucking swivel...
And what is it exactly
the Green Berets
were looking for, sir?
Fuckin' new guy.
Classified, motherfucker!
Hey, fucking classified,
all right?
I got moisturizer
that's older than you,
you little fucking bitch.
Here's what the fuck I want.
I lost my fucking Green Berets
and I need y'all
to find 'em for me.
-Vultures will find 'em, sir.
-All right, we're gonna
come back here
for a meeting at 18:30.
Y'all check all your gear,
and you come back here
rested and ready to go.
That's it. Get the fuck out.
Fucking classified.
- Baker.
- Sir.
I'm gonna need you
to stick around
for another minute.
What's the rest
of the story, Colonel?
Are you... thinking
we might find a bunch
of SF corpses out there?
You go out there and you find me
something, all right?
And you let me worry
about the rest of it.
I'll come up with it,
don't you worry.
- That's pretty thin, sir.
-  -Well,
you go out there
and you get me
a detailed report.
That's all I ask.
And you make sure
that none of these fuckups,
all right,
these loose cannons of yours,
they don't try to play hero.
All right?
Now, are we tracking on that?
Can you at least tell me
what they were looking for?
Classified.
Take this seriously,
and I'll take a big eraser
to that 201 file.
All those allegations
that you had with McNeil...
...I believed in you
during that investigation.
I was in your corner.
That's why I had you
transferred over to LURPs.
All right?
I appreciate that, sir.
Just keep these fuckups in line,
that's all I ask.
Dismissed.
Yes, Sarge.
You don't need a poncho.
Makes too much noise.
And break down
the C-ration boxes.
If it's bulk or excess weight,
shit can happen.
LURPs write the wrong rules,
I guess.
There it is, compadre.
Carry only what you need.
If you can't carry it
in a pocket or a liner,
you don't need it, man.
But this...
...you most definitely need.
Got some loco dudes
on this team.
I knew what I sign up for
when I volunteered
comin' over here.
Listen, man.
Baker picked you for a reason.
It's his reason and he knows
what he needs in the Vulture.
Must figure you have
what it takes.
Best thing you can do
is prove him right.
Yes, Sergeant.
...just little more right here.
Get those to the squad.
Whoo!
Here's your canteens.
It's fucking pissing down there.
It's always pissing, man.
How's the arm?
Oh, it's fine.
What you got there, bro?
Oh, this...
...is a sacred libation.
-I found this hooch.
-Oh, damn. Where'd you get it?
Them two spooks,
they had it in their tent.
Figured they went out
there blowing bush
and trading rounds
with the gooks, so,
I rate good stateside hooch
more than they do.
This shit any better
than what they cook up at home?
No, it doesn't even compare
to Smoky Mountain bust head,
-but it'll do in a pinch. Hmm?
-Ah.
You remember you dragging
your drunken ass
out of that mess?
No, I was drunk.
But I owe you, if that helps.
Oh, what helps is you not
getting so shitfaced at camp
you can't see straight
on the next mission.
I'd seen what was waiting
for us on the other side.
Hence why I don't feel bad
taking this here hooch
as an advance payment.
Squid pro and sh-- shit.
Quid pro quo. Jesus Christ, Eli!
Don't try to sound intelligent
or you're gonna lose that charm
-we all love.
-Why don't you shut that mouth
of yours for once, Keyes?
Relax, compadre.
Or you're gonna miss out
on all these presents
I got here.
-Since Miller here has found
the Good Book...
-Mm. Mm-hmm.
...I'm gonna excuse him
from the, uh,
embarrassment of the Lord.
- Wow.
- Ho, ho, ho, buddy.
Huh, ho, ho.
You wanna work on your charm?
Follow Keyes, man.
This man can sell ice
to Eskimos.
Must've buttered up
some assistant to the colonel
to find these out here.
- Buttered it up and slipped it in.
-Mm-hmm!
Oh, man, I learned
from the best.
This better
have tits in it.
Well...
All right! The new guy.
You got
the most important choice
you're ever gonna make.
-What's that?
-Candy for your eyes...
...or...
...candy for your mouth.
What's it gonna be?
- I'll take the mouth candy.
- Wrong answer.
- You ever seen
a naked woman, man?
- Does your mother count?
- Oh, shit.
-New guy's got some balls.
-Oh. Come on, man.
Cut the shit, all right?
New guy just made an honest
and... truthful answer,
and we should respect that.
Wrong fucking choice though.
New guy's a moron.
That means... this is for you.
Oh. What would happen
to this club without you?
Huh?
Probably all kill each other.
Uh, Logan, man, uh,
hey, we gotta talk.
You wanna break up?
No.
Uh, it's about, um,
-what happened on the hilltop.
-Yeah.
I'm-- I'm-- I'm serious, man.
You gotta-- you gotta talk
to somebody about this shit.
-Man--
-U-- um, there's--
there's no range coaches
out there, man.
You can shoot
without chanting all that...
-...fucking brass bullshit.
-I can't help it, Keyes.
The voices are in my head
all the time.
But if I say 'em out loud,
it helps me stay on target.
- Yeah. All right.
Okay.
- Yeah.
But it's gonna get
your dumb ass killed.
Look... I don't wanna see
that happen.
So you promise me,
when we get back to the rear,
you talk to somebody about this.
All right?
Sure. I'll see somebody.
- Assuming we even make it
back to the rear.
I see the boys
are corrupting you.
Good.
Team brief in ten mikes.
All hands in the briefing tent.
Yeah, boss!
Gonna be some embarrassed
Green Berets
when we pull their asses
out of there.
Fuck yeah.
The fuck is that?
That's weird.
What's up?
The equipment's all screwy.
We're still
flying right, though.
We're coming up
on datum point zero.
Skids down in one mike!
One mike! One mike!
One mike!
Whoo!
Good luck, Vultures.
Gear up.
What was that cutting a path
through the trees
back over there?
Looks like a game trail,
but bigger than I've ever seen.
-Elephants?
-Some fucking
big elephants, Sarge.
-The enemy still uses them.
-Fuck, I can't
understand Jericho.
Would've something about that
instead of talking about
a stupid goddamn tiger
the whole time.
Ah, Jericho's shit
is fucked up, man.
- You cannot trust that motherfucker.
-  -Cut the shit.
Whatever dinky-di Phoenix
number he's running,
don't mean nothin'.
We got our job,
find those Green Berets.
Fan out!
What is it?
Track.
Is it our guys?
No. Animal.
Something big.
It's a big bird.
Ostrich, emu, maybe a cassowary.
I studied 'em.
There's another one right there.
Let's backtrack 'em, Leon.
They're weird enough,
I could absolutely see
the green beanies tracking 'em.
-What do you got?
-Jack shit.
Just these big ass
Liberace feathers.
Leon, you ever see
something like this?
No. Never.
-What do you got?
-Yeah, I got a backpack.
Xavier?
Piles of shit. Big piles.
-Don't look at me.
-No. Like guano, but,
but huge.
Sergeant.
Make sense of that.
There's a mark here that says
"Research Station Four."
Maybe where they were headed.
Was there anything else
around the pack?
Yeah, 5.56 casings.
5.56?
Yeah. And footprints.
Yeah, uh, two different
kinds of tracks.
US Army issue size tens
and some other shit.
Oh, and it look like struggle.
We follow those tracks
for a klick or two.
-You're on point.
-You got it, boss.
Sir.
Oh, shit.
Rock apes.
- Fucking things are
all over these hills.
That ain't
no fucking rock apes, man.
Well, fuck.
Time out. Keep moving.
Whatever that is,
it's moving in this direction.
Something's got Baker!
- Baker!
- Sarge!
I found him, he's down here!
- I found him! Sarge--
- Is he okay?
-What is that shit?
-You okay?
- Yeah.
- That thing looked huge.
- Anyone seen
where it went?
Fucked if I know, man.
-Could be anywhere now.
-Don't let the shadows
play tricks on you.
Whatever it was, let's get
some distance between us.
-It might not be
that simple, Sarge.
-Why not?
It wasn't scared of us.
And if it's hungry,
it wouldn't be scared
to come back either.
We gotta get out
of its territory.
How much territory
are we talking?
If it's a tiger,
60 square miles.
That's this whole
fucking valley, man.
Yeah! So quit your bitching
and get a hump at it.
- You heard what the colonel said about tigers.
-  -Yeah.
Great length.
But that ain't no tiger.
-Yeah, no shit.
-It's nothing we can't handle.
Let's move.
I wanna get
to that research station
before dawn.
Let's hump it.
Borodin's orders are
to track the Americans.
We engage only if they approach
one of our facilities.
Con Nhen, lead the way.
Such friendly people.
Only been here a week,
and I wish I could stay forever.
Your bones will.
Con Nhen, you need to relax.
How do you know if Russian
was telling you a joke?
'Cause they will say, is joke.
Still warm.
Can you pick up the trail?
Still may be close.
Spread out. Do not engage.
Be lower than the grass.
Be quieter than water.
Yeah. The Americans are pussies.
-We should just--
-Be quiet. Spread out
and keep moving.
Stupid kid.
Stupid country.
Stupid mosquitoes.
Tolstoy! Aleksandr's gone.
His riffle's filled with blood.
Are any of your people out here?
-What's so funny?
-Follow the blood trail.
Go.
- What is it?
- Don't look.
What is Tolstoy looking at?
I need to see him.
Let me s--
We need to find
all the Americans
and kill them all.
Con Nhen, Tolstoy. He's dead.
Let's go.
Clear that hole, Keyes.
See what you can find in there.
Yeah, all right.
What the hell do we think
that was back there?
Heard some Aussies in Phuoc Tuy
talking about gook spooks
stalking them
through the boonies.
Yeah. It was a couple gooks
in a turkey suit
dragging the sarge.
I could see that.
Could be some...
unknown species.
I'm telling you guys...
...there's monsters out here.
- Baker.
- Yeah.
We could call it in right now.
Say we didn't find shit.
We can all go home.
Tunnel goes on forever.
Probably to the other side.
For what it's worth,
I think we're going
the right way.
We go through.
You're on point.
-Miller.
-Sarge.
Ass in the tunnel.
Ah, ass in again.
I swear to God.
Fuck him.
Son of a bitch.
Contact rear!
- Fall back! Move!
- Fall back!
Move! Move! Move!
- Go! Come on!
- Move, move, move!
Move! Company, light 'em up!
Clear! Clear!
On your left!
- Come up.
- Fall back! Move.
Fall back!
Leon! Leon,
we gotta go this way!
Leon!
We lost the other guys,
Sarge! What do we do?
Now, let's kill
these fuckers first!
- Come on!
- We gotta go this way.
Hey!
- We walked
into a fucking nightmare!
Jesus fucking Christ!
I see an exit, now, let's go!
Baker's missing!
Keep falling back!
- Come on, let's go!
- Logan, come on, man!
Let's go! Right now!
Fuck you!
-I think we're clear.
-We ain't gonna post up here.
They'll be coming.
Fuck.
Now what?
The hell were those things?
Oh, fuck.
Climb. Climb, now.
Questions later.
Move it!
- Shit-- no!
- Sarge!
Light.
Fuck.
Suppose those things
got the other guys?
Not unless they're bulletproof.
Son of a bitch.
That trail, right over there.
Looks like the same one
we saw coming in earlier.
Yeah, it does.
We should see where it leads.
This is really fucked up, man.
Did the colonel tell you
these fucking things
were out here?
When we link up
with the other guys,
we jump on the radio
and ask Jericho point-blank.
I tell you one thing,
this ain't no fucking recon
looking for a bunch
of lost SF dudes.
Leon, if we want answers,
we're gonna have
to go find 'em ourselves.
I can't believe
I fucking volunteer
for this shit.
Oh, shit.
Something's in here, man.
We're fucking surrounded.
Remember I told you
about the voices?
These voices, they're real,
they're real, man.
I'm telling you
they're fucking real.
- I told you.
- Hold your fire.
Baker and Leon
could still be out there.
Pussies.
Holy shit.
Elephants.
They're fucking huge.
Sarge. Sarge!
I don't like this.
We shouldn't fucking be here.
This, this doesn't feel right.
I'm telling you,
something's not right.
This is what we do, Leon.
I picked you for a reason, man.
-Hmm.
-All right.
Rockslide.
It's asleep.
God bless--
Sir, what do we do?
-Run!
-Fuck!
Go!
Move it, move it!
Leon, come on!
Up here!
Down.
What the fuck was that?
- Fuck, man!
- Fuck this.
-Fucking dinosaurs--
-The fucking Flintstones, man.
This is, this is
fucking bullshit.
I didn't sign on
to kill fucking dinosaurs.
We gotta just keep
our shit together.
Best thing is to find
Baker and Leon
and get the fuck out
of Dodge ASAP.
Find Baker and Leon?
That's fucking bullshit, man.
I ain't going back into that
fucking cave of horrors
for no one or nothin'!
We gotta call
for emergency extraction
right fucking now!
Except Leon
was humping the radio.
-Fuck!
-Well, we ain't nothing
but sitting bait here.
-Let's move!
-Which way?
Towards whatever's making
- all that goddamn noise.
- Move!
Towards it?
- Take point.
- Come on, move!
Fuck!
Oh, fuck.
There's a river
around here somewhere.
I saw it on the map.
If we keep heading down,
-we'll hit it.
-Can it swim?
Gotta get there first.
Find cover.
-Come on!
-Fuck!
Over here, the tree!
Come on, move! Get down!
What are you doing?
Go! Go, go, go!
Come on, let's go!
Let's go!
Fuck.
You airborne qualified, Leon?
What?
Leon!
Leon. Leon!
Fuck!
Leon!
Stay with me, brother.
Stay with me, Leon!
Of course you can swim.
Hey. Hey! Over here!
Hey!
Follow me.
-Leon. Fuck.
-Your friend, is he alive?
Come on, Leon.
Wake up, brother! Wake up.
Get it out. Get it all out.
-Welcome back, brother.
-American?
Yeah, we're American.
Who the fuck is this?
My name is Sofia Wagner,
the woman who just
saved your lives,
thank you very much.
I have a place
over that way, my lab.
We should go there quickly.
We'll be safe there from the rex
and the flock of deinonychus.
-We should move.
-Rex?
As in, tyrannosaurus rex?
How are you even here
if you don't know what that was?
That's the mother tyrannosaur
across the river.
They mate for life,
with the mother
raising the chicks
and the father hunting.
Without the father,
the mother will be forced
to take chicks
on the hunt with her.
The father will do
whatever it takes
to get back
to his territory and family.
We should be safe for now.
Listen, lady.
We're a recon team, seven men.
Got separated when we ran
into those fucking things.
We're not going anywhere else
until I find my team.
If your men are
on the other side of the river,
then they're likely
already dead.
You can take it from me,
and I'm never wrong. This way.
Or you can stay and die,
your choice.
Get up.
Guess it don't matter, X.
Where we headed?
We go northeast
until we hit the blue line.
Looks like a klick or less.
Them notes we found
had it marked
as Research Station Four.
- And what about, uh,
Sergeant Baker and Leon?
Baker got the same map.
If they're still alive,
they'll head
in the same direction.
Fucking Jericho.
He had to know something
like this was out here, right?
I doubt it, man. Uh, you know,
if they knew there were
dinosaurs out here,
he'd send an Arc Light strike
and turn this whole thing
into a goddamn parking lot.
I mean, he's a--
he's an evil prick,
but he's not stupid.
Except we're north of the Z.
You think Washington
would strike up here
on some intel of dinosaurs?
Think he'd think
that's as crazy as me.
You doin' all right, man?
Yeah, too much goin' on
to hear anything else.
Well, that's good.
Quiet down.
There's still NVA out here.
Fuckin' doubt that, man.
There were gooks out here.
It is fuckin' conch snacks now.
Goddammit, look
at all this dino shit.
That's Eli's.
Welcome to my home, gentlemen.
My home away from home
for one year,
seven months, 11 days.
Research Station Four.
Very good.
There were more like us.
American soldiers.
-Green Berets.
-Green Berets?
What is this?
- It's the best men we have.
-Then they're probably dead.
It's all that happens
in this valley, death.
You survived.
Call me the lucky one.
Don't worry, this is
the safest place to be
in the valley.
Steel-reinforced concrete,
very thick walls,
four stories high on one side.
So now, you explain to me
why you are here.
- I think you're the one
with some explaining to do.
What is she doing?
Medicating.
What the fuck is she
putting in her arm?
Jesus fucking Christ! Sarge!
What the fuck is going on?
What are you doing here?
Hmm?
What is the purpose
of this facility,
and why the fuck
are there dinosaurs outside?
Oh, my God.
It is so great
to hear voices again.
I've been alone for so long.
Why? What happened?
General Borodin happened.
He killed everyone
who knew about this place.
Painted the walls
with their brains.
If everyone else is dead,
then what are you
still doing here?
I've been starving, hiding,
surviving with nothing else
to do but medicate.
You understand, don't you?
Leon, go see if you can get
a radio signal.
Now!
Hmm.
How very Chekhov, Sergeant.
I saved your life.
Now, I wouldn't have needed
saving if it wasn't
for the supposedly
extinct dinosaurs.
Charlie Oscar Six,
this is Vulture Bravo Two. Over.
And I'm gonna bet
my old friend Viktor Charlie
- had nothing to do with that.
- Charlie Oscar Six,
-this is
Vulture Bravo Two. Over.
-But you,
mysterious Russian
Little Miss Morphine,
you seem pretty good for it.
Oh, I am very good for it.
There it is.
Charlie Oscar Six,
this is Vulture Bravo Two. Over.
Borodin, what's his deal?
Why kill everyone?
It is the Russian way to protect
what he is doing here.
- And that is?
- The collider.
The hell is that?
Oh.
Oh, I don't think I want
to play this game, Sergeant.
Information is
the greatest commodity in war,
-and I can see
you've been deprived of it.
-Mm.
- Why don't I ask you
20 questions
and see if you know
what the fuck
you are even doing here?
Sergeant.
I got the colonel.
- Standby
for Vulture Bravo Actual.
Over.
Charlie Oscar Vulture.
- This is Six.
- Vulture, send SITREP.
Requesting immediate Dust Off.
We've come under heavy fire
and mission is compromised.
I say again,
immediate Dust Off. Over.
Is the mission complete,
Sergeant Baker?
Six...
I'm gonna get this out
in plain language.
I don't know what
you really sent us
out here to find,
but we found
a fuck load more than
just some missing Green Berets.
There's some kind of
crazy Russian experiment
that's been going on out here.
Why don't you ask higher
about a general named Borodin?
Somehow, his team have brought
dinosaurs back to life,
and it was dinosaurs
that ate your Snakebite team.
Now, since we inserted,
we've been attacked
by all kinds of
prehistoric beasts,
all of them hungry, pissed off,
and chomping at the bit
for their little piece
of the American pie.
We need an emergency extract
from this fucking zoo,
and that's not an option!
Hey, l-- li-- listen to me,
Sergeant Baker.
Take a fucking breath,
all right?
And give me your position.
That's all I'm asking.
Fucking listen to me.
Five of my men are missing.
I'm gonna go find them,
dead or alive.
When I do,
I'll send a POS REP...
...and we'll be bringing with us
one female Russian survivor.
- If you want her
to spell it out for you,
have the birds ready.
You think you can blackmail me,
you little son of a bitch?
You don't know, all right?
You've got one piece
in the puzzle, that's all.
If you want
that puzzle piece, Colonel,
then you will send evac.
LZ marked by flares by 22:00.
Sun's setting, Colonel. Out.
Listen--
I think they're
fucking delirious,
you hear-- did you hear that?
Goddamn dinosaurs,
losing their fucking minds,
-eating the fucking mushrooms.
-Yeah, sounds
just about right, Colonel.
I'll fucking rip his skin off
and make ponchos out of him.
Pawns, just pawns.
You are all just pawns
like I was.
That's my men
you're talking about,
and they're out there, lost!
Yeah, I know
where I would rather be.
You know all about these things.
How they operate
and where they're likely to be.
See, you're on point, lady.
Get your ass up.
Pawns don't got a choice.
Say again, over.
Any reason to believe
what he said?
I don't think so, Colonel.
I mean, we're out here
looking for some kinda
nuclear reactor or collider
that might be capable
of producing weapons-grade
nuke materials,
but... I mean,
million-year-old dinosaurs?
Yeah, but hold on, but he--
Baker's not crazy, all right?
So, w-- why would he lie to us?
Anything's possible
when you start fucking around
with nuclear materials.
Yeah. Well,
we damn well better find out.
Check with your spook sources
about this Borodin character,
all right?
-I'll get right on it, sir.
-Let's go. Come on. Fuck off.
Look!
They're harmless.
Yes, Sergeant?
We were attacked last night.
Little boys will play
as soldiers.
I ain't playing. I'm asking
your professional opinion.
Then, as professional courtesy,
I will answer.
It was fast and it was strong.
And it ambushed me clean.
It was covered in feathers,
I think.
It was at least
eight to ten feet tall.
Raptors, big ones.
A lot bigger
than specimens I've seen
for velociraptor or deinonychus.
I've counted six big ones
in the valley.
The most intelligent
of these monsters.
-Lady knows her stuff.
-Thank you.
It's what she's not telling us,
that I don't trust.
Trust is earned, Sergeant.
So far, I've saved your skins
and given you shelter.
Keep walking.
Site Three is about
a klick up ahead.
Then we go west to Site Four.
Figure if Baker and Leon
are still alive,
they'll head there.
Another mile to go, guys.
Thank God.
It's fucking hot. Fuck! Fuck!
Yeah, the heat,
that's the problem here.
Oh, fuck you, man.
It's hotter than Miss July.
Baking me a cake
in the middle of a--
Oh, shit!
Southside left!
- Southside left!
- Fuck!
- Jesus!
-  -What the fuck is happening?
Kill them all! No prisoners!
Keyes!
Fuck!
- Can't see 'em!
- Me neither.
- Oh, shit.
- Need to know
how many and where.
What in hell is that?
That's AKs and M16s.
Sounds like our guys
in a firefight.
-With who?
-Let's go find out.
- Need to know how many and where!
-  -Just came out
of nowhere!
- Logan!
- I got him!
Can't see shit.
- Where are they?
- Logan, goddammit,
you can kiss Keyes later--
Get to work, man. You good?
Keep firing!
-Motherfucker, are you good?
-Almost blew my cock off.
- Ah, yeah.
It's just circumcised, bro.
Yeah.
- Cease fire, cease fire!
- Cease fire!
- Oh, it's bad.
- You good?
I gotta put an--
no, it's not bad.
- God--
- You gotta just lay down.
Deep breaths.
...fucking damn it!
Fuck.
Oh, they've got air support now.
That's, that's good.
Grab Keyes.
Stay low and head for the trees.
Gotta move on.
Fucking monster.
- Oh, fuck. Fuck that, man.
- Keep moving!
Don't look back.
Don't look back, man.
Keep moving.
No, no, no.
No, no, no. Keep moving.
Let's go. Come on.
Run, Sergei!
Run!
Fire!
Run, Sergei!
Only two of you now, huh?
Why you run away? Hmm?
What in hell are those things?
You just left us there.
My job is to find GI,
not babysit you.
Let's go, let's go!
Let's go!
Easy, easy.
- We gotta get moving, Keyes.
- Jesus.
You good to go?
- You okay?
- I've been shot, man,
in dinosaur Vietnam.
About 12,000 miles
and a million fucking years
from being okay.
Oh, you're gonna be okay, man.
God fucking Jesus!
Oh!
Logan, when you're done
patching him up,
- take point and keep us in the trees.
-  -Yeah.
- Through and through, Keyes.
- Oh, fucking Jesus!
-Fucking-- take it easy.
-Can these things smell blood?
- Eat shit.
- Zip it, Eli.
Check fire, Vulture.
I'm coming through with Leon
and a hitchhiker.
Ah, damn, Baker!
-Glad to see you alive
and kicking, man!
-Who's the chick?
SITREP, who's shooting at you?
What the fuck happened to Keyes?
I don't know and I have no idea.
Goddamn flappy fucking big bird
dinosaurs cleaned 'em up.
Took a round in Keyes' thigh.
He won't be easy to move now.
- Who's this?
- Yeah.
Just someone who can help.
Listen, evac is inbound
and Sofia here
has a safe place to wait it out.
Let's get him patched up
and move.
And the skirt?
She knows what's going on?
She knows more than we do.
She's our ticket outta here.
I prefer
to think of you as my ride.
Russians? Our ticket home
is a fucking Russian?
I'm born in East Berlin,
if that makes you
feel any better.
It doesn't. No fucking way,
not after
what we've been through.
So those guys out there
are fucking Russians
shooting at us? Not MVA?
Yeah, and there's likely
more of them out here.
Jesus.
Whatever these things are,
they were stalking us
last night.
Sofia, ideas?
Deinonychus.
Pack hunters. They like to--
half the pack on the ground
and the other half
in the treetops.
Watch for their sickle claws
on each toe.
What is she,
like a dinosaur freak?
A dinosaur super freak,
you stupid redneck
-fascist ass wipe.
-Jesus fucking Christ, lady,
I was just asking, is all.
Enough.
Fire on anything that moves.
Watch out! Watch out!
- Xavier!
- On your right!
They're in the trees, man!
- Fuck you!
- Fuck you! Fuck you!
How many
of these things are there?
One shot, one kill!
Oh, fuck!
Look out, look out!
Take that.
Logan!
-Logan!
-Cease fire! Cease fire!
It got Keyes!
-Logan! Logan!
-Wait!
-You have to run fast
to catch him!
-They will drag him
until they feel it's safe!
-Fuck.
-Let's get after him. Go!
-Go, go, go.
Baker!
Fuck-- get the fuck off me,
you little shit!
Get the fuck off me. Logan!
Fuck off!
Where the fuck are you,
guys? Fuck!
You goddamn fucking
murderous turkeys.
You coming at me?
You're gonna need fries
and fucking gravy.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
That's what
I fucking thought.
Ugh, fuck.
It's so fucking hot.
Okay.
Keyes!
I swear I heard him.
- Keyes!
Keyes!
Oh!
- Light it up!
- Oh, shit!
- Cease fire!
Keyes! Oh, shit!
- Keyes!
- There he is!
-Oh, shit!
-Fucking help me here.
-Give me, give me--
-Miller, get in here!
I'm on it, Sarge!
-Eli, stand watch. Keep it on.
-Put pressure bandage--
Keep pressure on that.
Eli, stand watch.
- They tore
his fucking guts out, Sarge.
- Oh, Jesus! Oh, fuckin--
Looks like he's been--
he's been run through
a fucking meat grinder.
Yeah, I know.
Miller, Miller.
Get that stretcher out.
- Leon!
- Yeah.
Grab a couple of poles
to carry him back
to the research station
for evac.
Leave him. Those big raptors
will come back
with their full pack of six,
and when that happens,
we'll all die.
-If we leave him, we might
have chance of survival--
-I don't give two fucks
- how bad he's cut up.
- He goes with us.
- Vultures,
sun sets in half hour.
I do not wanna be
stumbling around in the dark
with Marlboro Man passed out
on the stretcher.
- Rig him in there
and let's roll.
- Here. You can have some weight.
- Leon!
- ...God! Oh, my God!
- More bandages,
more bandages.
Stay on that.
-You're in the best
of hands, Keyes.
-Fuckin' hurts--
- What you doing this
twice for in one day, man?
- Oh, my God.
Best of hands, brother.
Best of hands.
- Hurry up!
-  -Move, move, move, move, move, Logan!
Move, Logan! Move, Logan!
- Get the door! Come on!
- ...at the door!
- Got it.
- Move.
On the table! On the table!
Lay him down, lay him down!
Hey, Keyes, Keyes,
look at me. Look at me.
- Get on that--
- You're okay.
- Fuck. Fuck, fuck,
fuck, fuck, fuck.
- Keep the pressure
on it.
I've got the light!
- Come on, Keyes--
- Miller, Eli.
Take perimeter.
Do an ammo count,
premise review.
- On it, Sarge.
- Look at me, Keyes.
- You'll be okay, Keyes.
- Leon!
- Yeah.
- Cover for the sergeant.
I'm on it.
- Okay, okay--
- Sarge...
Breathe, breathe, Keyes.
- ...is there
anything else we can do for him?
He ain't gonna make it
much longer, Sarge.
He's bleeding bad.
Maybe change the dressings,
but I-- I-- I don't know--
Get some morphine into him
and see what we can do
to stop the bleeding.
Let's go.
You gotta get
that morphine in right now.
- Keyes, Keyes!
- I got-- I got th--
Keep your eyes on me.
Eyes on me.
Come on-- I'm coming,
Keyes, I'm coming in.
- I need you to calm down--
- Okay, ready?
- Keyes--
- Here we go!
We got any more?
- Where's the other one?
-  -Get the morphine into him!
- Where the fuck
is the other one?
Where's the second morphine?
Here we go.
-Son of a bitch.
-...feel that?
You feel that, man?
-Keyes. Hey, listen to me.
Take a deep breath.
-There you go--
Can you breathe?
That's good, that's better.
That's good, man.
- I need you
to stay with me, man.
Hey. Hey, look at me.
Just couldn't help yourself,
could you?
I did nothing to stop this.
What?
The dinosaurs.
We could've stopped it.
It was just accident.
An accident?
Why didn't you say this before?
I wanted to,
but you are--
-What?
-You are the enemy.
Lady, I'm not the one
trying to shoot you or eat you.
I know, I know. I see that now.
You are good men.
You are all good men...
...but I needed
more than good men.
I needed someone who could stop
what is happening
in this valley.
Baker, we need more eyes
on the perimeter.
- Leon, help the Sarge.
- Yes, Sarge.
Leon, cover that window.
Listen. My mission is
to get my men home,
not fight dinosaurs.
There won't be a home
if Borodin isn't stopped.
Look out there!
Sofia, what exactly
was going on here?
It's all right. We got you.
Put pressure...
My husband was
nuclear research scientist.
My field is paleontology.
We were sent here
by Soviet madman Borodin
to do what was
strictly research.
Nobody conducts
scientific research
in the middle of a jungle
in the middle of a war.
Even Russia didn't want
his research on home ground.
When you are ordered
to do something
by a man like Borodin,
you do it or you die!
When we arrived, this collider
had already been tested.
We were told that
he was working on wormholes
so that Soviet Union
could crush America,
send tanks
onto White House lawn.
But my husband said
that Borodin...
...cut corners, you would say.
Particles did not collide
and some elements slingshot
beyond speed of light.
Wormhole... opened in the past
and dinosaurs walked through.
I came with my husband
because of my knowledge.
Best team.
Where's your husband now?
I was out
studying the herbivores
that came through.
Borodin wanted to... see
if he could make use
of the dinosaurs.
- I heard cracking of machine guns and came home...
-  to find whole team dead.
Darling husband included.
And so I've sat here,
doing the only thing I can
to ease the pain.
We should have stopped him.
He just left his mess of lizards
and moved on to rebuild
another collider.
He won't stop.
Look at where
playing God got us.
Hmm?
I know.
You know where this
rebuilt collider is?
They entered
a river in the mountains.
He thinks I'm dead,
but I know about it.
You have to help me
make this right
or more people
will suffer the consequence.
- How we looking?
- Uh, not good.
- It's okay.
It's okay, man. It's okay.
- It's all right.
- I wanna go home.
We're gonna get you
back home, man.
What you gonna tell
your mama about this?
- You good?
- Yeah.
Yeah, these things
just freak me out, man.
You can handle it.
Yeah.
I'd handle it better
if I had me a drink.
Should've brought along
that lucky flask.
Baker catches you
with that flask in the field,
he's gonna jam it up your ass.
That little flask
saved my ass one time.
When you and I were
running for CAV,
before we went to the LURPs...
...we're clearing out
this little, uh,
this little
piss ant village...
...Charlie jumped out
from behind a pile of bamboo
and just fucking nailed me
with one round from his SKS.
The round hit the flask
in my pocket, flattened it,
but all I got was
knocked in my ass.
If it hadn't been
for that flask in my pocket...
- That was God.
- Mm.
But I remember well.
That what happened after that...
...never gonna forget
those four people.
Gonna take more
than a whisky flask
-to save your ass this time.
-Yeah.
Gonna take more than God
to save yours.
Where is he?
He's not there.
You're here. They're here.
That's what I believe in.
You know why I carry
these beads every day?
I'm asking those people
we killed for forgiveness.
Nah, the fuckings--
Don't listen to me, man.
- I'm just fucked up.
-  -Hey, you still with me, Keyes?
- Keyes, wake up!
- What?
Keyes is gonna
fucking die for sure
if we don't get him
outta here, man.
He's gonna make it.
Hey, Sarge, we got movement.
Shit. Need more time.
What's the ETA
on those choppers?
Last ETA was about an hour.
Fucking rotor heads
don't like flying at night.
- Fuck.
- Can we hold for an hour?
They still out there,
just pacing the perimeter.
Logan, need you out here.
You're gonna get
to the other side of this,
-you're gonna be fine.
-Go. I got him.
- Hang in there. I'll be back.
- Grab your left.
-What's going on?
-Let me know when you got
a target you can shoot.
He's just walking around.
You got a shot?
You want me to give away
our position?
They already know we're here.
-Lost it.
-Stay on it.
-Pretty smart for a bird.
-Way too smart for a bird.
Listen, man, I found out
some shit talking to the woman.
- Oh, shit,
they're inside!
There's a bird!
Get on it. Left, left.
Shit, it's here!
Go, go!
Miller!
- Spread out!
- Yeah! Let's go!
Left!
- Motherfucker!
-  -Here, here, here, here!
Cease fire!
Everyone, full mag.
It's probing us,
goddamn it, it's probing us.
Eyes on, eyes on.
Quick as you can.
- The fuck is that?
- Got it.
Fuck!
On your left! Whoa!
Get out!
- Fall back! Fall back!
- Fall back!
Go, go, go, go! Go, go, go, go!
Leon, move!
There are six in the flock
that came through!
They will find a way!
They always find a way!
Hey, don't worry about it.
Our chopper's
on its way, okay?
Shit. Up top!
- Up, up!
- Up top!
Son of a bitch!
He won't survive an hour!
Your men still die!
-What would you have me do?
-There's a boat
on the docks outside.
-There's a boat there?
-Yes, it needs fixing,
that is not my skill.
Your men can.
Look, there's a escape hole
over there, the vents.
-Fuck--
-Trust me!
Open it. Everybody, we're
moving out through the vent!
-Leon, give Sofia a hand.
-Okay, we're gonna do
a new LZ, Keyes, okay?
- We're gonna move you to--
- I can't, I can't.
- Move, Keyes. Grab a leg.
- Put me in the corner.
- Huh?
- Corner!
-Put me in the fucking corner.
-He wants to go in the corner.
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, we--
-He wants to go.
-We--
-It's his decision.
-...man.
-We're not doing--
-Three, two, one.
Move it!
- What are we doing?
-  -We need to open this vent.
God be with you, Keyes.
- God be--
- Go, go, go, go.
Sergeant!
-Give me a grenade.
-I gotcha, I gotcha.
-I got you. I got you.
-Fuck no, man. Don't do this.
- Give me a fucking grenade and go.
-  -I got you.
Let's go, let's go!
Go!
-Man--
-Oh, my God.
- Baker.
-You're not going anywhere humping a fucking casualty.
Be quick!
I can't do this
without you, man.
-Yeah, you can--
-I can't.
-The voices in my head--
-...you fucking can!
You fucking listen to me.
Th-- they're trying to hurt you.
- You want a cigarette?
- Yeah.
Okay. Let's go.
Here you go. Enjoy that. Okay.
Logan!
You're a goddamn hero, man.
G-- go. F-- fucking go.
Fucking go, man!
Come get some,
you Foghorn Leghorn
motherfuckers.
All right. Let's get
this old lady started.
The back. The back.
Doesn't seem right,
leaving Keyes behind
with those lizard birds.
He's in God's good hands, man.
What's going on, man?
We heading north, Sarge?
Yeah, that's right.
Would you mind telling me why?
Vultures, let's bring it in.
Listen, um...
...Keyes was
a tough one to lose,
particularly knowing now
that we were sent here
on a bullshit mission.
But here we are,
in the deepest of shit.
Last comms with command said
they were sending chopper
as soon as we sent them
a POS REP for the extract.
We got maybe one shot at that
with what little juice we have
left in our last radio battery.
That's one thing.
The other just might be
more important.
We stumbled
on some real nasty stuff.
Some Soviet shithead,
name of Borodin,
has been brewing
out here in the jungle.
It's a end-of-the-world shit,
and we just can't leave it.
Fuck yeah, we can!
We can do that in a heartbeat.
-End-of-the-world shit's
not our deal.
-The Sarge made the call, Eli,
-we're already on the way.
-How the hell can
some dipshit Russian dude
destroy the whole fucking world?
You've all seen
what could happen,
and that was accident!
Again, that is not
our fucking business, Sarge.
Th-- this is us
in the chain of command.
Here's where
end-of-the-world shit
gets sorted out.
That's presidents
and generals shit.
-That's Jericho level.
-Do you trust Jericho, Eli?
Do you trust him?
Maybe not Jericho, Sarge, but--
Nobody, Miller.
No god, no country,
no man should have
this fucking power!
This fucking thing
will make hydrogen bombs
look like Eli lighting
one of his farts.
I-- I do have some pretty
powerful farts, Sarge.
Shut the fuck up, man.
This is worse.
-No man should have that power.
-Hmm. Damn straight.
Let's keep this
simple as possible,
given the circumstances.
We find it, tag it,
send in all the bombers we have.
No. No!
No, you can't do that.
You can't d--
Oh, fu-- fuck.
Sarge, take the wheel.
- What's wrong with her?
- She's dope sick.
Oh, good. We're following
a junkie in to hell.
I said it right from the start,
there are monsters out here.
Thinking I'm crazy, don't you?
Y'all think I'm crazy,
but I knew, I told you all.
You fucking Baker, new kid,
all of you, told you.
- Listen, focus on your job.
What was that?
That was just the father Rex.
Still looking for his family.
- You know that thing can swim.
- It's just animals.
We stay away from it,
it'll be fine.
What did you mean before,
that I can't do that?
- Collider is unstable.
- Right.
It throws off wormholes
like sparks.
Space and time are
same thing to wormhole.
You drop bombs on that,
you will be dropping bombs
all over the world instantly.
You ever say something
that doesn't take
a bad situation
and make it worse?
I'm Russian and you ask me this.
So, what do we do?
You must go in and pull plug.
Do what?
-Literally, pull plug.
-And what if you're wrong?
I am never wrong.
Sarge, situation up here.
-What do you got?
-Over there.
It's just animals grazing.
We stay away from them,
we'll be fine.
Think they're harmless?
Oh, fuck. Shit!
We stay the course, Xavier.
-Hey, hey, put that down!
-No, I need it!
-Fucking drop it. Fucking drop--
-I need it, give it to me!
- Let go of that, lady!
- I need the morphine.
Get on that.
The fuck was that?
- You need to get
your shit together
'cause we're doing
what you want.
And we're probably all gonna die
screaming because of it.
Can we talk about that
screaming and dying bit?
Hey, hey, focus.
What was that?
Spinosaurus.
Uh, we have to, to hurry.
You need me to tie her up?
Smoke these. Hmm?
Cope, the American way.
- Yeah.
- No.
I think she's gonna be
just fine.
Right?
-Son of a bitch, stay on that.
-What, they can
fucking swim now?
Should've seen 'em fucking fly.
Breathe. Relax.
Aim. Squeeze.
Relax. Aim. Squeeze.
Logan, shut it down.
Squeeze.
I hate 'em.
Logan, it's okay. Stand down.
Okay.
I'll shut it down.
I'll sh-- I'll shut it down.
Yeah. You can all go.
I am gonna go.
- I-- -Hey, hey, hey, hey.
-  Hey, dude.
You t-- you told me
to shut it down.
-Yeah, it's not
your time, brother.
-I was just--
-Hey. It's not your time.
-What?
-No? Are you sure?
-No. Yeah. I need ya.
-I feel...
-We need you.
...I can't feel anything.
I can't feel anything anymore.
-Okay. Yeah.
-Huh?
Yeah.
I can do this.
Yeah, I know.
-I know.
-Yeah. I'm good.
Make it stop.
Stay hydrated.
Think the sergeant likes her?
The drug
must leave your system--
The sergeant's
just doing his job.
...can guarantee you,
dinosaurs have ventured
into Cambodia. In months,
they could be in Burma,
in China, in India.
Once they run out of food
in jungle,
where do you think
they're going to go to eat?
We'll stop them.
- Huh.
- You ready for this?
Face my past?
Not really.
Just smile, pull the trigger,
the problem goes away.
It's also the American way.
Fuck.
This looks painfully familiar.
Should've stayed
on the damn boat.
You sure it's this way, comrade?
It's this way.
- We push through.
-  -Oh, God, I hate doing that.
- Oh!
- Sarge! Oh, fuck!
Behind you!
They're fuckin' everywhere.
Fuck off me!
- Come and get me!
Come and get me!
- Logan!
- Guys, we gotta move!
- Take the squad,
I'll go after Logan.
Come on!
Come and get me!
Fuck. Shit.
I'm done with all you fuckers!
Get out of my head
with this shit...
Fuck.
You're a goddamn hero, man.
Thank you, Keyes.
- We have a visual
on the compound.
Standby to copy. Grid 197545.
-How copy? Over.
-Solid copy.
Say ETA for the extract.
Uh, 30 mikes.
Uh, tell the pilots
to look for a big ass fire
and a pile of rubble
at the grid I just sent.
Negative, Vulture.
That is now
a national security site.
Do not damage or approach it
in any way.
All right? You know
who you're dealing with?
I ain't McNeil, all right?
Yo-- you understand
what I'm saying, Vulture?
I'm losing the radio, Six.
I copied,
approach and destroy the site.
We'll be standing by
for inbound choppers
and a side of fries.
Vulture out.
Don't get fucking cute
with me. Hey!
Hey!
I will personally crucify
that motherfucker.
You might wanna think
that over, Colonel.
A man who saves the world
from a swarm of dinosaurs
-might just be a hero
to some folks.
-Not if anyone
hears about it, all right?
Fuck, I need, I need,
uh, escorts fueled up
and armed to the fucking teeth,
all right?
We're gonna show 'em
what millions of years
of evolution accomplishes.
Might be better
that site get destroyed
than let that stuff fall
into any hands.
-Ours or theirs.
-Yeah, well, you pussies
better get fueled up
and get ready.
Leon, you still got
the demo kits?
-Yes, sir.
-Outstanding.
Rig at least three full charges
at the base of the site.
Dig 'em in. I wanna see
that fucking structure collapse
- when they blow. Miller, Eli.
- Sir.
Find and rig
any shipments outside.
And Xavier, find high ground.
Cover me when I move inside
and pull the plug.
Plug, Sarge?
You even know where to look?
I know. I will go
with Sergeant Baker.
Drop pack, let's go.
Miller.
Grenade.
You reckon the colonel's
really gonna send the choppers?
You just pissed him off enough
to make him forget about it.
- He'll send them.
He owes me that much.
Sarge, who is McNeil?
McNeil was the original
leader of Vulture Squad.
Picked me fresh out of ROTC.
-And he was everything
a leader should be.
-What happened to him, Sarge?
Long story short,
he got fucked over by Jericho.
And he took the fall
on a failed airstrike mission.
We--
we lost most of the unit.
McNeil got a discharge
and I wound up in hospital
with a lot of dead brothers
on my conscience.
And shit, I got
a lot of live ones too.
I don't know about you,
Vultures, ma'am,
but I'm about ready
to bring it all on home.
-Cool.
-Let's get to work.
Good fucking shit.
The dogs of war,
you have returned just in time.
-One more test run tonight.
-Your big machine is in there?
It is.
What's it do?
I wouldn't expect you
to understand.
So, my dealings with you...
...all done?
Just so, my dear.
...and I wish you good luck
in striking the Yankees
out of the skies
over your homeland.
You have turned my homeland
into dinner for monsters.
-That's Borodin.
-I know those men.
Did you know
of the monsters out there?
Mere beasts, not monsters!
-Beasts of burden...
-They must be the men
who ambushed your team.
And now they're questioning
their allegiance.
Where are Americans?
Dead by now.
Nothing can survive out there.
Trying to talk Borodin
into more caution,
saying dinosaurs might wind up
in the Red Square.
Is there any chance he'll stop?
Nyet. Borodin used them
like he used me.
The only monsters
I released in this valley
are men like you.
You were told to fetch
and you happily went
out there looking to kill.
You madman!
Do it.
You are a threat to history.
To the people.
We need to find a way in there.
Come on.
With me! Now!
Americans.
General, I found this one
sniffing around the camp.
There was another one,
but he hid in the trees.
What is this thing, General?
You fool.
Don't you know
what you have done?
Shut the fuck up.
-Okay.
-I'm the one that helped
Borodin with dinosaurs.
This all needs to end
or he will destroy everything.
The asshole needs to be stopped.
Do you wanna join us?
-Da. We will.
-Da.
- We got incoming.
- Incoming?
Yeah, big incoming.
What is this thing, General?
Get rid of it.
Don't shoot.
Go! Get inside!
Let's go.
Target on the move.
...out of my way!
Okay, let's move.
Fuck, fuck.
You sure
about this, Sarge?
This way! This way!
Back, back, back, back!
-Go! Go, go!
-Go, go, go!
Move, move!
Follow me. Sergeant!
- Here, here.
- Inside, inside, inside!
We go now!
Wire the collider.
Do not wait for my command.
Miller!
Miller, where are you?
Demon!
You demon!
American demon!
You kill my family!
Oh, shit.
Miller!
- Anyone else wanna be a hero?
- Hands up!
'Cause this will be
a real quick conversation.
The collider is still charging,
could go off any minute.
Get on it.
Leon, take the Russkies.
Keep planting the C4
and rig whatever else you can.
-Leave nothing behind.
-Let's go.
Please, forgive me.
No forgiveness!
Miller!
- You will die,
but we will rebuild!
God, forgive me.
God, forgive me!
No!
Miller!
- Hey! I thought
all you had to do
was pull the plug.
It's too late.
It's set to automatic discharge.
I have to take console apart
and do a rewiring.
-How long is that gonna take?
-F-- a few minutes. Then finish.
-Focus.
-Sofia.
-Don't worry.
Husband taught me fail-safes
and I'm never wrong.
Oh, I-- I hope.
Vulture One, Vulture One.
Father Vulture. How copy, over.
Vulture, can you hear me?
This is Six.
Listen to me, all right?
I want that compound
secured and untouched.
You understand me? Hello.
Mother fuck-- Hello!
Goddammit! What the fuck?
All this fucking work
for nothing.
You don't understand me!
You gotta secure the perimeter,
you fucks!
Fuck!
Eli coming through!
Xavier too!
Where's Miller?
Miller's dead, man.
Leon standing by
with the last demo charge.
-Do you want him to blow it?
-You don't want to do that.
Oh, you don't know me at all.
Think about what you could do
with all this power
and my knowledge. Hmm?
I've seen enough of your power
and your knowledge.
- Sofia.
-
I guess all is fair
in love and war.
Oh.
You cannot trust this woman.
She is fucking traitor.
Oh, fuck.
Your husband,
he cry like baby.
Do it.
They were all better men
than you.
- Is it done?
- I've done it.
Fuck's going on?
Baker, need you here!
Son of a bitch.
Oh, fuck.
You said there were only
six of them that came through.
Da, depending if Keyes
killed them on his way out.
Maybe I could have been wrong.
What the fuck?
-Holy shit!
-We need to blow
this shit up now.
Gotta get outta here first!
Sarge, pop smoke
and get everyone top side.
Top side? This is the only exit.
No, there is other side
of collider.
Pop smoke. Eli.
-Leon, C4 good to go?
-Oh, yeah, good to go.
Rig the blow.
-Frag out.
-Frag out!
Fall back.
Fall back!
Fall back! Go, go, go!
Run, Sergei!
Claymore! Set up!
Setting, Sarge!
Come on. Fire.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Okay. Uh.
- Fresh mags.
- Ready.
You're a vulture now.
Where the fuck are we going?
That way.
Pick it up, pick it up!
Move, move! Let's go!
Keep going, keep going!
Next one.
- Go! Go!
- Go, go, go.
Move, move. Go, go, go, go.
Holy shit!
Help me!
- Eli!
- Help me, God!
Don't leave me.
Come on buddy.
Don't let me dying, Sarge.
- Let's go!
- Eli!
He's gone! He's gone! Let--
Let-- Let's go! Sergeant!
Now, Leon!
Get up there. Focus!
-You look after her.
You have to--
-No--
Go now.
You're not killing
any more of my men.
Come on! Come on!
Spread out! Spread out!
Let's go, 180.
Let's go! Let's go!
I need a SITREP, Sergeant!
Let's go!
What the hell was that?
Dinosaurs, sir.
Where's Baker?
I wanna see that son of a bitch.
He's not coming!
Open fire!
Eat that!
Incoming.
Stop this fucking shit!
Hang on!
Come on, fuckers.
Keep it coming.
Colonel, we need
to get the fuck out of here!
Load up!
What the hell was
that shit show back there?
We're supposed to seize
the technology, not destroy it.
I guess you got
some explaining to do, sir.
It's all about escalation.
It's not gonna end
with the destruction
of that fucking machine.
No, It won't. Look!
Did you know, Colonel?
Know about all this?
-That's classified.
-Just tell us the fucking truth!
Truth is what I tell you,
all right?
Well, you wanna know
that the war could end
with that down there?
That the world could end?
Colonel! You need to hear this!
We're getting overrun here.
It looks like
giant goddamn lizards.
What the hell's going on?
Hurry up let's move!
Go, go, go! Come on! Let's go!
Hey, check this out--
Hey, get over here!
Check this out!
Holy cow!
Come on, check this out!
Shit.
The president this morning
addressed the press
about the presence of dinosaurs.
That's right. Dinosaurs.
In the South East Asian warzone.