So you call this
punk music?
Oh, my God.
You're a punk.
Huh? I'm not a punk.
Yeah, you're
a fucking punk.
No, I'm not
a fucking punk. I'm a...
I mean,
I don't know what I am, but...
So where are you going?
Um... to the... country
with... Malcolm.
Uh, to a cabin, I guess.
Like, his cabin.
A city subway rat
like you
at a cabin in the woods?
Yeah, it'll be
my first time up there.
Well, fuck.
It's been a while, huh?
Yeah, almost a year.
Wow,
that's gotta be, like,
an unofficial record for you.
No, shut up.
Uh-oh,
better break up.
No, no uh-ohs.
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
So, what are
you wearing?
What does a person wear
to a cabin?
It's, like, buffalo plaid?
He got me a cardigan.
Is it... is it beige?
- It is. It is beige.
- Ugh.
I don't even think I've ever
heard you say "beige" before.
I didn't even think
-you knew the bitch.
-I don't even know the bitch.
So, does he want kids?
I don't... uh, we--
we haven't talked about that.
Don't you think
you should?
Uh, well, you know,
I've never
pictured myself as a mother.
So... are you happy?
Yeah.
And he's
still not hiding
a wife and kids
in the basement?
No. No secret family.
Just... him and...
just the two of us.
Fuck, it is...
it's trippy as shit
talking to you like this.
Call me sometime, okay?
...draw the line.
-Make yourself at home.
-Uh-huh.
Oh!
First things first.
-Your masterpiece.
-Mm-hmm.
Knock yourself out.
Come on. Ooh.
Here we go.
Somebody left you a cake.
Uh, yeah,
the caretaker.
Yeah, it's a bit of a tradition.
Her way of making up
for being so bad
at taking care of the place.
Hey, come take a look!
The crown jewel
of my collection!
-So, what do you think?
-Mm-hmm...
"Mm-hmm"? "Mm-hmm"?
- That's it?
- Mm-hmm...
- It looks good.
- Oh, it's good.
It's good. It's great.
I love it.
-You're good.
-Mm.
Like, really, really good.
You know that?
-Mm-hmm.
-Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm is right.
Oh!
Who lives there?
-Just my cousin, Darren.
-Hm.
Not my family's
proudest contribution
to civilization, but...
he won't bother us.
Good old weird
and cranky recluse,
Cousin Darren?
Actually, he just goes
by regular asshole,
Cousin Darren.
But, uh,
I didn't see his car, so...
Hmm.
I'm gonna start
getting things ready
-for dinner, okay?
-Sounds good.
Ah...
Mm.
Malcolm?
You say something?
No. Nothing.
Oh. Okay.
I'm not a punk.
Not a punk.
No, I don't know
what I am, but...
I thought you'd be happier
seeing your painting up.
You know how I feel about it.
It's decorative,
and that's fine.
No. No, but you made that,
you know?
If I could do what you do,
I don't think
I could stop myself.
I'd just be doing
it all the time,
again and again and again
and again and again.
You--you sound
like that old joke.
What was it?
If men had tits, they'd never
stop playing with them?
Yeah. Yeah, well,
if men had breasts...
Rome definitely would not
have been built in a day.
Oh.
Are you expecting someone?
No.
The caretaker... whatever?
At this hour?
No, uh, no, of course not.
- Very insistent.
- Damn it.
- It's Cousin Darren.
- No.
And his date.
No!
I can see you.
I'm going to let him in.
Okay.
Malcolm!
Hey-hey-hey!
What's going on?
Cousin Darren, Liz.
- Liz, Cousin Darren.
- Hi.
- Yup! Hah.
- And, uh...
Minka!
Minka's a model.
- Minka.
- Oh, cool.
- Yeah.
- Hello, Minka.
Keep trying.
Yeah, yeah. Heh-heh-heh.
But, uh, not a lick
of English, this one.
No speaky.
See?
It's Eastern European.
One of the "ania" ones.
Not Transylvania,
but almost Transylvania.
-Right, babe?
-Wow.
No? Who cares?
She loves,
loves, loves her Molly,
though, doesn't she, babe?
Yeah, yeah.
I wish you'd told me
that you'd be stopping by.
- I'd have made more.
- Oh, no problem.
We already had ours.
Couldn't wait!
Plus, we wouldn't want
to intrude on your special...
night of nights.
Yeah.
Malcolm's a romantic one.
Always has been. The slow one.
Uh...
Cousin, a...
a word in the other room?
Excuse me a minute.
You okay?
Tastes like shit.
Okay!
Time to go.
Upsy-daisies.
Let's let the lovebirds
have their privacy.
She's a keeper, cousin.
Don't wait too long
and let this one get away.
Huh?
Oopsies!
There you go.
You're all right.
Up, up, up.
You're okay. Yeah.
Out the door. Good job.
Night-night time. Come on, now.
You okay?
No. Liz, Liz isn't here anymore.
They had to scoop out her brains
to fill out her tits.
See, I can only apologize
for my cousin.
You know, he was charming once,
but now he's just
a superficial, cowardly asshole.
But...
...not you, right?
You don't go
for the 10 out of 10s
or whatever the fuck...
with a little drawstring
in their back with...
with two or three
pre-recorded sentences.
Oh, where we go?
We go to clubbing now?
Come on, hey.
My cousin, he's a...
he's just an empty box,
you know, with a...
with a stupid fucking bow on it.
And, uh, that box
is gonna stay empty
-unless he's willing to put a...
-But me?
The box that is me
has something in it.
Yeah, it's filled to the rim.
What are you talking about?
That's why I'm in love
with you, Liz.
And, uh...
And even more concerning
is, uh...
I like you.
I really, really...
like you.
It's weird that you paid me
for my painting.
It was for sale.
It had a price tag next to it,
and no little red dot to tell me
that somebody'd gotten
to it first.
And it spoke to me, you know?
It said... "Bring me home."
So I listened,
same as I did when I met you.
Hmm.
We exchanged money
after we exchanged spit
and everything else.
Yeah. It's just money,
Liz, you know?
If it is so upsetting to you,
you know,
you can give it to charity.
No, no, no, no.
I want to keep the money.
Mm!
I want to keep all...
the Westbridge money
so I can throw it back
in your face someday.
-I think I might like that.
-Oh...
Yeah, I bet you would.
Wait.
Just wait.
The cake.
- The cake?!
- Just--you're gonna love it.
Just please, just sit, sit.
Two seconds.
Okay.
The caretaker,
she--she can't keep...
mice out of the walls but, uh...
but she... she makes
a really great cake.
-Mm. I don't like chocolate.
-What? Since when?
Since... forever,
since I was a kid,
since the entire time
we've been together.
Oh, well, shit.
I'm...
I'm an asshole.
I thought all women
liked chocolate.
Classic Westbridge boy.
I guess I got more of my cousin
in me than I thought.
It's really good, though.
So?
Tastes like shit.
Oh...
I hate being outside.
Fuck. I wish for Uber.
Hi?
Oh, fucking you, ass-in-holes!
There you are.
Sorry.
Morning.
You feeling okay?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah. Um...
I got a patient coming out
of a medically induced
coma today,
and, uh...
and I'm just waiting
for somebody to tell me
she's all clear.
Mrs. Portnoy. Yeah.
A darling old gal, and I'm...
I'm pulling for her.
What are you drawing?
Nothing.
Malcolm?
Fuck!
Fuck. Bad--bad--bad news, hon.
What happened?
Uh, Mrs. Portnoy, she's, uh...
She's not waking up. Yeah.
Her kids are there
at the hospital.
Daughter's inconsolable.
Oh, shit!
- Yeah.
- So what?
So I--I gotta--I gotta go.
I gotta go deal with it.
Oh.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm--I'm--I'm...
I'm really sorry.
But duty calls.
Um, you know,
and if--if everything goes
the way these things
normally go...
How do these things normally go?
She'll wake up, you know?
But I'm--I'm not
worried about her.
I'm worried about you.
It's fine.
I think I'll just maybe...
...settle in here.
Okay.
Okay. Uh, the--the--the fridge
is stocked.
There's wine
in the kitchen.
And, uh...
there's good wine
in the basement,
if you feel like celebrating.
When will you be back?
Six.
With traffic,
seven at the latest.
It's fine.
I'm fine.
I can handle myself.
You go. Go fulfill your oath.
I'll just be here,
looking through your drawers.
Okay.
Hello?
I'm spying on
the rich neighbors.
And... you said call, so...
You at your cabin?
Oh, it's not my cabin.
- Not yet.
- Ha-ha.
So, what is it,
like, some fortress, or...
No, hardly.
Privacy's, like,
not really a thing.
The bathroom's the only room
with a door that locks,
and it's all windows
with zero blinds.
Horrifying!
Yeah. Also, I feel
like I took mushrooms.
Well, is that
because you took mushrooms?
And the man
of the house,
what's he up to?
Hello? Liz?
No, I'm here.
Uh, Malcolm went into the city,
so I'm just kind of, like...
snoopin', not snoopin'.
Wait,
he left you alone there?
Yeah. But it's nice, actually.
Oh, Liz.
He didn't want to.
He had to work.
Yeah, he had to work
his wife's pussy.
What the fuck, Mags?
Listen, I'm just
telling it to you straight!
-You know what you are.
-And what am I?
-I don't want to say it.
-Yeah, so don't.
You're
a side piece, Liz.
Cool. Thanks.
Glad I can count on you.
Do you want me
to come get you?
-You don't have a car.
-This isn't
who you're supposed to be,
some kept woman in a house.
Kept? That sucks. Fuck you.
-Fucking hold on a minute--
-No, it's fine. Bye.
Fucking bitch.
Oh, my God!
What?
Oh, Jesus!
How did you get inside?
I am inside now.
So am I.
Yeah...
What's going on?
You know what you are.
Is Darren with you?
You'll wake the children.
Where did you come from?
The distant past.
There.
There is why the children think
you are their mother.
Oh...
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit!
Shit, shit, shit!
Oh!
Okay.
I can see you!
Be a good
little Westbridge boy
and open the door.
What's done
is done, man.
I brought
our traditional libations!
He's not here.
Uh...
What--what was it again?
Was--was it... Linda?
No, uh, Liz, actually.
Where's Malcolm?
Uh, he had to go back
to the city to see a patient.
He'll be back any second.
He left you here alone
on your big weekend?
That's... not good.
Is... Minka with you?
Mind opening the door?
Yeah, uh... I, uh... I...
Maybe you should
come back later.
You caught me in the middle
of a nap, and I--
Yeah, how about you let me
into my own family's home?
Thank you. I'll be quick.
Fuck.
Where did he say he was going?
Uh, to the hospital
to see a patient.
Oh.
And you're just,
uh... hanging out?
Uh, yeah.
You like it out here?
You feeling good? Or...
- Yeah, it's good.
- Uh-huh.
So you had
a nice dinner?
What did you think
of the caretaker's cake?
Um, it was fine.
Yeah?
And, uh,
you feel sleepy?
You said
you were having a nap?
I love naps.
But you know what will
keep this party going?
What?
Scotch!
I'm really not in the mood.
Heh.
Malcolm's right,
you know.
There's something
special about you.
You're not like
all the other girls.
Yep, he does say that.
-One drink?
-Oh...
Come on.
Sure. What the hell?
Uh, you know
where the glasses are?
Mm-hmm.
-Where are you going?
-Uh...
- The bathroom.
- Okay.
Go away!
Shit!
But that's all right.
No need
to call me back, bro.
You've reached
the voice mailbox
of Dr. Malcolm Westbridge.
Um, Malcolm...
Your cousin was here.
He seemed surprised that I was.
Can you just be here already?
Malcolm?
Oh!
Uh...
Okay. There we go.
Hey.
Oh, shit, I'm sorry. Could--
Any chance you're still
willing to come get me?
The fuck?
Heh, I--I--I just need to get
the fuck out of here.
Uh... There's something...
I don't know, this...
There's something wrong.
- Can you get up here?
- Oh... um...
Yeah.
Sure, I guess. Of cour...
...me just...
throw the...
I hate the fucking country.
Oh... you're cutting out?
Huh, what?
Just telling it... straight.
Are you--are you
gonna come get me?
No.
You're the mother.
What the fuck are you
talking about?!
Just tell me
you're coming to get me.
Tell me that you're right now
figuring out a car.
Maggie?
God!
Liz.
I called you a bunch of times.
There were people here.
I'm leaving.
Well, no--what? Uh, people...
Uh, no. What do you mean,
you're leaving?
Hey, what's going on?
Who the fuck was that woman
who just shows up?
A woman, what woman?
An old lady
with a bag on her head?
Is that the...
is that the caretaker?
I don't understand. A--a bag?
She--she put a bag?
It was fucking creepy
and fucked up!
She had a...
a fucking plastic bag
on her face!
Yeah. That sounds awful.
I'm sorry, honey, but can we
please just calm down?
No, no, no, no, no!
Your--your cousin was here, too!
-He just dropped in.
-What?
-Yeah!
-Darren w--?
Yeah, he just, he seemed
pretty fucking surprised
that I was here, too.
What the fuck, Malcolm?!
Is he still here? Darren!
No! I don't know.
He just showed up
and then he left
without saying anything.
He left his watch
in the fucking sink.
Don't ask me!
What? No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Please, please, please, please.
-No, I'm leaving.
-You can't just leave.
I'm leaving. I don't feel well.
I... I... This place isn't...
This place isn't right for me.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Just... Let's just...
Okay? Just a half hour.
I just need a half hour.
I just need a...
I--I--I got to do a few things.
Just... But what can I do?
Tell me what you want me to do.
Go search the house!
Search the house? Okay.
Make sure
that they're... all gone!
Okay. Okay. I'll make sure.
Sure. All right.
Okay, take your coat off.
Please, honey.
My God.
Anybody here?
Hello?
Where are you,
you sneaky bitches?
Anybody here?
-BOO!
-Oh, my God.
What are you holding?
Hmm...
Hmm? Oh, yeah.
Uh...
Oh.
Look what I found.
I'm sorry I left you alone.
- Yeah, you are.
- Mm-hmm.
-You're a dick.
-Yes, I am.
Yep.
Shall we have a glass?
- A glass?
- Yeah.
Come on.
Oh.
Oh, I love watching you smile.
Hmm.
You're a liar.
What?
What are you talking about?
You're
a fucking liar.
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
You said
you'd be back way later.
Oh.
Well, what can I say?
There was no traffic
on the bridge.
How's Mrs. Portnoy?
Who's Mrs. Portnoy?
Oh. Heh.
How terribly cold
the heart of a doctor can be.
How quickly I can
set work aside when...
when I'm--I'm looking
at the woman that I love.
- Hmm.
- Mm.
-She died.
-Oh, no.
Yeah, she died.
She died, um, peacefully.
Mm-hmm.
-Her children were by her side.
-Aww.
I think... I think
that is the... very most that...
-Yeah.
-...any of us can ask for.
-Yeah, that's good.
-Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
- Do you want more?
- Sure.
Ah. Hey, hey!
Where are you going?
Tell me what you want. Tell me
what you want, I'll get it.
- Bathroom.
- Okay.
Well, I can't help you there.
Stupid, stupid, fucking idiot.
You feeling okay?
Hey, just a second.
Please tell me
you're not pregnant.
Uh, no, I'm all good.
Just peeing.
Why don't you
come out of there
so we can talk about this?
Talk about what?
Oh.
It's not
what you think.
So you're not married?
You weren't just in the city
with your wife?
I wasn't
in the city with my wife.
I'm not married.
Look, Liz,
I fucked up and you caught me.
Come on,
just open the door.
I just want
to talk to you about it.
It doesn't really lock. Uh...
It's just, it's more hospitable
to let it feel like it does.
What--what is this?
-Can I see that?
-Who is this?
Who the fuck is this?
It was a long time ago.
That's you, isn't it?
How the fuck is this you?
I--I--I want to leave now.
I...
I understand,
but I can't let you do that.
You can't let me do that?!
Who the fuck are you?!
I'm Malcolm Westbridge.
I'm your friend. I'm your lover.
I'm the same man
that you've known for a year.
I'm a doctor.
I'm a decent guy.
I save lives when I can.
When I can't, I can't.
But there's a bunch
of other stuff, too.
I want to go.
I understand.
It's just...
Hmm.
Can we just sit
in the living room,
you know,
just talk for a minute?
I'm not
fucking sitting down.
It's a pretty
good offer, considering.
Oh.
Come on.
Would it matter
if I said that, um...
I never wanted you to suffer?
Because I love you. I do.
And what is about to happen
is not in vain.
It is
the most beautiful act of love
one could ever commit.
You're giving me life.
Malcolm, whatever you think
you need to say to me, just...
Just go back to your family.
And let me go.
One nibble of the cake. One!
One nibble of the cake,
and the lion turns lamb,
limp and languid.
It was supposed
to knock you out.
But you had
to go ahead
and eat the whole thing.
You're... I should've
known you'd be different.
They present themselves
to you as women, do they?
Because that
they are not.
In truth, I--I--I
don't know what they are, um,
and I've known them a long time,
a long time.
Uh...
- Malcolm...
- Yes, Liz?
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Yeah, Darren and I,
we were--we were kids
when we found their mother...
in that creek you saw.
That was
more than 200 years ago.
But somehow,
you look exactly like her.
She was
a beautiful woman,
their mother.
But she was
a trespasser
on my father's land.
We'd seen her
many times before,
dancing naked in the river
by the light of the moon.
And that
wasn't allowed.
We threw her
in with the swine...
...not caring about her
or whatever bastard
she was carrying.
When we returned,
we saw she'd given birth.
But to what?
Malcolm...
j--just let me go.
Just let me leave.
So the fairy tale goes,
the lowly fisherman draws
in his line
and finds ensnared
on its hook a fish.
To the lowly fisherman,
the fish speaks,
a voice escaping its...
white and throbbing throat.
"Pray you, kind sir,
throw me back into my ocean,"
the dying fish says,
"and I will grant you
three wishes."
Why doesn't the fish
wish itself off the hook?
Why doesn't it grant
itself its own freedom?
Perhaps
because it knows...
it is nothing more than a fish.
The creatures
that live in this house,
in these woods...
they're the fish on the hook,
incapable of imagining
their own freedoms.
While we, the perfect
little Westbridge boys,
we see our wishes granted
for all time.
We are given
life eternal
while they cringe and cower
and feed in the shadows
of our houses,
unseen and unloved,
standing in their own piss.
And when
they get hungry,
...when the wailing
of their hunger pangs grows
too loud for the neighbors,
we feed them.
Malcolm...
you love me.
You said that.
Yes, and that--
that is--that is why
I--I don't stay to watch
or to listen when it happens.
Uh... Malcolm, let's go back.
I want to go back...
to before.
Mm-hmm, to when we didn't know
each other,
to then.
Can we do that?
Can we just do that?
Just when...
we didn't know....
we didn't know any of this?
You're gonna die, Liz.
Oh, my...
So I can...
live a little longer.
It's gonna happen
in this house.
A wooden box
for your coffin.
I wish it weren't so.
Oh, I really do.
But it is.
Be thankful
I'm not my neighbors
up the way on Teacup Road.
Standing next to them,
Darren and I were
perfect little gentlemen.
They seal the place.
Don't ask me how,
it's their magic.
FUCK!
No, no, no...
Oh...
Ah! Ah!
Guess what I found?
Hi, Julia.
Hey, Leslie.
Francis.
Louise.
Meet Liz.
Oh...
What the fuck?
What are you?
Your children.
And all the women
that came before.
NO!
NO! NO--
Ah...
Help!
Hey!
Morning.
Liz?
Oh, thank God.
Cut me down from here.
Please.
Please!
Liz,
what did they do to you?
They asked me to stay.
But this is my...
This is my house.
Oh.
I'm the master here!
You live here
'cause I live here.
No... I don't want any.
Malcolm.
- Oh.
- I don't want any.
Mm. Malcolm, listen...
This fork is going
into your face
one way or another.
Might as well taste good.
I never wanted to hurt you.
You didn't. I'm fine.
Now here comes
the airplane.
That's a good little
Westbridge boy.
Oh, Malcolm.
You were the one...
I really loved.
I bet you say
that to all the girls.