Downloaded from
YTS.BZ
Official YIFY movies site:
[tense music playing]
[explosions]
[man] Okay, so we messed up.
Somebody pushed the button,
and the world nearly ended.
We still don't know exactly who it was,
but it doesn't matter.
What matters is the world didn't end.
We rebuilt it and made it better.
[man scoffs]
Well, better for some.
They are called the Genetics.
Genetically-improved humans
that live like kings.
Then there's the rest of us.
The Specials.
Although there's nothing special about us.
For us, genetic improvements
just don't work.
We're as normal as humans have ever been.
But in today's world,
that makes us the scum of the Earth,
or what's left of it.
This is our story.
[suspenseful music playing]
[birds chirping]
[guide]
Sixty-five years ago,
the great nuclear war brought
the old world to an end.
Structures once thought of
- as formidable, the electric...
- [woman] Leon, go. Move on.
And the international
communication networks
crumbled overnight.
Plunged into a world
of technological crisis,
humans finally turned to a power
that had always been close at hand.
Nature.
How many of you know who this man is?
[woman] Liam Smith.
[guide] Correct. Liam Smith.
Our greatest botanist
and genetic engineer.
In the forests of the Amazon,
Professor Smith found the Genesis Tree.
[rattling]
Leon? You ready?
[Leon] Just give me a second here.
[guide] A marvel of nature
that appeared after the war.
As a result of the war,
the old power system was destroyed.
But scientists soon learned
to utilize the Genesis flower
to harvest and source energy to replace
the damaged electric grid.
The Genesis Tree flowers accumulate
an incredible amount of energy,
and nowadays,
the Genesis energy is everywhere.
- The Genesis Tree is very...
- Chloe. I'm in.
- To the external conditions...
- How's it going out there?
[Chloe] Hurry up, it's damn boring.
[guide]
and humidity.
Considering the significance
of these plants,
every single Genesis Tree
is controlled by the government.
They're grown and maintained...
[guard 1] You see the game last night?
[guard 2] Yeah, D'Abruzzo's pass
nearly knocked Juniper out.
It's really hard to find
a good linebacker these days.
All right, little buddy.
Time to cause some trouble.
[whirring]
[guard 2] Seriously,
Juniper couldn't catch a ball
even if a courier handed it to him.
[guard 1] What the hell?
Come here.
[guard 2] They let us
bring toys to work now?
Come on! Stop, you little shit!
[guard 1] Get back here.
[guard 2] What is it?
Beats me. We better call it in.
- [mouse] It's me!
- Oh.
[both groan]
[mouse] Good night!
[Leon grunts]
[scoffs]
Good work, Mr. Stinky.
Okay.
[Leon] Come on.
[sighs]
Yes!
[panting]
[guide] In the aftermath,
90 percent of children
were born with devastating
- genetic disorders...
- This one.
- But then, hope blossomed.
- Okay.
- Quite literally.
The flower came to our rescue!
Access for one, access for two...
[sighs]
[pants]
Yeah.
[guide] ...and successfully
integrated it
into the human genome.
This groundbreaking achievement sparked
- a biological revolution.
- Yeah.
Humans transcended
their physical limitations,
taking an evolutionary leap forward.
With careful genetic engineering...
[Leon] Come on, come on, come on.
[tense music playing]
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
[guide] Mankind was no longer constrained
by its old vulnerabilities.
We had entered a new era
of possibility and potential.
For more than half a century now,
every person is born
with a genetic improvement
that they received before they were born.
Take a look at each other.
Some of you have improved hearing,
others can run faster,
some have improved vision
or highly evolved smell and taste.
And some of us may even
sing like an angel,
like Mira,
recipient of one of the Institute's most
advanced vocal improvements.
[high-pitched vocalization]
[girl] Oh, my God, that's Mira!
For all these improvements,
we have Dr. Liam Smith
to thank.
Shame he didn't find
a cure for the freaks!
- [laughs]
- [student] Yes.
[guide] Bobby! You know
we don't call them freaks.
We call them Specials.
Because not everyone is as lucky as us.
Ten percent of humans suffer
from an immune deficiency
that prohibits genetic improvement.
[guide]
It's not their fault,
and they can still live meaningful lives
and be of great use to society doing
maintenance, cleanup,
and other less demanding tasks.
[guide] But without someone
taking care of these tasks...
[Leon] Oh, Chloe.
Chloe.
The code's incorrect.
You... you need to get the code.
[Leon] Give me the right code, now.
Okay.
For that,
we call them "Specials."
There's nothing special about them.
They're just a bunch of freaks.
Yeah. My dad says we should
put them down like dogs.
- You sick bastard! Shut up!
- Hey! Hey, what are you?
A freak lover?
- [group] Fight! Fight! Fight!
- Help, I'm being bullied! Help!
- Help! Shut up!
- Hey, hey, hey! Stop!
Knock it off, I said,
everybody! Calm down!
Mister! Mister, help!
- They're being mean!
- Get off!
What the hell is going on here?
Everything's fine.
I'll take care of it.
Okay, Leon.
[Chloe] Now, please try
1304-2029. Okay?
- [beeps]
- [lock clicks]
[Leon] Rock and roll.
We're in.
[guide] Now, children,
we still have a class to finish.
I don't want to contact your parents.
I don't care.
Snap it.
Follow me to the next exhibit.
[guide] The institute was established
to house the Genesis Tree
at the heart of our city,
harness its power...
[Leon] Okay. Sleep tight.
To study its remarkable
biological properties.
Teams of dedicated scientists
work tirelessly
to unlock the mysteries
- of the Genesis Tree.
- [Leon] We're all equal.
Sure thing, Mom.
Okay, Chloe.
Three minutes. Get ready.
[whirring]
[whirring continues]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [Leon grunts]
- [thumping]
- [Chloe] What was that?
- [Leon] Nothing. It's nothing.
[Leon grunts]
[whirring]
[guide] The Genesis Tree
absorbs nuclear material
from the contaminated atmosphere
and transforms it into pure energy,
which it stores in its blossoms,
the Genesis flowers.
These flowers, our most valuable resource,
are safeguarded within Genesis Institutes
across the globe.
Each tree functions
as a self-sustaining "reactor,"
providing energy to power our cities
and fuel our vehicles,
ensuring the survival
and advancement of humanity.
[Leon] Okay. Come to Daddy.
[beeping]
[automated voice]
A breach has been detected
in the containment chamber.
Facility lockdown imminent.
All nonessential personnel,
please vacate the premises immediately.
[Leon] Okay, that's everything.
[alarm blaring]
Attention, kids!
We must leave the building!
[security] Kids, everybody out!
[Leon] Hello?
What do we have here?
[security] Everybody out!
- [guide] Please follow me.
- A breach has been detected...
- Follow in an orderly manner.
- Facility lockdown imminent.
All nonessential personnel,
please vacate the premises immediately.
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct chuckle]
[Chloe] Hey, you better watch
where you're going, huh?
I'm sorry.
Give it back to me!
[ticking]
What's that sound?
Oh. It's...
It's, uh... It's just a watch.
- [ticking]
- [indistinct chatter]
You think we're all equal here, freak?
[Leon] No, no, no, no, no, not at all.
It was my mom's.
My, uh, parents liquidated
the radiation zone.
[Leon] Mom used to say that, uh,
we all get sick at some point.
Rich, poor,
we're all in this together.
Get out of here.
[tense music playing]
[tense music ends]
I'm Senator Frank Kessler,
and I'm a firm advocate
for a Brilliant Genetic Future
accessible to all!
Join me in proclaiming a resounding "Yes"
- on Proposition 42...
- It's 25.
- Okay.
- A groundbreaking stride
toward enabling human treatments
in Post-Natal Enhancement Therapy.
[woman] I'm Mira Jones.
In support of Prop 42,
I'm starting a Special District tour
from January 7th!
Tickets are free, so come party with me,
and let's celebrate Genetic Unity for all!
Oh, my God.
- What took you so long?
- Shut up!
Just because I'm on wheels
doesn't mean I'm a racing car.
Whatever, old man.
Did you see that?
See what?
She's coming to our district.
We have to go!
Oh, oh.
It's a hard no.
Come on, now!
Don't be such a relic.
[kid] What's going on?
[indistinct chuckle]
- No more school.
- [Chloe] I mean,
since when have we ever had
a concert in our district, huh?
She's just another elitist Genetic
pretending to care
about us Specials, Chloe.
At least she's trying to help.
All you do is bitch, bitch, bitch.
- [groans]
- Can't you see?
If Prop 42 passes,
it's gonna make our lives so much better.
Don't believe everything
you see on the TV.
Especially if it's coming from
a slick politician like Kessler.
You're so cynical, you know that?
Yeah, well, you're so naive!
Oh, I'm naive?
Yeah?
- Oh, Chloe!
- Oh!
Oh, Chloe. Just stop it!
- [grunts, groans]
- Get out of here, you freak!
You see? Off limits.
[man chuckles]
[mumbles, gasps]
Bunch of jerks.
Mom, who drew that picture?
The bad guys did.
[daughter] But why?
[mother] Because they want to hurt us.
But you don't have to worry about them.
Me and your dad will keep you safe.
[car horns honking]
[upbeat music playing]
[fans cheering]
[sighs]
[breathes deeply]
- [Mira] Carol?
- Mira.
The Special District is unsafe.
The concert is a big enough risk as is.
I simply can't allow you
to do an autograph session.
The whole point of the Echoes Tour
is to include the Specials
and meet them in their own backyard.
Prop 42 is about uniting people, right?
"Genetic unity for all."
Isn't that what we're selling?
And how am I supposed to do that
behind a huge security detail
and bulletproof windows?
It makes no sense.
Stop being so dramatic!
I'm not being dramatic!
They still love you
even if they can't touch you.
I'm just being cautious.
I'm done arguing about this.
Pick up the phone and uncancel
what you've just canceled
because I'm going to meet the Specials.
[tense music playing]
[crowd chatter]
[upbeat music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[guard] Halt. Identifications.
- [indistinct chatter]
- [dog barking]
It's my niece's birthday.
We went to Greenwood to buy her a present.
[indistinct chatter]
- [Leon] Thank you.
- [Chloe] Thank you.
[Leon] Come on, Chloe.
Let's go home.
[guard] And these freaks
complain about being poor.
Bunch of scam artists, if you ask me.
[vendor] Step right up, step right up.
Hey, buddy.
- What's up, T?
- [T] Hey. What's up?
Is that the, uh... THX 1138?
- [T] Eh, yo, this one?
- Yeah.
[interviewer] Senator Kessler,
if the Proposition 42 passes...
[Kessler] When it passes.
[interviewer] Yes, well...
many are wondering,
how will you be able
to hold on to your promises?
Uniting the Genetics and Specials...
the idea is not without its detractors.
The answer lies in science, Laura.
For many years now,
I've been leading a research team
in the development of a drug
that enables genetic enhancements
to take place not only before birth,
but also during adulthood.
For everyone, including Specials.
[Kessler]
That's why I'm campaigning
for Proposition 42,
which allows for treatments
in Post-Natal Enhancement Therapy
to move forward.
[Laura] Your campaign is heating up
as the Senate hearings
are coming to a close,
while many artists,
such as pop singer Mira,
- have become vocal proponents.
- [sighs]
Chloe.
- Chloe!
- [Chloe] Huh?
Come on.
What do you think?
Will he succeed?
I think we've got a lot of work to do.
Come on.
Okay.
[Kessler]
Laura, can I just add...
Scram! What have I told you
about playing...
[kid] Hey, screw you, buddy!
Hey, calm down!
They're just kids.
[kid] All right.
[grunts]
[Chloe] They're not doing
anything that serious.
[Leon] All right, all right.
Home, sweet home.
[Chloe] Come in there.
- [Leon sighs]
- [switch clicking]
[Chloe] I'm gonna check on my plants.
[Leon grunts]
[pensive music playing]
[Chloe] Hi, Mom. Hi, Dad.
[sighs]
Here you go.
Hope it was worth almost getting caught.
[Leon] Of course, it was.
Kidding me?
Now we can make some serious cash.
Wait.
You used all of my acid fruits,
didn't you?
Do you have any idea
how hard it is to grow them?
Screw your fruits.
Check it out.
- This is...
- Genesis flower extract.
Use it wisely, "Doctor."
This is hard to find.
This is... awesome!
Now I can experiment on...
Why don't you start by experimenting
on those dishes? Huh?
They're growing their own ecosystem.
Why is it always my job?
[sighs]
Because when your parents were taken,
I promised them that you could make it
in this big, scary world, all on your own.
Yep.
That's why I have to do the dishes.
That's why you have to go do the dishes.
- Great. Thank you. Thank you.
- Go on, scram!
[whirring]
[singing]
[Leon] Easy does it.
[sighs]
[Chloe] ♪ Leon ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ The dishes that I'm washing
While I'm singing ♪
♪ I don't care
If you don't hear me ♪
♪ I'm just washing the dishes ♪
♪ And dancing
While I'm singing ♪
♪ Oh, Leon ♪
♪ You probably don't care ♪
♪ And I don't care
If you don't hear me... ♪
[EDM music playing]
All right, young lady,
time to earn your keep!
Let's make some money!
[Leon] You again.
Let's see what's up this time.
I'm gonna start my new
greenhouse project tomorrow.
Mm.
Well, if I find any
prickly bindweed on my wires,
your green friends
will be out on the street.
Just try it.
Need I remind you, this basement
belonged to my parents?
You are just a tenant.
[Chloe] Without me, your business is done.
[grunts]
Ah.
That's not gonna be enough, buddy.
Thanks.
Next!
- [voice] New device detected.
- There.
Pretty nifty, huh?
And it records video too.
Next one!
All right.
[sighs]
[moans]
[ringing]
[sighs]
- Leon's Wares, yes?
- [man] Guys, it's an emergency.
- You need to come here now!
- No, we're done for today.
You gotta call us again tomorrow.
[man] No, no, no. Hold on.
Don't hang up.
You need to come and fix this suit now!
No, we don't do on-site repairs.
You'll have to come to us.
[man] I've got the money.
Just come over!
It doesn't matter how much you pay.
[man] I'm in the Genetic District.
Especially not in the Genetic District.
Hello.
- How can I help you, sir?
- Hey, you gotta solve this.
- Get your ass here now...
- Money matters.
And fix my suit.
I'll pay you triple.
Triple fee? Deal.
[man] I'm at the Saint
Devonshire restaurant.
At the Genetic District...
Yeah, yeah, I know where that is.
- [man] Please make it quick.
- Uh... Yep. We're on the way.
We're on the way.
Are you nuts?
Triple fee!
[exhales]
Money is survival, Chloe.
You'll learn that eventually.
Just in case you forgot,
what we do is illegal.
So, we have rules, Leon!
We don't go to the customers.
The customers come to us.
It'll be in, out, boom!
Triple fee.
Look, we need the money.
How are we gonna get there
without being captured?
You'll end up in jail,
and I'll go to an orphanage.
Is it worth an extra couple of hundred?
I know a shortcut around the checkpoint.
Everything will be fine!
Just trust me.
[Leon] The main thing is not
to get caught by the patrol.
First, you go through
the old fence at 62nd Street,
then cross the border wall
through an opening
on Classon Avenue.
And finally, you take
the old underground tunnel
at Brighton.
And voila!
You're safely on the other side.
[Chloe sighs]
I hate you, Leon.
[dramatic piano music playing]
[guest 1] One of the things
I love about this wine
is that its bouquet is so fragrant.
You can smell the roses and cherries.
And it's delicate.
Isn't it lovely?
[guest 2 laughs]
[guest 2] That's right.
Uh, wonderful.
Um-um. No.
No, that's not well done.
Right.
She was going to show me
that data, you know?
[waiter] Ready to order?
[man] Yeah, the customer looked great.
[Leon] Go!
[Chloe] Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go.
- [man] Hey! Over here!
- [Leon] Is it just you?
Yes. Hurry up.
[beeping]
All right. Keep those
pesky Specials out, huh?
[man sighs]
Very funny.
[Leon] Look at this suit!
[man] Where the hell have you been?
I almost got busted.
Gah...
Look at what you've done to my suit!
I can see the problem right here.
[man] Hurry up.
[suspenseful music playing]
[waiter] Oh, my God!
It's the Anti-Genetics.
The... the Anti-Genetics!
There. Yes...
There she is.
Hold still.
Testing one, two, three!
- [whirring]
- [chuckles]
[man] Thank you.
Thank me?
Thank me once, thank me twice,
thank me three times.
Remember the deal?
Oh.
[indistinct chatter]
[gang leader] Smells great.
Hope you all enjoyed your meals.
'Cause they're your last.
[guests murmuring]
[guests gasping]
- [indistinct screaming]
- [Chloe] What?
- What is going on?
- [Leon] What?
- Stay here.
- [Chloe] What?
- I'll go have a look.
Give me the cash!
Give me the money!
- What?
- [man] Just stay calm.
[Leon] Let's deal with the money first.
Let's get out of here.
Please, now!
It was triple-price, Chloe.
Leon, let's get out of here, now!
[tense music playing]
[man] It's the Anti-Genetics.
They're killing everyone...
[Leon] We gotta get out of here, Chloe.
[Chloe] What's going on, Leon?
What are we gonna do?
[Leon] Chloe?
Chloe, come and help!
Pull this as hard as you can.
[both groaning]
Leon, we wouldn't get far anyway,
not with you in that wheelchair.
Wait.
Chloe, Chloe, I need your help right now.
Help me put this thing on.
[humming]
- [AGS 1] What do you think?
- It's a frigging masterpiece.
[suspenseful music playing]
Shh!
[AGS 3] Seems like that's the last of 'em.
Man, I was just getting started.
[gang leader]
Consider this a rehearsal.
So save your energy.
Tomorrow, the gig, and the day after that,
the big thing.
[AGS 3] Oh, I'm full of energy.
I can keep on hacking these...
[gang leader] Tomorrow, we do
everything like I said.
No diverting from the plan.
- That clear?
- [AGS 3] Yes, boss.
[gang leader] I can't hear you.
[AGS 3] Yes, boss!
[muttering]
[gang leader]
Here. Tag this wall.
[AGS 3] Okay, boss.
[spray hissing]
[AGS 1] Cops are on the way.
Let's go.
[gang leader]
Let's get out of here.
Oh, no!
Shit!
[grunts]
[gang leader] No survivors.
I told you. Get him!
[intense EDM music playing]
[men grunt]
[AGS 3] Ah, it burns!
- [shouts]
- [groans]
[Leon] Come on!
Chloe, come on! Run!
[gang leader] Leave them!
We have to go. Now!
[Chloe] Go, go, go!
Go, go, go!
[painful grunts]
- [Leon grunting]
- [distant sirens wailing]
[both panting heavily]
[yelping]
[both panting]
[grunting painfully]
Hey, hey.
Are you all right? Can you...
Can you walk in that thing at all?
[Leon groans]
- [Chloe] Come on.
- [Leon] Okay...
- [Chloe] Come on, come on.
- [Leon] Okay.
- Be careful!
- I got it.
[grunting]
Today's attack
at Saint Devonshire restaurant
by the extremist Anti-Genetic Squad
is the cruelest and bloodiest so far.
The police have reported dozens of victims
and no survivors.
A sketch of the perpetrators
has been released,
based on eyewitnesses.
The police are on the lookout
for a tall man,
possibly wearing
some kind of mechanical armor,
and a girl.
If you encounter these individuals,
you are advised
to immediately call the police,
as they are armed and extremely dangerous.
Dangerous?
We didn't do anything!
Just hold on. I'm thinking.
They're lying.
We didn't do any of it!
Go tell that to the police.
Be my guest.
[reporter] Captain Hughes!
Captain Hughes!
Would you care to comment
on the upcoming raid
in the Special District?
Special District is an ulcer
on the body of the city.
- Look.
- It's time to clean up...
[Chloe]
What do you think I'm doing?
Wait, no.
It's the maniac with the machete!
It breeds freak gangs like this one.
Hughes?
Isn't he, like, the head
of the Special Forces?
That scar!
You saw it, Chloe.
[Hughes] Freaks!
Remember, we are coming for you!
It is him.
[sighs]
Well, that explains
why they've never been caught.
Why would the Genetics
attack their own kind?
It doesn't make any sense.
I have no idea.
What? What is it?
One of them dropped it.
[Leon] Mira?
I can't see these guys being a fan of her.
[Chloe] I heard them say
they're planning more attacks.
There's some sort of a diagram here.
Wait.
The concert is tomorrow.
The concert I was supposed to be going to.
Mira is their next target.
Of course.
A star that big in the Special District?
If the AGS wanna frame the Specials,
then they're not gonna miss
a chance like this.
But what are they trying to achieve?
I don't know.
This man wants to paint the Specials
to be criminals and murderers.
Probably to push us back
even further on the pretext
of fighting crime.
This guy is a psycho!
Well, we gotta do something, then.
Yeah, we do.
[Chloe] Leave town?
But what about Mira and all
of the people at the concert?
- We have to save them.
- Crazy?
Save them? How?
You're a 12-year-old girl,
and I'm a paraplegic.
It's not like we can go to the cops.
We're wanted for murder!
But if this happens,
all Specials will be considered criminals!
Don't you understand?
It's not just about us anymore!
It'll be bad for everyone.
Why don't you care?
I care about us and saving our asses.
How?
If we run,
we'll lose my parents' workshop,
and then we'll be out on the street.
They're looking for us
all over the country!
It's not like we have
a choice here, Chloe.
We have to at least warn people
and warn Mira.
Then we'll definitely get caught
and thrown in jail
for the rest of our lives.
So stop talking nonsense and get packing!
[somber music playing]
I'm not going with you.
Chloe, stop.
Mira and the people
didn't take care of you.
I did.
If it wasn't for me, you know,
they would've put you
in a home years ago.
You're my responsibility.
And you will do what I tell you!
So, get packing.
Screw you.
Excuse me?
I've always thought of you
as my older brother.
As the only decent person
in this crappy town!
But you're just out for yourself,
and screw everybody else!
You're nothing
but a piece of shit on wheels!
[inhales deeply]
[stammers]
Chloe!
Chlo...
[sighs]
[frustrated grunt]
[irritated groaning]
[sighs deeply]
[Chloe] It's not just about us anymore!
It'll be bad for everyone.
Why don't you care?
"Equal," my ass.
[Chloe] I've always thought
of you as my older brother.
Just "a piece of shit
on wheels."
[sentimental music playing]
[approaching footsteps]
[Leon]
You're a 12-year-old girl,
and I'm a paraplegic.
[Chloe] All you do is bitch, bitch, bitch.
Maybe I can level the playing field.
[resolute music playing]
[faint crackling]
What the...
[crackling continues]
[Chloe] Leon?
What is this?
Oh, Chloe, good timing.
Can you give me a hand?
[Chloe] What are you doing?
Well, giving it a new paint job,
tweaked a few things,
and... I think I got an idea.
I thought you were leaving the town.
Yeah, well, I changed my mind.
You gonna help me
get in this thing or what?
- [machine whirring]
- [chuckling]
[whirring]
[strained grunts]
[chuckles]
Mm.
- Careful, careful.
- [groans]
- Slow down. Okay?
- Yeah.
- Slow down.
- Yeah, I got it.
- Slow. You got this?
- Yeah.
[grunting]
I'm gonna take Hughes down,
make him confess,
and throw him to the police.
Hell, yeah!
What you gonna fight him with?
Uh...
Give me that.
Oh, yeah. Sure.
- Here.
- All right, stand back.
- Yes.
- Sure.
Oh, careful, careful!
Are you all right?
You really gotta be
careful with that, okay?
Not that, not that.
Give me that.
Just slow down.
[grunts]
No.
[Chloe] Wait.
Wait... wait. Wait!
You've got these bio-wires.
I can make reagents
that'll allow you to...
- Arm the suit.
- Exactly.
- [pipe clangs]
- That's genius.
You'll be able to release pollen!
Shoot thorns!
Grow roots!
Roots? Roots? Why roots?
Well, I don't know.
Just because you can. Why not?
[chuckles]
[groans]
[pop music playing]
♪ Reach out your hand
And we'll find harmony ♪
♪ The future is here
Bright and new ♪
♪ We all deserve
To be happy and free ♪
♪ Though you're nothing
Like me ♪
♪ And I'm nothing like you ♪
♪ Don't tell me your voice
Is a drop in the sea ♪
♪ 'Cause there's so much
You can do ♪
♪ Give me a chance
And I'll make you see ♪
♪ That you're someone like me ♪
- ♪ And I'm someone like you ♪
- ♪ Someone like you ♪
[security] Get back, get back!
Get down from the fence!
Step down, right now!
[crowd cheering]
Move back, everyone, move back!
- Move back!
- [crowd cheering]
- So what's our plan?
- [grunts]
Well, we know Mira is the target.
So, we guard her
and wait for the AGS to attack.
I'll stop them and hold them.
You call the police.
But what if something happens to you?
We need to make sure that doesn't happen.
I'm gonna need a lot of ammunition.
Got it.
[Mira screams]
[Carol] Stop, stop! Help!
No! No! Leave me alone!
Get away! Help!
Let me go!
No! Carol!
[screams]
Carol!
[Hughes] If you ever wanna
sing again, princess,
I suggest you behave.
[Leon] Let her go!
[rock music playing]
[Leon yelps, grunts]
[panting]
[Hughes laughs]
What the hell are you?
- Who is this clown?
- [AGS laughing]
So what's the deal, Flower Man?
[Leon] Mira, get in the car!
Mira! Mira, over here!
[rock music playing]
[Hughes]
Don't let them get away!
[both grunting]
[Leon grunts]
[panicked screams]
Shh!
You were the target!
- [Hughes] Get in the truck!
- [AGS] Yes, sir.
[Hughes] Come on.
Get in the car!
[Mira] Who were those guys?
[Leon] That's the Anti-Genetic Squad.
They're trying to kidnap you.
But don't worry,
we're gonna take you somewhere safe.
[tense music playing]
[panting]
[creaking]
Is... is this some kind
of a kidnapping?
- What's going on?
- It's quite the opposite.
- You're...
- What?
You're safe here, I promise you.
I'm Chloe. He's Leon.
[news anchor] ...and occupy
the lowest tier of society.
Everything's all right.
You're safe here.
Gosh, Mira, you're...
you're really here, this is...
Okay, can someone just tell me
what's going on?
- I'm like, I'm really confused.
- Wait! I'll be right back.
- Where am I?
- Just a second. Just a second.
I'll be right back.
Just wait a second!
[Chloe giggles]
[sighs]
It's... it's quite...
[news anchor]
launched a brazen attack...
[mumbles]
I know this isn't
the right time and place, but...
Chloe!
- Go to your room. Now!
- In a shocking turn of events,
- the criminals attempted...
- Shut up.
To abduct the singer.
Fortunately, Mira managed
to evade capture and escape
with the help of an unknown entity,
and her current whereabouts
remain unknown.
- Wait, you... So...
- During the incident,
Mira's manager sustained injuries
- and is currently...
- You saved me?
Just... it's nothing.
[news anchor] Special forces
led by Captain Hughes...
Are you wounded?
[Leon winces]
I'm fine.
- Let me have a look.
- [pained groan]
Now, let me see. Let me see.
[news anchor] ...the search
for Mira continues.
Okay, we're gonna need that...
We need to get that patched up.
[pained grunt]
[news anchor] ...miraculously
managed to escape
the clutches of assailants.
As of now, her current
whereabouts remain unknown...
Okay. It'll burn.
[pained yelp]
[woman on TV]
I want to assure everyone
that discrimination will not be...
[huffing]
You seem pretty good at this for a singer.
Yeah...
Actually, I've always wanted
to be a doctor.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Help others.
[pained grunt]
Can you just help me
a little more gently, please?
Sorry.
[pants, sighs]
Okay, this should hold,
but no sudden movements,
or you're gonna need
much more than that, okay?
Thanks.
- [groans]
- [soft chuckle]
[Mira] Aw.
Flower power, huh?
- You?
- Yeah. Very cute.
I suggest we focus
on something more important.
- Really nice.
- Thank you.
[chuckles]
[Leon] The police are looking for us.
And the Anti-Genetics are planning
for their next attack.
But why?
All they're doing is making everyone
hate Specials even more.
Well, that's the point.
The AGS are a gang of Genetics.
They're trying to frame the Specials.
- Hughes is their leader.
- [Mira] Wait.
Hughes, as in Special Forces Hughes?
- Yeah.
- No. That's ridiculous.
Well, they obviously wanna stop Prop 42.
The main question now is,
where's the next attack gonna be?
No, no. No, no, no.
The main question now is,
how do I get back home?
I've got a big event tomorrow
at the Family Planning Center.
Kessler's expecting me,
all the media is gonna be there.
I need to be there.
Wait, that's it.
That's where the next attack is gonna be.
[Mira] Wait, what?
The Family Planning Center
is the next target?
Yes, that makes perfect sense!
They were talking about it
at the restaurant.
- Exactly.
- What are you going on about?
- It doesn't make any sense!
- Don't worry about it. Trust me.
It all makes perfect sense.
Today, they tried to get you.
Tomorrow, Kessler.
- Kessler?
- Yeah.
Do you remember what they did
to his poster at the club?
[hissing]
[Leon] Remember?
- Oh, my God.
- [Leon] Yeah.
Oh, my God. Maybe...
Maybe he is the next target.
Okay. We have to warn the cops.
No, no, no, you're not calling anyone.
Hughes himself works for the police.
We do not know who else is involved.
If we're gonna stop him,
it has to be a surprise.
I'm, like, your biggest fan,
but he is totally right.
Okay. This is absolutely crazy.
- I'm getting out of here!
- No, you're not going anywhere.
- Hey, let me out!
- No!
- Okay, so you did kidnap me!
- No?
- Not originally.
- Plans change.
- [Chloe] Guys.
- Guys, please...
- [Mira] This is outrageous.
It's outrageous!
Didn't she say she wanted
to be close to the Specials?
Well, look, here you are.
Enjoy it.
I'm gonna make some changes to the suit.
You're in on this too now,
so just sit tight.
Chloe, look after her.
[Kessler]
I'm Senator Frank Kessler...
Meaning what?
For a Brilliant Genetic Future
accessible to all!
Join me in proclaiming a resounding "Yes"
on Proposition 42.
[news anchor] Senator Kessler
will appear tomorrow
at Family Planning Center.
[announcer]
Family Planning Center.
Your babies. Our future.
[Kessler] Where we, the Genetics, walk...
I have a plan.
And you're gonna help me.
[laughs]
Yeah, I'm gonna help you?
We're gonna have a baby.
[laughing]
- [Chloe] What?
- [laughs]
[Leon] The trick is to get inside
the Family Planning Center.
We pretend we're having a baby.
I'll disguise myself, and we get in,
get everybody to safety,
and prevent the gang
from killing all those people.
Then wait for the cops to arrive.
That'll clear our name.
And Hughes gets locked up.
Chloe, you'll stay outside on the lookout,
and give me a signal
when you see them arrive, okay?
[upbeat music playing]
Mira? Is that you?
Yes, hi. Um...
Miss, you're quite early.
- The event isn't about to...
- Yes.
I've got an appointment
with the head doctor.
- Mm-hm.
- Okay, sure.
I mean, of course, yes.
- One moment, Mira.
- Thank you.
And who may I tell them you're with?
Me? I'm, I'm...
Uh... Doctor...
uh, Doctor Plan-ing Guy.
Doc... Doctor Planning Guy?
Doctor Guy Planning.
[chuckles]
It's my stage name.
You... you probably
recognize me.
I'm afraid I don't, Doctor Guy.
I'm... I'm... I'm very famous.
Oh, I'm sure.
Let me just check the schedule.
Uh, no, you won't find my name there.
My office called in today,
and they just told us to stop by.
- [Leon] Yeah.
- Yeah.
Please, could you hurry?
We don't like to be kept waiting.
- [receptionist] Of course, sure.
- Thank you.
[whispers]
"Doctor Guy Planning"?
- What is wrong with you?
- Would you cut me some slack?
I'm a mechanic, not an actor.
[whispers]
But it's a stupid name.
Mira!
Oh. What a nice surprise.
I'm terribly sorry,
I wasn't made aware of your appointment.
And you're not alone.
- No, this is...
- Oh, Doctor Guy...
Planning. I'm famous.
Very famous.
You look familiar.
And now, what can I do for you?
Um...
I hope this can stay between us.
I'd like to avoid all the media attention.
You understand what I mean?
We're not...
- Oh.
- Going public with it yet.
- I see.
- [Mira] So...
Good thinking, Ms. Mira.
You can trust my discretion.
Strictly confidential.
Have you already decided
which improvement you would like
for your future child?
I'm sorry?
We have many options.
Uh, increased physical strength.
Or allow me to say, your beauty?
Or maybe your incomparable voice?
All of this is possible.
You just need to choose.
Listen, Doc, can I...
can I call you Doc?
Since we're both doctors.
[laughs]
Seriously, though, Doc.
Uh, before committing, I wanna make sure
that my girl, my princess,
gets the best treatment available.
Can we have a look around your hospital?
Oh, hey...
Our clinic is the very best,
I can assure you.
We're the only ones in this country
providing the most advanced
prenatal improvements.
Unfortunately, uh...
- The Senator Kessler's visit...
- Oh, yeah.
No, mad respect for that, mad respect.
But I really need to see what I'm buying.
Certainly.
Okay. Uh, follow me, then.
The Family Planning Center
will celebrate its
thirtieth birthday next year.
We've provided impeccable improvements
to celebrities such as
Felicity Pugh, Bob Jenkins,
and, well, now you.
Your wonderful voice
was one of our designs.
[woman crying]
Sorry.
- Doctor...
- [Chloe] Leon. They're here.
Yo, Doc, thank you so much!
We are so grateful
and impressed with your facility.
We have a little surprise for you.
Mira is gonna perform
a special private gig
just for you and your staff right now.
- No, it's not really necessary...
- No. We insist, we insist.
Guys, everyone!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Mira herself is gonna
perform just for you.
One-time private gig!
- It's gonna be cool!
- [Mira] Hi, everyone. Thank you.
Yes, I have a couple of new songs,
if you wanna follow me.
Yeah. Follow me, everyone!
[Leon] That's right.
Come on in. Come on.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Leon] Hey, boneheads!
[Hughes] You again, Flower Man?
You got lucky last time.
[Leon] Come on.
Don't worry, I won't bite.
[Hughes] Ugh. Let's get
this freakshow over with.
Grab him by his petals, boys.
[ASG 1] Come on.
- [Leon grunts]
- [both groan]
[both grunting]
[Leon] I made a few improvements.
[Hughes] It won't mean a thing.
Get him!
[all grunt]
[fierce grunt]
[yelling]
You'll pay for that, you freak.
[Leon grunts]
[grunting]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [Hughes] Let's get out of here.
- [ASG 2] Let's go!
[security] Stay right there!
Don't move!
Hold your fire.
[Leon groans]
Dad?
What? [groans]
Mira?
[groans]
Mira.
Leon?
I'm sorry.
I warned him about this.
He told me everything.
He's here to help.
I don't understand.
Why did you just let him go?
'Cause you're all that matters to me, son.
That's why.
Son?
He's your dad?
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Look, Chloe.
I'm sorry.
[Chloe] So, you're...
- You're one of them.
- [Leon] No.
No. Chloe. Chloe!
It's all right, son.
You did good.
I'm proud of you.
- You're safe.
- [reporter 1] Mira!
Mira! Why are you here?
My son is proof that the disparity
between Genetics and Specials
has gone too far.
Tomorrow, we vote for Proposition 42,
and then the healing can begin.
[Kessler] Genetic unity for all!
[reporter 2]
Senator. Se... Senator?
[overlapping chatter]
[reporter 3] Senator, over here!
Just a moment of your time.
Today, the Senate voted
in favor of Proposition 42,
which will enable postnatal
improvements on all citizens.
After last week's attack
on the Family Planning Center,
the Proposition 42,
locally backed by Senator Kessler,
was met with near-unanimous approval.
Earlier, Senator Kessler
and his security team
appeared at the scene
in the Family Planning Center.
There, they managed to stop
an Anti-Genetic Squad attack,
saving many lives.
Preparations for the new
genetic treatments are underway.
Starting today, Special citizens
will be transported to a new medical camp
established outside the city.
After the new treatments,
the Special District borders
will be opened,
and the newly improved citizens
will be allowed to join
the Genetic population,
creating, according to Senator Kessler,
a new, more unified future for all.
[man] Special citizens, you are required
to follow directions to the designated
unloading zones.
Please remain calm and proceed
in an orderly fashion.
[machine beeping]
[door opens, closes]
You'll be staying here until we complete
the procedure, then you're...
free to do as you wish.
Chloe...
What happened to Chloe?
The girl I was with.
Where'd she go?
She ran away.
But we're looking for her.
And I promise I'll let you know
as soon as we find her.
And Hughes?
You know he's the leader
of the Anti-Genetics.
Why has he not been arrested?
Right now, you need
to focus on yourself, son.
I let everybody down.
I want my suit back.
I... I need my suit back.
Where is it?
You don't need that suit anymore.
Now that I've found you,
I am gonna cure you.
Just like you cured Mom?
[somber music playing]
Leonard.
I did what I thought was best...
to try and fix you.
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have listened
to those idiot doctors.
Well, you were the one that
let them experiment.
I loved your mother.
So much.
And...
I made a terrible mistake.
She left you a letter.
And I was so afraid
of what you would do...
that I never gave it to you.
And then you disappeared.
[somber music playing]
[woman's voice] Dear Leon,
this is your mother.
I'm happy to have a chance
to see you and hold you.
Unfortunately, we have to part soon.
I believe you'll become
a kind person, free and open.
The only thing I'm afraid of
is that you'll hate your father
and your heart will become hardened.
Life can be cruel, son.
We have to learn to forgive,
no matter how difficult it might be.
After all, no matter what happens to us,
despite all of the mistakes,
family stays with you until the end.
We are all the same.
We are all equal.
I love you.
[somber music continues]
She wanted you to forgive me.
[crying]
[door opens]
[Mira sighs]
I'm gonna take care of him.
[Mira] They won't stay here long.
Your father said they'd be given
treatment as soon as possible.
[woman]
Does anybody have some water?
And you will walk home on your own.
Chloe?
[stammers]
Chloe!
[chuckles]
They told me you ran away.
[laughing]
Believe it or not, I missed you so much.
[Leon laughs]
Me too.
Almost.
- [Leon laughing]
- [sniffles]
Come on.
[chuckles]
Okay, you all right?
You know I'm all right.
Why didn't you tell me?
Are you now one of them?
I don't know. I...
[sighs]
I'm one of you.
[both chuckle]
Mira.
Why did you warn my dad?
[Mira sighs]
You could have been killed.
I had to do something.
[Leon] Don't you see that...
he's the one behind all of this?
The gang, the attack on the Genetics.
Why would Kessler be behind all this?
Who stands to benefit
the most from all of this?
Him.
His project is now supported
by the Senate.
Yes, but his project is meant
to save Specials' lives.
I mean, he found the cure.
Why would he support the gang
- that wants to kill the...
- I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
Hey, Leon.
If Kessler's plan is real,
I won't be needing your service anymore.
[scoffs]
I wouldn't be so sure, buddy.
There's something about this...
[mutters]
that stinks like a dead rat.
You're gonna need more
than a dead rat to prove it.
The lab, the lab.
The laboratory.
[stammers] If...
if I'm right about my dad,
then, uh, the answer is in the lab.
We just...
We need to find a way to get the proof.
[whispers] The cam.
- [Mira] What?
- The cam.
Maybe you're not just a...
an annoying little squirrel.
- Shut up, old man.
- [chuckles]
Shh.
- Just leave it to me.
- Okay, okay.
[clears throat]
Buddy?
Yeah?
How's that camera working out for you?
[tense music playing]
[guard] You, come with us.
This one?
[nurse] Yes. That one.
[guard] Move it!
[nurse] Please lift your arm.
This will sting a little.
[groans]
[beeps]
- You did good.
- Thank you.
I knew it.
So that's what it's all about.
And how does it all work?
Honestly, I don't fully
understand your plan, Frank.
I'll show you.
First, we extract
the necessary biomaterial
from the donor's brain.
He won't feel a thing.
It's completely painless.
[whirring]
[clicks]
Almost.
[whirring]
Then...
We mix the biomaterial
with the variant of the gene modification.
[whirring]
The donor's untouched genome
binds with the genetic enhancement
and...
Voila!
We have the essence.
Which allows us to instill
any enhancement into any Genetic,
regardless of age, and without limit.
It's a goddamn miracle.
We've cracked the enigma
of human evolution.
[chuckles]
You promised the Senate
you'd treat the Specials.
I hope we're not
going to waste your miracle
on some human garbage.
Curing my son is all that matters to me.
As for the rest of them,
there's nothing we can do.
Their genetic disposition
prevents their evolution.
Harvesting them is
the only humane solution.
It's the...
loving thing to do.
Great!
Because I've been waiting
for some new additions
for quite a while.
Get this garbage out of here.
[whirring]
[crying]
The necessary biomaterial
from the donor's brain.
He won't feel a thing.
It's completely painless.
[crying]
[panting]
- I'm sorry.
- [Leon] No, it's okay.
[Mira] I'm so sorry.
I didn't know. I had no idea.
[Leon] Hey, hey.
I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- [Mira] I'm sorry.
[Chloe] Mira, no, this is not your fault.
It's not your fault.
Listen.
The question is,
what are we gonna do about it?
[man 1]
So, what are we gonna do?
We fight!
- [man 2] Fight?
- With what?
[panting]
[stammers]
With... with...
with anything we've got!
All we have to do is just...
just... just hold them off
until the police come.
That's all we have to do.
[man 3] It'll be a slaughter.
No, no.
That's what they want you to think.
All right?
That you're useless
and you're worthless.
It's not true!
It's that we're...
We're all one.
We're all equal.
I just need my damn suit.
I know where they keep it.
The storeroom.
[soft chuckle]
- We're gonna fight.
- We fight!
- Yeah.
We fight!
[tense music playing]
[machine beeping]
Today is the day, Leonard.
First, I'm gonna cure you,
then the rest of the world.
- Ow!
- Don't call me that.
- [pained groan]
- Tell me, Dad.
Tell me, where exactly did
you get this essence from, huh?
I know everything.
Your dealings with Hughes, the gang.
Killing all those innocent people
for your own pathetic ego!
Oh, it's so much more than that.
It's evolution, and you can't stop it.
I gotta ask you one question.
Why?
You were supposed to be born a Genetic!
You're not a Special.
You were always one of us.
With the Specials' untouched genome,
I can cure every illness,
every disability,
and we'll ascend to the next level
on the evolutionary ladder!
And it all starts with you, Leonard!
My only son.
You did all of this to help me?
To cure me?
There's only one thing, Dad.
I'm not the one who's sick.
You are.
Leonard...
- Leonard!
- [door closes]
[door locks]
Chloe, tell me you've got some more ammo!
Why? Did you use
all of them up again?
You wouldn't get far without me.
- Okay, so I've got...
- What you got?
- Two wings, here.
- Okay.
Two wings, one spikes,
two pollen, one roots.
[Leon] Uh-huh.
[Chloe] I guess that's all.
No, wait!
- One acid fruit.
- One?
That's the last one.
[sighs]
Please use it wisely, Flower Man.
Time to show them some flower power.
Good luck.
[guard] Sector is clear.
Who are you?
[both grunting]
- [Leon grunts]
- [guard groans]
[alarm blaring]
Chloe, Hughes will be here any minute.
We gotta get this video
to the cops as soon as possible.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah...
[automated voice]
Security breach detected.
Initiate full lockdown.
- [Mira] Hurry up!
- Got it!
[automated voice]
Security breach detected.
No, I still need some time
for the connection.
- How long do you need?
- Five minutes.
Make it four.
[automated voice]
Police dispatch.
Please upload your video.
Wait, Leon!
You'll need this.
Yeah.
- Security breach detected.
- Okay.
Lock this door.
Whatever happens,
do not unlock it.
Oh, Leon.
- What?
- Be careful.
Oh, come on now.
Get a room, you two.
Ew, gross!
[panting heavily]
[man on PA]
Attention all residents.
For your safety, please remain
in your assigned living areas.
A search will be conducted
as we seek to locate
a dangerous individual.
Please be advised that providing shelter
or assistance to this individual
is a serious offense
with severe consequences.
Your cooperation is mandatory.
Thank you.
[tense music playing]
[Specials shouting]
[Hughes] Flower Man.
You're like a goddamn weed, you know that?
But don't worry.
I've got just the right tools
to deal with you.
And I won't drag it out this time.
[Leon] Oh, so you're gonna
surrender right away, then?
[Specials shouting indistinctly]
[Hughes] Why don't I bury you right here?
[Leon] Bring it.
[all shouting]
[all grunting]
[man grunting]
[man] This is team Alpha One
requesting immediate support!
Situation not under control.
I repeat, situation not under control!
[tense music playing]
[indistinct shouting]
[gunfire]
[grunting]
[whirs]
[Hughes shouts]
[Leon groans]
[Hughes]
So, how are you feeling now?
[indistinct shouting]
[man] Get it out!
[Leon groaning]
Let's finish this, Flower Boy.
Where do you think you're going?
- [guard grunts]
- [gasps]
- What's going on here?
- [grunts]
[gasping]
[Chloe] Let her go.
[Hughes grunts]
Are you tired yet, creepy freak?
[clattering]
- [Special man screams]
- [groans]
- [Mira grunts]
- [clatters]
[gasps]
[Special man]
Are you okay, miss?
- Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
- [Chloe] Mira! Mira, Mira.
I'm fine.
Tell her, tell her, tell her.
[police] Confirm receipt.
Checking.
[Mira] Tell her.
We need you
to come here now! Fast!
[police] Stand by.
We're sending units to the premises.
Help us!
[both grunting]
[groans, pants]
[Leon grunts]
[Hughes] Missed!
- [grunts]
- [Leon] Whoa!
[grunts]
[Leon groans]
[Leon yells]
[grunting]
[shatters]
[groans]
[gasping]
- What's that?
- [blade rings]
I can't hear you.
That's flower power.
[grunts]
- [blossoms whipping]
- [groaning]
[moans]
[groans]
[coughing]
[gasps, chuckles]
It's flower power.
[sirens wailing]
[officer] Attention, this is the police!
You are ordered to lower
your weapons immediately
and stand down.
Any resistance will not be tolerated.
[guard]
Okay, okay! Don't shoot!
[police 1]
Don't move! Stay back!
- [guard] We're not resisting.
- Hey! Hands above your head!
[officer] Prepare
to be taken into custody.
This camp is now under police control.
[guard] Okay, okay.
[police 2]
All units, green light!
Engage and secure the targets.
Let's end this.
Securing the room!
[police 3] All clear.
[police 4] Two casualties.
No hostile activity detected.
[officer] What is this?
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
[Chloe] You're alive!
You... you did it! You're alive!
We did it.
Hey. Hey, hey. You okay?
[Chloe sighs]
[Chloe] You're gonna traumatize me,
you know that, huh?
[news anchor] Shocking
new details have emerged
about last week's raid
on a secret medical facility
outside the city,
where Senator Kessler
orchestrated a gruesome plot
to harvest brain matter from Specials.
But at the center
of this dramatic rescue was
an unnamed masked vigilante
clad in mechanical armor,
who intervened to save lives.
Some have claimed that he may be
the estranged son of Senator Kessler,
but officials have denied these rumors.
[squeaking]
[news anchor]
This mysterious figure,
along with a group of Specials,
infiltrated the facility,
dismantling the operation
and halting planned executions.
Their actions exposed Kessler's conspiracy
just as police arrived,
though the senator escaped capture.
In response, the government
has repealed Proposition 42,
ending segregation policies...
You know, I used to make
a great soup out of that.
- What, really?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Can you teach me that?
- Yeah, one day.
- Mira!
- Hey!
- The search for Kessler...
- [Chloe] Mira, hey!
And the identity
of the heroic masked vigilante
- remains unconfirmed.
- How are you feeling?
- Stay with us for updates.
- [Leon] Hey, come here.
[hoarsely] You're a...
- You know what?
- What?
[indistinct]
Oh, it's just...
how I like to roll.
Guys, are you done there yet?
No!
You know what, I'm sorry,
- but we're going shopping.
- No, Chloe.
- Let's go!
- Chloe.
[news anchor]
The circumstances around
Police Commander Hughes' demise
are yet to be disclosed,
leaving many questions unanswered.
As the city is slowly recovering
after these shocking revelations,
the search for
Senator Kessler intensifies.
We'll continue bringing you updates
on this developing story
as more information becomes available.
Stay tuned.
[plaintive music playing]
♪ We are like snow and fire ♪
♪ We're dancing on a wire ♪
♪ But now I realize ♪
♪ It's time to sympathize ♪
♪ To share and to admire ♪
♪ Reach out your hand
And we'll find harmony ♪
♪ The future is here
Bright and new ♪
♪ We all deserve
To be happy and free ♪
♪ Though you're nothing
Like me ♪
♪ And I'm nothing like you ♪
♪ Don't tell me your voice
Is a drop in the sea ♪
♪ 'Cause there's so much
You can do ♪
♪ Give me a chance
And I'll make you see ♪
♪ That you're someone like me ♪
♪ And I'm someone like you ♪
♪ Look at the bridges burning ♪
♪ Mm-hmm ♪
♪ The wheels of time
Are turning ♪
♪ What makes you think
I'm strange? ♪
♪ Don't be afraid to change ♪
♪ And see
The brand-new morning ♪
♪ Reach out your hand
And we'll find harmony ♪
♪ The future is here
Bright and new ♪
♪ We all deserve
To be happy and free ♪
♪ Though you're nothing
Like me ♪
♪ And I'm nothing like you ♪
♪ Don't tell me your voice
Is a drop in the sea ♪
♪ 'Cause there's so much
You can do ♪
♪ Give me a chance
And I'll make you see ♪
♪ That you're someone like me ♪
♪ And I'm someone like you ♪
♪ Reach out your hand
And we'll find harmony ♪
♪ The future is here
Bright and new ♪
♪ We all deserve
To be happy and free ♪
♪ Though you're nothing
Like me ♪
♪ And I'm nothing like you ♪
♪ Don't tell me your voice
Is a drop in the sea ♪
♪ 'Cause there's so much
You can do ♪
♪ Give me a chance
And I'll make you see ♪
♪ That you're someone like me ♪
♪ And I'm someone like you ♪
♪ Someone like you ♪