- See anyone?
- I don't think so.
Shh.
Greetings!
It's a nice little farm you got
on this piece of land!
Couldn't help but notice
how good some of your
crops are doing!
Best corn I've seen in years!
Hope you don't mind us
cutting through!
We were on our way east!
We're looking
for a place to rest!
So, I was thinking...
Get back! Go! Go!
Raine, any more?
Last one bee-lining
the way they came in.
He get away,
he bring more back.
I got him.
What you got
there, Manny?
Nothing.
Just a female intruder.
I got a headshot.
What'd I tell you
about wasting bullets?
You think bullets grow on trees?
Use your blade the next time.
How'd they get past
the perimeter?
Probably a short
in the fence again.
She looks like a dead Raine.
- Ugh. Why would you say that?
- All right. All right.
What? She does.
Danis, with your mother
in the corn.
Cookie, pick up shell casings.
Raine, with me.
Manny, you got the rest.
Let's have a full inventory
by lunch.
Yes, sir!
Oh, fuck! She's alive!
What'd I tell you about
the cussing?
- I meant, "Oh..."
- I don't give a damn
about what you meant.
I don't want that kind
of language around those two.
Missed the heart again.
You always miss the heart.
Hey. All right. All right.
You got your assignments.
Let's go.
Yes, ma'am.
Clean it up.
Manny!
Yes, ma'am.
No.
Not bad, but...
Okay.
Well, shit.
Excuse me.
- Your words to her mouth.
- I didn't even say anything.
What you waiting on, soldier?
You better get it on the floor
before I put you there.
- So, you think that's funny?
- I mean...
I mean, don't you owe us
a book report
on The Proletarian's Pocketbook?
Tell me something funny
about where that is.
I've been reading
something else.
Oh, and that is?
Parable of the Sower.
I did not assign that.
Thematically, it deals with so
much that is historically-based.
Okay, Classism,
genocide, oppression...
I need a report on what
you supposed to be reading
by Monday,
and since you so eager
on Octavia,
I want a report on Parable...
...by Wednesday.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Mm-hmm.
Twelve.
- Thirteen, 14.
- Oh.
Manny, what's up with the corn?
Why're the outer edges
turning so quick?
The beetles
and the cutworms are back.
I thought y'all rotated them.
He's trying a compound
of red dogwood
that the elders used to talk
to me about when I was young.
My morning and evening
perimeter checks
take a long time.
So, maybe Raine
and Danis could help?
If they help you,
then how we going to meet
the Kush quota?
Who going to get the Jeep back
up and running?
Ain't nobody pushing the seed
through the soil, is there?
No, ma'am.
Mm-hmm. We beat the blight.
We can beat this.
Takes hard work to survive.
You work now...
Rest when we're dead.
At least they're listening.
Mm.
Well, listen to this.
I want all that rot
out of the ground
so we can burn it
for Danis's Earthstrong.
And since Sarge is going
on a salvage run,
you can head to the depot
for a drop-off to Augusta
at the end of the week.
What? Again?
When do I get to go?
When you can follow directions
as well as he does.
Hey. Watch your six.
You see anybody, double back.
Do not engage.
These folks'll kill you
for the boots on your feet.
Yes, ma'am.
Here we go! Hey, yo!
Let's go! Let's go!
Hey yo! Here we go!
They wanted to stay the night.
Then they said
their boy was sick.
Now, they just won't leave.
Some of our tools
are missing, too.
We can't trust them.
Yo. Heading out
for a perimeter check.
Have fun!
Fight. Come on.
Dance or fight.
One or the other.
Yes. Come on.
That's good, Danis. Get into it.
Back in the barn again, eh?
Sarge.
Anybody out there
willing to trade?
Mm-hmm.
Nice.
Reload.
Nothing we've planted
has taken root.
If we don't start
growing viable crops,
we're all gonna starve.
This mold,
it's suffocating everything.
There's blood everywhere,
but no bodies.
Fucking craziest thing
I've seen in months.
They took everything.
How are we gonna survive
another winter?
Have you heard
from the Flemmings lately?
No.
Haven't heard from them
in over a week.
That's strange.
Jim never misses a check-in.
I'm starting to get worried
about them.
Me, too.
He was supposed to come by
and fix our solar array.
Augusta 24 to Freeman 1.
You copy? Over.
Afternoon, Augusta. Over.
You forget about me?
You know, everybody don't get
to sit on their porch
sipping lemonade while the help
do all the harvesting.
Some of us actually do
our own land with our own hands.
Says the gal sipping
my homebrew,
creeping other people's gossip.
Bitch, you don't know me.
At least you got
land producing
and kin to work it.
All these damn
children over here,
and not a one in the garden.
Ain't nobody tell you
to take in all them strays.
Thank God,
my niece came through
to help out for a bit.
I figure you've heard
about the attacks by now?
Thought your Union army
was gonna come
and take care of that shit.
Yeah. Well,
with the Flemmings missing,
that makes three farms
gone dark.
Starting to feel serious.
Farmers could use your help.
Union government sent
some soldiers...
Government ain't done nothing
but kill, steal,
and lock up Black folks since
before they even fell apart,
so I'm sorry.
I ain't stepping in to help
any of them motherfuckers.
But I ain't asking
you to help the Union.
Fuck 'em. It's farmers.
Even if you came out here,
trained them for, ah,
a couple days,
it'd make all the difference.
Sorry.
I can't risk the exposure.
They sent you doctors.
I'm sure your Union army
gonna show up soon enough.
In other words,
you still got
plenty of my moonshine,
so you ain't leaving
your little bunker.
Look, bitch.
You don't know me.
Don't make me pull
back my re-up.
Easy, now.
You keep the bud growing,
and I'll keep
the shine flowing.
Deal.
You know
I had to try, Hailey.
Anyway, stay vigilant.
Look.
It's been nearly a week
since we've had any food.
We'll do anything.
Chris is a strong boy.
He can help around...
Clare,
we gave you what we could.
But...
I know you've been lonely, so...
Look. I'm just saying,
maybe we can
work something out.
Augusta 24 to Freeman 1.
Do you copy? Over.
Afternoon, Augusta.
You heard about
the Flemmings by now, right?
Yeah.
Jim's a good man.
I hope they be alright, though.
They're not. They're dead.
Kids, too.
They were eaten, Hailey.
All of them.
Shit. Damn cannibals.
Scout said
they left a big footprint.
Now, this ain't
a small group out there.
How'd it go?
Found plenty.
Saw an ATV flipped
on the trail down by the ravine.
Thought it was Manny's
for a second.
Took some fire,
but besides a little blood,
it looked good.
I'll head back tomorrow,
strip it down.
But more importantly,
I found this.
Down by the waterworks,
there's a sealed bunker that had
a shit ton of preserved spices!
- Paprika.
- Ooh.
Jerk! Saffron.
Sarge don't even know
what saffron is, I bet.
Laugh all you want,
but people would kill for these.
Oh, you think it's funny, huh?
Raine, pull the tarp.
Oh! No!
- Is this a 1911?
- Looks like it.
The slide keeps jamming,
but you'll figure it out.
Hell yeah, I will.
You ever see a smile
like that before?
- What'd you get me?
- The greatest gift of all.
What is it?
Don't pout.
- Talked with Augusta.
- How's the old girl doing?
Flemmings are dead.
She know what happened?
She thinks flesh-eaters.
Her scout said
it was a massacre,
like a pack
of savage animals attacked.
I think people forget
what animals were like.
Manny's still out there.
He'll be fine.
He can handle himself.
Whoo! Yeah.
I am a soldier,
and I do not fear men!
I fear only God.
If I must die,
I will die a soldier of honor
who has nothing
to reproach himself for.
I will nonetheless
continue to see to it
that persons and property
are respected...
...to see to the prosperity
of the colony,
and to protect all individuals.
And what was Louverture
talking about?
The moral responsibility
of the soldier.
Feel like
I don't remember
the last time I did this shit.
But I can remember
I used to dance around a fire
with my home girls
in my mom's backyard
all the time
when I was Raine's age.
They deserve it.
You do too.
An Oglala chief once said,
"It is the mothers,
not the warriors,
who create a people
and guide their destiny."
That line work for you
back in the day?
Still does.
Where the hell you been?
Depot run for Augusta.
I didn't ask
where we sent you.
I asked you where you been.
I got sidetracked.
You get a pass off farm
and you miss
your sister's ceremony?
Go put the stash away
and pack it in.
You're done for tonight.
Babe?
- Y'all don't feel bad?
- About what?
We're just burning it.
We're burning the rot.
Feel bad about
having a good harvest?
It wouldn't be rotting
if we brought in some help.
From where?
The network. Other farms.
I don't know.
Exactly. You don't know.
You got no idea
what these people
are like out there.
Have you even tried
talking to them?
Boy, who the hell
you think you talking to?
You got a roof over your head,
food in your belly
while half the world starving,
and you got the nerve
to complain about that?
You see anybody around
here offering us anything? Hmm?
It's 'cause we don't need
nothing and nobody.
All we need
is what's right here, right now.
Clear?
Yes, ma'am.
You so concerned about the burn,
you can put it out yourself.
Girls! Time for shuteye!
- What?
Party done.
Our Father,
who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come.
Thy will be done on Earth
as it is in heaven.
Give us this day
our daily bread,
and forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive those
that trespass against us.
And lead us not into temptation
but deliver us from evil,
for thine is the kingdom,
the power, and the glory
forever and ever.
Amen.
How you doing, Sister Amanda?
Emmanuel. Come.
Come on.
You don't remember her.
This is your mother.
Go on. Say hello.
Go on.
It's alright.
I'd be upset, too.
Manny.
Ma! Can you knock?
Boy, save that talk
for your sisters.
Sarge is taking Danis
on a depot run tomorrow.
I want you with them.
Isn't going to the depot, like,
a father-daughter rite
of passage type of thing?
Look.
Farm been in the family
since 1852.
Your great ancestor
Fountain Freeman
worked it his entire life
after he escaped
from a Georgia plantation,
where he left behind
his entire family
so that his children could have
the chance to survive
on this Canadian soil.
This farm, Manny,
it's all we got
in the entire world.
And I ain't about to lose
it because you
and your sisters ain't got
a lick of perspective.
So, when you're told to go
with your stepfather
and your sister
to watch their back,
the only words
I should be hearing
coming out of your mouth
is "what?"
Yes, ma'am.
You my left hand, Manny.
I don't know what's been
going on with you lately.
But do better.
Clear.
And then
when I turned around...
...he was the only one
from the platoon
still going at it
with the bouncers.
That's how he lost
that back tooth.
So, love at first fight.
Yeah. Well, no, no, no,
'cause we lost track
of each other for a while there,
but...
when animals started dying...
there wasn't a lot of men
who understood how to live
in the natural world
like your father.
So, when I invited him to help,
he said this looked like
a good place for you to grow up.
But I think he just still had
a little crush on me.
Is this you?
Yep. That's me.
Are there any others
like us in the network?
Ain't nobody else out there
like us.
Most folks'd be surprised at
what we done built around here.
I mean any others my age.
You're okay.
Easy, now.
We come in peace.
Relax.
Everybody just relax.
We're Union, special envoy.
We're here to support
the local farming network.
There's a farm nearby.
That's where we're stationed.
That's why we're all on patrol.
Looks like somebody set up
quite the ambush.
Patrol?
You must be
at the Flemmings' property.
That's right.
You must be part of the network.
Augusta said the Flemmings
were killed weeks ago.
Let's go.
We should search them,
find out where they're from.
Make it fast.
Anything you find
we'll sort out later.
All right.
Shh.
Danis!
No. Bandage.
Baby, breathe!
I need your arm!
Relax your arm.
Hey.
You should get out
of those clothes.
We could've left...
but I said to search the bodies.
She's alive.
That's because of you...
not the other way around.
Freeman 1 to Augusta 24.
Do you copy?
We've had an incident. Over.
Augusta 24, this is Freeman 1.
The trade depot
has been compromised. Over.
Freeman 1 to Augusta 24.
We found your goddamn animals.
Now, pick up.
Stop right there!
Don't move. I will shoot you.
Turn around slowly.
I need help! Please!
We're on high alert
until further notice.
Everybody carries a sidearm
and a radio at all times,
in the fields,
when you sleep, everywhere.
Some of these people
are posing as Union soldiers
and workers,
trying to get information.
We can't trust what anyone says.
The only thing
we do know for sure
is they want
more than equipment or land.
- They're "W."
- What does that mean?
Means they eat people.
Y'all left a messy trail,
so make no mistake about it.
They're looking for us.
But what matters now
is how we react.
Raine, you're on inventory.
We need
a full count of reserves.
Medicine, ammo.
Yes, sir.
Cookie,
keep an eye on those monitors.
Manny, you, Hailey, and I
take inner perimeter.
How did they find the depot?
How they find anything?
Other people.
Watch your six. Shoot first.
Don't ask questions.
We ain't waiting on no revenge.
They going to end up
dead any damn way. Clear?
Yes, ma'am.
Hold on.
We need you
to look out for us now.
I know you don't feel good
about what happened yesterday,
but she's alive...
because you acted quickly.
You stepped up.
That's all I want.
Hey! Hey!
Hey. Stop. Stop fighting.
If I wanted to hurt you,
I would have done it already.
You're fine. I got you water.
You okay?
All right.
I'm gonna remove that,
but you can't scream.
Neither of us want that.
You understand?
I... I just...
I need to check that
laceration on your arm.
Slightly higher.
Okay.
Yeah. You need stitches.
How did it happen?
- Hey, I'm trying to help.
- Are you?
If there's bacteria present,
you could get an infection.
I'll leave the stitches
loose just in case...
Just give me the gag.
Shit.
Cookie, check the south
side monitors for movement.
Cookie, come in!
Raine, where is your sister?
No idea.
I'm on ammo and reserves.
Find your sister
and strap her down
to the monitors
in front of that chair.
And you get up top.
All right.
Yo, yo, yo. Just...
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Have you even done this before?
Yes, I have.
Yeah. This isn't gonna work.
What?
I have training.
You still have the gun.
All right. Okay.
I'm putting the needle down.
- And I'm loosening the ropes.
- Why are you narrating?
Just don't make me shoot you.
'Cause I will.
I'm sorry.
It's my mother.
She doesn't like strangers.
Neither do I.
Especially ones that kidnap me.
I'm not kidnapping you.
I just don't know who you are.
So, you lock me in a barn?
You would be dead
if I didn't put you in here!
Now, tell me who you are
and why you came here.
If you were gonna hurt me,
you would have done it already.
And the safety's on.
Manny,
what's your position?
Just west of the barn.
Circling back.
What you doing over there?
Just... just being thorough.
Boy, stop wasting time
and get your ass down
to the south perimeter.
Copy. On the way.
Hey. Hey, wait. Wait!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck.
You got to dip
the bannock in the stew.
Oh, I finished the, uh,
Proletarian's Pocketbook.
Not now.
Yeah, but I actually
did the report like you asked.
Okay.
- What's your problem?
- I don't want it.
What make you think
you got a choice?
I don't like it.
Fine. Don't eat.
- Give the rest to your sister.
- No! I want corn!
Check your voice before
I snatch it out of you.
You understand me, little girl?
So, Danis said that the bodies
were hanging upside down.
Why would they do that?
Bleed them out.
Blood makes the body rot faster.
You trying to preserve a body?
You think that's funny?
- I think he was just...
- No, Sarge.
I think he can
answer for himself.
You think bodies
hanging in the depot...
people we probably knew, dead,
soon to be eaten by the same
bastards that shot your sister,
you think that's funny?
No.
No. I... I think
you think it's a joke.
All of y'all.
Did I or did I not say
we were on high alert?
Was I unclear?
No, ma'am.
The whole property could
be lurking with these bastards,
but you wouldn't know 'cause
none of you was in your position
when I called!
And you got the audacity
to be sitting here
and be making jokes?
I think we should, uh...
I think we should do shit.
Baby girl...
I know I've been hard on y'all.
But you can't be
laid up in there
like this too much longer.
You got to fight.
If not for me,
then for the farm.
Because I can't lose
my sunshine.
Hmm?
You're not allowed
to leave us. You hear me?
You're not allow to leave us.
I need
some answers from you.
It's important.
There's... there's
been some incidents...
happening around here lately,
so everyone's...
a bit on edge.
Now, either you know exactly
what I'm talking about...
or you're really unlucky.
But if you don't
tell me something,
I won't be able to protect you.
You know, you got some
pretty major trust issues.
Guess I do.
It runs in the family.
You got separated
from your family?
Who attacked you?
Please. Just please
let me use the radio.
- How did you end up here?
- I followed the creek.
The creek is a ways away
from the farm.
- Why are you keeping me here?
- I... I just need...
No! I haven't done
anything to you!
Look. I need to find out
if they're alive!
I'm sorry.
I'm s... I'm sorry.
When I was a kid, people started
showing up without asking.
Since then,
my mother ain't been about
having random people around.
I'm sorry about what happened
to you and your family.
But I just need to find
the Freeman farm.
Look. If you could just
let me use the radio
to try to contact them.
And you'll never see me again.
- Why the Freemans?
- My aunt...
She told me they're the only
ones that could help.
Who's your aunt?
Manny?
Sorry. Uh, I was...
I was just thinking about,
uh, how I'mma tell my mom
about all this.
About you, when she wakes up.
But, uh, yeah.
Uh, I like to swim...
sometimes.
It's, uh, it's a proficient
way to exercise the body.
It's fun too.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
There's a river a mile
out that I go to.
I know that one.
I knew there was
somebody there that day.
Were you watching me?
No. No. No. I mean...
I mean, I saw you,
but I wasn't like
wa... watching you.
I found the river 'cause of you.
What?
I used to go for walks.
One day, I saw you
in the forest.
You went to the river to swim.
I've been going
there ever since.
What's this?
Hey. Hey. Hey, no, no, no.
- Where... where'd you get this?
- No, no, no, no.
No. Where'd you get this?
What's going on here?
Yeah.
Manny says
Grandpa loved barbecue.
Yeah, he liked to barbecue,
but not with this
colonial diabetes
in a synthetic pouch bullshit.
Do you have any idea
how old this shit is?
Half your blood
is Sweetgrass First Nation.
We cooked with fire on these
lands for thousands of years
before anyone,
and we don't fucking use
the fucking Burger
fucking Lord sauce!
- Dude.
- Hey, where you going?
To burn this
and any of the half-life shit
these scavengers found
in the salvage stock.
You know he's sensitive
about that shit.
Clear this up
and get on monitors.
We got a full day.
Where's Manny?
Probably in the barn again.
He goes there to jerk off.
What's a jerk off?
Mom?
Ma! Ma! Ma!
The fuck is wrong with you?
Don't hurt her!
Mom, listen to me!
- Don't you hurt her!
- No!
No! Mom! Please!
Mom, listen to me!
Boy, say one more word.
It'll be the last thing
she hears.
You understand me?
Now, look here,
I ain't my son,
so you ain't got nothing
to offer me but facts.
I'm gonna ask you
some questions,
and if I smell
one whiff of bullshit,
your brain's gonna be
fertilizer all over my fields.
You got me?
That's a question.
- Yes.
- Good. Who are you?
Dawn. My name is Dawn.
I don't give a damn
about your name.
Who are you?
I'm a nurse.
I'm part of a government
program, volunteers.
We're sent out to help farms
that need medical support.
- We were stationed...
- Why are you here?
- We were attacked.
- How many?
Uh, we were 12,
including the guards assigned...
I'm not asking about your group.
Who attacked you?
What they look like?
Uniform? Well-armed?
Those the descriptions
I'm looking for.
Not military.
They were rough-looking.
They... they just showed up!
Kind of like you.
How you find this farm?
I followed the river.
I was told to come here,
that the Freemans would help.
Bullshit. Union don't know
nothing about this farm,
and nobody around here
would ever tell you
to even come here for help.
Please. Please, please, my aunt,
my aunt Augusta Taylor!
She told me
to find the Freemans.
She told me to find you
for help, please!
You heading back or getting out?
A little bit of both.
Mind if I take a look?
Have at it.
Since I got back
from my last tour in Texas,
your father's been a blessing,
pulling the community together.
Well, you must at least
be happy to be back with him.
All due respect, Augusta,
you don't know me.
I came back for my son.
Felix can take up
his many mistakes with his God.
Ain't that what y'all say?
We do.
But I've seen enough
these past couple years...
restored my faith.
You act like
you ain't seen the shit I seen.
Public executions.
Bodies hanging
from street lamps,
whole suburbs on fire.
Don't confuse what's done
in God's name with God.
People did those things.
Not God.
People confuse they self
with God all the time,
just so they don't have to look
at they self in the mirror.
I ain't trying to tell you
how to live your life.
Well...
But I can say you need
to figure out a way to make sure
your past fights
don't become your future ones.
Or maybe not.
You do what you gotta do,
Hailey.
I'm just an old white bitch
who likes to hear the sound
of her own voice.
Oh, you weren't lying about
them loose lips, huh?
At least take me to dinner
before trying
to get in my pants.
Goddamn.
You a nasty old
little white woman.
It's true.
Good Lord.
Felix.
Hey, it's okay. I'm here.
Where's Manny?
Felix!
Just tell me where Manny is.
You wanna give me the gun?
Okay. Come here.
Come here. I got you.
I got you, baby.
I got you.
Freeman 1 to Augusta 24.
Do you copy? Over.
I repeat, do you copy?
Freeman 1 to Augusta 24.
Do you copy?
Augusta, it's Manny.
I think I found your niece,
but... she's in danger.
You need to answer,
please. Over.
Go on upstairs.
What are you doing here?
I'm trying... trying to
get Augusta on the radio.
Hello? Augusta?
Freeman 1 to Augusta 24.
Do you copy?
Augusta, I'm here.
Ma! Augusta's on the radio.
Freeman 1 to Augusta 24.
Augusta, I'm here.
Do you copy? Over.
Freeman 1 to Augusta 24.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What the hell is going on?
Boy, what are you doing?
Augusta was just on the radio.
I came down here to
contact her, but...
You talked to her?
No, no, no, but...
I tried, but she didn't answer.
But just then, the signal just
came back from her farm.
You expect me to believe that
she reached out to you?
- She did.
- Ma, I saw it. She did.
Maybe she needs our help.
We can go there and she can
confirm that she sent Dawn.
Augusta is a fucking Marine.
She can handle herself.
We ain't doing a goddamn thing,
but sitting here
and securing this farm.
- Then, let me go find her.
- We're down Danis already.
We're not splitting ranks
'cause of what some girl says.
Ma, I brought her here.
You're damn right
you brought her here.
And we ain't get
anything useful out of her
until I put a gun to her head.
Time and time again,
I keep asking you to step up
and you keep choosing yourself.
You chose to leave me
on this farm to go fight a war.
It is my job to make sure
you know how to continue.
It is my job to
make sure you survive.
"Survive, survive." Ma,
how are we supposed to survive
without people?
I can't even talk to a girl.
I don't even know
how to talk to a girl.
And what's
she gonna tell you, Manny?
That if given a chance to
escape, she'd do anything?
Including kill
every single one of us.
No, she's not gonna do that.
She's gon' play you.
She is lying.
No, Ma, you're lying!
You don't want us
to trust anyone else
because you can't
trust anyone else.
This is your miserable life,
not mine!
Who are you talking to?
Get off!
He knows
how to handle himself.
- I know.
- It's probably a trap.
I know.
- Take care of them.
- Yes, ma'am.
Looks deserted.
Pa? Pa?
All right.
Can you get up there?
Open the door.
What are we looking for?
They made me go to your farm.
They have my aunt
and the others.
They wanted me to find you.
To tell your family
they had my aunt,
so you'd split up and come here.
That's how they've been
taking over the farms,
by holding people's
families hostage.
I needed to save my people.
I'm dreaming.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I'm going up.
You stay here.
I'll be right back.
Oh, fuck.
Nohtâ, come in.
They're here, 800 yards out.
Nohtâ!
Nohtâ, do you copy?
Damn, girl.
That how you greet
an old friend?
Raine, do you copy?
Raine, come in!
Pa, come in!
They're crossing into the corn.
Listen to me.
Abandon your post.
Get down to the booth now!
Girl came by the farm...
said she was your niece.
Oh.
They made her go.
Figured you would shoot her.
Bitch, you don't know me.
Manny found her.
Kept her safe.
I thought
they came here.
Oh. Oh, thank you.
Oh, that boy. Such a good boy.
Oh, thank you, Manny.
Oh, Hailey Freeman,
you raised that boy right.
Thank God for you.
- Oh...
- I'm gonna get us out of here.
Hailey...
...outside...
- the sheds.
- I seen... I... I know.
- I've seen the barrels.
- No, no, no. Listen.
We hid some
of the children.
Every day is a lesson.
She said you were different
from the other ones around here.
Any of these other farms,
they'd go radio silent,
like clockwork.
Someone from nearby
would check in.
But you,
you really don't give a shit.
You're a different breed,
I'll give you that.
And you eat people.
While you just kill them.
Or you get your children
to do it.
The truth is,
we're a lot more alike
than you probably want to admit.
We do what we need to survive.
Fuck the foreplay, motherfucker.
You gonna do something,
then do it.
Mm.
The juice really is sweeter.
Tie her leg off.
The boys are gonna need
a meal when they get home.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
No! No!
No!
You motherfucker.
Thank you for the food.
I know you're mad,
but if I told you
it was an ambush,
you might not have come...
...and they would have died.
I'm gonna go find your aunt.
We may have to move quickly
when I get back.
Manny...
I'm sorry.
Fuck.
Go. With me.
Come on, man.
No, no, no! No! No! No! Come on!
Wait, wait, wait!
There are more of us
than you can imagine,
but I can make sure
none of them harm your family...
Only I can do that.
Nohtâ!
Danis radioed down.
She's hiding in your closet.
What happened?
I'm coming with you.
No.
Stay put. Both of you.
I mean it this time.
I'm sorry, old girl.
- Ma?
- Manny.
God damn it, Manny!
Boy, you can hate me
all you want,
but I can't lose you, too.
Ma, I can never hate you.
Everything you did, you had
to do to help us survive.
I just gotta find
my own way now.
Yeah.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Shutter on my mark.
Now!
- What the fuck?
- Hey!
You fucking shot me!
I got him!
Come on! Come on!
Raine, lights!
- Ma, wait.
- We got to go.
- I know, I know. Jus...
- Did you find my aunt?
I did, thanks to you.
Ma, we can't
just leave 'em here!
I know you think
you can't trust anyone,
but Augusta trusted us
to find them and we can
take them...
Boy, you ain't got to do
a damn speech for everything.
Grab them children and let's go.
Shit. Come on.
All right,
go, go, go, go, go, go.
Come on.
I got her. I got her.
Yeah, I got her. I got her.
Shh. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
You're safe. You're good.
Nohtâ!
Fuck. Fuck. No. No! No!
- Pa!
- Please!
Boy, what the hell you doing?
We can slip in this way.
Come on!
Come on.
- Come on, let's go.
- Hurry!
Come on, watch your head,
watch your head.
Watch your head. Come on,
come on, come on, come on.
Watch your head, watch
your head, watch your head.
- Go, go.
- Manny.
You know we're gonna talk
about this hole
in my fence later, right?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Uh-huh.
We got two left.
They're gonna burn
the house down.
We gotta get Pa out of here.
Take the kids to the booth!
I'll draw 'em away!
No! Ma!
Go!
Stay put till I get there!
Go.
She's been shot.
Check the rooms.
I need to keep working
on her to save her.
Cookie, gauze.
No!
You. Move over there.
You, over here.
Do it.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
Jackpot.
Run!
Eat this, motherfucker.
Fuck! Seriously?
You fucking little fucker.
Nohtâ.
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
- Stay low.
- Go! Go! Go!
Stay behind me.
Stay close.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on!
Manny!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Come on in.
What the fuck is she doing here?
And who the fuck are they?
Just get them inside!
No, she's not fucking...
What is your problem?
What's with you
and kidnapping people?
First her,
and now all of these...
Can you all just shut up?
I need gauze,
a suture kit, and saline.
Can you tell him I need him
to try and stay awake?
Nohtâ, she says
you need to stay awake.
He understands English?
Him speak pretty good, too.
You're fucking with me.
I speak the language
of my ancestors.
Will still live on
through my daughters
when I'm gone.
And yeah, I'm fucking with you.
It's a hell of a lot funnier
when you don't understand
what I'm saying.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Shh...
Raine, I'm going for Ma.
Thank you.
Oh, shit.
- You're okay.
- How many left?
- None. We're good.
- Danis...
- She's fine. She's fine.
- Cook... Sarge...
- Ma. Ma. Ma.
- Raine...
Ma. We're good.
We're good.
I thought I told you
to stay in the booth.
Yeah. Yeah, you did.
I...
Ma. Ma.
Ma? Ma.
Ma! Ma! No, no! No!
Ma. Ma!
No, no. You're gonna be fine.
You're gonna be fine.
Ma! Ma! No!