That's right...
I have to go.
CP, this is Alpha 2.
Nothing unusual to report at Point 1.
Alpha 2, this is CP.
Continue your observation mission.
Emergency Kaiju alert. Emergency Kaiju alert.
An emergency Kaiju alert
has just been issued. I repeat...
Emergency Kaiju Alert
An emergency Kaiju alert
has been issued for the South, Central,
Yokohama Gate
Emergency Evacuation Shelter
Stay calm and head for the shelter!
and Isogo wards in Yokohama City,
Kanagawa Prefecture.
Citizens in the designated areas are
to seek refuge in a shelter immediately.
The epicenter's projected route is...
Target is currently en route
from Yatobashi to Yamashita-cho.
Its estimated body length is 60 meters.
Fortitude 3.5. Over.
No one on thermals
within a 3 kilometer radius.
Roger.
All units, open fire.
I repeat. Open fire.
Roger. Luring target to the TO.
Fire.
Special
Kaiju Alert
Kaiju Alert in
Yokohama City
Will we succeed in getting its attention?
Which division will come, you think?
Since this is Yokohama,
it'll be the Third Division.
Man, they got its guts over everything!
Looks like it'll be overtime
for me for a while.
Okay, time to get to work.
Yes, sir!
I can't cut through this!
The fat's jamming the saw!
Bring me the heat chainsaw!
Sure.
Hey, don't start lifting that yet!
Oww...
Over here! Bring a stretcher!
Don't worry. It only got on your skin.
I've had it happen to me a bunch of times.
Make sure you file for workers' comp!
Will do!
Things always get messy
when the Third Division's involved.
Hard to tell what's organs and what's not.
Anyway... do they really expect us
to finish this by the end of the week?
Kafka, got a new job for you.
We have an opening elsewhere on-site.
Where?
The intestines.
I've already got permission from management.
Have fun!
I'm so tired!
I can still smell it...
And now, tonight's feature story.
Today, the Kaiju that appeared
in Yokohama was defeated
thanks to the heroic efforts of
the Defense Force's Third Division.
Third Division Greeted With Cheers
Special Report: The Third Division
And the division's leader is none
other than the famous Captain Mina Ashiro.
Captain     Mina Ashiro
Not only is she captain
at the young age of 27,
she's also defeated several hundred Kaiju.
An Up-Close Look at The Third Division
Special Report: The Third Division
Captain               Mina Ashiro
Let's wipe out all the Kaiju together!
Special Report: The Third Division
Captain        Mina Ashiro
Her cool, elegant demeanor makes her
the most popular of all the division captains!
They say she's in the running
to be corps commander, too.
Special Report: The Third Division
Future                 Corps Commander
She's definitely one to keep an eye on.
How'd I wind up on this side of things?
Morning...
Oh, good, you're here!
Kafka!
Come here for a second!
I'll go get things ready.
Thanks.
Morning, Kafka.
We've got a new part-timer starting today.
This is Ichikawa-kun.
He says he's aiming
to join the Defense Force!
This guy was once like you!
He gave up, though, and now
he's part of the furniture here!
Well, this sucks...
Toku-san... You're freaking the new kid out.
Why?
Why'd you give up?
I did do my best, you know, but...
No matter how good you are,
there's always somebody better.
I guess you could say I reached
the limit of how far I could go?
You'll understand when you're older.
I won't.
'Cause I'll never give up.
So I won't know until the day I die.
Not that I'd even want to.
I'll go change.
Huh... I thought you
and him would get along.
That's not fair!
There's nothing I could've said
that wouldn't make me sound like a loser!
Is giving up that bad?
Hey!
Okay, let's get started.
Miike's team can stay on bone cleaning duty.
Get the important ones ready for Izumo Tech.
On it!
Yoshimura's team can start
taking apart the legs.
Dump all of it.
Okay.
New kid, you're on intestines.
Follow me.
Yes, sir.
Hah! That's what you get!
You too, Kafka.
Follow me.
Me too?!
Two days in a row!
You're good with intestine work, though.
Damn it! Fine, I'll do it!
He complains, but he never says no.
He would've done a great job
in the Defense Force if he'd passed the test.
Yeah, he's definitely feeling it.
And so am I.
Tea
You...
Is that lunch box all the food you brought?
I don't feel up to eating it.
Yeah, I bet.
Here.
What?
Multivitamin
You can have it.
You need to get something in your stomach,
or you won't last the afternoon.
I'm fine...
And these. You can have these, too.
These help a lot.
I can't understand what you're saying,
but I really don't need those.
Quit playing coy and put them in your nose!
Stop it! Senpai, really...
Yeah, everybody's like
that their first time.
You're all responsible
for carrying your own stuff.
Good work today!
Good work today.
See you tomorrow.
Sure, goodnight.
Well, at least the smelliest
part of the job is over.
Senpai.
Oh, Ichikawa.
What, did you come to get back
at me for what I did at lunch?
Thanks to you...
Thanks to you, I made
it through my first day.
Thank you.
That's all.
Goodnight.
Oh, and...
They're raising the age limit to 32.
For applicants to the Defense Force.
Not enough young people anymore, apparently.
I can't tell you what to do
with your life, of course...
But when you talked about
giving up, you looked so sad.
Of course, I really don't care at all.
So if I'm wrong, you can just give up
and I won't care.
Goodnight!
Ichikawa!
Thanks.
You're a lot nicer than I thought you were.
I told you, I really don't—
Senpa—
A Yoju?
Ichikawa, run!
Get as far away from here as you can!
Once you're sure you're safe, call it in!
You can't fight this thing alone!
Another body won't make any difference!
You want to join the Defense Force, right?
So why would you let
yourself get killed here?!
Over here! I'm the one you want!
There!
Whew!
Now it can't follow me...
Damn it all!
It's all gone...
Your place, my place, our school...
Yeah...
I'll get you for this, Kaiju!
I was so close to beating Guramon!
That's what you're sad about?
I'm sad that Miiko died.
Miiko, your calico cat?
I'm going to join the Defense Force!
Kafka has arrived!
Mina has arrived!
That's dumb. You're just a little kid!
For Miiko
You're in elementary school too, Kafka!
All right...
Let's see who can be
a cooler Defense Force officer!
Let's wipe out all the Kaiju together!
Damn it all! It wasn't supposed to be like this!
Damn it...
I ain't afraid of you, Kaiju!
Aim for the leg...
Aim...
Ichikawa...
You idiot!
Why?
I called it in!
That's not what I meant!
If I left you to die here...
I'd never make it in the Defense Force!
Application Result
Mr. Kafka Hibino
We regret to inform you that you have not passed
the first round of the recently concluded
Anti-Kaiju Defense Force selection tests.
Damn it...
Anti-Kaiju Defense Force
Accepting Applicants
Damn it...
Damn it.
I'm so powerless...
Nothing's changed at all!
I can't protect anything.
Not my game console, or my friend's cat...
Or even the new kid at my job!
Damn it!
Target down.
We have wounded.
Initiating rescue operations.
Igarashi. Takaragi.
Take care of the wounded.
Everyone else, follow me.
We'll check the area for any other Yoju.
You okay?
Don't move. Just stay there.
Mina's incredible...
She took down that scary
thing in less than a second...
She's left me in the dust.
Senpai!
When that Kaiju showed up
and you told me to run away...
If you hadn't saved my life then,
I would've died today.
You were so cool.
Let's see who can be
a cooler Defense Force officer!
You really should think
about joining the Defense Force.
I mean, it's your call. Not my problem.
Yeah...
I can't just keep running forever!
Thanks, Ichikawa.
You really are a nice guy.
I don't think there's anything
wrong with giving up...
But it's not good to lie to yourself.
I'm going to give
the Defense Force another go—
Found you.
A Kai... A Kai—
Senpai?
Are your wounds bothering you?
Senpai!
WHAAAT?!
Ichikawa! It's me! It's me!
Don't freak out like that, please!
Oh! We can show him
it's a misunderstanding!
Senpai, give him a smile!
A-A smile?
Got it! A smile!
Yeah, that's definitely not gonna work.
I knew it!
Hey, gramps, you okay?
Huh?
D-Did I do that?
I'm, like, totally a Kaiju!
Wh-What was that? An explosion?
Huh? A Kaiju?
The Defense Force is probably on their way!
Let's get going, Senpai!
H-Hey! Wait!
If you encounter a Kaiju,
the first thing you do is target the legs.
You bind it so it can't move...
I get a little scared.
Of what?
When I imagine fighting a Kaiju
that's so much bigger than I am.
Don't worry!
Whenever you get scared...
I'll always be right by your side!
Liar.
Yes?
A Kaiju has appeared at
Yokohama South General Hospital?
Yes.
No.
It's fine.
I'll get my team ready,
and we'll eliminate it.
A small Kaiju has appeared within Yokohama.
I repeat. A small Kaiju
has appeared within Yokohama.
The Kaiju is fleeing from
Yokohama South General Hospital.
It's heading for an evacuated area.
That's a cordon.
Once we're inside, there'll be nobody around.
Senpai?
Shh! Something's coming.
The Defense Force?
No, it's coming from underground...
What's this?
Another Kaiju?
Car 2, maintain course.
We'll head to the new location.
It's the same type
as the one that attacked us.
You can tell?
Luckily, they already started evacuating
when the alert was sent out about you.
Let's just pray there'll be no casualties.
Mommy! Mommy!
Run... quickly!
Just wait! I'll get you out!
Run!
No! You're coming with me!
Run... please...
Please!
No!
Mommy!
Please! Please! Please!
W...
Wow. I'm really strong.
You okay?
Yeah, of course. Sorry. Sorry.
Um...
Smile!
No!
G-Got it! I'll be gone
in a moment! So don't cry!
Senpai!
H-Hey...
Mommy! Mommy!
She's just unconscious. She'll be fine.
Really?
Yeah.
Ichikawa, get them out of here.
What are you going to do?
I'm gonna try...
Punching it as hard as I can.
Let's get out of here!
One, two...
Three!
You, uh...
definitely can't do that to a person.
What the hell?
Drawing Based on Witness Testimony
Kaiju No. 8.
This is the eighth Kaiju that
the Defense Force has given a codename.
Kaiju No. 8
(Witness Composite)
They still haven't found this guy?
Right?
No. 8 remains at large, with
the Defense Force actively searching for it.
He's probably dead already.
This has gotten way out of hand...
Male Eyewitness (103)
It's been three months.
Senpai became the first Kaiju in history
to escape the Defense Force,
Male Eyewitness (103)
The Secret World of Cryptids
and every Defense Force officer
in the country is looking for him now.
Oh, right. Ichikawa.
You and Kafka got something in the mail.
Application Result
We are pleased to inform you that you have passed the first round
of the recently concluded Anti-Kaiju Defense Force selection tests.
Oh, you did it!
Nice!
Yes!
Wow...
So this is the Defense Force's
Tachikawa Base...
I went to Kumagaya Base on
a field trip once, but this one's way bigger.
They share this area
with a Self-Defense Forces garrison.
When something happens,
both sides work together
to dispatch troops all over western Tokyo.
If you transformed here,
you'd be dead within seconds.
No point in getting scared.
Let's go!
Hey, old man.
We're a little early,
but let's get checked in.
I said, old man.
Senpai?
Yes. You.
Pay attention, old man.
Old Man?
Me?
That rust bucket is yours, right?
It's in the way.
I can't park my car, so move it.
There's tons of open spots!
I want to park it there.
My lucky number today is five.
Your lucky number?
What's the deal with this little brat?
Come with me.
This young man is going to
teach you a lesson in manners.
Whatever.
I'll move it myself.
What are you going to do?
That suit...
Monster Sweeper, Inc.
No! The company car!
Wh-Who are you?
Examinee number 2016.
Kikoru Shinomiya.
My hobby is murdering Kaiju.
Remember that.
Shinomiya? That last name...
Anyway, old man...
Did you know you smell like a Kaiju?
Here are the applicants this year.
A lot look pretty interesting.
Huh? What the hell is this?
I can't keep up at all!
I'd been keeping up my training out of habit!
And I do really hard
physical work every day!
Before, I used to be just below average!
But now...
Do you really get this weak
when you turn thirty?
Damn it... My body doesn't want to move at all!
Kafka Hibino
Fitness Exam Rank
219 out of 225
I feel so much better.
You really didn't use
your Kaiju power, did you?
Everybody's put
in a lot of effort to get here.
It wouldn't be fair to use my power.
I thought it would be so cool
to say that, but I should've used it!
It's been ages since I last tried this test!
There's still hope.
Let's bet it all on the next part!
Area 2
Wow.
It's huge.
I'm Third Division Vice-Captain Hoshina.
I'm the head of the second
stage exam committee this year.
You'll be doing your aptitude test
here in this area.
Your task in this area will be
to find Kaiju and...
Neutralize them!
But we can't send you in empty-handed,
so you'll be wearing these.
What is this?
Wow...
It's pressing itself up against my body...
I'll start measuring the unleashed combat power
of the ones who have their suits on.
Reno Ichikawa. Unleashed combat power, 8%.
Haruichi Izumo, 18%.
Aoi Kaguragi, 15%.
Iharu Furuhashi, 14%.
What?
We're lucky to get one
applicant a year above 10%.
This year might be a bumper crop
like we've never seen before.
Kikoru Shinomiya...
Unleashed combat power, 46%!
Whoa. She's already at the level
of a platoon leader.
This has to be a record for anybody
who hasn't officially joined yet...
Just 8%...
Oh, there's no reason
to get down, Ichikawa-kun.
Honestly, if you don't have a zero
at this point, you pass.
And I've never even seen a zero!
Grr!
Kafka Hibino...
Unleashed combat power, 0%!
What's wrong with him?
Wow, he's my first zero!
Huh? Are the measurements wrong?
Just give me a little more time!
I'm trying to squeeze it out!
You're not trying to take a dump!
You can't squeeze it out!
Why?
Damn it! There's got to be some trick!
I need to figure it out
before the exam ends!
Defense Force Screening Exam Final Test
I'll explain the test.
Your targets are a Honju and 36 Yoju
that have been placed throughout
the urban training area.
These Kaiju caused sixteen
fatalities in Hachioji last year.
We captured them alive
to serve as training aids.
You're going to fight them
with anti-Kaiju weapons.
You'll all be tracked with a drone
that will monitor your actions.
If we decide your life is in danger,
we'll remotely activate
the shield on your suit,
but be aware this will mean you fail.
To be honest, I can't guarantee
you'll survive this next part.
Only if you're willing
to accept that, then...
Go.
What the hell?
Yoju 12 down.
Yoju 03 down.
Wow...
Damn it! Let's get going too!
Don't fall behind, Ichikawa!
That's my line!
This equipment is incredibly heavy
without the suit helping you!
Only I, the zero, can understand this!
Don't make it sound cool!
Oh, I forgot.
Captain Mina Ashiro is here
for the test as well.
Do your best to look good for her.
That's right...
Who cares if I'm a zero?
Calm down. This is your last chance.
Ichikawa.
Why are the examining officers
following us all with drones?
True... If all they cared about
was how many Kaiju you killed,
they could just track
that number with sensors.
Yup.
They're testing our abilities,
but also how we can adapt to the situation.
Which means since we lack that kind of
offensive capability, we should...
Yup!
Support all the attackers as best we can!
Right!
Those hooves...
I know this guy!
The one we did a joint
disposal of with Iida Cleaners!
So that's why they included
these in our equipment...
Eat this!
A stun grenade?
It's got weak eyesight
but incredibly good hearing!
Once you've deafened them,
they're easy targets!
The stomach!
The skin on its stomach
is weaker than most Kaiju!
Aim for the stomach!
What?
We did it, Senpai!
Yeah, we've taken apart more
Kaiju bodies than we can count!
We know you guys inside and out!
I'll throw the next one!
Let's keep it up!
Another one?
Senpai!
Area Delta, Number 2032 injured.
Irregularities detected in vitals.
Yoju 23 is continuing to approach.
Prepare the remote shield.
Oww...
Stand up...
She's...
She's watching!
Figured he'd be the first to drop out.
He was a funny guy... Too bad.
Activating remote shield!
When I'm on the battlefield,
nobody gets to quit.
Kikoru! You saved me!
I'll go defeat them,
so you just lie on the ground like a loser.
She's going after the main target?
I'll take it out first!
Better pay attention!
She's so much more powerful!
Is that really the same equipment we've got?
So your unleashed combat power makes
that much of a difference, huh?
Damn it... I'll go too!
Senpai!
It's broken?
I can't stand up!
2032, can you hear me?
This is Hoshina in the operation room.
We're seeing irregularities in your vitals.
Multiple fractures, probably.
Possibly organ damage.
No...
As the exam proctor,
I recommend you drop out.
Even those shields aren't perfect.
I'm the one who decides if I give up or not.
Senpai.
I'm too old for dreams...
I know I look like an idiot, but...
I've decided to bet my
whole life up to this point
and chase my dreams again!
This time...
This time, I'm not giving up, no matter what!
Are these guys for real?
Let's go, Ichikawa!
By our powers combined!
Everyone's staring at me,
and I'm really embarrassed!
Follow Kikoru and don't worry about me!
Hurry!
Got it!
Hang on tight!
He's so damn fast!
She's not even letting us help her, huh?
Number 2016 has taken down
the last Yoju in Area Delta,
and is now engaging the Honju!
Last one.
Th-The Honju has been destroyed.
The final stage of the exam is complete!
Recovering drones.
Good work, everyone.
That girl is just too goddamn fast!
Combination
Undone
Kikoru Shinomiya's even more
powerful than the rumors say.
So she's enough to catch even your eye, huh?
I'd imagined we'd see
about thirty people drop out.
But nobody did.
And with only minimal injuries.
And it's clearly all thanks to her.
That's what you'd expect to see
from Director Shinomiya's daughter.
She'll be a big shot in the Defense Force
someday, that's for sure.
And a ray of hope for this country.
I was perfect, wasn't I, Daddy?
Now, time to go back and laugh
at Kafka Hibino a fourth time...
Kikoru Shinomiya was every bit
the monster everybody said she was, right?
Yeah.
But thanks to her, we made it to the end.
Now we just wait for the results.
Yes...
What?
What's going on?
Senpai, let's get out of here!
What the hell are you?
There, there. I'll let you handle this.
It can talk?!
You're still moving?
What's going on?
Die!
Make sure you chew before you swallow.
Something's wrong!
Abnormalities detected in 2016's vitals!
What's going on? What's happening out there?
I don't know!
But we're picking up live signals
from the Kaiju they already killed!
What?
Those Kaiju shouldn't be able to
come back to life like that...
We have an estimated fortitude
for the revived Honju!
It's 6.4!
It's more powerful now?
Hoshina, we're heading out there.
Roger.
Emergency. Emergency.
Examinees are to immediately
evacuate to the nearest shelter.
I say again...
Evacuate?
I can't evacuate...
If somebody doesn't stop this thing,
lots of people will die!
I can still move. I can still fight!
When I'm on the battlefield...
Nobody dies!
Be perfect, for the sake
of this nation's future!
I need to be perfect!
Honju sighted!
Kikoru Shinomiya is nearby, and injured!
The Honju's severed offensive
uniorgan has regenerated!
It's condensing energy for an attack!
I'm done for...
I'm sorry, Daddy.
I couldn't be perfect.
I'm sorry.
You did a great job, Kikoru!
What are you doing here?
Because you worked so hard,
everybody was able to evacuate!
Now leave the rest to me!
What?
What's going on?
You're a Kaiju?
Kikoru.
Please! Please!
Please don't tell
the Defense Force about this!
Please!
I'll tell you more in a bit.
I only need a sec to kick this thing's ass.
So just relax and get some rest.
I'm detecting a mysterious ultra-powerful
energy source near the Honju!
It might be a new Kaiju!
Another one?
Do we have visual?
The explosion knocked out our comms network.
We do not have visual.
Wait, is this number right?
Fortitude 9.8?
Impossible.
The blast must've scrambled
the measurement system.
R-Right?
Otherwise it'd be one of
the most powerful Kaiju in history!
Sorry. I'm running out of time here.
So I'm cleaning you up...
with one punch!
Who is this guy?
Looks like you'll be okay.
I'm glad you're safe!
But let me say one thing.
You can't put yourself in danger like that!
You too!
Ichikawa! What are you doing here?
You ran off while my back was turned,
and sure enough,
I find you here, transformed!
I was thinking maybe I could
just transform a part of my body.
But when I saw the Honju
I was like, "No way!"
You need to be more careful!
Shinomiya!
Ashiro and Hoshina have
arrived at the scene.
What is this?
What would you have to do to cause this?
I've seen this before somewhere...
This is the operation room.
An additional three examinees
have arrived at Shelter 6.
It's Kikoru Shinomiya,
Reno Ichikawa, and Kafka Hibino.
They're safe, huh?
All examinees are now accounted for.
Roger.
During a Defense Force
selection exam,
an unusual incident took place,
with Kaiju suddenly coming back to life...
Radio
There were several injuries during
the incident, but zero fatalities.
The Kaiju that came back to life
were defeated by members
Zero? Zero?
of the Third Division
who were present during the exam...
No, no, no. No way there were zero.
Or is one of these
"Captain" people that strong?
Kaiju No. 8 remains at large,
and the Bureau of Neutralization
is enhancing security...
No. 8? What?
Um... this is how you answer a phone, right?
Hey, where've you been?
Breaktime's over, you know.
Uh...
Don't you "uh" me. Get back here.
Right.
I'll be right back.
Sheesh. Humans are so particular about time.
Sorry, sorry.
I had a bad case of diarrhea.
You had us all worried, you know?
Tell someone where you're going
before you hole up in the toilets, new kid.
Sorry, Toku-san.
Hey, I heard there was
an accident at the exam site.
Seriously?
Oops.
Are Kafka and Ichikawa okay?
How careless of me.
Okay, we open it on three.
No matter how it turns out,
this is my last shot.
Will the path I'm on
take me all the way to her?
Time to find out!
One, two...
Examinee Number 2032
Kafka Hibino
Examination Results
Kikoru Shinomiya will speak
on behalf of the incoming class!
Yes, ma'am!
The twenty-seven of you are,
as of this moment,
officers in the Defense Force!
On behalf of all 27 of us, I swear that
we will lay down our lives for the cause!
You helped a lot during
the incident after the exam.
Thanks to you, there were no casualties.
Again, you have my thanks.
It wasn't me who defeated them.
Kafka Hibino, you should be
the one hearing these words...
So why aren't you here?
This is humiliating!
I still want some answers
from you about that Kaiju form, too!
I'm not gonna let you just up
and disappear on me!
Excuse me!
Sorry to interrupt the ceremony!
The old dude!
Number 2032. Kafka Hibino. Failed.
He scored the lowest on the fitness exam
and a zero on his aptitude test,
so there's not much to talk about.
Yeah, sounds about right to me.
I don't—
All righty, I'll take him, then.
Sure, his numbers are below average.
He's not cut out to be an officer.
But in actual combat during the last exam,
he was able to locate the enemy's weak points,
and he aided the overall effort by prioritizing
helping others over his own kill count.
Not many people are capable of that.
And more than anything...
The dude was funny as hell.
Is that really all you care about?
I'm not sure if we'll ever
promote him to a full officer,
but I'll bring him into my platoon as a
cadet and give him some more training.
He's being enrolled as a cadet,
so I had him sit out the induction ceremony.
Glad to hear it, Kafka Hibino.
All right, now that we're all here,
let's have a word from Captain Ashiro.
Everyone, I'm glad that you all decided
to volunteer for the Defense Force,
enduring and passing that difficult exam.
I thank you.
These last few years,
we've seen far more Kaiju with far
higher fortitudes than was typical before.
We've also now seen this strange incident
where dead Kaiju came back to life.
These neutralization missions
will be extremely dangerous.
Some of you may die on your very first one.
There's absolutely no guarantee
that you'll survive.
But even so...
No, that's exactly why...
I want you to entrust your lives to me.
I swear to be standing at the very front,
acting as both your shield and spear!
I'll...
I'll be standing next to you soon, Mina!
Huh?
Awkward
What the hell?!
He's gone crazy!
He's calling Captain Ashiro by her first name!
Oops
Kaf...
Kafka Hibino.
You spoke out of turn and
disrespected a superior officer.
You owe me one hundred push-ups.
I didn't mean to say that out loud!
He's already at it!
Captain Ashiro, I think you're going
a little easy on the guy...
Huh?
Did I just see her smile?
He just got here, and he's
already bringing the comedy?
I know, right? I told you.
This place can get pretty gloomy sometimes.
We need a guy like him.
You can do it, old dude!
Ninety-nine...
One hundred!
You really hung in there, old dude!
Arms tight against your sides, wrists slack.
Let your instincts aim the reticle,
and don't pull the trigger...
Squeeze it!
Squeeze!
Reno Ichikawa,
fire training exercise complete.
Time, 2:35.
Estimated unleashed combat power, 18%.
Haruichi-kun, I've got a question!
I'm impressed. He's grown
a lot in a very short time.
Reno set another personal best!
Come on!
I won't let him beat me!
Iharu Furuhashi, 2:15.
Estimated unleashed combat power, 20%.
Hell yeah!
I win!
Don't get cocky, Reno.
I won't.
Kikoru Shinomiya, 1:16.
Estimated unleashed combat power, 55%.
Play nice, kids. Both of your scores
combined are still worse than mine.
Sheesh.
The more I train, the more she makes me
realize just how average I am.
You've got time to worry
about people better than you?
My combat power's as good as yours now.
Got to worry about those above me
and those below me, huh?
I'll set a new best when it's my turn, Aoi.
Kafka Hibino, 6:39.
Estimated combat power, 1%.
Yes!
Did you see that, Kikoru?
I finally turned that zero into a one!
Stay away from me!
Well? Tell me how awesome I am.
Why are you acting so happy
when you're 1% and I'm 55%?
Kafka!
Yes, Vice-Captain Hoshina?
You're never gonna be
a full officer at this rate.
You'll be fired in three months.
What?
Old dude...
Okay, ten laps around the perimeter
and we call it a day.
What?
You complained, so now it's fifteen.
Get going!
Yes, sir!
The new recruits have quite
a few rivalries between them already, huh?
Yeah.
Looks like, even when I'm not around,
they're competing with each other
and making each other better.
I'm so tired!
We had to do laps at the end, too...
The vice-captain is a monster.
Looks like you need to build
up some more muscle, Reno.
No, yours aren't that
much different than mine.
Our fitness eval scores are always the same.
Are you serious? Look at these biceps!
They look like they're just for show to me.
Reno's more stubborn than I thought.
Quit bickering over stupid stuff, kids.
Behold the muscles
of a hard-working grown-up!
Wow, you're getting some bulk...
Exhale
Bounce
Aww, so close!
You can't be in the Defense
Force with a spare tire!
That's very rude, Iharu-kun.
It'll happen to you too
when you hit 28 or so!
I've actually lost a ton of weight!
Forget the stomach.
I challenge you all to arm wrestling!
Yer on!
All right.
Okay, let me just set a towel down here...
Huh. It's awful noisy tonight.
What's wrong?
We were just talking about
how scrawny we all were.
Just what you'd expect
from a former military officer.
What matters isn't your muscles!
Right, Reno?
You know, it's been a while
since I've done anything like this.
Yes, what matters is your results!
I'll outdo you in training tomorrow!
You won't beat me!
I don't have a lot of time.
I'll have to work twice
as hard as everybody.
Working hard, huh?
Vice-Captain Hoshina!
Getting your Zs is part of the job too.
I can't let myself get fired.
For Captain Ashiro?
How did you know?!
Remember what you said
at the induction ceremony?
I promised I'd fight by her side!
Oh, you know I could interpret that as saying
you're going to steal my vice-captain spot.
I didn't mean it like that...
No.
I do mean it. I'll do my best
to make it happen.
Fine.
You've got two more hours.
Turn off the lights when
you leave and lock the door.
I'm not letting you have my
spot next to Captain Ashiro.
Thank you—
And...
You shouldn't get too close
to the rest of the officers.
In this line of work, something could
happen to any one of them at any time.
A Kaiju?
This isn't a training exercise, is it?
See what I just said?
Let's go. It's time for your first mission.
Emergency Kaiju alert.
The epicenter is located in Sagamihara.
Citizens in the surrounding area are asked
to follow JSDF orders and evacuate.
Stay calm, everyone!
Kaiju Evacuation
There's room on the buses for everyone!
All platoons and all JSDF
forces are ready to go.
Captain Ashiro has reached the sniper point.
Please lure the Honju to Sector Bravo
and provide fire support.
Roger that.
JSDF Artillery Regiment Command Post,
now initiating fire support
for the Defense Force.
Time for your big debut.
Start by showing your superiors
just how damn good you really are.
It's begun.
But it's not like the exam.
I feel strangely calm...
I can tell the suit is helping me.
Unleashing combat power!
You're too far out in front!
Your combat power is 1%,
so stay in the rear!
There we go!
Two legs down. Finish it!
Well done, Furuhashi!
There we go!
You see that, Reno?
Did you do that by yourself?
Yes.
I swapped out the burst rounds
in my gun for freeze rounds.
I think it's a better fit for my style.
I can slow down the enemy while I fight.
I think, once I get the hang of this,
I'll be even better at hunting Kaiju.
Our observation teams have verified
that Sector Juliet is clear of Yoju.
All Yoju have been defeated.
The kill reports keep coming.
They're all amazing!
Ikaruga Platoon will advance,
with Ichikawa and Furuhashi at the forefront.
Ichikawa and Iharu, too?
This is no good.
Everyone's working so hard,
and I'm just slowing them down.
Isn't there anything I can do?
Senpai, look!
What the hell's he doing?
Wow, even with just 1%,
the suit makes it easy
to dismantle their bodies.
This is a pretty standard structure
for fungal-type Kaiju,
but the core's not where it usually is.
Where is it?
If it's not here, then maybe over there?
Wait a second...
Vice-Captain Hoshina,
I've located the Yoju core.
What?
It's at the base of the neck,
but there are hard, fibrous muscles on top
of it that serve as its backbone.
Officers with weaker attack power
might need to hit them from the sides.
And there's one more thing.
This one's important.
The Yoju have reproductive organs too.
The white, bumpy organs near their rears.
If we don't destroy those organs,
their corpses might spawn new Yoju.
Kafka.
That's some damn fine work.
Okonogi-chan, share that news
with the rest of the team.
Roger that.
Sharing information on Yoju core
and reproductive organs with all officers.
I'm sure you picked up some
of that at your last job,
but I guess your studying really paid off.
Well done.
I helped the Defense Force!
Honju has reached the designated
combat initiation point.
JSDF ground and air forces
are requested to withdraw.
Target sighted.
Compensation for Coriolis force,
gravitational force complete.
No additional targets in area.
One round loaded and ready to fire.
Roger.
All conditions met for firing to commence.
You are cleared to fire.
Kafka-kun...
This is who I am right now.
Unleashed combat power, 96%.
Watch this one closely, Kafka.
Fire.
That's the power of the person
you're trying to stand beside.
Second round loaded and ready to fire.
Roger.
You are cleared to fire.
Honju vital signs have disappeared.
It's collapsing!
Damn it!
It's totally different from when you look
at it on TV or through binoculars!
She's incredible!
Just like I thought.
Here they come.
The Yoju inside its body
swarm out now that it's dead.
All right, guys! We're wrapping up here.
Once we're done cleaning up the riff-raff,
we can all go home
and have a yummy breakfast.
Kafka Hibino.
As of today, as of this moment,
you are no longer a cadet,
but a full-fledged Defense Force officer.
I swear to give everything
I have to the fight.
A-Anyway, I'll be going...
Don't get too excited.
You're a long way from being
able to fight by my side.
So Mina does remember!
Yeah, just you wait, Mina!
Give me fifty push-ups for failing
to address a superior by their title.
I did it again!
Kaiju No. 8...
and No. 9 need to be discussed at HQ,
which requires my presence.
Whew...
I've put Vice-Captain Hoshina in charge,
so ask him about the paperwork.
Roger!
And... it was Hoshina who
recommended you for full officer.
Of course, it only happened because
of your success in the last battle.
The vice-captain...
Live up to his expectations.
Roger!
I can't let him down!
Okay, I've finally taken the first step!
Time to get some sleep
so I can be ready for tomorrow.
Getting rest is part of the job, too...
Operation room, what's going on?
We're seeing dozens of Kaiju inside the base!
It appears the Kaiju have
attacked us from the air!
Estimated fortitudes 6.1, 6.3, 6.2, 6.5...
Each and every one of them is...
K-Kaiju!
...Honju class?!
This is Hoshina.
Captain Ashiro is away,
so I'll be giving the orders here.
Anybody who's on night watch,
take battle stations.
Get the off-duty officers here, too.
Roger!
Lure as many as you can into the training area!
Make damn sure none of them get off the base!
But we're not hearing any reports
of damage from outside the base...
That can't mean...
Are they after the base itself?
What's going on?
Wyvern-type Kaiju?
Those things are bad news...
Wyvern types?
But then... that means something's not right.
Vice-Captain!
Kafka! You're still alive, huh?
Yes.
But there's something wrong here.
You only see about a dozen or so
wyvern-type Kaiju each year,
but there's always something
they have in common.
They're always alone.
But these guys showed up in a group!
Yeah. Which can only mean one thing...
There's something out there that's got
the power to make them swallow their pride,
and the intelligence to act
with a goal in mind.
An incredibly powerful leader.
Target sighted.
I'm hangin' up, Kafka.
Are you the strongest human at this base?
It can speak, too?
The captain ain't here,
so yeah, I guess.
I see.
That settles it, then. You are my prey.
Honju's estimated fortitude
calculations complete!
It's 8.3... That's Daikaiju class!
Ikaruga, do you copy?
Yes, sir!
You command the fight against the Yoju.
Prioritize keeping them in the base
and away from civilians,
and keeping the main building online.
Roger!
As for the Honju, I'm...
You dodged it?
You pass.
This thing's punches hit like a meteor strike!
One solid hit, and I'm a dead man.
Fire!
It's unharmed?
Gunners, swap to oscillator rounds.
Don't attack from the front!
That voice... Hibino?
You need to attack their backs...
They're the same type that was reported in '03!
Senpai?
The old dude?
The front is easier to hit
when they're in flight,
but the skin's thick!
The skin on the back is as thin as possible
to help keep their weight down!
Nice, Hibino!
Split up to run decoy in front
while hitting the back!
Roger!
I'll be the decoy.
Get behind it, Haruichi.
You owe me one for this!
He's good.
Combat power fully unleashed!
What?
The Kaiju are working together?
It's no good! We can't get behind them!
We've failed as well!
Another Kaiju blocked us!
What do we do?
If we can't get behind them, then how...
There's another way.
Shinomiya?
I just...
use my unstoppable power...
to smash right through their front armor!
Sh-Shinomiya's new weapon?
Hits pretty hard, for a prototype.
One thing I don't like, though,
is that such an ugly weapon doesn't suit me.
Squadron-Style Axe Technique
Number One: Falling Thunder!
Number Two: Water Skimmer!
Now, who's next?
Above me?
Freeze rounds?!
Reno...
Be careful, Shinomiya.
They attack from the sky, too.
You aren't going anywhere!
I'm impressed he can fight like that
against Kaiju this strong.
Number Three: Half Moon!
Did she get them?
Reno.
You can have the honor of helping me.
If you can keep up, that is.
Sounds great to me.
All right, search the battlefield for openings
and catch the enemy off guard!
You heard that, right?
Yeah.
Which means we need to...
Hit the enemy from behind
when Shinomiya's got 'em distracted!
Vice-Captain!
You really are strong.
Here in the training grounds,
I don't have to worry about
hurting the officers if I go all out.
Unleashed combat power, 92%!
All right, time to neutralize this Kaiju.
They're so powerful!
I won't make it in time...
If I just transform part of my body...
H-Hibino-san?
You okay, Minase?
Thanks!
I guess you learned to use your suit, huh?
W-Well, I am a full officer,
you know! So of course...
Hibino-san, behind you!
Kikoru!
You okay, Senpai?
Reno and I will distract the Kaiju.
Get the wounded out of here while we do.
Roger!
Senpai...
Just don't take any risks, please.
You're a full officer now.
Believe in your fellow officers.
Right.
I'm off!
When did they learn to work together like that?
Report! Nakanoshima's unit has arrived!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Ikaruga!
Ebina's unit has arrived as well and is
heading to assist in the southern quadrant!
Thought you could get away with this,
huh, you damn Kaiju?
The senior officers who were off duty?
They came to help!
This is Takao Platoon.
We'll attack the Yoju in the air
with freeze rounds.
This is Itakura Platoon.
We've secured the warehouse area.
We're starting to push them back,
even without the captain here!
We're gonna win this fight.
Again...
You're slicing right through
the tiny gaps in my exoskeleton.
This is no fun at all.
Now that I know exactly what
you're aiming for, it's easy for me to...
handle it...
Hoshina-Style Sword-Slay Technique
Number Two: Cross Slasher.
Number Four: Wild Slasher.
So aiming for the gaps was just a diversion?
Yeah, this is how a fight should be!
A head-on battle against an opponent
whose strength rivals your own!
Rivals! Rivals! Rivals! Rivals!
Huh?
Your core's a lot smaller than I thought.
Number Six:
Eightfold Slasher.
Got him!
That's the vice-captain for you!
You see that, Kaiju?!
This is...
Not yet!
Vice-Captain?
Hibino-san?
It got bigger?!
The position of its core shifted,
so I wasn't able to fully destroy it?
Its fortitude is rising alongside the heat...
No way!
Fortitude...
9.0!
It's massive...
The vice-captain can't handle
something that size by himself.
Number Three: Return Slasher!
Your speed won't save you!
Incredible. He's still fighting it,
even after it transformed. But...
My blades aren't cutting all the way through!
This is why I hate giant Kaiju!
Exceeding operational limits.
Cancel maximum release immediately.
I'm overheating?
It's been ten minutes
since your maximum release!
You have to shut it down!
Self-destructed?
That's just like a Kaiju.
Totally cold-blooded.
They're like living missiles!
But...
It gave me a nice smoke screen.
Number Six!
Limit exceeded. Canceling maximum release.
Seek medical treatment immediately.
Vice-Captain! Vice-Captain!
Vice-Captain!
Don't worry... I'm still alive.
Oww...
I had my shields set to max...
That Kaiju hits like a truck.
I lost my maximum release.
So what now?
What can I do?
Guess I'd better keep
fighting till the end, too.
But you can't fight like that!
Hoshina-Style Sword-Slay Technique
Number One: Air Slasher!
I've figured it out now.
You can't defeat me with those weapons.
But she told me something else...
When it's time for me to shoot my foe,
will you clear a path for me?
She left me in charge of the base.
I'll protect it if it kills me!
Vice-Captain!
I don't have a choice!
No...
No, Senpai!
I'm sorry, Ichikawa.
My comrades' lives are more important!
Great work, everyone.
That voice...
Hey, Kaiju.
I win this fight.
I'm the vice-captain of the base.
My job's to pass the baton to her.
Okonogi. This is an emergency,
so I'm skipping the procedures.
Yes, ma'am!
Time to blow this thing up.
I was right to make you my vice-captain.
Unleashed combat power, 96%.
Now it's time for me to shoot my foe.
Th-The Honju is down!
We did it.
Yeah.
Yes!
That's Captain Ashiro for you, huh?
I was right...
This is the Defense Force
I've wanted to be in since I was a kid.
They're all so cool...
I want to stand right there
with them someday...
Your face is a mess.
What? How can you say that when
I'm having an emotional moment?!
You've got a heart of stone!
We're just getting started.
Let's do our best, too.
Yeah.
The captain and I will deal with the Yoju.
No, you get some rest.
You too, Captain.
Leave the Yoju to us.
No, I'm fine.
What is that?
The Yoju...
So that last scream wasn't its death rattle?
Energy levels rising...
It's an ultra-massive Yoju bomb!
The blast's estimated impact
is equal to 20 kilotons of TNT!
That's the same as a nuclear bomb!
No! Don't shoot!
Evacuate!
No... there's no time...
If that thing hits the ground...
Human...
Looks like this fight is a draw.
No, Senpai!
Kafka?!
Get back here! There's nothing you can do!
Wait...
How's he so fast?
That's not what 1% unleashed
combat power looks like!
We're detecting a gigantic
Kaiju signal above the base!
Fortitude 9.8!
This signal, it's...
Kaiju No. 8!
Sorry, Ichikawa.
I don't think I can keep my promise.
You're a long way from being
able to fight by my side.
Mina... I...
I...
Senpai!
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
Everyone else risked their
lives during this fight!
I can't be the only one
who puts his own safety first!
I'm part of the Defense Force, too!
I'm an officer of the Third Division, too!
So now it's my turn!
Everyone, on the ground!
Shields at max!
Well, now I've done it...
My arms and legs
are barely holding together...
I'm too old to be pulling stunts like that.
Kafka Hibino...
No...
Kaiju No. 8.
I'm taking you into custody.
Kafka Hibino.
In accordance with Article 13
of the Defense Force Code,
you are to be transferred
to the Ariake Maritime Base.
To ensure the safety of the citizenry—
Mina.
Can I still... try to stand by your side?
Yeah.
I'll always be waiting.
Idiot.
Third Defense Force, salute!
Jeez... are you okay, Senpai?
Why would you eat
until you got sick like that?
I was thinking about the track and field
meet we have this weekend and got nervous...
Most people stop eating
when they get nervous!
Ichikawa...
Right, right. I bought you a bunch of stuff.
Want some water?
You're not planning on solving your
stomach troubles by becoming a Kaiju, right?
9:30 AM
The weather's so nice.
I feel bad for Senpai, but it's
the perfect day to be off duty.
Oh! So you and Reno are off tomorrow, huh?
The Previous Day
Yup. You too, Iharu?
Most people in our class have
the same day off.
That's right.
There's a place I want to go!
Wow, that sounds great!
Ask somebody to go with you, old guy?
N-No...
Soshiro Hoshina
So Vice-Captain Hoshina is off, too?
That's rare.
Okay...  I've actually got
the whole day off for once.
Time to enjoy it!
Time to make today a great day!
And here I am doing my
daily weight training!
I didn't even think about it!
How do you spend days off, again?
What's everybody doing, I wonder?
What, Ichikawa, you don't know
how to spend your days off?
You're young. You need to have fun.
Eventually, I'll show you the fun ways
to spend your off time in Tachikawa.
Um, are you going somewhere
today, Vice-Captain?
Yeah.
I've got somewhere to be.
Reno? What are you doing?
Iharu-kun? What's that?
Was gonna tune up my ride.
Anyway, were you talking
about something with the vice-captain?
Yes.
But it seemed like he was
doing something important.
He's a mysterious guy.
What did he mean when
he said he had somewhere to be?
It's gotta be a lady!
No, it didn't feel like that...
I wonder what she's like!
Is she pretty?
He's not listening.
Hmm... that tense air about him...
I know! He must be doing
extra training on his day off!
That's why he's so strong—
No! He's a man too after all!
Come closer! I'll give you a good petting!
That's just your type, Iharu-kun.
I don't think he's the kind of guy who'd...
He's allowed to fall in love!
I mean, he is, but...
But I don't think that's it!
Not today, at least...
Want to bet, then?
Loser buys dinner.
Huh?
Iharu-kun, this is a bad idea!
It's the only way to settle the bet!
But we can't be tailing the vice-captain...
If he finds us, we're in
for a lot worse than a lecture!
He won't find out! We've got our helmets on!
And it sounds fun, right?
Just shut up and come with me.
You weren't doing anything anyway, right?
He knew...
Look! He's going into the parking lot!
Hokkaido Products Exhibition
Welcome!
Thank you!
It's delicious!
Try a free sample!
Mission complete, Captain Ashiro.
I have attained the limited-run
top-quality dried squid snacks.
Ezo
Excellent work.
Well done as always, Hoshina.
You have my gratitude.
Dried squid?
What? Well, that sucks.
So he was on an errand
for Captain Ashiro, huh?
I'm kind of jealous...
There's two weird guys over there!
Don't look!
Looks like you lost the bet.
It wasn't his girlfriend.
Wait, no!
I said "a lady"!
So I win, just barely.
A lady, sure, but she's his boss!
That doesn't count.
What did you say?
Sorry to ask you to do something like that.
It's been a while
since you've had a day off.
No, it was on the way to where I'm going.
It's fine.
Goodbye.
Now, then...
I can't say I'm excited for this...
But time to go.
Next is his real destination?
Look! The bet's not over!
Let's go, Reno!
Come on!
Nobody's stopping.
We could just walk.
What's up?
Vice-Captain Hoshina!
Um, we have a reservation for lunch,
but we're running late.
We can't get a taxi to stop.
I'll give you a ride.
No, we couldn't ask you to do that!
It's fine! Hop in!
Th-Thanks...
We appreciate it!
We owe you one!
Thank you!
Bye!
Welcome!
Oh, you're on the reservation list, right?
Right this way!
Oh, how about this one?
It's got a nice design,
so it'd go well with the fire grill.
Yeah, this should give
the place some atmosphere.
No, I don't recommend it.
It's not that strong, or that functional.
And you can't carry it in a backpack either.
You might end up having to
carry it for days at a time.
You need to be ready to survive
even the harshest circumstances.
I think you're imagining
something totally different.
Got a second?
Vice-Captain!
So basically...
So yeah, buy an older model for cheap.
They go for about this much.
Oh! I see!
Good to know!
Good luck bargain-hunting.
That was close!
Can I take your order?
Sorry!
We're not really getting anywhere.
This is...
I can't wait to find out
what it is he's doing!
What are you doing here?
Shinomiya!
You don't have to get
that surprised, do you?
And Minase-san and Igarashi-san...
what a coincidence.
We all went out to lunch!
And get this!
Who do you think drove us to the restaurant?
Your hint is...
Sorry, we know the answer.
You're tailing Vice-Captain Hoshina?!
Poking into someone's
private life like that...
In America you'd get sued!
Boys are such idiots.
Wait, where's Kafka Hibino?
He's off today too, right?
Oh, you've got a good grasp of his schedule.
Were you hoping to see him?
No way!
I was just thinking that it was nice not to
have him sweating up the place on my day off!
What are you doing?
More people!
You're tailing the vice-captain?
I'm surprised. I didn't think you
were the type, Shinomiya.
No way! I would never...!
Shh! Shh! He'll hear you!
I could never be so vulgar!
Quiet.
Nobody saw you, right?
Who knows?
But I'm not the type that stands out.
Sarcastic asshole.
So, where's the stuff?
Oh, right.
There they are!
The guy's huge!
This is it.
I'll be going on ahead, then.
You come at the designated time.
We'll meet at the rendezvous spot.
Wh-What the hell was that?
I'm kind of scared...
C-Calm down, everyone!
That case...
It looked like the ones we use
to transport equipment.
Don't tell me he's selling stuff
on the black market...
The black market?!
More and more Kaiju have been showing up,
which means more money
is needed to fund our defenses.
What we just saw was...
him selling weapons to the underworld
to get the money we need.
Maybe, anyway.
Well, the vice-captain's one
person who would never do that,
so there must be another reason...
What's wrong with him?!
He's doing the dirty work all alone
so we don't have to...
I'll stop him, even if I have
to punch him in the face!
No, I'm sure that's not it.
Corruption is wrong!
The Defense Force is a symbol of justice!
We'll make him realize this is wrong!
Yes, let's do it!
Wait... Shinomiya, Reno,
don't tell me you're agreeing with them!
Out of the question.
I knew I could count on you, Aoi!
I'm glad somebody agrees with me!
If it's true, he needs
to be punished appropriately.
First, we need to see
if it's true, Haruichi.
You agree with me, right?
Wait!
He drove off somewhere!
Hunt for him!
No luck...
Any other suspicious buildings
or abandoned warehouses around here?
At this rate, the vice-captain
will become a criminal!
No... If it's true, he's already a criminal!
And I don't think it's true, anyway.
We need to hurry...
Vice-Captain!
You saw the handover, didn't you?
Why...
Why would you do something like that?
It makes me so sad and angry!
Sheesh... If you've seen it,
then I've got no choice.
You'll have to help me.
No...
I'm so disappointed in you!
Just... stop this!
Vice-Captain Hoshina!
It's really him!
Wow!
He's so cool!
I think he's cute!
Is what you were doing...?
Tachikawa Disaster Prevention Center
We cannot possibly thank
you enough, Hoshina-san!
The star of our show is the
"Mina Ashiro Sniper Experience," but...
I've never seen these before!
And thanks to you, we've finally
finished our new virtual Soshiro Hoshina!
And our permanent exhibit, as well.
It's all thanks to your kindness in donating
those old weapons you don't use anymore!
Now, if you could just put your
autograph on the wall like I asked...
I'd rather not.
It's like I'm pretending to be a star.
You really are a star, though!
Just shut up and sign the wall.
These are the new recruits this term, right?
Y-Yes.
You know us?
I've seen you in
the Defense Force newsletter.
It gets sent out to former members.
I used to be in the Third Division.
Right now I serve as the vice-president
of this Disaster Prevention Center.
Apologies, sir!
It's fine.
Relax.
Let's do it together!
Wow, it's the vice-captain!
They're from a day care in the area.
We invited them for a private opening
of the renovated exhibits.
Everyone!
These men and women will show you
how to play with the exhibits!
Ask them anything!
Wow!
All right!
Correct!
I'm next!
I made it up to the top!
Sorry!
Ichikawa!
Here.
Herbal Medicine
This is Chinese medicine that'll
heal any stomach problems instantly.
This brand's stuff works great.
Give this to Kafka.
Thank you!
I really appreciate it!
He ate too much last night, right?
So he couldn't come with you today.
I figured he's probably lying in his room.
Um, where'd you buy this stuff?
The department store.
While I was getting those snacks.
He saw us right at the start!
He really is a scary man...
I'm glad this place is popular.
It helps us, because people learn
about the Defense Force.
And this might be
where we get our new recruits.
Yes. But our ideal is...
that when they're grown up,
nobody will need the Defense Force anymore.
Yes.
Your juniors are working
hard towards that goal.
Emergency Kaiju alert!
A Kaiju has appeared in Chofu City.
Fortitude 3.8.
Its speed is extremely...
Just in case, I'll get the kids to safety.
The JSDF is presently evacuating citizens.
This way, everyone! It's fine!
Yeah. Don't worry about a thing.
We'll go beat up the scary Kaiju.
I hope you'll be cheering us on.
Yeah!
Are you going, Hoshina?
Yeah. Take care of things here.
Vice-Captain, we'll provide support!
No need to bother.
Its fortitude isn't that high.
And you're not on the team that's
supposed to respond to emergencies today...
Sheesh.
You're all a bunch of workaholics.
Sir, if I may...
You're wearing your suit under your outfit.
You're the guy who doesn't
know how to take a day off.
It's not good to tease
your superior officer.
Well, whatever.
Let's go.
Roger!
You can do it!
Go get 'em!
Hoshina...
I really appreciate what you did today.
By the way,
why did you suddenly change the handover
point for the weapons and equipment?
Aww, I saw them following me,
so I decided to play a little prank.
It certainly did make
for an interesting day off.
Hokkaido Milk Coffee