[♪ ominous music playing]
[beeping]
[music stops]
-[water splashing]
-[rowers shouting in Old Norse]
[rowers shouting]
[in English]
Our men will be glad to return home.
We will have more gold than we can carry.
You and I do not fight for gold.
Remember that, Anders.
I know, Mother.
Tell me why we fight.
Because our enemy still lives.
Good.
I pray you bloody your spear tonight.
You are ready now.
You all have traveled far
and miss the warmth of home.
You seek gold and plunder,
but tonight, think of only one thing.
Killing the Krivich.
Anders, my beautiful son.
If I should fall tonight,
avenge me.
[warriors shouting]
[warriors groaning, screaming]
[prisoner panting]
There are no others, Sea Queen.
We searched every dwelling
and slew every Krivich tribesman.
This is the last one.
[prisoner panting, grunting]
You know who I am.
You are Ursa,
Valkyrie of the Northern Seas.
I am Ursa, daughter of Einar.
I am searching for your leader,
the chieftain called Zoran.
-[pants]
-[Ursa] Where is he?
[spits, chuckles]
You might look around and think,
"I am the lucky one. I am still alive."
You would be wrong.
They are the lucky ones.
No, no, no, no, no!
[screams]
[groaning]
Where is Zoran?
[panting]
-[screams]
-Where?
[grunts] He…
[panting]
He has built an immense fortress
many leagues to the east,
high above Lake Ladoga.
Let me live. Please.
[groans, panting]
Give him a merciful death.
[prisoner] You'll never go to Valhalla.
If you kill an unarmed prisoner,
the All-father will not allow you in,
and I… [breathes shakily]
…I will haunt your dreams.
Little boy, you and I will meet
in the darkness,
and I will haunt your--
[screams]
Sorry, young one.
We'll find Zoran before the overwinter.
[warrior] Forget all this.
[warriors shouting]
[engine whirring]
[wolves howling]
All of you, get your rest.
Tomorrow we bring death.
Anders.
You are old enough now.
It's time I tell you what happened
to your grandfather.
[whimpering]
Papa?
[gasps, sobbing]
Papa, get up.
Get up, Papa, please.
Please get up. [whimpering]
[panting] Slay me, Zoran.
You have won that honor.
[sobbing] No, Papa.
But free my daughter.
-[sighs]
-[grunts, whimpering]
Your family must learn its lesson.
She will die by my hand.
Or you will die by hers.
-Please, Papa, please. Please.
-[panting]
Ursa.
[sobs] Papa?
[Einar] Listen to these words.
No. Please, Papa.
-No, I can't, I can't. [whimpering]
-This blood… Listen!
-Please, please, please…
-[Einar] This blood marks you
as my father marked me,
and his father marked him.
No… [breathing shakily] …no…
You will find strength in this…
Please, please, no.
…I promise.
I can't. [sobbing]
-Please.
-Avenge me.
Please, please… [stammering]
-Please, no, Pa--
-Avenge me!
[screams, muffled]
[screams]
[sobbing] Papa!
[Ursa] That day,
something was born inside of me.
A monster!
With claws around my heart,
breathing fire into my soul.
[sighs]
And there is only one way to kill it.
[predator growling]
Well, what's the plan, Ursa?
I'm going to knock on the front door.
[sighs]
[Ursa exclaims]
[grunting]
[warriors grunting, exclaiming]
[grunts]
-[exclaims]
-[warrior 1 groaning]
[warriors shout]
[grunts]
[warriors screaming, shouting]
[exclaims]
[all grunting]
[warrior 2 exclaims]
[pants]
[warrior 3 shouts]
[warrior 4 screams]
[grunts]
[screaming]
[warriors shout]
[screams]
-[roars]
-[followers roar]
[pants]
[warrior groans]
[warriors grunting, groaning]
[grunts]
[splutters]
[pants, grunts]
[panting]
[grunts, sighs]
[footsteps thudding]
[predator growling]
Hear me, Zoran,
for fate has brought us together again.
Some call me Stormbringer Shieldmaiden,
the Valkyrie of the Northern Seas.
My name is Ursa, daughter of Einar.
Who?
Ursa, daughter of--
[laughs] You look like
a Viking washerwoman.
These floors could use a scrubbing.
Silence!
My father, Einar,
-was the earl of Ladoga.
-[chuckling]
I remember now.
Einar and you.
Oh, you were a lovely little one.
It appears your cowardice
has ruined your looks.
You are the coward!
You killed your own father.
Any decent Krivich child would have
fought me, even if it meant death.
You were so afraid, you still are.
Fear is etched on your face.
Your father must have been ashamed
to have such a weak and disgusting daugh--
[gags]
[breathing shakily]
[vibrations throbbing]
[shouts]
-[groaning]
-[warriors gasping]
[warriors shouting, exclaiming]
[older warrior] Grendel!
-The boy!
-[grunts]
[roars]
[breathes shakily, grunts]
[warriors shouting, grunting]
[shouting]
[grunts]
[shrieks]
[predator growls]
[panting]
[shouting]
[grunts]
[sneers]
[growls]
[snarls]
[growling]
[Anders grunting]
[growls]
[pants, shouts]
[grunts]
-[grunting, straining]
-[predator growling]
[groans]
[grunts]
[powering up]
[vibrations throbbing]
[strains, shouts]
[grunts]
[building creaks]
[screams]
[grunts]
[strains]
[gasps]
[grunts, screams]
[grunts]
-Avenge me!
-[young Ursa screams]
[breathing softly]
[footstep thuds]
[thudding]
[growling]
[electronic crackling]
[snorts]
[snarling]
[inhales]
[panting]
[footsteps thudding]
[growls]
[panting]
-[growling]
-[powering up]
[shock wave booms]
[shock waves booming]
[growling]
[roaring]
-[grunts]
-[growls]
[grunts]
[snarls]
[panting]
[grunts]
[shouts]
-[growls, snarls]
-[powering up]
[pants]
[grunts]
[clangs]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
[roars]
[chain clangs]
[snarling]
[clanging]
[powering up]
[snarls]
[clangs]
[grunts]
[grunts, panting]
[wind howling]
No.
No, no, no, no.
[panting]
Anders.
[gasps]
Anders? Anders?
[breathing shakily]
Mother.
Oh, Anders.
[pants, sighs]
My son.
[Anders continues breathing shakily]
Oh. Oh.
Anders. Anders. [inhales sharply]
Mother… [groans]
…did you kill the monster?
[grunts]
No. [breathes shakily]
Anders, no, no.
[gasps] My son.
[gasping, panting]
[sobbing]
[birds chirping]
[person, in Japanese]
[grunting]
[chuckles]
[grunts]
[wood creaks]
[grunting]
[shouts]
[♪ inspirational music playing]
[both blowing]
[music fading]
[grunts]
[child breathing shakily]
[inhales sharply, breathes shakily]
[breathing deeply]
[exhales sharply]
[sighs]
[breathing shakily]
[inhales sharply]
[shouting]
[grunting]
[pants]
[panting]
[pants, winces]
[whimpers]
[breathing shakily]
[sighs]
[bell tolling]
[tolling continues]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[grunts]
[music stops]
[growls]
[growling]
[grunts]
Hmm?
Hmm.
[grunts]
[chokes]
[snorts]
[grunting, panting]
[predator growling softly]
[growling softly]
[guard exclaims]
[gasps, grunts]
[grunts, strains]
-[guard groans, grunts]
-[attacker panting]
[gasps, grunts]
[exclaims]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[panting]
[grunts]
[pants, sighs]
[groans]
-[grunts]
-[guard 2 grunts]
-[groans]
[bell tolling]
[sighs]
-[tolling continues]
-[sighs]
[screams]
[grunts]
[exhales sharply]
[guard gasps]
[guard groaning]
[guards scream, groan]
[breathes heavily]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[predator growling softly]
[exhales deeply]
[grunts]
[both grunting]
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
[pants]
[both grunt]
[sighs]
[shouts]
[both grunting]
[pants]
Hmm.
[grunts]
[grumbles, chuckles]
[thuds, clangs]
[both grunting]
-[groans]
-[chuckles]
[grunting]
[straining]
[pants, grunts]
[predator growling softly]
[both grunting]
-[panting]
-[grunts]
-[strains]
-[panting]
-[both grunting]
[grunts, panting]
-[wood creaks]
-[gasps]
-[screaming]
[panting]
[breathing shakily]
[wood creaking]
[thuds]
[breathing shakily]
[growls]
[snarls]
[guards shouting]
[growls]
-[snarls]
-[gasps]
[shouts]
[whimpers, screams]
[snarls]
-[growling]
-[shrieks]
[groans]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[snarls]
[grunting]
[predator growling]
-[grunts]
-[groaning]
[gasps, grunting]
[straining, panting]
-[predator growls]
-[roof thuds]
[predator breathing heavily]
[footsteps thudding]
-[grunts]
-[predator roars]
[grunts, panting]
[predator growling]
-[grunting]
-[roof tiles clattering]
[pants]
[predator snarls]
[growls]
[grunting]
[gasping]
[coughs, panting]
[grunts]
[shouts]
[both grunting]
-[groans]
-[shushes]
[pants]
[growls]
[grunts]
[panting]
[growls]
[groans]
[grunting]
[roars, snarls]
[both panting]
[growls]
[grunts]
[both straining]
-[snarls]
-[groans]
[exclaims]
[grunts, straining]
-[snarls]
-[grunts]
[growls]
[snarling]
[groans]
[strains]
[snarls]
-[grunting]
-[growling]
[snarls]
[grunting]
[pants]
[grunts]
[growls]
-[gasps]
-[device beeping]
[panting]
[snarls]
[grunts]
-[groans]
-[grunts]
[panting]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[shouts]
[snarls]
[♪ sorrowful music playing]
[panting, straining]
[birds chirping]
[♪ boogie-woogie music playing]
[propeller whirring]
[engine revving]
[music continues]
Whoo-hoo!
[inhales deeply]
-[tires squeak]
-[engine sputtering]
[music stops]
[groans]
[in Spanish]
[in English] I was gonna ask you
the same question.
-[propeller whirring]
-You were gonna ask me?
You're the one with a broken engine.
Oh, you want to fly.
[chuckles]
You think you're Charles Lindbergh?
I'd like to be a pilot one day.
What's wrong with that?
Ah, Charles Lindbergh
could fix his own car.
I think he's got people
that do that for him, Dad.
[speaks Spanish]
[sighs]
[engine starts]
[engine purrs]
[sighs]
[engine stops]
Well, Dad?
You figure it out?
You flooded the engine.
-So how do we fix it?
-You tell me, Lindbergh.
-Dad.
- Mijo, listen to me.
Dreams are fuel.
But you're not flying
because you can't make the engine work.
I'm done bailing you out, mijo.
You'll have to bail yourself out
from now on.
[mechanic]
Grounded pilot fixing his plane?
[chuckles] Who in the hell taught you
how to rebuild a radial engine, man?
[Torres] Ah, just a little something
I picked up back home.
[commander] Ensign Torres.
A lot easier wreckin' planes
than putting them back together, eh?
At ease, Delgado.
How about if she runs,
you put me back in the sky?
Well, let's see what you got.
[grunts]
Clear prop.
[engine starts]
[engine sputters]
Delgado!
Hey, man, can you take
another look at this?
Keep going, Torres.
Take care of it.
Vandy!
[grunts] Sir!
With all due respect, I'm not a mechanic.
What's flying mean to you, son?
Speed?
That's hitting the gas.
Fancy maneuvers?
That's steering.
Sir, I'm a pilot.
Doesn't look like it to me, son.
-[explosions boom]
-[crew member shouts]
-[alarm blaring]
-[crew clamoring]
Holy shit!
Medic, fire crew, get your asses up here!
Handling team, get the crash crane ready!
Come on, boys, let's suit up.
[pilot] It killed everyone.
And it went right for our engines.
I've never seen anything like it.
Hooks in the sky. Hooks in the sky!
[coughs]
What in the world?
[Vandy] Torres!
I want that engine running
before I get back.
[pilot 2]
Commander Vandenberg, we gotta go!
[pilot 3] Let's go! Let's go!
[grunting]
Okay, run me through this again.
You said something went
through the engine block?
Like a hot knife through butter.
[grunts]
[pants] It's cold.
Torres, I'm not sure we should be
messing with this thing.
What are you?
All right.
[metallic clinking]
[sighs]
[drill whirs]
[object whirs, clangs]
Clear prop!
[object thrums]
[screams] Holy…
-'Gado! You okay?
-[pants]
No. Hell no!
-[object whirs]
-[gasps]
The heck?
[Delgado] Hey, Torres, look out!
[grunts]
Oh, shit.
Bandits. Nine o'clock low. Here we go.
[spacecraft engines whirring]
[Torres] You're not hearing me.
There's something else up in the sky,
and it's not Vichy fighters.
We gotta let the Aces know.
I already told you. They're out of range,
or the Frogs are jamming us.
We gotta get someone up
in the air to get them a message.
All of the pilots are
already in the air, ensign.
Not all of them.
That's one more down for the Texas Aces.
Texas Aces, kings of the sky!
[exclaims] Nice shot, baby!
[grunts]
[engine whines]
Torres!
[grunts]
This plane barely starts, man.
Give me a minute.
[breathing deeply]
[sighs]
[engine whines]
[strains, grunts]
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Whoo-hoo!
[groans] He is going to die.
[Vandy, on radio] Whoo-hoo, boys!
Looks like we got 'em.
Stay in formation for one more sweep.
[Torres] Tex squad, come in.
Can you hear me?
-Tex squad, this is the Bullet.
-[Vandy] The Bullet?
Torres?
This is a combat zone.
Return to the carrier immediately.
Sir, listen to me.
We're all gonna get smoked
if we stay up here.
Torres, clear this channel.
We just shot down the last of--
[grunts, screams]
Tex Two, do you copy?
Tex Two?
Fellas, don't engage
with whatever that is.
[Vandy] I give the orders, son.
[Tex Three] Listen to Vandy.
Stay in your lane, Torres.
[gasps]
Tex squadron, we have
a hell of a bogie on our hands.
Tex Three, Tex Three! On your six!
He's got a bead on you.
Get out of his line of fire.
[gasps, groans]
[groaning]
[screaming]
[Vandy] You got any guns
on that boat, Torres?
We need 'em. Now!
Of course I do, I just…
[grunts]
Son of a bitch!
[Tex Five] Tex squad,
I got this bastard in my sights.
-[Vandy] Keep after it!
-[mutters in Spanish]
[Tex Four] Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
[grunts] He's got me by the--
[snarls]
[screaming]
[grunting]
[Vandy] Torres, your wing.
Ah, shit.
Here we go.
[panting]
[wind whistling in cockpit]
[grunting]
Damn it, kid. What the hell are you doing?
[muffled] What the hell am I doing?
[grunting]
[exclaims]
Torres!
[Torres screaming]
[panting]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[exclaims, gasping]
Shit.
Yeah, you want some of this?
[growls]
-[snarls]
-You missed me, sucker.
[snarls]
[device beeping]
[gasps]
[grunting]
Oh, God.
Get off my plane!
[gasping]
[growls]
[grunting]
The heat.
[exclaims, groans]
Sir, we gotta get back to the ship
and call for backup.
We've got no shot against this thing.
[Vandy] Wait, Torres.
I need you to listen up now.
It's just you and me here, son.
No one is coming to bail us out.
Now, what have you got?
Well, I-I think it only sees heat.
Keep going. What do we do with it?
Think Torres.
So then we climb.
We need to cool off these engines.
That's something, kid.
Dale, motherfucker.
[on radio] Come on. Almost there.
Stand by to kill the engines.
You got eyes on him?
[Torres] He's gaining on us.
Torres, I'm gonna buy you some time.
-But, sir!
- You heard me.
Torres.
You're flying now.
No, sir! Do it!
Now! Turn her off!
[engine stops]
- Torres.
-Sir!
Kill this motherfucker for me.
No, no, no, no, no. Turn it off!
Vandy! No!
[growls]
[snarls]
[shouts]
Damn it, Vandy. Damn.
[growling]
You're blind now.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
[snarls]
It actually worked!
[growls]
Holy shit!
Now I got a bad idea.
Goodbye, invisibility.
[engine starts]
[growls]
-[speaking in French]
-[people exclaiming]
-[propeller whirring]
-[shouting in French]
[shouting]
[panting]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[screaming]
[panting]
[growling]
[sighs]
[in English] Never thought
I'd be so happy to see the enemy.
[grunts]
[grunting]
[snarls]
[growls]
[grunts]
Whoo-hoo! Take that, you son of a bitch!
Whoo-hoo!
[sighs]
[panting] We did it.
We did it.
He got nothin' on us.
[growling]
No, no, no, no. No, no.
Come on. Come on, what do I got?
What do I got? What do I got?
Think, think, Torres.
[sighs]
Thanks, Dad.
Gotta flood the engine.
[grunts, panting]
[growls]
[straining]
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on, you son of a bitch.
Shoot me down!
[snarls]
[exclaims in Spanish]
[screaming]
[gasps]
[coughs, pants]
[♪ "If We Should Ever Meet Again"
playing on radio]
[singer in English]
♪ If we should ever meet again… ♪
[song continues faintly]
[sighs]
[building rattling, rumbling]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[exhales deeply]
-[cicadas chirping]
-Hmm.
Huh?
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[electronic beeping, whirring]
[music stops]
[rhythmic beeping]
-[door clicks]
-[air whooshes]
Huh? [gasping]
What? How long was I asleep?
[sighs]
[gasps]
Oh, God.
[pants]
[guard growls softly]
-[snarls]
-[grunts] The hell is this?
-[buttons beep]
-[collar powers up]
[growls]
-[mutters in Spanish]
-[door closes]
[gasps, in English] Amazing.
Other humans.
He-He-Hello, ma'am.
I'm Torres. You just wake up too?
That's very sweet. [sighs]
[in Old Norse]
[gasps]
[in Japanese]
[in English] Oh, you… you're Japanese.
I had to learn some of that in basic.
Think, Torres. [stammering]
[in Japanese]
[in English]
You just take a load off. You too, ma'am.
And I'll just get us outta here.
Okay, Torres, think this through.
How would you get out of the brig
on the Ranger?
[lock beeps]
Oh, boy.
[guards grunt]
Be cool now, Torres.
Be cool, be cool, be cool.
-[rhythmic thudding]
-[distant chanting]
[door opens]
[chanting in alien language]
[chanting stops]
It's a shot in the dark, guys,
but I don't think we're on Earth anymore.
[spectators growling]
[spacecraft engines whirring]
[horn sounding]
[speaking in alien language]
[electronic voice, in English]
[speaking in alien language,
continues in background]
[electronic voice, in Old Norse]
[in Japanese]
[predator, in alien language]
[spectators cheering]
[prisoner, guard growling]
-[spectators chanting]
-[horn sounding]
[growls]
[button beeps]
-[collar beeping rapidly]
-[breathing heavily]
[roars]
[in English] Holy shit!
You guys, they put bombs on our necks.
They could blow our heads off
-with the press of a--
-[horn sounding]
[electronic voice]
[in alien language]
[in Old Norse]
[in Japanese]
What the hell?
This isn't even from my century.
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit. [grunts]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't make me!
[pistol clicks]
-No!
-[grunts]
[in Japanese]
[in Old Norse]
[both grunt]
[in Japanese]
[in Old Norse]
[in English] Okay, okay, okay, okay.
The language is clearly a problem.
But if we can get up to that ship,
I think I can fly us out.
I shot one of those down before.
[in Old Norse]
[in Japanese]
[in English] Gotcha. [grunts]
[in English] You said fight her. [grunts]
[in Japanese]
-[Torres groans]
-[grunts]
-[in Japanese]
[grunts]
-[growls]
-[button beeps]
Uh, guys!
[both grunting]
[in Olds Norse]
[in English] Okay, okay. Okay, okay, okay.
[stammers] How does all this, uh…
All right, bullets, gunpowder.
[both grunting, exclaiming]
[creature growling]
Oh, no.
-[growls]
-[guard grunts]
[Ursa grunts]
-Grandma!
-[both grunt]
You've got to be kidding me.
[in Old Norse]
[grunts]
[pants]
[panting]
[sighs]
Listen to me!
One of us might win today,
but nobody is gonna survive this place.
-I have a plan to get us out of--
-[creature growling]
[screaming]
[roaring]
[snarling]
-[grunts]
-[creature snarls]
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Wait a minute.
Yes!
[pants]
[sighs]
-[creature growling]
-[grunting]
[device beeping]
[Ursa grunts]
[pants]
[growls]
[snarls]
-[growls]
-[Ursa shouts]
[pants]
[grunting]
Ah! [grunts]
[creature groans]
[roars, whimpers]
[panting, grunting]
[grunting]
[roars]
[Ursa grunting]
[grunting]
[shouts]
[creature snarls]
[grunting]
-[gasps]
-[creature whines]
[Ursa pants]
[both shout]
[laughing]
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Guys, I'm still in here!
[in Old Norse]
[in Japanese]
[spectators cheer]
[both grunting]
[in Japanese]
[in Old Norse]
[in alien language]
[horn sounding]
[pants, grunts]
[both panting]
[in Japanese]
[spectators murmuring]
[exhales deeply]
[in alien language]
[in Old Norse]
[snarls]
-[growls]
-[buttons beep]
-[collars beeping rapidly]
-[grunts]
[in Japanese]
-[sighs]
-[Torres yells, exclaims]
[in English] Hey, guys. Remember me?
[pants]
Are we friends now?
[button beeps]
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
[spectators murmuring]
[panting]
Come on, girl!
[groaning]
[Ursa grunts]
[growling]
[in Old Norse]
[shouting]
[groans]
[pants]
[grunts]
-[growling]
-[spectators cheering]
[Ursa groans]
[panting]
[shouts]
-[snarls]
-[grunts]
[shouts]
[snarls]
-[shouts]
-[growls]
[grunting]
[predator snarls]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[in English]
Let's get this thing in the air.
All right, Torres.
Can't be that different from a Wildcat.
-[grunting]
-[snarling]
[growling softly]
[roars, snorting]
[both grunting]
-[roars]
-[spectators cheering]
[pants]
[both grunting]
[snarls]
[groaning]
[gasps]
[groans]
[in Old Norse]
[spacecraft engines whirring]
[growls]
-[groans]
-[grunts]
[growling]
Whoa!
-[strains]
-[pants]
[both straining]
[inhales deeply]
-Guys! Get in here!
-[both grunt]
[in Japanese]
[both panting]
[predator roars]
[groaning]
[grunting, groaning]
[in Old Norse]
[groans]
[grunts]
[in English] All right, girl.
[grunting]
[sighs]
-[gasps]
-[exclaims]
[groans]
[exclaims]
-[gasps]
-[grunts]
[groaning]
-What happened?
-[grunts]
[grunting]
[sighs]
[pants, inhales deeply]
[in Old Norse]
[in Japanese]
[in English] What are you doing?
[grunts]
[snarls]
[screaming]
[grunting, snarling]
[shouting]
[grunting]
[in Old Norse]
[in Japanese]
-[growling]
-[Ursa panting]
[in alien language]
[♪ dramatic music playing]