[Overlapping Conversations]
Sounds good.
[Man 1] All right.
That was so much fun, man, I got two.
Last night I got two
shots. Bullseye, baby.
[Woman] Hey, girl,
What can I get you, sweetie?
Surprise me.
I need a shot of tequila
and some beer, please.
Here. And your tequila.
I went out with this guy.
Ice cold, honky ass white
boy beer and your tequila.
My favorite.
Okay, daddy, you let me know if
you need anything else, okay?
I'm...
I'm... I'm looking for somebody.
Who are you looking for?
A white boy named Jensen'?
Hm. Don't ring a bell, but I
can go ask around if you want.
No. No, fuck, no.
No, he's not Jensen.
I'm sorry. It's... It's... It's Jensen.
-Jensen.
-All right, I'll see.
No, no. no, no, no.
-[Man] Come over here for a second.
-Um...
Do you know him?
I don't... I don't think I do.
You know him because
you've been fucking him.
What do you want?
-Same here.
-I want to see you.
I'm busy, okay?
We're friends.
That's all. We used to hang out.
Sit down.
Don't make a scene. Nobody cares.
Come on, sit down.
Don't worry. Nothing's gonna happen.
Come on.
[Man] Hey, what about
another tequila shot?
Hey, doll, get us two more tequilas.
You're pretty.
You know you are.
You are.
But you shouldn't believe the lies.
You shouldn't believe
the lies, the bullshit.
The bullshit.
People play games and they
pretend they're something else.
But deep down in the dark,
the quiet...
we all know we are alone.
Yes.
Did you know that your
friend is fucking up with me?
Please stop.
Stop? Stop what?
Whatever this is,
I don't know anything about anything.
[Laughing]
Ah! You don't know
anything about anything?
No?
You know what, baby girl?
I know a lot of things. A lot of things.
Hm! A lot of things.
I know your name.
I know your address.
I know the people you love and care.
I know, I know, I know everything.
Lizzie.
We are who we are.
Animals, animals, animals.
And this place is the wild, wild west.
It's a dangerous place.
It is very dangerous.
Pay attention, Lizzie, pay attention.
Pay attention.
You feel that?
You feel it?
It's a switch blade.
My thumb's right on the
button that trips the spring.
You think your boy will keep
coming back by your place
if I open you UP,
if I pull your guts inside out?
Please stop.
Your friend doesn't
know who he is out here.
People forget sometimes.
And that is how they got hurt.
That is how they got hurt.
Lizzie, I could paint a portrait,
beautiful portrait with your blood.
And I would not even remember
your face the next day.
What do you want?
You go and tell your friend
that I want back all he stole from me.
Huh? Could you do that?
Good girl.
Good girl, Lizzie.
Now finish your shift.
Go home, find Jensen for me.
But don't run and don't hide.
Rabbit, you can't get away from me.
You know why?
I am the fucking king.
Now you can go.
GO, go; g9, go! go'
A fucking king.
[Insects Chirping]
[Door Slams]
You got a problem, motherfucker?
I'm talking to you, chico.
Chico!
[Grunting]
[Grunts Softly]
[Hr]
A|| right?
[Sizzling]
-[Tag] Bo?
-Yeah.
[Grunts Softly]
[Bowdrie] Lord, thank you for this day
and for this food.
And she who made it.
Lord, forgive us our wrongs.
And please help us to
forgive those who wronged us.
Guide us, O Lord,
that Your will be done always.
In Christ's name we pray.
Amen.
Dive in.
[Grunts, Exhales]
[Indistinct Conversation On Tv]
[Voices Overlapping On Tv]
[Hr]
[Gunshot]
[Door Creaking]
-[Exhales]
-[Tag] Night, Bo.
Night, kid.
[Sighs Heavily]
[Praying Inaudibly]
Amen.
[soft country music playing over radio]
♪ I've been working So hard... a'
[Radio Station Scrambles]
[Song Continues Over Speakers]
[Music Continues Over Radio]
[Paper Rustling]
[Tag Chuckles Softly]
[Sighs]
[Birds Chirping]
[Fishing Line Reeling]
[Door Creaks]
[Bowdrie] Hey.
[Door Closes]
[Grunts Softly]
Hey, how much for this push mower?
How much for Bill's old mower, Ed?
[Ed] Oh, shit.
That mower don't mow.
It don't run.
Well, it should be cheap, then.
How much, Ed?
Blade don't turn.
Brand spanking new
blade, but it don't turn.
I like to piddle.
[Ed Sighs]
I can do you 45.
I'll give you 20.
This business is gonna kill me.
I take it that's a "Yes, 20."
[Birds Chirping]
[Woman] Help! Help!
[Gun Cocks]
[Hr]
-[Sighs Softly]
-[Door Creaks]
[Grunts Softly]
Tag.
[Hr]
Hey, baby. You around?
[Door Clicks Open]
[Rapid Footsteps Approaching]
I found something.
[Tag Panting]
[Water Gushing]
-Over there.
-Okay.
Oh, boy.
[Sighs]
[Shuddering]
Okay.
You're safe. I gotta move you.
[Groaning]
All right, we got you.
Okay. All right.
Uh... Give me the heavy blanket.
-She needs to go to a hospital.
-Oh, yeah.
Look, I know it hurts.
I'm gonna have to look.
Okay, honey?
Okay. I'm sorry.
Oh, my goodness.
Baby, I'm gonna need some rags,
some alcohol, some hot water.
Keep you warm.
Oh!
I have to turn you over
and look at the back. Okay?
Qkay_ "[9 Roans]
[Continues Groaning]
[Sighs] Okay. In and out.
Passed right through.
Here, let's get you warm.
[Gasping]
[Stuttering]
No hospital.
Please.
We'll see. We'll see. All
right, let me get you.
Honey, could you hurry up with that stuff?
Look at me. I need to keep
some pressure on here, okay?
-I'm sorry.
-[High-Pitched Scream]
Okay. All right.
Oh, baby. Wet rag. Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
Okay. Get the kit
above the refrigerator.
Okay. All right.
Help me out with this. What?
Drag that. I'll turn her over.
Oh. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
-What happened?
-[Bowdrie] Oh!
She got shot through the back,
and it went straight through the front.
Nothing vital, I think.
Um, I'm gonna need to clean this, pack it.
It's gonna get pretty screamy in here,
so either get tough or get out, okay?
I am sorry about this, I am sorry.
[High-Pitched Scream]
[Wind Whistling]
[Grunts Softly]
Can we still take her to the hospital?
[Bowdrie Sighs]
She practically begged me not to,
but I think we should.
Let's think about it.
Bullet holes make questions
that'll bring the law.
Is she gonna live?
Well, it takes an awful
lot to kill a person.
She lost a mess of blood, though.
I've seen worse.
[Grunts Softly]
It's... It's chicken soup.
You're gonna be okay.
I promise.
[Bowdrie] Hey.
You did good today. You were strong.
You too.
I gotta go into town again tomorrow.
Get more medicine and whatnot.
It'd be a good idea if you
didn't go fishing for a while.
You get me?
Stick around the house.
-Yes, sir.
-Got to leave early.
So, just keep her in bed.
Give her a bunch of liquids.
Hey, we don't know her,
so we don't trust her.
Okay?
Night, Bo.
Night.
[Hr]
[Firewood Crackling]
[Grunts Softly]
[Groans]
Huh?
Good morning.
Did you handcuff me?
What did you do that for?
We don't know you.
[Sighs]
[Grunting]
[Coughing]
Bo told me that if you tried to move,
I'd have to shoot you.
I'm just kidding.
[Chuckles Nervously]
[Exhales Heavily]
I'm Tag.
Hi.
I'm January.
[Indistinct Conversations]
-[Sighs]
-Hey, there.
There you go.
[Scanner Beeping]
Well, would you look at that?
That brings back old memories.
Good choice. That'll be 38.99.
[Siren Blaring]
[Brake] Put the condoms down.
Now, why'd I do that?
Keeps your wife's lipstick off of me.
[Chuckles] Well, how you doing, ugly?
What, you really wanna know
or are you shitting me?
I'm just shittin'.
Hey, you got time for a bite?
We're going to Lucille's.
No, I got some errands to run.
All right. Well, hey, this is Davenport,
fresh from Tulsa.
-Hey.
-This is Bowdrie.
He's trouble. River folk.
Yeah. Don't take the wrong turn.
[Brake] We go way back.
Hey, uh... Hey, you bag anything
worth bragging about yet?
Oh, Tag got one a couple of days back.
-Big?
-Big enough to eat.
I went out the other morning.
I didn't see nothing.
That's 'cause they saw you first.
Gotta sneak up on em.
[Brake] How's the kiddo?
I think she'll outlive me.
All right, well, you keep on keeping on,
and, I'll probably come see you sometime.
-I get bored enough.
-You bet.
-A|| right, well, see you, big man.
-See you.
Keep your nose clean.
[Door Creaks]
[Sighs]
[Knocking]
[Tag] Did you see that
January has tattoos?
Let me get me that 5l16th over there.
Thanks.
Did my mom have tattoos?
She had a few.
They were all kind of run together.
She had a lot, actually.
I used to think that they
looked kind of weird,
but I think January's look cool.
Did you see it?
Yeah.
Don't you go getting any ideas.
Oh, that's not gonna work. No.
[Faucet Running]
[Switch Flicks]
[Bowdrie Sighs]
You're gonna live.
[January Sighs]
How long have I been here?
A couple of days now.
[Grunts]
Who are you?
My name is January Evers.
You think you can tell me what happened?
[Sighs]
They took me.
I was just coming home from the gym.
I just walked into my apartment,
and they were there.
[January] Lizzie.
Liz was hurt.
[High-Pitched Scream]
They beat the shit out of me.
{[Thug Grunts]
-[Thud]
Just heard 'em screaming about
some guy who was his friend.
And that they had stolen
something from them.
He took us, put us in a car,
drove us, I don't know how long.
Car stops.
[Sobbing]
They pulled us out.
[January Shudders]
She told them she didn't know anything.
[Stream Gushing]
-They shot her.
-[Lizzie] No, no, no, no.
Lizzie!
-[Qunsh<>T]
No!
[Sighs]
And I left her there,
I just started running.
I broke free, and I just, uh, I...
I heard the shot.
I felt it, I fell over
this bridge by the water, and...
[January Sighs]
I heard them looking for me.
So I crawled into the water
and just held my breath
for as long as I could.
The last thing that I remember
is them saying that I must be dead,
and they left.
[Sniffles]
Tell me about the other girl.
Liz. Uh... Elizabeth.
She was my best friend.
[Exhales]
She was my only friend.
[Grunts Softly]
-[Sighs] '[Door Opens]
-Where the hell have you been?
-Oh, I took a walk.
Figured I'd give the season a final look.
Why didn't you tell me?
Well, you talk too much.
I needed some quiet.
-Where did you go?
-Nowhere.
You know, around the
woods. What the hell?
Where were you?
I'm gonna need to run
back into town again.
-You just went.
-Yeah, well, I need to go again.
I need to pick up some
spark plugs for that mower.
And why don't you get to your schoolwork?
-I was about to go looking for you.
-Tag.
Stay near the house. All right?
-Yes, sir.
-How's she doing?
She's sleeping.
Good. I won't be long.
[Gun Clicks]
What is... What is it?
[Sighs] What's what, kid?
You don't go to town this much,
and we're not gonna use that
lawnmower for another four months.
I mean, you say yourself that
people live season to season.
This ain't like you.
Eventually we're going to have
to take her back into town.
-To the hospital.
-Why?
Because there's nothing
more we can do for her.
You said that she was healing
up and she didn't want to go.
-And then you agreed...
-Yeah, I know what I said.
Well, that's bullshit.
Yeah, it is. Come here.
[Sighs] But it's necessary bullshit.
Right now you're gonna keep
tugging on the sweater.
I'm gonna drag you right into it.
There's a dead woman in
the river down there.
I just saw her, all tangled up
in the branches and left to rot.
Somebody shot her right in the face,
blew her brains out,
dumped her in the water.
Now, do you think our
newfound friend in here,
in our home, might have been
shot by the same fellas,
left her for dead?
What do you figure they'll do
if they find out she's alive?
Come back here and get her is what.
The world is full of ugly
people doing ugly things.
Some horrible shit you can't
even wrap your head around.
It's just the nature of the beast.
Get back in the house, tool
up, and lock all the doors.
-Okay, baby?
-Yes, sir.
-Okay.
-[Door Creaks]
-[Sighs]
-[Line Ringing]
[Dispatch] Antler Sheriff
Station, may I help you?
Hello?
Could you do something for me?
I gotta go to the bathroom.
[Hr]
[Grunts Softly]
[Tag] Are you okay in there?
Just need a sec.
-Oh.
-I think I need to sit down.
[January Groans]
[Breathing Heavily]
You're pretty.
-I don't feel too pretty.
-You are.
Just going through a hard time right now.
My mom was pretty.
Where is your mom?
She died when I was little.
But he says she didn't hurt, so...
That's the way it goes.
Life's hard.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about your friend.
Bo told me.
Me too.
Do you want your tea?
Sure.
Where is your dad?
Bo? He, uh...
He went to town.
Bo?
Yeah.
His name's Bowdrie, but I call him Bo.
His old man was a huge
fan of Louis L'Amour.
You ever heard of him?
Oh, he's like this old cowboy writer.
He wrote a bunch of Western stories.
Anyway. There's this character
in one of them named Bowdrie.
And Pa-paw liked it so
much that he stole it.
So it's... it's an homage.
Why not call him Dad?
I just always called him Bo, I guess.
I mean, that that is his name.
What about Tag? What is that from?
He says that momma used to always
call me his... his tag along.
And I like that more than
my other name, so it stuck.
[Chuckles Softly]
[Grunts Softly]
[Leaves Rustling]
-Uh...
-What is it?
Nothing, I'm just... I thought I...
It's all good.
[Sighs Heavily]
Oh, hey. You're up.
-Yeah.
-Good.
Are you mad at me?
No.
She had to go to the bathroom.
I was trying to do your sheets a favor.
Gee, thanks a lot, Tag.
Well, like I said, we don't know her.
I know her.
Why don't you go and
get washed for dinner?
[Bowdrie] Lord, we thank You for
this food and this warm home.
We ask Your forgiveness
just like we forgive others.
We ask for guidance, Lord.
But above all, Your will be done.
Nothing more, nothing less.
In your name. Amen.
-[Girls] Amen.
-Right.
[Sighs]
Hey!
Thank you.
Yeah. You got a ways to go, but
you'll be fine. I've seen much worse.
Smoke?
Yeah.
-It's cold.
-Yeah.
It's gonna be a hard winter.
[Tag] Night, Bo.
Night, kid.
[Tag] Night, January.
Good night.
-She's sweet.
-Yeah, she's all right.
What are you gonna do?
I'll take you into town tomorrow.
They got a clinic in Antlers.
They'll take good care of you there.
Okay.
[Hr]
[Music Playing Over Speakers]
[Knocking On Door]
Hey, yo, Alejandro.
-Yeah, baby.
-[Door Opens]
It's Irish.
They just brought Jensen in.
Can you feel that?
What a stupid mistake.
Fucking stupid. Are you stupid?
-I didn't tell anyone. I swear.
-Yeah, you did.
You know you're fucking dead.
-Pay attention.
-Okay.
[Siren Wailing In The Distance]
Why did you do it?
I was coming back.
-I swear.
-Why did you fucking do it?
-Look at me.
-I...
I can explain this.
All of it.
[Irish] Good luck explaining this.
Did you get my shit?
No, I fucking did what I was told to do.
A|| right?
This is just a misunderstanding.
They're putting it on
me, man. But it's just...
It's a mis... It's a misunderstanding.
Look at me.
-[Blow Lands]
-[Exclaims]
-Damn!
-That was a nice hit.
All right, cowboy.
Get up now.
The Academy taught you
better than that, boy.
You a tough guy. Hang in there.
[Jensen] I swear to you,
I swear I did the drop.
[Coughing, Spitting]
I did the drop.
And it wasn't light, man,
it wasn't like. I swear.
Running for me is like running from God.
I have eyes everywhere.
So what do you want to do now?
Did you get the wife?
In the trunk...
-[Muffled Screaming]
-with the kid.
[Alejandro] You hear
that? We got your wife.
We got your fucking wife.
Tell me. Tell me.
[Sighs]
Tell me...
Tell me.
What is her name?
-[Muffled Screaming]
-[Metallic Thud]
Laney. Laney.
Laney?
[Speaking In Spanish]
And Laney won't like it at first.
She'll try to fight it.
[Jensen Sobbing]
I was...
poor, abandoned, lost.
Orphan...
Going to the worst.
The worst place you could ever imagine.
-[Sighs]
-Even
I'm gonna do to her what
those people did to me.
Inside.
Please. Please.
I'm sorry, man, I fucked up.
I fucked up.
I know it's my fault.
Don'... Don't hurt them. Please, God.
You smell like death.
You don't have to do nothing.
No, I can... I can still...
No, I can still help you, I can...
[Alejandro] We took care
of your little lover.
[Jensen] I can drive, I
can make the runs, I can...
-Please.
-Now it's your turn.
-Oh, God.
-Stop.
No! God! No! [Sobbing]
No more suffering.
Coward!
-[Drill Whirring]
-[Jensen Screaming] No!
[High-Pitched Scream]
Hm... January is sleeping.
Well, that's good.
That's God's medicine.
That's what you Pa-paw always used to say.
Yes, sir.
Speaking of old guys,
you ought to ride up to old Whitehorse's,
see if he's okay.
I haven't seen him for a few days.
I thought I was supposed
to stay around the house.
You're going the opposite way away from
the river, so I figure it'd be all right.
I'll take the truck.
Oh, no, I need the truck.
-You need it?
-Mm-hm.
It looks like rain.
Well, you could use the shower.
Anyway, the fork's low, apple butter.
Might as well treat myself on my birthday.
-Which birthday again?
-Who's counting?
You better slow down on them birthdays.
You'd be 42 by next month.
[Hr]
[Door Clicks Open]
I'm ready.
It's gonna be all right, you know.
[Hr]
[Siren Wailing]
You may want to stay inconspicuous.
I'll be right back.
Can't resist the smell of
bacon. What's going on?
This world ain't right for it.
Body washed up down the
river. Just got the call.
One of our boys.
Oh, yeah. County. Which one?
Name 0' Jensen. Deputy.
Three years.
They tortured him with a drill.
Dozen holes in him.
Beaten, shot, dropped in
the upper river last night.
-Yeah. Sorry.
-The wife and kid...
Missing. Can't even
get 'em on the phone.
Have you seen anything weird out there?
You've been down at the Fork?
Nothing. It's all pretty quiet.
This morning,
body of an Antler's girl
got caught in the trot-line
down at Broken Bow Lake.
Shot in the head.
Looks like she came up through the Fork.
Through the delta, caught in the shallows.
Turns out she disappeared from
her apartment a few nights back.
Roommate's gone missing too.
She turn up yet?
God, no. Hope she's alive.
[Bowdrie] Right.
Yeah.
[Brake] Word is, the
Brotherhood and the cartel
have joined forces here in town.
You don't want to mess
with these breed of people.
-Bad dudes.
-I'm planning on it.
You see anything upriver?
Yeah, I found some tracks.
Might be something.
Bit of a hike, though.
About a mile or so.
Do me a favor.
Keep Tag off the river
till we get this settled.
[Bowdrie] Yeah.
-[Brake] People are crazy.
-[Bowdrie] Yeah.
[Brake] Fucking Brotherhood, cartels.
Indians, Russians
running heroin, meth. Fuck!
People now, kids.
It's all gone to shit.
Hm.
[Brake] What you got there?
[Bowdrie] Oh, yeah.
She's a niece from out of town.
She's come to visit Tag for her birthday.
-Do yourself a favor.
-Mm-hm.
Get the hell out of here.
Good advice. Good luck.
What the hell's going on?
[Bowdrie] I'm getting the sense
you're not telling me everything.
[Engine Turning Over]
What do you know about
this crew here in town'?
This Brotherhood?
[January] I don't know them...
but I saw their face.
[Lizzie] I don't know. I don't know.
He didn't tell me.
[Irish] That's a real fucking problem.
I swear to you, I swear.
He's married. We haven't talked.
Fuck. Make the call.
[Lizzie] No. No, no, no.
I swear we haven't talked in three weeks.
Jensen's not here.
Only his girlfriend and a roommate.
[Koontz] What?
-He said clean it up.
-Oh, no.
No. Please, please,
please don't hurt us.
Please. Please.
[Sobbing] Please. Please.
[Irish] Muzzle that bitch.
Tell Egon to bring the car around.
[Faint Groaning]
[Koontz] Hey, baby-
You're January, huh?
Look at me.
Yeah. You know what we're looking for?
Hm? No, no.
Yeah. [Shushing]
I believe you.
You shouldn't have come home, bitch.
I'm sorry.
[Sighs]
[Hr]
[Tag] Do you have any family?
Uh... I got a brother in North Carolina.
We don't talk much.
Husband?
Mm-mm.
Boyfriend?
-[Chuckles]
-Not for a while.
-Kids?
-Tag.
I'm just trying to see if
anyone's worried about her.
[January] Hm,
No. I don't really have anybody.
I just came down from Wilmington...
for a guy, that was dumb.
I met Lizzie at work, and...
She offered to pay half rent or whatever.
Um, but I just keep to myself, mostly.
I don't really have anybody.
Neither do me and Bowdrie.
[Indistinctly Muttering]
-[Door Clicks Open]
-[Grumbles]
Alejandro.
The fucking roommate.
She's alive.
[Scoffs]
-She got seen today.
-Shit.
[Mumbles Indistinctly]
Didn't I tell you to take care of it?
So, you...
You, open your mouth.
[Gun Cocking]
Open your mouth.
Come here.
-[Gun Cocking]
-Open your mouth.
Alejandro!
[Alejandro] Uh, uh, uh...
This is what you're supposed to
do when I say end a motherfucker.
You put her on her knees.
[Koontz] Alejandro. No, please.
And you end it, end it, end it, end it.
I'll take care of it.
All right.
[Chuckles Softly]
-[January] What is it?
-I don't know.
[Irish] Oi, oi!
Can I help you?
Is this the Johnson place?
-No.
-Oh, shite.
So this ain't 1436 Kickapoo Place?
-[Bowdrie] Is that the Johnson place?
-Right.
Well, I already told you that it wasn't.
Yes, sir. I guess you did.
Look, I ain't gonna
bullshit a bullshitter.
I'm out here in the
fucking asshole of nowhere.
Is that them?
I don't know, I can't see anything.
[Grunts Softly]
[Gun Cocking]
What are you doing?
Do you know how to use a gun?
-Uh-uh.
-[Gun Clicks]
Just in case.
[Irish] I'm trying to find my sister.
You see, I got word that
she came up the river
and went camping with
some prick called Johnson,
and they got into some bother.
I'm sorry. I hope you find her.
She's a pretty girl.
A couple of tattoos, dark hair.
Her name's January.
Like the month.
Doesn't ring a bell.
Okay.
I don't think you understand.
I really need to find my sister.
You haven't seen her or talked to her?
-I'm pretty sure.
Right.
We got a problem then,
because I don't think I believe you.
All right.
[Tag] Hey, Bowdrie.
'[Door Opens]
-Hey.
Your dinner's getting cold.
[Bowdrie] Oh, you get started without me?
-I'm tired of waiting.
-[Bowdrie] Well, don't wait.
Say grace. Dig in. I'll be in directly.
Cute girl. Big mouth.
[Chuckles]
I won't push my luck.
Don't let me keep you
from a hot fucking meal.
Sounds like the princess means business.
Look, I'll...
I'll keep looking and
digging for my little sister.
I'm sure she'll pop up.
See you soon.
[Car Door Closes]
[Tag] Is that them?
[Bowdrie] Yeah.
Well, why didn't you shoot them
for what they did to January?
It's not our fight.
Let's get inside.
[Sighs]
[Hr]
[Indistinct Conversation On Tv]
[Man] Hey, January. Look at me.
[Groans]
[Breathing Heavily]
[Grunts Softly]
Don't, don't, don't.
Oh, you fucking up, my man.
Fucking with the
Brotherhood now, ain't ya?
What do you want?
I wanna go home, bitch.
Best put that shit down, country boy.
You crossing lines now?
-Fucking up.
-How many you got out here?
What you need to be asking
is how many we got in there.
-It's me again.
-[Muffled Groaning]
-[Screaming]
-Shut the fuck up.
Fucking too dumb to die.
Come here, where do you
think you're fucking going?
-Huh? Shut up! '[939Qing]
Too dumb to die.
You don't even matter.
That's what's crazy.
But you had to fight.
You had to make it so
fucking hard, didn't you?
|-| [Toaching]
-[Grunting]
-You're next.
-[Irish Grunts] {gunshofl
-[Rapid Gunshots]
-[Glass Shatters]
[Groaning]
[Grunts, Pants]
Tag? Baby?
[Coughing]
[Breathing Heavily]
[Bowdrie] It's all right,
honey. It's all right.
-[Irish Coughing]
-I'm sorry.
-I'm so sorry.
-Could you come here, please?
Okay, Tag, you stay here.
[Hr]
[Sighs]
I'm gonna need to get rid of their truck.
Take it to the quarry.
I need you two to follow me, okay?
[Engine Turning Over]
[Footsteps Approaching]
I made you some tea.
You didn't have to.
Bo thinks that you
ripped your stitches out.
[Grunts Softly] It's okay.
I froze.
What?
I was really, really scared, so I froze.
Tag, no.
You saved me.
[Door Clicks Open]
-I need to go.
-Where are you going?
You need a stitch or two there.
You could take me to the clinic.
Come here. Sit down, please.
Please.
[Grunts Softly]
You need to tell me everything.
That guy I told you about
that Lizzie was seeing.
That's Jensen, that cop.
But... [Sighs]
They were just...
I don't know, it wasn't
serious, I didn't...
I never talked to him.
I don't trust cops.
She did tell me that he
was involved in some shit.
I was scared. I just didn't...
I don't even know you.
And you saved my life.
And I owe you for that.
You don't owe me nothing.
I never would have stayed
here if I knew they'd come.
I wouldn't have done that to you and Tag.
I don't know what I was thinking.
They almost...
Just take me somewhere. Anywhere.
Drop me off.
They're gonna keep coming back.
Jensen was afraid of
him. I'm in the mix now.
I saw Lizzie die.
Clearly, they want me dead.
I cannot do that to y'all.
[Hr]
[Bird Cooing]
[Sighs]
[Bowdrie] What I'm about to tell
you has to stay quiet, all right?
[Brake] All right.
[Bowdrie] I need your word.
[Brake] What is it?
[Bowdrie] That girl washed
up down at Broken Bow.
[Brake] That's right. What about her?
Now where are you at with all that?
I know she was executed.
That deputy, Jensen, we
fished out of the fork.
He was connected to her.
Found text messages, pictures...
He was compromised.
I always had a feeling about him.
Too friendly with girls,
too much of a fucking bully.
Ain't out yet, but we're finding shit.
Turns out he was in with the local crew,
helping runs in and out
of Arkansas looks like.
His wife and kid are still missing.
His crew, who are they?
They're scary motherfuckers,
that's who they are.
Hillbilly meth cooks working
with the Brotherhood, cartel.
Fucking mess.
Hurts my heart. No sense in it.
Yeah, Bowdrie?
Get to it.
You know something, you gotta talk to me.
Se had a roommate, went missing.
That's right. Evers.
Collateral damage most likely.
I got her.
-What did you say?
-I got her.
She washed up out of the
river. Tag found her.
She's alive?
-Where is she?
-She's safe.
Not for long, she ain't.
You understand what kind
of mess this girl is in?
These people, they got
their own laws out there.
God-dang animals.
Where is she?
She's scared the hell
out of is where she's at.
Now, we already know we
can't trust the cops.
But I will bring her to you.
But you got to keep Tag and
me out of this, all right?
I don't want no reports,
no questions, no nothing.
She washed up a few miles
down the bend and...
And that's the end of it. Okay?
We cannot be dragged into
this. I can't be part of it.
Tag can't be drug in.
Damn right, you can't.
[Grunts Softly]
You got to get her out of here.
All right.
I'll drive her over a few counties.
Down here, we're all too damn related.
They're gonna take good care of you.
I know Bowdrie doesn't look smart,
but he is.
Get you fixed up.
You're pretty awesome.
You know that, right?
[Door Clicks Open] -Couldn't
remember if I'd told you that.
Okay. He's gonna take
you to a safe place.
That gets you out of county,
and you can figure it out from there.
Right?
-That's the only way this works.
-Okay.
Okay.
Tag, I need a minute.
I'll meet you out at the truck.
I'll miss you.
Thanks.
You're...
-Here, hang on to this.
-What is it?
That's just a little something
to hold you over until you,
you know, get on your feet again.
You can trust this fella.
I trust you.
Okay.
Well, we best get going.
[Hr]
Come on. Let's get you out of here.
[Bowdrie] In Your holy
name we pray. Amen.
[Sighs]
[Bowdrie] We didn't have a choice.
[Tag] Neither did she.
[Bowdrie] Well, the
world's tough that way.
Sometimes we don't get to
pick what we want to do.
You know that.
Sometimes we just have
to do what we have to.
[Tag] I liked having January here.
It reminded me of what it might
be like if Mama were around.
-Just the three of us?
-Yeah. All right.
It's true.
Baby, you never even
really knew your Mama.
You were too little.
And she was so lost before she passed.
January trusted us.
The only thing I care about
in this whole wide world
is you... keeping you safe.
And nothing's gonna stop me from
doing that. Not her, not you.
Why don't you go back inside and be ready?
No...
[Hr]
[Sighs]
[Grunts Softly]
[Groans Softly]
Sleep all right?
Yeah. Me neither.
Hey, let's go check in with Brake.
[Line Ringing]
[Brake] This is Sheriff Brake.
If this is emergency, please call 911.
Otherwise, leave your name
and number after the beep.
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.
[Line Ringing]
[Brake] This is Sheriff Brake.
If this is an emergency, please call 911.
[Engine Turning Over]
[Grunts Softly] Uh, go on in.
Don't come out for nobody, okay?
I wanna stay with you.
[Sighs] Here.
Go on in, please. Here,
get something you want?
I wanna speak to Brake. Is he in?
[Boy] Hey.
Can I help you with something?
No, thank you.
Well, if you do need me, I'll just...
I'll just be right there at the counter...
Billy Ray, there's a
clean-up on aisle two.
[Indistinct Conversations]
Hey, where's Brake?
-Let's take a walk.
-Sure.
[Davenport] Nobody knows.
He was a no-show today.
Sol blew up his phone, got his voicemail.
Called his wife, and she said he
didn't come home last night.
-So...
-Uh-huh.
Nobody knows where he is.
Huh? No idea?
Look, I know you, uh...
you guys are boys or whatever,
but, I need you to cut the shit, okay?
There's a lot of talk.
Oh, yeah? Like what?
Well, you know,
the Jensen case and the dead girl.
You know, there's some theories
that Brake might be involved.
Now, see, I'm new here, so
that's just my perspective.
And to me, it seems that...
Well, everybody's related.
This department is full of cousin fuckers
and 30-year favors.
Now, now, I don't think
like that. Just...
There's a lot of talk.
I've known the man 35 years.
That doesn't fit the picture.
Yeah. Maybe he just got
tired of the bullshit
and owed somebody some money or something.
Or maybe he just didn't
want to retire with some
shitty pension and a big 0|' gut.
[Chuckles] Right, yeah.
I mean, I get it, I get it.
I respect the guy. I guess,
you know, he was tired.
Well, I'll try and get
in touch with him later.
So what is it that...
that you needed, though?
-Just...
-Nothing. Just to talk.
Is there something in
particular, though, maybe?
You know, because from what
I've heard about you is
is that you're the type of guy that
doesn't really need anything.
-Nope.
-Okay. Hey, you were...
You were with him yesterday, weren't you?
-I was.
-Yeah.
Yeah, 'cause I was there
when you called him saying
you had to meet up over
at Lucille's Coffee Shop.
-Mm-hm.
-Yeah. Mm!
I haven't seen him after that.
Or maybe there's something that you know
that maybe you wanna... wanna tell me.
-Nothing.
-No? Okay.
What is it you needed though? Come on.
Well, I just check in on
him from time to time.
It's one of those times.
Okay, well, I'll tell you
what, I'll tell you what.
Um, if I hear from Brake...
Or anybody for that matter,
I'll make sure I hit you up real quick.
-Appreciate it.
-Yeah.
You know, there's a lot going
on in this town, isn't it?
With Jensen and the girl and...
People are crazy.
Hell, you got your hands full.
Yeah, I sure do. I sure do.
-Hey, uh... Hey, Bowdrie?
-Yeah.
Don't say nothing to nobody about this.
-Did you talk to Brake?
-Nope.
Hop in the truck, we gotta go.
What's going on?
Brake's dead, Tag. They killed him.
And I'm damn sure there's more
men coming here right now.
What about January?
-I don't know.
-[Gun Clicking]
Did she make it out?
Is she okay?
[Sniffles] Is she okay?
[Sobbing]
Don't go jumping to any
conclusions now, okay?
She could be fine.
-We don't know.
-[Sobbing]
[Suspenseful Music Plays]
[Faint Music Playing Over Tv]
[Thudding]
[Hr]
[Groaning]
[Bowdrie Grunting] Okay.
Son of a bitch.
-[Sighs]
-What the fuck?
What the fuck is this? [Groans]
Ahh! Fuck!
Damn thing won't start.
Well, won't you fuck me?
Can you fucking untie me?
-Where'd they take her?
-Oh, fuck this shit.
Where'd they take her?
You know January. Where
did they take her?
Oh, fuck you!
I'll make this simple for you.
Um...
You tell me what I want
to know or I'll kill you.
Okay, okay. Hold on.
Hold. Just hold... Hold the fuck on.
-Okay.
-Just hold on one second.
-Where is she?
-I can't think.
Oh, that's where she is. She's dead.
She's already dead. Yeah.
Sorry, you're fucked.
No, no, no. Stop! Stop!
-Please.
-Keep talking.
Okay, it was Brake.
Okay? He was trying to
fucking sneak off with her,
that fucking dumb piece of shit.
Okay? He fucking knew better.
It was his own damn fucking fault.
-Is he dead?
-Yeah.
Who killed him? You?
Yeah. I fucking killed him. Okay.
What the fuck are you gonna do about it?
Okay! Fuck!
-Where's January?
-Fuck.
I took her to the compound.
Okay, the brother's wandering
the fucking compound.
-So I took her there.
-Is she alive?
If she was, she's
wishing right now that...
that she wasn't.
Listen, Alejandro, just...
He wanted that bitch, man.
-And, well, he fucking got her.
-Where's the compound?
It's fucking over,
man. It's fucking over.
-Where's the compound?
-I'm just doing what I had to do, man.
Fuck. I'm a runner, okay?
I come here to make sure
that fucking shit runs right.
Do you understand me?
I'm not supposed to be dealing
with that fucking shit right now!
-Let me out of here!
-Where's the com...
-Look, what is wrong with you?
-Ahh!
If you had a lawn mower in my face,
I'd be telling you everything.
[Screaming] Fuck!
[Davenport Grunts]
Oh, I see the problem.
It's a spark plug.
-What?
-I should have that fixed in a jiffy.
-Oh, it'll work now.
-No!
-No! Fuck!
-[Motor Turning Over]
Oh, yeah.
-Fuck!
-Hey, relax.
-Fuck you.
-I'm just gonna take a little off the top.
No, no, no, no!
-[Flesh Squelching]
-I'll fucking tell you!
[Groaning]
Ah! Fuck! I'll fucking tell you.
Okay, okay, okay, I'll take
you to the fucking compound.
-[Groans]
-[Bowdrie Sighs]
All right, let's get to it.
[Bowdrie] Dear Tag.
Kid, you are the best part of my life.
And I have loved every second with you.
Every second, every minute, every day.
A long time ago, I told you a lie.
I did it to protect you.
But maybe I was just scared.
Maybe I was just trying to protect myself.
I don't know anymore.
I was never scared before you were born.
Then the day you came...
Well, I learned different.
You always believed your mom was dead.
But she's not.
She's been imprisoned for
doing some horrible things,
but she's a different person now.
Last four months, every week
since she got out of jail,
she's been sending you letters.
She misses you, and she loves you.
But I destroyed those letters.
Each and every one Because I
didn't feel that she deserved you
or your forgiveness or your love
after what she had done.
But maybe it was me
who didn't deserve you.
The things I did for what I've been...
A liar, a coward.
Every day I've lied to you
because I didn't want you to be hurt.
I thought I was protecting
you, but I don't know.
I hope someday you can forgive me.
You can take your time about it.
I've never been much for forgiving,
but I think you are.
One of the things I love about you.
I'm gonna check on our friend.
And, if you find this,
it means it didn't go so well as I hoped.
And I'm sorry for letting you down.
[Gun Cocking]
The cabin is yours.
You know where the money is buried.
Don't spend it all on dumb stuff.
Take good care of the truck,
and she'll take good care of you.
Keep your gun clean. Never stop drawing.
The world is ugly, but you are
beautiful and strong and good.
And good wins down the line.
I love you forever. Always have.
-Bowdrie.
-[Engine Turning Over]
[Davenport Groans]
Davenport.
Hey, my friend here has a...
[Gagging]
[Hr]
[Guns Clacking]
Hey, front gate.
Where you at?
Ricky, where you at?
[Davenport Grunting]
Ricky. What's up, dawg? Where
you at? Come in, come in.
[Scoffs] Shit.
[Shotgun Cocks]
[Alejandro] You look lost... pardner.
No, I'm looking for a friend.
I know she's here.
Ff lend?
We have no friends here, cowboy.
I can see that.
Why don't we make this easy?
Hand her over.
Because, you know I'm not
going home without her.
[Alejandro] I know who you are.
Flag him in the back.
I sent some of my boys out to you,
and they never came back home.
Did you kill them?
Look, I just want my friend.
I don't want any trouble.
I figure I can make a
trade with this fella.
A trade?
[Alejandro Scoffs]
"A trade."
Two of my guys are missing, probably dead.
And you want to make a fucking trade?
-Yep.
-Fucking shit.
No. Cowboy...
you fucked up coming out here.
He's gonna kill the both of us, man.
-You understand?
-I just want the girl.
Well, I'll give you your girl
if you give me yours.
Huh?
Bowdrie!
We know everything.
[Clanking]
You know that I know,
and I know that you know.
-[Tag Breathing Heavily]
-And I know...
I'm gonna take Tag.
[Gunfire]
Move!
[Grunts]
[Sighs]
[Gunfire Continues]
[Panting]
Oh, baby!
Motherfucker!
Stop shooting at the lab!
[Grunting]
Fuck you!
Yeah.
[Panting]
[Hr]
Fuck!
[Breathing Heavily]
It's gonna be all right.
I'll come back. Okay?
-Fuck you, motherf...
-Go away!
-Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Run away!
[Indistinct Radio Chatter]
[Grunts]
[Alejandro] I was different
than the rest of the kids my age.
Oh, yes.
I was the king.
That is something...
[Bowdrie Groaning]
-[Groans Loudly]
-All this shit for nothing!
Over nobody! You don't even know me.
I am the king.
-I am the f...
-[Gunshot]
[Over Tape] I was a kid full of joy.
[Sighs, Grunts]
Kid full of expectations.
A kid full of expectations
and dreams to come true.
But I stepped at some
point with the wrong stone.
I was very young.
-[Woman Sobbing]
-[Bowdrie Breathing Heavily]
[Sobbing Continues]
[Hr]
[Sighs Heavily]
You're gonna be all right.
I've seen much worse.
[Bowdrie] Uh... Want me to go with you?
-Yeah?
-No.
All right.
[Hr]
♪ When the morning Fades us a'
♪ Tangled up inside A rage A'
♪ Like the clouds Could
break away apart 4'
♪ Bring it back to colors A'
♪ Echoes of the open tongue a'
♪ Do you remember How it feels? a'
♪ Do you hear it calling? S'
♪ Do you hear it Calling out? A'
♪ It's like the waters
Into rivers into lakes I
♪ Do you hear it calling? S'
♪ Do you hear it Calling out? A'
♪ Is it the start Of something
Better than we make? I
♪ It's a tunnel vision A'
♪ Make it breathe And come alive S'
♪ Smoke that station lingers
Long before the fire S'
♪ No more tainted sorrows A'
♪ No one cares When it collides A'
♪ I grabbed your look Tumbling down a'
♪ Do you hear it calling? S'
♪ Do you hear it Calling out? A'
♪ It's like the waters
Into rivers into lakes I
♪ Do you hear it calling? S'
♪ Do you hear it Calling out? A'
♪ Is it the start of
Something better Than we made?
♪ Loose threads Start to make a mess ♪
♪ When you cut the fence a'
♪ You hear it calling out A'
♪ Hear it calling out a'
♪ Do you hear it calling? S'
♪ Do you hear it Calling out? A'
♪ It's like the waters
Into rivers into lakes I
♪ Do you hear it calling? S'
♪ Do you hear it Calling out? A'
♪ Is it the start Of something
Better than we make? I