Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Aria.
Aria. Come on, baby.
You gotta get up. Let's go.
Come on.
Look, Mom, I coded it.
I know, baby. That's very good.
But I'm gonna move it
because I spent my last
on those batteries and wires.
And if your science fair project gets wet,
it's not gonna work.
I'm old enough to bathe myself.
I don't want you to fall
and hurt yourself again, okay?
Do we have to go to school today?
We go through this every day.
Aria, you have to go to school, okay?
That's why you're so smart.
Can you give her the money today
so she can stop making fun of me?
Who?
The teacher said
I need $40 to pay for lunch
so I can stop eating the special lunch.
- Did she say that in front of the class?
- Yeah.
Come on, baby. Let's go. Come on.
Come on.
Please pick that up. Don't drag it.
I want the clear one.
Oh, come on. I don't have time
for this today, all right?
Oh, Benny, I'm sorry.
I don't have nothing for you today.
Where are your teeth?
Get in the car.
Go ahead and put your seatbelt on.
This is all I have, okay?
God gonna bless you, baby.
- Don't you go buy no liquor.
- No.
I don't drink no more.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Oh, so you can give him money
but you can't pay me my rent?
I'm getting real tired of your shit.
I done already filed the eviction.
I get paid today,
and I get a break at 10:00.
- I'm gonna bring the money. I promise.
- You better!
Or all your little shit gonna
be right out there on the street!
Think you can get them to turn the music
down so my baby can sleep at night?
Hell no! He pay his rent!
What the hell she talking about?
Put your seatbelt on.
The moment I wake up
Before I put on my makeup
I say a little prayer for you...
All right.
We made it.
And wondering what dress to wear now...
All right, baby. I get paid today, okay?
So I will be here
to give you that money for lunch
so you can eat
with everybody else, all right?
You promise?
I promise.
Come on, let's go. Can't be late.
All right, love you.
- Love you too.
- Have a good day.
At work, I just take time...
I'm coming.
All right-- You gonna help us?
Just gotta clock in.
All right, well,
if she come over there,
y'all can tell her to call me.
I've been trying to reach her ass all day.
Yeah.
There's always a damn zoo up there
the first of the month.
Angela called in sick.
Yeah, so I got two registers open,
so hurry up and get up there.
I said hurry up. Why you walking?
Shit.
She gonna walk her ass up here all slow.
I can take the next person over here.
Um...
I'm sorry, ma'am. You can't buy
some of these items with a WIC card.
Bitch, I do this all the time.
I don't know who did it for you,
but we not allowed to do that.
What, you the damn
WIC police or something?
I'm gonna need $38.28, miss--
$38? Fuck you! Give me my card. Come on.
What the...
Clean this up.
They're just waiting for a slip and fall.
- Hurry up! Hurry up!
- Aww!
She'll be right back, y'all.
- She'll be right back.
- Oh really?
Did that bitch cut you?
No, it's okay.
How is she?
My baby's fine.
- Oh--
- Here, take it.
No, I can't take that from you.
You barely making it yourself.
I can spare it.
It'll help out with her medicine.
No, I can't take that from you.
We get paid today.
I'mma be okay.
Janiyah, you can't keep going this hard.
I'm worried about you.
It's okay.
The doctor said she's gonna outgrow
some of this stuff, okay?
And then I'll have more time,
and then I can go back to nursing school.
We'll be okay.
Just gotta get through this. That's all.
Okay.
Shit. Let us get out of here before this
motherfucker come back with his bullshit.
Wait, I'm coming.
Hello.
Oh yeah.
Um, Aria told me about the... the money.
Look, I'll bring the lunch money up there.
But why did y'all do that?
It's embarrassing to them kids.
She fell in the tub. No!
Please don't do this.
She fell! Ask her. She'll tell you.
I told you how sick she is.
Please don't do this.
I can't leave my job.
Do you want this damn job or not?
It's my daughter's school.
I don't give a damn if it's the president.
You see that line out there!
Okay.
And you're on the damn phone.
You know that's against
company policy, don't you?
Richard, wait! Richard, please.
There's something going on
at my daughter's school.
I have to go. I'm sorry.
I know you're not
trying to leave here, Janiyah.
It's out of my hands.
They said I have to come.
Janiyah, it's always something with you.
Some bullshit.
Come on, Richard, please.
It's just me and my daughter.
I don't have anybody else.
You better have your ass back here
in 30 minutes. Hear me?
- I can't make it happen in--
- Do you wanna go or not?
Okay. Can I get my check?
Oh shit, you done
lost your damn mind, girl.
Huh? You know, I got
to tend your register, do your job.
And now you want me to do you a favor?
Get on out of here.
Thirty damn minutes!
Excuse me.
Hi, my name's Janiyah Wiltkinson.
I work across the street.
Yes, I know who you are.
Yeah. I was just trying
to get $40 out of my account,
and the machine keeps saying
"insufficient funds,"
and I know I got $47 in the bank.
Well, you're getting that message
because it will close your account
if you have less than the minimum
required to keep it open.
- Okay, well, can I close it?
- I'm sorry, but you have to wait in line.
- I know, but my daughter--
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry. I got here as fast as I could.
- I'm sorry, Miss Wiltkinson.
- Mama! Mama!
- What? Wait!
I'm Dianne Hutchinson
from Children and Family Services.
- Let me just talk to her, please.
- Mama! Mama!
You don't understand!
She has seizures, okay?
She needs her medicine.
- She doesn't like to be without me.
- Listen to me.
I wanna go to my mama!
No, no, no, we can't upset her like this.
- Listen to me.
- No, no, no.
No!
She has asthma really bad.
Don't scream! Don't scream, Aria!
Wait a minute.
You're taking my baby?
She'll be in good hands.
- She's in good hands with me.
- Mama!
That's what we have to determine.
- No! My daughter is safe with me!
- Mama!
The teacher and the principal
said she comes to school very hungry.
You...
I work two jobs, okay?
I work two jobs to make sure
we have what we can to eat, okay?
She-- she can't even eat everything.
You know this!
I give her exactly
what the doctor tells me to give her!
The teacher also says
she's usually not very clean.
Oh my God, that's a lie! That's a lie!
Listen, okay, sometimes I don't have gas.
All right? I don't have gas,
and so I don't have hot water.
But I bathe her. I bathe her.
She is just... She gets... She gets very cold.
Okay? And I'm telling you the truth.
I swear to you, I'm telling the truth!
- We need to do a home visit.
- Please.
Why are you doing this?
Please, don't take my baby.
It's already done.
Please, no!
Here's my card.
We have your information.
We'll be in touch.
What about her medicine?
She will be in good hands.
You stupid fucking bitch!
You're fucking mine.
Yeah, you're gonna wish
you never fucking left the house.
Oh, I'm so glad you showed up.
This guy just ran me off the road.
I have his license plate number.
That's him!
You didn't know I was a cop, did you?
I need your license
and registration, ma'am.
I didn't do anything wrong.
- You hit my fucking brand-new car!
- You hit me!
License and registration, lady.
And please tell me you don't have it
so I can lock your ass up, bitch.
Come on, I got this.
You're too hot.
Head back to the station. Go on!
If I see you again, anywhere,
I'm gonna find a legal way
to fucking blow your brains out!
- You hear me?
- Hey! Get out of here.
Make her suffer.
Do you have your license
and registration, ma'am?
It's expired.
I know. I get paid today,
and I was gonna take care of it.
Today. Please.
I'm gonna write you a ticket.
- And impound your car.
- No, please, please.
I have to have my car.
- Ma'am--
- I can't afford a ticket. No.
No, I need my car!
Ma'am, if you start that car,
you will be arrested.
I'm going easy on you. He won't.
You want me to call him back here?
Stay there and don't move.
I can help the next person.
No, ma'am, ma'am.
Use the other one, please. No, no.
Thank you. Thank you.
I called Michelle in.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
You've been gone for two hours.
Look at you. Hmm?
Go in the office.
Go ahead.
Look at you.
Dripping all over the damn floor.
I'm...
I'm gonna have to let your ass go.
I need this job.
Oh yeah, well.
You should have thought about that shit
before you come in here two hours late!
I know you was across the street
at the damn bank!
Michelle saw your ass over there!
You told me you was going to the school!
I was trying to get money for my daughter.
She needs it for lunch.
You got too many fucking excuses!
I'm sorry, but I'm gonna have--
No, wait a minute.
I'm not sorry.
You brought that shit on your damn self!
Your ass is fired.
Can I have my check?
Oh, you want your check?
You know, when you get fired,
check is in the mail.
Now, that's company policy.
I can't wait for the check in the mail.
I have to pay my rent,
and I have to get this money
to my daughter so she can eat lunch.
Well, what you want me
to do about it, huh?
The check is right there.
I ain't giving you shit.
Now get the fuck out of here.
No!
What did you do?
You was supposed
to be back by ten o'clock on your break!
Ain't that what you said?
- No!
- I know you ain't got my damn money!
That's why all your shit is right there.
Whatever you don't pay, the rest
of that shit is going in the trash!
No!
These are two...
Why would you do this?!
You must think I'm a fucking fool!
No!
Where the hell have you been?
I've been calling you all day.
Oh, woman!
What the fuck?
I need my check.
What part of mail don't you understand?
I'm not gonna have no way
to live for me and my daughter.
Please.
Why do you think
that's part of my problem?
You're fired. Now get the fuck out.
Jeez!
Okay, now, I'll pick you up on Saturday.
Hey, how you doing, Miss...
"Janiyah."
I was wondering
if y'all sell Black and Milds.
Excuse me. You're not supposed--
Shut up and give me all the money!
- Oh shit!
- Give me the money! Huh?
- Here!
- All of it!
- Take it!
- Give me what's in the safe too!
Get the fucking money, old man!
Hurry up!
All right, just take it easy!
Let's go!
- Put it down! Get on the ground!
- Okay!
- All right!
- Yeah, run it!
Get the fucking money!
All right, take it! Take it! Just take it!
- Matter of fact, put it in here.
- No, no, please!
No, I need this for my daughter! No!
- Put the money in the bag!
- No!
Give it to him!
Give me this thing! What the fuck?
Oh shit! Give him the bag!
You think I'm a fucking fool?
You did this!
Yeah, you!
You set this up!
Oh, your ass is going to jail.
I didn't know him.
He called your name, Janiyah.
- Hello.
- He read my name tag.
Yes, listen.
There's been a robbery,
and the woman
who works for me, she set this up.
Her name is Janiyah Wiltkinson.
Your ass is going to jail. Yeah.
Why didn't you give him the damn bag?
Talking about giving it to your daughter.
She knew him! Janiyah, you knew him.
Your ass is going to prison!
See what kind of parent
you're gonna be from prison!
I'm sorry. We're closed.
I gotta cash my check.
I'm sorry. It's after 4:00.
Jones.
Let her in.
Thank you.
Hi again. She'll help you.
What the hell?
Mm, yeah, this is a mess.
Robbery?
Money's still here. Looks like
this one tried to rob the place,
and we confirmed
that this one is the manager.
Shot at close range,
one in the head, one in the chest.
Did they both get shots off?
No.
Cameras?
- Do they work?
- That's what I wanted to show you.
Everything's in working order.
Put it on repeat.
Do we know who she is?
911 operator said
her name was Janiyah Wiltkinson.
The victim called and said
that she set it up, and she shot him.
Here's her employee file.
It was in the file cabinet.
Looks like these two came
to rob her when she was getting her check.
Anybody else know her?
Detective Kay Raymond.
Did you witness this?
I just saw Janiyah in there.
I heard some gunshots, and I ran.
What can you tell me about her?
She's a good person.
She's a good mother.
She wouldn't do nothing like this.
Is she the type of person
that would set up a robbery?
No way.
Not this girl.
Janiyah is my friend.
Look, I know some hood bitches,
and she ain't nothing like this.
I ain't lying.
I'm telling y'all the truth!
She wouldn't do this.
She's a mother.
She got a kid and all that.
Do you know if she knew the guy
that robbed the place?
She don't talk to nobody.
- I'll have the officer ask more questions.
- Y'all gotta help her.
She dealing with a lot of shit,
and I'm the only one she got.
You don't know what that's like.
She wouldn't do it.
I'm telling you, she wouldn't do it.
Thank you for your time.
Yeah, she's definitely in on it.
She left in the perp's car.
Get me an APB on her car
and her as a person of interest.
Person of interest?
You need to watch that again?
Billy, I got this.
And make sure you find
the license plate readers in this area.
All right.
Uh, next, please.
I need to cash this.
You must have kids.
Uh, did they
spill slushy on this or something?
May I have your ID?
Your ID?
Oh, it was stolen.
Oh, I'm sorry,
but I'm not gonna be able
to cash this without your ID.
Mm-mmm.
You've helped me before,
so just cash it.
- Yeah, I know, but I--
- Please.
Listen, it's the policy of the bank.
I cannot cash the check without the ID.
Tessa, you've helped me before.
Cash the check.
Listen, I understand, but,
look, you can speak with our manager,
and maybe she can help you, but I...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but--
- Oh God!
- Just cash the check. Cash it.
- Okay. Okay.
- Please.
Okay, uh...
Benevolent Bank and Trust.
Nicole speaking. How can I help you?
This is 911. We have an alert
that a robbery's in progress.
Um, yes, that is correct.
You said your name is?
Nicole Parker. I'm the manager.
And this is Mimms St. branch?
Yes.
Do you have eyes on the person, ma'am?
If so, can you safely describe them?
Yes.
A Black female.
About 5'7".
Um, she's wearing a red vest and jeans.
She comes in here all the time.
She works across the street
at the Super Center.
Do you know her name?
Um...
I-- I can't remember her last name.
It's something like Janay, I think.
Janiyah Wiltkinson, ma'am?
How do you know that?
The police are en route.
Oh my God.
What is it, ma'am?
She has a bomb.
Stay on the line, ma'am.
And you evicted her today?
I sure in the hell did.
"Aria Wiltkinson."
- Who's that?
- That's her daughter.
She was sick.
Janiyah was always
taking her to the hospital.
Yeah, even though she be struggling,
she still give me change.
She's a good girl.
I don't give a damn about
none of that shit that Benny is talking.
I have a right to put her ass out,
so that's exactly what I did.
Can we see the apartment?
You got a first and last month's rent?
Otherwise, you ain't seeing shit.
Look, ma'am, it would be nice
if you could just cooperate.
This-- This one ain't even worth it.
The fuck you mean?
Think I give a fuck
about the police? And don't.
You okay?
Yeah.
Too many memories, Billy.
Too many memories.
Bank robbery in progress.
Subject is Janiyah Wiltkinson.
What the hell? Come on, let's go.
Wait, wait, wait.
Why are you giving me--
I don't want all of this!
What are you doing?
No, I just want my check cashed.
My check is for $521. Cash my check.
- I don't want that.
- Um...
Yes. Okay. Jones.
You need to get everyone out of the bank.
We're being robbed.
Yes, she has a gun and a bomb.
Um, yes.
I'm going to let you talk
to the security guard here.
Here, Jones. Talk to her.
I'm sorry, sir. The bank is closed.
- Hold on. The fuck is you talking about?
- Shh! Sir!
We need you to leave.
Ma'am, I been standing
in this long-ass line.
- Now, what's up?
- I need my money.
You know how long we've been waiting?
We are being robbed.
Sorry, we're being robbed--
- Excuse me!
- Yes.
I don't know what's wrong with her.
Can-- can you please...
Uh, yes.
Yes.
I don't know why she's giving me all
this money. I just want my check cashed.
I can do that for you.
Why is she acting like that?
I didn't do anything to her!
- I know. I know you didn't.
- She keeps saying I need an ID.
- I don't have an ID.
- She's right.
- She knows me! Tessa!
- She knows you, Tessa.
- Why's she acting like she doesn't know?
- It's okay. I can do this for you.
Because I know you.
I know you.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Yes.
I just need my money.
I just need to cash my check. That's all.
- Tessa.
- $521, that's all I need.
- Please. That's it.
- I got it. I got it.
- Tessa.
- Yes.
Cash her check.
- Tessa.
- Why is she crying?
It's okay. Ca-- Cash the check, Tessa.
Eyes on, eyes on!
I got my eyes on her!
- Right. How long on the mobile unit?
- Ten out, Chief.
- You two called out the APB on her?
- Yes, sir.
All right, well, tell me about her.
Janiyah Ann Wiltkinson, 42, no priors,
was caught on camera committing the murder
of her boss at the Super Center.
All right, I need a line in that bank.
We need a line patched
to the bank right now.
Tell them to hurry their asses. I wanna
put some eyes in that bank as well.
- Was the crime scene bad?
- Yes, very bad.
We think that she set up the robbery
at the Super Center, and then it went bad.
She left in a getaway car.
Or...
Talk.
In the video,
she looks as though
she was a victim caught up in a robbery.
Okay, so how do you
explain her killing her boss?
She was evicted from her home today.
Which is all the more reason
for her to rob the bank.
Or maybe it was just too much for her,
and she wanted her pay.
She got caught up in a robbery
and snapped, so she killed him.
You, come with me.
20s, please. I need some-- I need 20s.
No!
Shots fired, sir! Get down!
We have shots fired!
Hands up! Hands up now!
- All right! It ain't even us!
- Keep your hands up!
Look, the lady's still robbing the bank.
All right. This is the security guard.
Did she shoot at you?
Nah. When I tried to take her down,
her gun went off.
This motherfucker wasn't doing shit.
Well, that was stupid.
Get up!
Stop acting like that!
I didn't do nothing to you!
Tessa!
You gave me that money. You set me up!
I just needed to get the $40
and take it to the school.
On the scene now
at Benevolent Bank and Trust
where there is a robbery in progress.
The police received a silent alarm,
and when they got on the scene,
they heard a gunshot.
And, Martha, we heard it as well
just moments ago.
It was chaos.
Two gentlemen came running out of the door
and were immediately met
with commands from the police.
Now, from what we have learned,
the suspect's name is
Janiyah Ann Wiltkinson.
Our sources at the police department
have shared that she is wanted in question
for an earlier murder
that happened at the Super Center
on Beneville Boulevard near the branch.
Tessa, give me the phone.
Benevolent Bank and Trust.
Uh, yes.
It's for you.
Who's calling me?
Uh, our bank lines run on cell phones
so we can move around.
Hello?
- Janiyah, this is Chief Wilson--
- Mnh-mnh.
- Okay.
Get back, please!
Mobile unit is here.
She hung up. Call her back.
- Where in the hell is the negotiator?
- He's close, sir.
Sir.
What is it?
Perhaps I have a better shot.
And why do you think that?
Female voice, someone she can relate to.
Okay.
And what makes you think
that's the right thing to do?
I mean, she was robbed by a man.
She was set up by a man.
She killed a man.
And how are you so sure she was set up?
I just feel it, sir.
- Come with me.
- Yes, sir.
- If anything goes wrong, it's your ass.
She doesn't wanna talk to you.
Can you put me on speaker?
You're on.
Hi, Janiyah.
My name is Detective Raymond.
Why are all the police
out there like that?
Negotiator's here.
Great news.
One of my officers made contact.
- Wanna take over?
- Hold on.
- Just let me listen.
- All right.
We got a call the bank was being robbed.
- Oh, no!
- Listen.
I know it may be scary,
but I need to ask,
is everyone in there okay?
We heard a gunshot from inside the bank.
No! No!
It went off when he ran into me.
And then-- And then the gun went off!
I hear that. I hear that.
But we have to be very, very careful.
There's a lot of people in there that can
get hurt, and we don't want that, okay?
Listen, I didn't rob the bank.
I just came to cash my check.
That's all.
It's good to know
that you're not robbing the bank.
How about you put the gun down,
just step outside with the backpack
and let's figure this out?
She gave me the money, and I told her
I didn't want all of that money!
Did you call the police?
Why would you do that?
Why did you do that?
Stop screaming!
Janiyah, listen to me.
This seems to be one big misunderstanding.
It is, because I didn't come here
to rob the bank!
That's what I'm trying to tell you!
I come here all the time.
Why would you do that?
Janiyah, it's okay.
Okay, well, you never came into the bank
with a backpack and a gun.
Can you see how this can all be confusing?
She's doing good.
Good.
This gun is not even mine!
Okay, well, let's just put it down
and come outside and let's talk about it.
Let's get it all sorted out.
No, no, no.
No, all I need is my money,
because I have to get
the $40 to the school,
because she gotta eat.
And if she doesn't eat,
they're gonna tease her!
I just... I... I...
I just came to get the money for my baby!
Okay, okay, and I can do that.
I just need you to come out
and talk to me first.
You're lying.
You can't help me.
Nobody ever helps me!
I do it all myself.
Every fucking thing, I do it myself!
You wanna-- You wanna kill me!
You wanna blame me
for robbing this bank, and I didn't do it.
And you wanna lock me up,
and then what about my baby?
What about my baby?
You're lying!
Okay, well, the best way we can do that
is by helping you
get your side of the truth out.
How many people
are in there with you, Janiyah?
I don't know. I don't know. Uh...
If you don't wanna come out right now,
can you at least let them out?
No one else needs to get hurt, Janiyah.
I don't want anybody to get hurt!
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
I didn't come here to do that!
Hang up the phone. Hang it up!
She hung up.
Hey! Is there an electrical issue?
Why are the lights strobing?
Is that why we lost her?
Get her back on the phone right now!
Dan, do you wanna take over now?
- No, no, she actually did really well.
- All right. Good.
And she's established trust
with Detective Raymond.
- Mm-hmm.
- I think she should stay.
Where'd you learn this?
I was a negotiation specialist
in the army.
Hoorah.
Mm-hmm.
Ah.
Here-- Here's your money, Miss Wiltkinson.
Janiyah.
There-- There's your money.
You know...
I think this has all been
a misunderstanding.
But we can fix it.
I-- I can tell them this is all a mistake.
Would you like us to do that?
Can you give this to my daughter?
- Take it!
- I-- I--
Please.
I'm sure she would want you
to give this to her yourself.
He ain't gonna let me.
- Tell them to close the blinds.
- Um...
Now!
Tessa, Rayah, close the blinds. It's okay.
Hurry, run!
It's okay. It's okay. Just do it.
All the way! Pull it all the way down!
- And come back over here. Hurry.
- Come on.
Okay. Okay.
Surveillance is up.
- All right, let's zoom in.
- Zoom in!
- Where in the hell's the bomb squad?
- Moving into position.
All right, get someone in here
to tell me what that is right there.
Copy that.
I need to sit down.
Uh, oh yeah.
Um...
Go get her a chair.
Go!
Look, I'm-- I'm sorry, okay?
I know you all got lives to get back to.
Then let us go!
I'm sorry!
I...
I just need a minute to figure this out.
Young lady, ain't nothing to figure out.
Just give yourself up.
I can't let him kill me.
I don't know what's the matter with y'all.
We ain't never stolen nothing from nobody.
I haven't either.
Then what is all this?
Okay, can we-- Can we not?
She said she wasn't trying
to rob the bank.
Let's not upset her.
Shit, this is upsetting!
Y'all don't wanna work
for nothing no more.
I am a veteran!
We fought long and hard
for y'all to have all these freedoms
and look at the thanks we get.
Um...
I'm not dealing with this shit.
I'm leaving. Come on.
Is she just gonna let them both walk out?
Hey, we got two hostages coming out.
Just a little further, okay? All right?
Lock the door! Lock the door.
All right! Come back.
Come back. Come back.
Janiyah, you don't have to do this!
We can all walk out of here together!
I can't let him kill me.
Who's gonna take care of my daughter?
She's all I have.
I just...
I need you to stay with me, okay? Please.
I don't ask nobody for nothing. Please.
Okay? I just...
I just need to work this out, okay?
Just gotta work this out.
Just need to think.
She's gonna kill me. She's mad at me.
Tessa, you need to stay calm.
She's not gonna hurt you.
Why can't we just run for the door?
She let them go.
This lady is elderly. She can't run.
Can't I go with Rayah? Please!
We gotta do something.
- Don't.
- I can't take it.
She has a bomb in her backpack.
Oh my God.
A bomb?
All these years. Oh God.
I don't wanna leave out like that.
Here you go. Yeah.
There. There.
Here!
Okay.
All right.
Sit down!
Sit!
Have you heard of a robber
getting chairs for people?
No, but you saw the crime scenes.
Now...
Now you don't have to stand up.
I know what it feels like
to be on your feet all day.
Chief, all right,
we got the blueprints for the bank.
We can go in now, flash grenade, storm it.
Teller said she had a bomb.
I'm not so sure
she has any munitions training.
- Are you sure about that?
- Not that we know of.
It could be fake.
Or she could have learned it
from the internet, and it's real.
Okay. Well, since we don't know right now,
we're just gonna stand down and wait.
We can't get in there with four hostages.
Look.
- I think we should get the FBI in here.
- Shit.
- All right?
- This is not your average bank robber.
No, it's not. She's a murderer.
She didn't even try
to stop them from walking out.
She's literally getting chairs for people.
- Yeah.
- A witness said this is not like her.
Another witness said
that she's a good girl.
I really think she may have just snapped.
Okay, so what's stopping her
from snapping out
and blowing up the damn bank?
Now look, look.
This detective has a good eye, all right?
I think we can end this thing peacefully.
If the FBI gets involved,
they will take over.
They may not have
the same interests as us.
Wait. You mean to stop the robbery, right?
No, I mean to save her life.
We saw her things get thrown out there.
We seen her medicine for her kid.
This is about giving her a chance.
Listen.
Let's hold off
on calling the FBI right now.
Matter of fact,
let's wait for them to call us.
Okay?
Buy some time.
Let's get her back on the phone.
Let's get her back on the line.
- Yes, sir!
- All right.
Dan, do you wanna take over now?
Detective Raymond.
It's on you.
Ooh, these phones!
These phones are driving me crazy.
I wanna unplug 'em.
- How do you unplug the phones?
- It might be better if you talk to them.
Janiyah.
No, I wanna turn 'em off.
You might want to answer it.
They may have an idea
on how to get you out safely,
to your daughter.
Hello.
Janiyah, this is Detective Raymond again.
Thanks for answering.
How's it going in there?
Why you got all those police out there?
Just for me?
I told you I wasn't robbing this bank.
We are getting reports
that the suspect has gone live,
and we are getting that feed up
for our viewers.
Yes, yes, we have it.
I just needed to cash my check.
I ain't never stole nothing
a day in my life.
I didn't even know I had this gun.
That is why I'm trying to tell you
I didn't want this to happen.
And you've made that perfectly clear,
so how about we stop this, Janiyah?
I can't come out there
and let them shoot me.
No one is gonna shoot you.
No, he said it.
He said if he sees me again,
he's gonna blow my brains out.
Who said that?
That police officer, he's out there!
He's out there.
He said he was gonna kill me.
The officer out there.
- He ran me off the road earlier.
- Hey!
And that other officer,
she's out there. I saw her.
She had my car towed.
I told them that I needed my car,
because when my daughter gets sick,
I have to take her to the hospital.
I can't wait for an ambulance!
Okay. I got it.
Everything's gonna be okay.
I promise you, no one will hurt you.
Just please come on out
and let's talk about this.
I can't come out there
so they can shoot me.
I needed my money
to get my daughter's medicine.
She's sick.
Janiyah. Janiyah.
Come out and I can help you.
Are you gonna help me with my boss?
He thinks I set up
the robbery at that store.
That man robbed me,
and he hit me.
Just because he read my name tag,
my boss thought he knew me,
and he thought I set it up!
Then he wouldn't give me my check!
He fired me!
My boss fired me.
He fired me because the school called
and told me to come and check on my child.
So he fired me.
My baby's medicine is so expensive.
It's so hard.
I work so hard.
I have two jobs.
I'm barely making it.
I just wanna do what's right for my baby.
That's all.
They took her...
...because she fell in the tub
because she's sick.
She lost her balance. She wanted to...
She wants to bathe herself.
She fell.
She had bruises on her back,
and they blamed me.
They took her.
They didn't care.
Okay, you're right. You're right.
And you have every right
to be upset, okay?
But we can try and figure out
how to get you some help, Janiyah.
I don't want you to get upset.
I got put out.
I got put out today.
We have nowhere to live.
My daughter's medicine...
...was... was put out on the street.
And I told her.
I said, "I just got fired."
"My boss is gonna mail me the check."
She couldn't wait for three days.
Three days!
You don't know how hard it is
to take care of my baby
off of what I make.
I can't get half of what she needs.
And my landlord didn't care.
She just put us out in the rain.
What am I gonna tell her
when she gets home?
It's just too much.
I'm all we got.
Nobody cares. Nobody sees us.
This is my life.
Over and over and over and over.
I just don't know what to do.
You can understand that, right?
I have nothing.
Yes. Yes.
I can see how this can be a lot.
I see you.
I hear you.
Janiyah, I care.
Steady yourself. Okay?
You don't know me. You don't care.
You just want me to come out there
so that man can shoot me.
No, I don't know you.
But I recognize me in you.
Not only was I raised by a single mother,
but I am a single mother, okay?
Everything is on me.
I remember coming home
from school one day, and we were evicted.
My mother was so angry.
She was so upset.
No, go in another direction.
This might trigger her, okay?
How old were you?
I was nine.
My daughter's eight.
So I get it. But you know what?
I remember telling my mother
how much I loved her.
I told her I loved her,
and I told her we would be okay.
And, Janiyah, I promise you,
you will be okay.
You and your baby girl. You will be okay.
You'll be okay.
Chief, we're live.
What?
Okay, put it over here.
Just listen, okay?
It sounds like it's been
a really, really long and trying day.
It sounds like you haven't slept, okay?
I think if you came out,
we could figure this all out. I promise.
Stop saying that!
Stop saying that. I'm not coming out
until you make him leave.
She's getting too emotional
and so are you.
Just get back to asking her to surrender.
The one that ran me off the road and said
he was gonna find a legal way to kill me.
And that other one
who wrote me all those tickets.
- Just listen.
- She knows I can't afford 'em! I told her!
'Cause nobody cares about me.
So, no! I'm not coming out.
What--
What?
I'll check on her.
You okay?
Yeah.
Hey, look.
I know I've been giving you shit.
That was a damn good job in there.
Sorry.
I didn't know all that about you.
- Are we good?
- Yeah.
How in the hell is she on TV?
Chief, one of the hostages
went live on their cell phone, sir.
It was one of the bank tellers.
All right, get the damn
cell signal jammed right now.
I wanna find out who in the hell
is this officer she's talking about.
We're on it, sir.
If she was written a ticket,
I wanna know who wrote that ticket.
Copy that. Jam all cell service...
- Where do these cameras go to?
- Um...
- Uh, to our corporate offices.
- No, no, no.
Where in here? I wanna unplug 'em.
- I don't understand--
- Where are the cameras plugged up in here?
- In the-- In the back.
- Take me.
- Don't move.
- Uh...
Don't move.
Did she unlock the door?
- No, she didn't.
- She did. To the left. It's unlocked.
She pushed it hard. It's not.
I gotta get out of here.
I gotta figure out
if that door's unlocked.
Girl, she has a bomb. Sit down.
- I need to get out of here.
- Tessa. Tessa.
- Look. Shh! Keys are behind the counter.
- No! Tessa! Tessa!
Tessa.
Tessa!
You should be careful with that.
Yeah, I know. We worked hard on it.
Do you know a lot about electronics?
No.
Wait.
- What in the hell happened?
- We lost connection, Chief.
Damn it!
Tessa! Tessa. Tessa.
Tessa! Tess--
What are you doing?
Uh, I have to go to the bathroom.
We all have to go.
Okay.
Uh, is there a bathroom in here?
Yes, it's back there.
Okay.
All right, one at a time.
No, nothing.
Not one ticket in her name?
No, maybe she was in Dale County.
We could check there.
Okay.
You're not hearing me!
What do you think they're doing out there?
You want a peppermint?
Is that where all the peppermints go
when I put them out?
As much as y'all charge for fees,
I know I can have a peppermint.
Look, I'm sorry,
but she is holding us all here,
and y'all are treating her like a martyr.
This is wrong.
Tessa, enough.
No, let her talk.
No, she needs to shut up.
How old are you?
Why?
'Cause I don't know anybody
that can hear what she's been saying
and feel nothing.
I'm not saying it's right,
and I don't agree,
but I sure do hope
this works out for you, baby.
Thank you.
They always keep the air up
on high in here.
I have a jacket in my office.
And it's right there.
I can get it for you.
This is crazy.
- She has a bomb.
- Then hush.
Um...
Here it is.
Thank you.
Mm. Smells good. I like the perfume.
Is it expensive?
It was a gift from my husband.
Is he-- Is he nice to you?
He's the best.
Good for you.
You gotta be so careful
who you have a baby with.
It seems like you had
a lot to get over today.
Black women always have
something to get over.
Is this your family?
Yes, it is.
Big brick house in the suburbs, huh?
It's not so big.
Oh, it's big to me.
Hmm. Hmm.
My apartment ain't
no bigger than this room.
I always dreamed of
having a place like that
for me and my baby.
How old-- How old are your kids?
My oldest is Jennifer,
and she's 16.
- Hmm.
- And...
my youngest is Jasmine,
and she's seven.
Aria. That's my daughter.
She's got so many complications
I hope she grows out of,
especially the seizures.
I've seen you in here with her.
How attentive you are.
I notice those things.
For what it's worth,
I see so many single mothers come in here.
I swear if I didn't have my husband,
I don't know what I would do.
No. You figure it out.
Well, we need to figure this out
so you can get back to your daughter.
And I can get back to my family.
You will.
But they gonna put me in jail
for all of this.
Janiyah, I'm not gonna lie to you.
This is bad.
I know.
You will spend time in there,
but you will get out,
and your daughter will be waiting.
So what does that mean for her?
Foster care?
No.
Is there somebody in your family
that can help?
No.
I don't want her anywhere near
my sister and my mother. They are crazy.
It's okay.
It's okay because
we are all gonna walk out of here
as soon as they let that man go.
Soon as they get rid of that cop. Come on.
Shit!
- I knew it wouldn't be long.
- This can get ugly very quick.
- I need you to help to find that officer.
- I'm trying.
What is that?
- I don't know.
- Well, go see.
What are they saying?
They're saying, "Free Janiyah."
They're here for you.
It's on the news.
Free Janiyah! Free Janiyah!
Free Janiyah! Free Janiyah! Free Janiyah...
Let's see if I can get in this crowd
and see what's going on.
Hi, ma'am, why are you here?
Because we're tired of all this
fucking shit! We go through too much.
We can't have the colorful language.
Oh, sir, what about you?
My name is Benny. I know her.
She ain't lying.
She's been going through it.
I'm here for you, Janiyah.
I'm homeless.
She ain't hardly have nothing.
But she made sure I had something to eat.
But you do know
that she is wanted for murder.
But what did them motherfuckers do?
Shit, I get it.
All this shit'll make you snap.
Go live, Janiyah. Go live on your phone.
I want to apologize
to our viewers for the language,
but as you can see, this crowd is feeling
very passionate
and emotional about this situation.
I have to tell you,
this crowd is in full support
of the alleged bank robber.
I've never seen anything like this.
All right, everybody out.
FBI's taking over.
- Shit.
- Come on, let's go.
Chief, you were in charge.
Now we're in charge.
Is that right?
That's right. Jim, grab that monitor.
- Susan, let me get you here.
- Yep.
Come on, Bryce.
You know we have this under control.
This has been going on for hours.
I would say that you don't.
Well, we made contact.
We're just working on getting her out.
Okay.
Well, that is
the whole objective, isn't it?
Yeah.
Seven hostages?
She released two.
And a bomb.
We're assuming, but, uh,
you know, I have a very strong feeling
that she's going to surrender peacefully.
A feeling?
Yeah. Our officer she bonded with,
Detective Raymond, right here.
This officer?
Yeah.
Okay. Listen, Chief.
You let this woman go live
and create a mob frenzy outside
of the bank.
I don't think you have this under control.
I strongly disagree.
She murdered her boss in cold blood.
She's got a bomb inside the bank,
and you have her bonding with an officer.
I don't think you have this under control.
So, as I said, we're taking over.
- Agent Bryce--
- Chief Wilson, you know what's next.
This is federal, so we're taking over.
We gotta find this damn officer.
All right.
I know you don't remember this,
but I was coming out of
the check cashing place across the street,
and you were trying to get me
to open up an account here.
You told me to stop
letting them take money from me.
I opened up an account because of you.
Why do you care so much?
I used to work at
the East Dale branch, and, uh,
all the women coming in with money,
they would get credit cards
and loans like it was nothing.
So I asked to be moved here,
so I could help us.
But there was so much red tape,
so much built into us not getting ahead.
I just wanted to make a difference.
You are making a difference.
Says the woman who is robbing the bank.
You ain't a nice person.
Oh, I'm sorry if I'm testy,
but we've been sitting here for hours.
And it's getting so hot.
Yes. Why is it so hot in here?
They turned off the AC.
They don't know me,
'cause I sleep in heat like this.
You don't have air conditioning?
No.
I was born in 1943.
We didn't even know anything
about an air conditioner
or a bathroom where I grew up.
Y'all just don't know how good you got it.
Even you.
'Cause, baby,
as bad as it is,
there's always somebody doing worse.
I know.
That's why I always try to be grateful.
Baby, walking out there
and giving up is being grateful.
I didn't mean to do this.
Okay?
Um, I...
I just, uh...
When I was at the hospital
with my daughter,
I just...
Something inside of me broke, and I just
feel like I've been floating
outside of myself ever since.
You know, that, um...
that hospital, they...
They don't care.
Um, my baby was a preemie,
so when my water broke,
they was telling me everything
that was wrong with her, and...
I just knew something wasn't right.
And the doctor kept telling me to sit up.
He said, "Sit up!"
And I knew that wasn't right,
and they was trying
to make me abort my baby.
I know it sounds crazy, but...
I'm telling the truth, and you know,
when you don't have insurance...
I believe you.
People don't know
how expensive it is to be poor.
I just don't have anybody.
Well, you got me.
Will you take my daughter for me
when they lock me up?
Like, foster care, just...
Keep her until I get out?
She won't be no problem either,
because she's a good girl.
She beat every odd so far.
She wasn't supposed to make it.
Please.
Because I don't have anybody else
to do it.
I will.
I will talk to my husband,
and I know he will say yes.
I will.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
- I'm feeling bad.
- Oh.
Oh.
Can you get her some water?
Wait. Are you diabetic?
Yes.
Oh no, no.
Okay, we gotta let her out.
We gotta let her out.
Okay. Tessa.
- Okay, Miss Isabella.
- Go. Take her.
- Okay, come on, Miss Isabella.
- Be careful.
Come on.
I'm so sorry.
Okay, I got you.
You take care of yourself, girl. Okay?
Okay.
Come on, Miss Isabella.
- Ooh Lord.
- Make sure she gets the help, okay?
Okay.
She needs a doctor!
Hey, she's a customer.
Hold fire. Hold your fucking fire!
Be careful! She's a diabetic.
Take your hands off me!
Listen, I can't let you go in there.
I'm sorry.
She trusts me.
I'm not leaving my folks in there.
Ma'am.
One of your officers
let a hostage back in the building.
Get the fuck off me.
Free Janiyah! Free Janiyah! Free Janiyah!
Free Janiyah! Free Janiyah!
I hope she's gonna be okay.
They got her.
Okay.
Detective Raymond.
Yeah, she's a diabetic.
They need to check her levels.
Can you please let me know she's okay?
This is Agent Bryce with the FBI.
Is this Janiyah?
Uh...
Where-- Where's Detective Raymond?
- I'm right--
- Hey!
Unh-unh. We're taking over
the investigation now.
How is everyone in there?
They're fine.
I need to speak to Detective Raymond.
Sorry, ma'am. You have to talk to me now.
Well, is that officer gone?
What officer is that, ma'am?
That's why I need to talk
to Detective Raymond,
because she knows.
Look, ma'am,
this has been going on long enough.
It's time for you to let the hostages go
and come out and surrender.
I'm not going nowhere
until I know that officer is gone!
I'm not going over this with you again!
Ma'am, when you rob a bank,
you don't get to pick
and choose what you wanna do, okay?
I'm not robbing the bank!
This is a federal crime.
It's been going on long enough.
We need you to come out of the bank.
I'm not coming out
until I know that officer's gone.
Ma'am.
He won't let me talk to Detective Raymond.
I need to talk to Detective Raymond!
Sir-- Sir, please--
Please get Detective Raymond.
She only talks to me now. Who is this?
I'm Nicole, the branch manager.
Nicole, she needs to talk to me.
Please, sir, get Detective Raymond.
- Ugh! This thing is driving me crazy!
- She's picked up the backpack!
- Janiyah, you don't have to do this.
- What?
Janiyah, please. Janiyah, please.
What's she doing now, ma'am?
- We can all walk out of here together.
- Please!
- This is driving me crazy!
- Janiyah, we can do this!
- Janiyah, please don't--
- So loud!
Oh my-- Just hang up the phone!
Don't, please!
Nicole! Nicole!
- Please!
- Please don't do this!
- Don't! Don't!
Come on!
Please.
My daughter made this.
Her science fair project.
It drives me crazy.
It's... It's not a bomb?
No.
It's not a bomb. It's...
They think this is a bomb?
All this time?
You-- It's not a--
Can you call
and tell them it's not a bomb?
It's for my daughter's
science fair project.
You gotta call them
and tell them it's not a bomb.
If we explain that, then...
then they'll know.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Go! Go! Tell them!
Tell them it's not a bomb!
We got a message.
"Bomb is not real. One gun."
- Call them and tell them.
- Okay. Okay.
Call Detective Raymond
and tell them it's--
it's been a big mistake.
Come on, you have to tell them
this is a science fair project.
What?
I don't think we should do that.
Why?
They have policies regarding explosives.
- But--
- That may be the only thing
that is keeping them from coming in
and storming the bank.
I don't want you to get hurt.
So, let's tell them
that we're going to come out,
and you're gonna leave the backpack.
You think that's for the best?
I do.
But that officer has to be gone.
Okay.
You promise me.
Promise.
Detective Raymond.
Yeah.
Tell her.
I wrote her the tickets today.
Expired registration and so on, all legit.
- Did you tow her car?
- Yes.
- Did you run her off the road?
- No, I didn't do that.
Okay. She said there was
another officer there. Who was it?
I don't have time for your bullshit,
Officer Sam. Just tell me.
I don't really know.
She said it was a cop.
You fucking lying to me.
You fucking lying to me?
Tell me the fucking truth!
- Who was it?
- It was Officer Oliver.
Did he hit her car?
I didn't see him.
Was there any damage to the car?
- Yes. It looked like he pitted her.
- Bet.
Raymond. Raymond, come on.
Don't-- Don't do this.
Hey, hey, hey! What in the hell
is going on, Detective Raymond?
He know what the fuck is going on!
Tell him what you did.
Tell him what the fuck you did!
I didn't do shit.
What in the hell is going on?
What's going on?
He gave her a fucking ticket.
He ran her off the road.
He caused all this shit!
I got the proof, Chief. I got it.
He did it.
You... with me right now.
Let's go.
You're done, motherfucker! You're done!
Agent Bryce, we know who the officer is.
- I said no more talking.
- The damn phones are ringing.
- Answer the phone.
- I said no more talking.
Answer the damn phone!
Fuck it and fuck you!
God damn it!
This is Detective Raymond.
It's Detective Raymond.
Oh.
Hello?
- Detective Raymond.
- Yes.
Who was that asshole?
You have me now.
I just wanted to let you know
that we found the officer.
You did?
Yes, it took us a minute
because he's in the county over.
The officer that gave you the ticket
told us that it was him.
And judging by the damage of your car,
he hit you.
Promise.
I promise.
Okay, I wanna see a picture then.
A picture?
I want you to prove to me
that you know who it is.
I wanna see a picture.
I can show you that,
Janiyah, when you come out, okay?
No. No.
Text it to me.
Janiyah, your phone is not on.
The ones you are using there
in the bank are only for inner calls.
Okay, well, then turn my phone back on.
You can do it. You have the power.
The FBI can turn my phone back on
and then text me the picture.
And you'll come out?
Yes, I'll come out. Text me the picture.
Okay. Now let me get your phone turned on.
No, not a chance.
She has to give me the hostages.
Janiyah, the FBI can turn your phone on.
But we're gonna need
something in exchange, okay?
Okay.
Well, send me the picture,
and I'll let everybody go.
Come on. This is worth a chance.
Are you gonna send it?
Yes, we're getting your phone turned on.
Okay.
But when you send me the picture,
then everybody can go.
And then you tell them what he did to me.
You show everybody what he did to me.
And 'cause I wasn't lying!
You let everybody know
I was telling the truth, okay?
Yes. Yes, we will. Yes.
And I know that female officer
had a body cam. She saw it.
She made him go back to his car
because she heard him threaten me.
Okay, and then you will come out?
Yes, I'll come out.
And you're gonna leave the gun
in the backpack, right?
Yes.
So when you walk out,
hold your hands up high.
And back up slowly,
directly toward the police.
You gonna be there?
Yes, it will be me. Just follow my voice.
Okay.
I'll call you back.
Just send the picture.
I'll get the photo to you
in a second, all right?
They found him.
I told you.
I wasn't lying. They found him.
I told you I wasn't lying.
Shut down all the lights.
- Wait, what?
- We're going in.
She's literally coming out!
Why would we be going in?
This has been going on
for 12 hours, all right?
Do you see those people?
No, do you see this?
They will fucking riot.
We can end this peacefully.
You had your time.
Turn the damn phones on.
Is everyone in place?
Fucking kidding me.
Free Janiyah...
Oh! Raymond, what are you doing?
Detective Raymond, what are you doing?
What the hell is she doing?
Detective Raymond!
Who is that banging?
Janiyah!
It's Detective Raymond.
Ooh.
Janiyah, it's Detective Raymond.
I've been speaking with you.
What does she want?
They will not turn your phone back on,
Janiyah. I'm sorry.
But I have the proof here in my phone.
I can show you the photos right here.
Okay, open it. Get the phone.
He's gone. I promise.
Okay.
I'll take it to her.
That's him! That's him!
I told you I wasn't lying.
I know you weren't.
Okay, tell her that's him.
She says it's him.
He's gone.
Y'all can go.
Come on, Tessa, Rayah.
Wait.
What are you doing?
No, go on.
- What are you doing?
- Go.
I'm gonna walk with her.
Okay.
No. You go.
You can go.
No.
We're gonna do this together.
I never had anybody stand by me
before.
I'm sorry.
For all of this.
You got me.
Will you come visit me
when they lock me up?
Yes, I promise you.
I will come visit you with Aria.
And I will tell her
what a brave mother you are.
And please,
make sure my baby gets her $40 for lunch.
I will.
Make it happen.
My phone is on.
It's my mother.
Hello?
Janiyah, the fucking FBI's at my house.
Why you robbing that bank?
I'm not robbing the bank, Mama!
I was trying to come and cash my check
so I could give Aria money for school.
- Janiyah!
- For lunch so the kids won't tease her.
Janiyah.
What? That's all I was trying to do,
and it just got out of hand!
- Stop. Just stop.
- You know I have to get her medicine.
Oh my God. Janiyah.
It just got out of hand. I promise you!
Nicole is here. She'll tell you.
She's the branch manager.
- Tell my mama I didn't mean to do this!
- Janiyah.
- What?
- She died.
She had a seizure last night,
and we took her to the hospital.
She died, Janiyah.
I'm coming.
Hello?
- May I speak to Miss Wiltkinson?
- Um, I'm sorry. Who is this?
We are calling about your past due bills.
Please don't do this.
I can't leave my job.
It's my daughter's school.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I got here as soon as I could.
I'm sorry, but we didn't call you.
Are you okay?
My baby died.
I know.
They told me earlier.
I'm sorry.
She died last night.
Hands in the air!
Come out with hands in the air!
Janiyah.
Janiyah. Janiyah.
Let's go.
Janiyah.
You have to put your hand up.
Surrender.
Janiyah!
Put your hands up high.
Turn around, Janiyah.
Now back up to the sound of my voice.
I am right with you.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
It's nice to meet you.
Black hue
Born from a golden hour
Black love
The tie that grew the flower
Mood changes
The world shapes the child
That grew into a woman
Sunlight strong
Sacrifices she made
Moving in silence
Barely a thank you for all she gave
She smiles
Powering through her pain
Black woman
Yes, I love you
Black, light, dark-blended
Every kind of hue
Soft, strong, a fragile life
That keeps the world from ending, yeah
Your complexity still a mystery
I am you, yes, instantly a wildflower
Born a queen, yeah
God gave you a spiritual power
Often misunderstood
Hey, you are me Black woman
You did good
Hey, Black woman!
I love you
Yes, I love you
My, my, my, my, my, my, my, I love you
Yes, often underestimated
Always the greatest
Black woman
Yeah, yes, Black woman
Yeah, all right
Mm-mm-mm