-Come on.
That's good.
Good girl.
Happy birthday, Mama.
-Not now, Argos.
-Hey, bud, I can't.
I got a date.
Argos!
You're not gonna give up,
are you?
-You're getting spoiled today,
Socks.
-No wonder she likes you
better than me.
Is that good, babe?
-It's great.
-Is it?
-Mm-hmm.
-You're doing great, Jake.
-Smile. You're on camera.
-I didn't want to tell you.
I almost don't want to jinx it.
-Oh, what?
Well, now you have to tell me.
-You slept last night.
-You know I do that every night,
right?
-I mean, really, really slept.
-Well, that's good, then.
-I'm glad you're not a cop.
You're happier training canines.
I'm not scared anymore.
-You're not scared?
You never told me
you were scared.
Of what?
-For you.
Like you were wrestling
with something.
-Yeah, that's just how I relax.
-Maybe. It just seems that...
you're so still.
Like, whatever force
or whatever you were fighting,
it's like...
-Side of ribs.
Come back soon.
-Thank you. We will.
It was delicious.
-Thank you.
-What were you saying?
Go ahead.
-It's like you won.
-Oh! There's a fire.
-What?
-At home. We got to go.
Come on!
Aah!
You didn't turn the oven off?
-I never turned it on.
-What is it, girl?
Socks...
-Mia, call 911!
-International 911.
What's the emergency?
-Someone's attacking us!
Please!
-Okay. Are you in danger?
-Hello? Yes, we're being
attacked. Please.
-And what is your name?
-Mia Rosser.
Someone's trying
to kill my husband.
-I'll see if I can get someone
to help you.
Ma'am? Ma'am? What--
-Jake?
-Jake?!
-Argos...
He's not going anywhere.
Socks? Get medical in here.
-I need a medic.
-Hang on, girl.
I'm not gonna move you.
Show me where it hurts.
I'm gonna get help.
-He's in there. Jake!
-Jake!
-Cobb! Socks is down.
-Brown already called it in.
Medical is en route.
-I'm okay.
-Are you okay? Huh?
Yeah.
-You're okay.
He looks okay.
-Yeah.
-Mia, you stay here, okay?
-Yeah, okay.
-Argos...
-My eyes are your eyes to
watch and protect you and yours.
My ears are your ears
to hear and detect
evil minds in the dark.
My nose is your nose
to scent the invader.
And so you may live.
My life is also yours.
Detail. A-ten-hut!
Port arms.
Ready! Aim! Fire!
Argos.
Go home.
Hey.
All right, get up!
Let's go.
Up, up.
I couldn't stand it...
to see you there.
Among the dead.
You got what I want.
Your playing house
by the ocean...
...ain't gonna fix it.
You're a good girl.
I'll see you soon, Socks.
I'll see you soon.
You're my insurance company,
but you're not insuring me.
How does that work?
-Mr. Rosser, in your agreement,
section 4, paragraph 9--
-Hold on. Let-- Let me.
Let me finish. Okay?
-Okay.
-I mean, because it just doesn't
get simpler than this. Okay?
-You're frustrated,
and I understand.
-I paid for business insurance.
-That's not under dispute.
-My business, which you insured,
got destroyed.
-Yes, it did.
-I mean, I don't know
how else to say it.
-Mr. Rosser, you listed
the security cameras,
and in an incident of this...
No, the footage is gone.
It's gone.
There's no more footage, okay?
I talked to
the security company,
and they got hacked.
All right, I can put you
in touch with them if you--
Sir, without the footage,
your claim
is likely to be rejected.
-Hold on. Say that again.
I missed that.
-Sir, without the footage--
-No, but there's
a police report.
Yeah, I got an idea.
-Can we take
the temperature down?
-Let's see who can
hang up first, okay?
He's okay.
-Hey, I'm not worried.
I heard you're good with dogs.
-No, just talking to him.
Jake, I'm Detective Thorne.
Is this a bad time?
-No, actually, because it's
been tough getting answers.
-Uh-huh.
-You mind if I work him out
while we talk?
-Not if you don't.
-Argos...
You're okay. Find it.
-So, what's he gonna be?
Cadaver dog?
-No. Narcotics.
He's got a heck of a nose.
Watch this.
Thataboy. Good boy.
-I bet he could find
a corpse in a landfill, huh?
-I was, uh, hoping you would
shed some light on a few things.
-Argos...
-What's that? German for "kill"?
Attack.
-He's not attacking.
-Yeah, well, he just saw
his family ripped apart,
so he's a little edgy.
-Uh-huh.
-You're not
from robbery/homicide, are you?
-Hey,
you should be the detective.
Even if you smoke the bad guys,
it's still murder.
-You know what?
You're right. Now is a bad time.
LAPD, man.
Doing what they do best.
Investigating me.
For what?
Because someone tried
to hurt your mom,
and I hurt him back?
Was it legal?
No. It's not a question
of legality.
It's a question of morality.
Eh, what do you care?
Even if I can explain to you
what a grand jury is...
...even if I could describe
to you what happens to a cop
who gets put away,
or what debt is, bankruptcy,
marriage, blah, blah, blah...
...it wouldn't matter.
You know why?
Because you're free.
Actually, you probably
understand better than I do.
I've seen how you get
when you're in a cage.
If by some miracle,
I can pay the mortgage,
the insurance does come through,
and these freaks stop
trying to kill me,
pretty good chance I'll go to
prison for the rest of my life.
We need to talk, Detective.
Make an appointment, Mr. Rosser.
-No.
-You can't be here.
-Yet here I am,
still in the system.
Why'd they put you on this?
You're a transfer.
You don't know me.
-I do know
that you're trespassing
and I could have you arrested.
-You could, but you won't.
-What did you do?
-Who was he?
-I asked first.
-Technically, I did,
but I'm not five years old.
Why are you scared?
-I heard about you.
-Yeah?
-We pissed off the same people.
Maybe you can help.
His name was Adolfo Reyes.
-Okay, that narrows it down
a little bit.
-He's not cartel.
He's not illegal.
He's a Mexican citizen
who lived there.
-So, how'd he wind up
in my house?
-There she is.
Did you eat?
- Late for an autopsy.
-You skipped breakfast.
-Am I grounded?
-You're going through a lot.
I know.
Won't help to starve yourself.
I'll drop off some tacos.
-Thanks. I'll work up
an appetite, I'm sure.
-Your mom doing any better?
-We're hoping.
-Some of the guys chipped in.
Send her love. Okay?
-That's sweet.
Really. Thank you.
Reyes was a journalist.
Not exactly a fan
of the cartels.
-What else?
-Retired cop,
former amateur boxer.
He and his family
were reported missing two days
before he broke into your home.
Where are you parked?
-What, no tacos?
-Tomorrow.
Text you the address.
Now, where did you park?
Tomorrow...
park further away.
-It's June, and you've been
playin' with skunks all day.
Faces, faces, oh, faces.
Yeah! Scrape.
Scrape it off. Right off.
You know what, Totec's
an asshole, and I'm prophesying.
Let a fake man.
I'm talking,
that faggot's coming here.
You think you in charge here,
asshole?
All this shit's pretend.
You like an animal all dressed
up in drag like a bitch-boy.
Try, try running away. Whatever.
Stop bullshitting. Your bitch?
She deserve more.
Your head's fucked, butt fuck.
You think she would ever
want you?
You gonna play Russian Roulette.
Beekman going up in smoke,
and you going down.
-All right, man,
take care of yourself.
-I'm an American.
-This place,
we don't need it.
-Hey.
-It's expensive.
-Hey, I'm gonna take care of it.
Argos is gonna fetch a pretty
penny...
...when he's, you know, ready.
-Jake, I want to help.
-No.
-I can go back to nursing.
-I'm fine with it.
-No.
-Part time.
Just until
the insurance comes through.
-Well, it might not.
Look, you wanted to stay home.
I made you a promise.
I'm gonna keep it.
-Yeah, well,
I made you a promise, too.
For richer or poorer.
-Yeah, well,
this is the poor part.
How am I sleeping lately?
-Like a baby.
-Yeah.
Babies crap themselves.
-I'm glad it's you.
-I volunteered for this.
I'm the only one I trust.
-Good.
'Cause I barely trust you.
-I didn't mean it
that way, man.
Everyone
in the department's solid.
Just got tired of Skid Row,
you know,
playing hopscotch
with dirty needles.
-Yeah, well,
Mia's a nurse now.
She can get you
some dirty needles.
-Scatter them on the lawn.
Make me feel right at home.
-All right, Cobb.
I appreciate this.
-I got you, brother.
-No. You know,
he -- he stayed sober.
He kept that promise.
I know, but...
-Argos.
-There's this evil voice
in my head telling me
that one day he'll just snap,
that I'll see him on the news.
But I know -- I know
that's not real.
It's just my fear talking.
You know, he's --
he's trying so hard to be
a good husband and a father,
and I'm trying to trust him.
But it's so exhausting.
Yeah, I know.
Makes me want to drink.
It's just like... Yeah.
It's just --
It's like I'm watching that guy
who's always pushing
a rock uphill.
I'm blanking on
the name now, but...
-Then she goes on to say she
knows I'm doing my best, and...
...it's not my fault,
so she shouldn't feel resentful,
but she does.
She has so much resentment
that it overpowers all of that.
And she still does love me.
I'm not saying she
doesn't love me,
but she thinks that if
I knew that she knew
how wounded I really was,
you know, it might, you know,
create this dynamic between us
where she thinks that
I think she has to rescue me.
So she makes this assumption
that I'm some wounded dog,
that I can't take care of my --
No offense, bud.
So she has to pretend
all the time,
which is really just
a euphemism for lying.
You know that she made up that
story about me sleeping better?
She feels like she has
to protect my image of myself
as a protector, as a provider.
So she feels
like she's doing for me
what I think I'm doing for her.
Just -- It's crazy. It's nuts.
It's -- It's --
Well, it's marriage.
It's a kidnapping, basically.
The ransom was me.
-Deliver Jake Rosser,
dead or alive.
Your family goes free.
Whatever you did to fuck
with their business in LA,
they're not happy about it.
-Why not just blow himself
up the second he came in?
-Forensics hasn't determined
what kind of bomb was used.
I think it might have
been remotely detonated.
Maybe a timer.
Reyes might have thought
they'd disarm it,
if he got you
and got away in time.
-Yeah, well,
cartels aren't exactly known
for keeping their promises.
-Depends on the promise.
-Anywhere you want, my friend.
-I'm still standing.
-Consider yourself lucky.
Whoever runs the Santa Muerte
cartel is a demon.
I wouldn't recommend
watching the rest.
That was released yesterday.
His family.
The cartel put their bodies --
what was left of them --
on display in the middle
of town.
They found his brother's
body nearby, but not his head.
Likely, it'll turn up
elsewhere on a stake,
in a gift box shipped
to the mayor.
Who knows?
-Santa Muerte.
Saint Death.
-Not exactly
sanctioned by the church.
-No. This Reyes must have
been quite a reporter.
-He was a troublemaker.
-Yeah, I know the feeling.
-There's no running
from this, Jake.
Reyes had a whistle-blower at
a major pharmaceutical company.
He never named the company
in his articles.
And he never named
the whistle-blower.
-I'm sure he sang like a bird
when they got his family.
-He didn't need to.
The day the article ran,
Barry Taft,
VP of Sales at Davro
Pharmaceuticals died
"by suicide,"
in quotation marks.
-In real life?
-Downtown. Happened yesterday.
-What was he blowing
the whistle on?
-Some connection between
the painkillers
produced by Davro,
the Chinese government,
and the Santa Muerte cartel.
Some of his company's
product produced in China
is being siphoned off
and sold directly
as a street drug in the US.
They're here, Jake.
-I'm ready.
-I'm not.
My mom.
I'm all she has.
They said they'll kill her.
- You can shoot it.
-Hey, that's not necessary.
Argos...
-I'm sorry, Jake.
-We do keep
our promises, Jake.
And I'm about
to make another one.
-Why don't you
just tell me what you want?
I'll tell you
to go fuck yourself,
and then you can shoot me.
-I'm not going to shoot you.
You're going to shoot yourself.
-Yeah. Well, I'm gonna
have to borrow a gun.
Your boy took mine.
-I like the way you think.
-Jake, please!
They're gonna kill us! Please!
-Sit!
Do what I say or they die.
It's pointing the wrong way.
Plomo.
-Lead.
-Your Spanish is very good.
-Gracias.
-We know.
We've been listening.
At home, in your car,
with your therapist.
Suicidal thoughts, Jake.
PTSD.
-Are we having a session now?
-Of sorts.
One click, your son lives.
Two, your wife goes free.
Three clicks, you get to save
your friend over here.
Or four...
we even let your dog go.
-And if I get five?
-Try again.
-You're a gambler, Cutler.
What are my odds?
- Jake.
- Congratulation--
-One more, Cutler,
and you're free.
Salud.
Mm.
It's been a while.
-It's like nothing.
It's like he's in a hur--
- Yeah!
-I was going to say 50/50.
-But you're stupid.
And your math sucks.
-Get her out of here.
Get my truck ready.
Get her out!
-Jake...
-Get out of here.
Vamos.
-Back to the show.
- I'll dream big.
-Hello? You got a customer
who wants takeout.
-Expecting someone?
- Hello?
I'm here for some takeout.
-She'll go away.
-I'm not going away.
I can hear you, asshole.
This is offensive.
-We're closed.
-Your sign says open, dickhead!
-We're closed! We're closed!
The door is closed!
That's why no one is answering.
We're closed!
-You are answering.
-Listen to him!
We're closed!
-Good boy.
-I take back that "good boy."
-Yo, Jake.
-They got Mia.
-Hold on. Wait, wait.
-Listen to me.
I just got jumped.
-Hold on.
-Don't you hear me?
They said they're
going to kill her.
-Jake, hold on.
-Hey! Come on!
Argos, get up!
Come on, man, I heard her.
-All good?
Jake, she's right here.
-What?
-I'm looking at her.
-Show me.
-You looking?
-That's them right now?
-Yes, sir.
-I'm on my way.
Argos, yo, sit down.
-Come on.
-You've reached
Detective Cutler.
Please leave a message.
-Where are you, Cutler?
-You know where you are?
-Who am I talking to?
-That truck belongs to me.
-Yeah?
Feel free to file
a police report.
You see your friend?
-Who's that?
-She's hanging
from the mirror.
You can't miss her.
-Not my friend.
-She's about to be.
You've been courting her
for a long time.
-Argos!
-Police.
On the ground.
Hands up.
-Argos...
-Control your animal.
-We're complying. Argos.
-I will fucking kill this thing.
-Argos...
-I said, on the ground!
Hey, man. Watch the hand.
Argos.
No.
-Talked to personnel.
Your story checks out.
-Good. Where's my dog?
-Animal control
till we figure this out.
-Animal control?
Am I being detained?
-You blew up a fucking car.
-I didn't blow it up.
-Oh, it blew itself up, huh?
-Yeah, it kind of did.
-Argos!
-Hey. Easy, man.
-Come on.
-Hey, hang on a second.
-Ohh!
-Come on. In you go.
Let's go.
-Where are you taking him?
Babe.
You're not wrong
for asking the question.
-I'm not sure
you understood my question.
-Well, then help me.
-I could have asked it
more clearly.
-You don't have to protect me.
-I know.
-Just tell me the truth.
I can take it.
-Jake.
-I deserve it.
-Don't accuse me of lying.
-I'm saying you're doing
what I always do.
You're running from conflict.
-I'm the one
who started this fight.
-We're not fighting.
-You know what I mean.
-This is not the conflict.
-Then what is the conflict?
-This is a distraction
from the actual question
that you wanted to ask me.
From what you need to know,
from what you had to know
before you married me.
-I just want this to work.
-Well, it won't work
if I'm not ready.
-Jake.
-That's it, isn't it?
-Jake!
-Jake?
-Ohh.
-I'm Liz. I'm a nurse here.
-What day is it?
-Can you tell me?
-You've been out
about two hours.
-How about something to drink?
-The pain medication
can make you thirsty.
I'll get you some water.
-Thank you.
-Be right back.
Have you seen the officer
that brought my patient in?
-He's in the break room.
-Thanks.
-Officer Bateman.
He's awake.
-Coherent?
-He's fine. Concussion, maybe.
-Can he be discharged
right away?
-Whenever the doctor
signs off.
About an hour,
I'm guessing.
- You got
to be kidding.
-Should probably go talk to him.
-What did he do?
-He's a terrorist.
He tried to set off a car bomb.
-It didn't go off?
-Oh, it went off.
Just not where it
was supposed to.
-Where?
-Where was it supposed to?
Or where did it go off?
-Probably a synagogue
or a KFC.
We're pretty sure he's
a White supremacist.
Let's keep moving.
All right?
Here?
-Thank you.
-Nurse.
You want to give us a minute?
Speak any Spanish, Jake?
-A little.
-Like you can order food or...
-Yeah. Pretty much.
-Yo quiero Taco Bell,
and that's about it, huh?
-You see my lawyer here?
-Jake. Jake --
-You're wasting your time.
-It's okay. You can just lie
there, hear me out.
Besides, we're way past
all that now.
Plata o plomo.
How about that one?
"Silver or lead."
That's what that means.
What does that mean for you?
What that means is,
when a cartel rolls into town,
they talk to people -- they talk
to farmers, they talk to cops.
Nice salt-of-the-earth
type folks.
These folks, they get a choice.
Either you're in on the take,
which is the silver.
Or...
I can see you're guessing
what the lead part means.
-Yeah.
Our line of work,
we don't make a lot of money.
You know that.
I know about you
and your mortgage,
your business insurance.
Well, they came to talk to me.
See, they need people
that don't look like
they loiter outside of
the Home Depot,
if you know what I mean.
They're moving north.
So they gave me a choice.
Now I'm gonna give you a choice.
Drink this...
...you go to sleep...
and never wake up, ever.
Or you watch your wife and kid
burnt alive on the Internet.
-Well...
I ain't dirty like you.
Come on.
I'm really sorry.
Liz, I just need you
to calm down.
Hey, can you do that for me?
I'm not here to hurt you.
I'm not a criminal, okay?
Not if you're hearing me.
Yeah?
Okay. Good, good. Listen.
That cop, he tried to kill me.
The water you placed by my bed,
he put something in it.
Tranq or fentanyl.
I don't know, you can test it.
They're trying to kill me
and my family.
Now, I gotta go.
I gotta get back to them, okay?
Listen, I need your help,
because I'm about to let you go.
-I appreciate everything
you did for me.
And I promise, if you scream,
I'm gonna beat the crap
out of you, okay?
You, Nurse.
Come here, Nurse.
Shut the fuck up.
-Just get the fuck over here.
Shh!
-Are you okay?
Oh, my God!
Are you okay?
Your face.
-I'm good. I'm fine.
-He's gone.
-Who's gone?
-The White supremacist.
-Okay.
Thank you for letting me know.
Where did he go?
-Are you sure you're okay?
-I'm fine. I'm fine.
This is -- I'm good.
Did you see where he went?
-Yes.
-Yeah?
-Where did he go?!
-Aah!
-Into the stairwell.
-The stairwell?
That stairwell there?
-Yes, yes.
-Okay. Yeah. Can I ask you
another question, one more?
-Are you gonna call it in?
-Yeah. Yeah.
How long before someone
comes through this door?
Well, I'd ha-- I'd have
to tell the doctor.
I'd have to call the doctor.
-But if you didn't,
it would be a while.
Good, good.
Good. You should sit down.
Yeah. Okay.
All right? Sit down, yeah.
You're good. It's fine.
Here, have some water.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
Okay. You sit tight.
You sit tight.
-Oh!
-Yeah, I fucked up.
-How is it that you fucked up?
-He's not dead. He got away.
-That's not good, Mr. Beekman.
-I'll find him.
-If he is arrested...
-He won't be.
-You understand, Mr. Beekman,
how we do things.
-Yes, I do.
-Then you understand that your
work from this point forward
is to ensure
the safety of your family.
-Come on, honey, pick up.
-Hello?
-Honey, it's -- Yeah.
-Honey?
-What's this number
you're calling from?
-Listen, I don't have time
to explain, all right?
You just need to listen
to me, okay?
-What -- What's this about?
-Don't say my name.
Just pretend like
you're talking to your mom.
This is life or death.
Please. You got to trust me.
-Okay, Mom. How's Dad?
-Good. Just like that.
Yeah. Now, uh,
I need you to go into the den.
-Okay, Mom, is --
is there something
you wanted me to check on?
-Yeah.
The, uh -- the Restoration
console near the TV.
-Mm. Mm-hmm. I can bring
some chicken salad.
-Pull out the bottom drawer.
You got it out?
-Yeah. The grapes are seedless.
-You see that nail there?
It's just not a nail.
Pull on it.
Yeah. There's a box in there.
Inside there are passports,
birth certificates for you
and the kids.
There's 60,000 in cash.
There's car keys
and a map to find the car.
Use the phone that's in there.
Do not use an Uber.
All right?
Now, um...
I'd love to say that
I'll see you soon, baby,
but I'm not gonna make it.
-What do you mean?
What are you saying?
Answer me!
-But you, uh...
-You run away.
-What?
What is happening here?!
You live.
And you be happy.
And you forget about me.
-Oh, God! Please, no!
-You get as far away
from here as you can.
-Are you serious?
-And you try...
and forgive me.
-Oh, my God.
-All right?
-Please, please don't do this.
-Because you'll, uh...
Yeah. It's always been you.
You'll be the last thing
that I think about.
-No, no, just come home!
Are you -- Are you
gonna be home?
-Come on.
-Don't speak.
I'm gonna speak,
and you're gonna act,
and you don't hang up.
-Are you sure it's that one?
-That's what they said.
-He's got a collar
and an address.
-I just spoke to the cop.
The cop said euthanize it.
-We've never done this before.
-You've never done this before.
Now, you need to ask yourself
why you are where you are
and I am where I am.
If you put a modicum
of initiative in,
your life would have turned out
very differently.
There's still time.
But you need to stop
being such a fucking incel.
Be somebody.
-No!
- Hey! What the hell?
-We have breaking news now.
Officials have released
the name Jake Rosser
as the suspect
of the stolen truck,
a former police officer
in LAPD's K-9 division.
According to his colleagues,
Rosser behavior was
often erratic and violent.
He was disciplined
for assaulting
a Hispanic ambulance driver
shortly before leaving
the department.
It's becoming clear
from today's events
that Rosser resented
not only his fellow officers,
but the diverse communities
he was sworn to protect.
We've been informed that Rosser
is currently in police custody
at an undisclosed hospital
in Los Angeles.
Before he was apprehended,
his tragic rampage has left
several restaurant workers dead
in what seems to be an act
of targeted racial hatred.
Forensic psychiatrist
Dr. Yan Sanyay
has been analyzing
the behavior of the suspect
over the past few hours.
-Of course, as I'm speaking,
he's not my patient.
I haven't examined the suspect,
but there were reports
of an Afghani child
in an incident in 2005,
a little boy named Abdul
whose death was caused
by the suspect.
According to an associate
of mine,
Dr. T. Morang,
who's a military psychiatrist,
the suspect felt at the time
that he didn't deserve human
friends after this incident.
So he transferred
his affections onto dogs.
-Hey.
-Further investigations reveal
that the suspect
got one dog killed
while on duty in Afghanistan
and, uh...
-Hey, man.
I'm lost.
I was coming.
Then boom.
-...and got
the three-legged dog.
-What you doing wearing my shit?
-Am I?
Uh...I thought this was mine.
-You lying.
-No, I'm just confused.
My head...
-Who are you?
-...veteran suffers
from severe PTSD
and exhibits traits of extreme
narcissism and psychopathy,
showing no remorse...
-You.
No.
You that racist bomber.
-No, that's not me.
-Police! Help!
Help!
-Depression is a journey.
I'd made some progress
on my antidepressant,
had some daily wins
at reducing my symptoms,
but I was still masking
my depression.
So I talked to my doctor.
-Alright.
Nice and easy.
It's over.
-Hey, I'm complying.
-I got the suspect outside,
Jake Rosser.
-Copy that.
Suspect in custody.
-Wait. What are you doing?
Stop resisting.
-Whoa, whoa.
You don't wanna do that, man.
-Officer needs assistance.
-No, you don't want to do that.
-He's going for my gun.
-No. Hey.
-Your prints are all over it,
wherever it is.
-Hey, man, you're on camera.
-You think I'm dumb enough
to take my eyes off of you?
-Nah.
-You're way too smart for that.
I want a copy of this tape.
-Connecting to OnStar.
-Welcome to OnStar, Mr. Raskin.
How can I help you?
-Yeah. Hi.
Uh, how you doing tonight?
-I'm doing fine, thank you.
How are you, sir?
-I'm good, I'm good.
Thank you.
Uh, actually,
this isn't Mr. Raskin.
It's, uh, Officer, um, Cobb
with the LAPD,
and, uh, we recovered
this vehicle stolen
and, uh, require assistance.
-No problem. I can report
the vehicle stolen.
-Actually, it's already been
reported, ma'am. Thank you.
We're just, uh, currently
impounding the vehicle,
and, uh, gonna
need you to start the engine.
-No problem. I'm just gonna
need your badge number,
Officer.
-My what?
-I'm just gonna need
your badge number.
-Uh...
It's, uh, Bravo niner five...
uh, six -- uh, 6-8-2.
6-8-2?
-I'm looking that up now.
-Thank you very much.
-Okay, thank you, Officer Cobb,
for that.
Processing your request.
-Thank you.
Ma'am, I'm gonna
need you to start the engine
as soon as you can so I can
transfer this car to impound.
-Copy that.
Stand by, sir.
-Hey, we got a report
of shots fired, man.
What's going on?
-Yo, man, we got a 10-71
at this location, man.
What's up?
-Yo, where's the shooter at?
-Oh, yeah, 42.
-You good?
-I'm fine.
-It's negative
on the shooter, man, negative.
-No one can see you do
what is necessary.
You must serve me in secret.
-Just tell me what the fuck
to do.
-Heel, little doggy.
Be a good boy.
I left a treat
in the trunk of your car.
Bring me my rabbit,
or I will put your bitch down,
along with her litter.
This is your last hunting trip.
-I married you.
-I know.
-So what more do you want?
-I want you to know
that I'm ready.
-I do know that.
-You're not wrong
asking the question.
-Honestly, Jake, it wasn't --
-Just love me enough
to trust me.
You should feel safe
coming to me about anything.
-I do.
-You know what
I've been through.
-A lot of it, yeah.
-Yeah, but not all of it.
You're right. I mean,
I don't talk about the war.
You want me to?
-No.
But you can tell me anything.
I'm right here.
-You've seen me falling apart.
You need to know
I can keep a family together.
You don't want to be 10 years in
with a guy you have to babysit.
-No.
No, I don't.
-Come on.
Oh, God.
What did I do?
Seriously, what did I do?
Come on, God.
I didn't check out.
I stuck around.
I did what you wanted me to do.
And, yes,
you gave me this beautiful life
and a beautiful family.
And now what?
You want to take it all away?
Come on, God,
I thought we had a deal.
Yeah, I'm not exactly
a model citizen, okay?
I have issues.
I'm a bum, alright?
Look, here's the new deal.
I'm sorry, okay? I'll repent.
I'll turn myself in.
I'll do whatever
you want me to do.
Just give me a sign.
Talk to me, something.
Come on, God, don't punish them.
Punish me.
I'll pay.
You gave me all this hope.
For the first time in my life,
I've had hope.
And now what?
Why?
Come on, please, just don't --
don't take away my family.
-You can't heal
in the place you get hurt.
One of the most difficult
experiences in life
is that unless you --
-Hey, man, you got duct tape?
-The base hit.
-What, man?
-Never mind.
I got it.
-Is that a fair thing to say?
-No, no, individually,
I love them.
Every person I meet
I sort of like,
and I'm not trying
to be corny here,
but I see the universe in them.
You can see...
-Ooh!
Sweet chili.
-You want to be on a skewer
rotisserie style?
-You know a good way to prepare
for a new year?
-As far as hitting a wall,
I don't know.
I'd say that...
-Man, I'm sorry about this.
-About what?
Fuck.
-Hands up. Keep your hands up.
Don't move.
-I'm not.
-Listen, man,
I don't want to do this.
-Do what?
-Just listen to me.
-Please,
just take whatever, man.
-I'm not here to rob the store.
-What?
-Just listen to me.
-Please, just take whatever --
-Doug.
-...ask for advice from.
Shouldn't worry about criticism
from someone
that you would
never ask advice from.
-What?
-Just turn on a gas pump
for me.
Look, Doug, I got a wife
and a kid, alright?
We're a little bit
on the rocks right now.
It's complicated.
They're in danger.
I need to protect them, okay?
-Most of the time
it's people...
-Yeah, man.
-You shouldn't worry
about criticism...
-Just turn on the gas.
-I-I gotta put my hand down.
-Fine. Go ahead.
-It hit me when I was
like 38 years old.
It was, like, amazing.
Wish I'd heard that
when I was 15.
-That's it.
-Okay.
Look, I'm not gonna hurt you.
I need to tape your hands
behind your back.
-Please don't
sexually assault me.
-No one's getting
sexually assaulted, okay?
-I'm already struggling
with my mental health.
Okay?
Officers, he's got a gun!
-I know this may be a bad time
to ask you to trust me, Doug,
but the man outside --
Doug, no!
-He's raping me.
Shoot him.
-Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God!
Please, please don't do this.
-My eyes are the eyes of God
but sharper.
God does nothing.
Either he can't or he won't.
But I'm a doer.
We know she ran, your wife.
But we will not follow, as long
as you stay and do your duty.
Now you will repeat what I say.
Say, "Jake, it's not me
talking anymore."
-Jake.
It's not me talking anymore.
-"It is God who speaks
through me."
-It's God who speaks
through me.
You talked to me twice today.
First time in my car.
The second in Mr. Raskin's.
-"You thought no one heard you
when you prayed, Jake.
But I was listening."
-You thought no one heard you
when you prayed, Jake,
but I was listening.
-You didn't sound like the God
I was praying to.
-"I am the only God
who heard you."
-I am the only God
that heard you.
Begging...
for me to take you.
-"To spare your family."
-For me to spare your family.
-"Now, you will lower
your weapon."
-Now, you will lower
your weapon.
-No, no, you, Mr. Beekman,
will lower your weapon.
And you will say, "I am not
merciful, but I am powerful."
-I am not merciful.
But I am powerful.
I've told my little dog to heel.
-And now I'm gonna
put him to sleep.
-And now --
And now I'm gonna
put him to sleep.
-Now you will withdraw the can
of gasoline from your trunk.
Now, Mr. Beekman,
you will soak yourself.
-I'm sorry.
Could you repeat that last --
-You will soak yourself.
-You --
You want me --
-And if you flinch
and if you falter,
your wife
will suffer twice the agony.
You will tell him...
..."Behold the answer
to your prayers."
-Behold the answer
to your prayers.
I offered you a painless death,
and you refused.
Still, if you pay now...
-If you follow in
my servant's footsteps...
-If you follow...
in my servant's footsteps...
-...your family will be spared.
- Keep her here.
-In the dark night
of your despair...
-...I am providing a torch...
-...I'm providing a torch...
-...lighting the way
to absolution.
-Now, Mr. Beekman,
you will light the way.
Argos!
-Argos, off!
Argos.
-Argos. Argos.
-I'm doing it.
I'm doing it.
Argos, off, off!
-Argos, here, here!
Come here.
Good boy.
-You're a good boy.
Yeah.
-Come on, let's save Cutler.
I need water, Jake.
-Alright.
Let's get you in this chair.
-Let me see.
Gonna just stand there
and let him shoot you?
-Hey, take your belt off.
-Why, you need a tourniquet?
-I heard him say
you got a tracker.
-Huh?
-Yeah.
-Son of a bitch.
- I do need a tourniquet, though.
-Wait!
-All units, be advised,
we've got a 10-93...
-I'm not gonna make it.
-We're making it.
-I don't deserve to.
-Neither do I.
Dispatch.
-Go ahead.
-We're going to need
the location of the nearest EMS.
-Ambulance located,
300 block...
-George H.W. Bush was
in Dallas when JFK was shot.
Yeah, working undercover
with the CIA.
So Reagan was against
all the globalist stuff
when he was running.
-Hey, yo, I'm eating, man.
-You always do this.
-No, it just -- all of this
gives me anxiety, alright?
Gives me indigestion.
-Then Reagan selects Bush
as his vice president,
and then he gets shot
by John Hinckley.
Hinckleys and the Bushes
were like BFFs
that are having dinner
that week.
-Yep. I'm having dinner now.
Mm.
-Mm.
-So how does
this secret government
all work for the same
communist conspiracy
and it's not even on the news?
-It's a globalist takeover,
right?
They're instituting
a new kind of world government.
Mainstream media is part
of the propaganda arm.
-Ohh.
-Yeah.
I sent you sources.
-Okay.
-What, y-you didn't read them?
-Well, you know, you sent
some right-wing bullshit, right?
And then, yeah, I'll get to it.
-It's -- It's not right-wing.
It's from these people
themselves.
It's the World Economic Forum.
"You'll own nothing
and be happy."
I mean, that's what they say.
It's in their own literature.
-Swear to God, man.
-Go ahead and laugh.
You won't be laughing when your
kids are in a fucking FEMA camp.
-You know what?
That's when I will be laughing.
'Cause that means
you would be right.
-Yeah.
This whole time.
-Start the car, dude.
We're dead.
We're not supposed to
have animals in here.
-Let's focus on her
till we get there.
-And then you'll...let us go.
-The second we get to the
hospital, I turn myself in.
-There's a hospital
two miles away.
-Not that hospital.
Just go where I tell you.
-What about Mia and John?
-We'll get them on the way.
-Hey.
I'm a detective.
-Well, I'm not gonna lie.
This is some strange shit,
Detective.
Anyway, you're stable.
How's your pain?
-Better.
-Come on, you got this.
That's right.
Climb the mountain.
You're doing good, kid.
Hey, buddy, you fell down.
That's okay.
You fell down.
If you didn't struggle,
if you quit
before we got up here,
you wouldn't be able
to see all this.
See?
What do you say, John?
See, I told you
it'd be worth it.
Look how beautiful.
-Hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
It's okay, buddy.
I might have hurt his leg.
We got to go.
-I know.
-Where are my keys at?
- I don't know. Here.
-Don't look at me like that.
-I'm sorry. I --
-Well, it kills me, too.
-I know, I know.
I'm sorry.
-I was scared.
-Let's go.
-Rosser, whose violent behavior
was evident
during his time
at the department,
is still at large and is
now suspected in the kidnapping
and possible murder of
LAPD detective Idalia Cutler.
With that, I'm happy to take
any questions you might have.
-You know...
murder's not entirely
off the table.
-You got to kidnap me first.
-Why would they lie?
-Dude, I think you just
got red-pilled.
-Alright.
Gonna drop you guys off.
You report the ambulance stolen.
Grand theft auto
is the least of my worries.
-Nope. Not happening.
I'm seeing this one through.
-Hey, can I use your phone?
Thank you.
- Los Angeles police officer
who was fired from his job
is suspected
of going on a shooting spree.
-Who is this?
-Hey, Mia, it's me.
-Jake. Thank God.
-You okay?
-Where are you?
-Where's John?
Mia?
-It's not safe here.
-Mia, where's our son?
Where is he?
-He's at my mother's.
-Okay, okay.
-What's going on?
-I was ambushed.
-Ambushed?
-The police, some of them
are with the cartel.
-Jake.
-They threatened you and John.
They had your voice.
-You're not making any sense.
-Mia, please, just listen to me.
-I love you.
-They played me your voice.
It was you.
You were screaming...
-What?
-...and begging me
to kill myself
because they had you
and the baby.
-Jake, stop, okay?
Just stop.
-What, you don't believe me?
-Don't say that.
-What, you think
I'm making this up?
-It's on the news, Jake.
What am I supposed to say?
-Ask Cobb. He knows.
-Cutler's with me.
She knows, too.
Cobb didn't tell you?
-No. He -- He just waved at me.
-Alright, go outside right now.
I want you to talk to him.
I'm not crazy, Mia.
-I hate that I said that.
-Mia, I know.
I'm sorry, too.
-Jake, we need help.
-I know, I know.
-Professional help.
Therapy.
-We'll get it.
I promise.
-Jake.
-No, I know.
I need it, too.
I'm grateful you asked.
-Good evening, Diana.
Tonight, police officers
across the...
-Hey, I love you, okay?
-I love you.
-Go get Cobb.
He'll keep you safe
till I get there.
Hey, Mia.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Jake!
Jake.
It's Cobb, Jake.
Jake, he's dead.
-Mia, listen to me.
I want you to run, okay?
Just go. Go! Run!
-Okay, okay.
-I'm not hanging up.
Just tell me where you are,
okay, and we'll find you.
-What's going on?
-Cobb's dead.
They're going after Mia.
-Get her, Jake.
-Then we'll take you
to the hospital.
-Just tell me where to go, man.
-Take this exit.
-I think I can hear you.
-That's us.
-How far?
-Two minutes, maybe less.
-Please. Please.
-Are you still in Mariposa?
-Um...I think I'm on Fourth.
-Alright, stay there.
We're on Fourth.
Keep heading east, 30 seconds.
- Jake!
Jake. I can't hear you.
-That's her right there.
You see us, Mia?
Mia!
-Jake, my phone's beeping.
I can't hear you.
-What beeping?
I don't hear any beeping.
Stop the ambulance.
-What?
-It's a trap.
Where's my gun?
Argos.
Hey, let me look at you.
Huh?
Cutler, you okay?
Jake.
My mom, take care of her.
Her name's Marie.
-Cutler. No.
-Argos, come here.
Listen to me.
I need you to get in the fight,
Argos.
I didn't raise a coward.
I need you to protect
our family.
Argos...
Hey!
I raised a warrior.
Come on.
I'll be right behind you.
Argos, come on.
- Argos, here.
Here. Come on.
Good boy.
- Jake.
-Mia!
Come on.
-Not yet.
-Mia, over the wall.
Argos, up.
-There's a loud noise
in the street.
I don't know what's going on,
alright?
Send someone as soon as you can.
There's some trespassers
right now, ma'am.
They're coming onto my property.
-What is your address?
Are you in danger, sir?
-Uh...
-Percy, what on earth
was that noise?
-Ahhh.
-Oh, my --
Percy!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
-Argos, up.
Come on, through the window.
Go through.
-Ah.
-Get behind the couch.
Argos.
-When I say,
you get in the bathtub.
You stay low, okay?
-Jake, please don't leave me.
-Ready? Go.
-Okay.
Hey. I need you more
than you needed me anyway.
Hey, you went though it, you
made it back to me on your own.
You're solid, alright?
Now, Argos.
-Come here, come here.
The only ones for me
are the mad ones.
Mad to live.
Mad to talk.
Mad to be saved.
-We have to go, ma'am.
-I can't.
-Ma'am, there's no time.
We have to go now.
-I'm not leaving my husband.
-Desirous of everything
at the same time.
Those who never yawn
or say a commonplace thing
but burn, burn, burn like
fabulous yellow Roman candles
exploding like spiders
across the stars.
And in the middle you see
a blue center light pop,
and everybody goes...
..."Awww!"
I was in awe of living with
such abandon, such passion.
But then I read more
and I thought clearer
and I got older and I --
and I wasn't hypnotized
by the music of the words,
but I was actually
understanding what they meant.
-And I met people
who burned, burned, burned
like fabulous
yellow Roman candles.
I spent time with them.
And you know what?
-Argos.
-They were assholes.
Selfish, impatient, decadent.
-Argos.
-If everyone was like that,
civilization would collapse.
I mean, look at what happened
to Kerouac.
So you don't want that.
But best case,
even how I grew up --
two parents, unconditional
love, all needs met --
let's say you give that
to someone.
No abuse.
Nothing that you can call trauma
unless you're lying about it
for attention.
Let's say you do an A-plus job.
The best you're going to get
for that kid
who is your whole life...
...is to watch that spark
slowly fade away
and realize that spark's
just narcissism.
-And when they get old,
if they're lucky,
they get to watch the ember
in their own kid burn to ashes.
-Perfect.
Jake, please.
-No, he's right.
-That's what I'm fighting for.
What?
I mean, actually, it's not
what I'm fighting for.
That's without trauma,
without being on the run.
Being hunted.
-Are you asking me
to go on the run with you?
-I'm asking you, don't run away.
-I can't.
-Yeah.
You're trapped.
-I'd rather be trapped
with you than anybody.
-I really need you.
-Time's up, Rosser.
-Say bye to Daddy.
Say bye.
- Pop D12.
-Man, they gonna fuck you up
in here.
Gettin' fucked tonight, man.
Once they find out,
you're getting fucked!
You're done!
-Come back here, motherfucker!