London's criminal
underworld is controlled
by two of the worst gangsters
you could ever hope to avoid.
Mrs Vine may look like
the prim and proper sort,
but she rules her empire
with an iron fist.
Wake the boys up.
I'm all over it, ma'am.
And Frasier Mahoney,
well, he looks like what he is.
A right horrible bastard.
Mate, you say something
like that in my earshot
and I'll cut your fucking tongue
out and shove it up your arse.
To make matters worse,
there's a new lot causing havoc.
The Mushka street gang
are growing in numbers
and they don't fuck around.
Even the law won't go near
the Mushka estate
without serious backup.
- Please don't kill me.
- Fucking die, pig!
The police tried to
enforce the first curfew in the
history of London,
but that didn't
go down too well.
Tensions have
reached boiling point
and East London's criminal
underworld is on the brink of an
all-out war.
And I'm about to find myself
right in the middle of it.
Edward, all I need
you to do is what?
Stay put, watch the
car, keep it running.
You can trust me,
all right? I promise.
No, I know.
- Three...
- Two...
This
is Vine's Jewels.
Do you speak English?
Fucking jackpot!
Ooh!
Expecting somebody?
Must be this Russian lady
that's got an appointment
to buy a ring.
It's half an hour early, though.
She on her own?
Yeah.
Buzz her in.
You can come in.
Open... the... door.
- For crying out loud!
- Can't she just push the door?
- Ready?
- Go.
Pow, pow, pow!
Fucker.
Fucking hell! Look
at the size of this bad boy.
Ba, ba! Fuck. Shit. Fuck.
Just speak English
because I ain't got a clue.
Drop the fucking gun.
- Two seconds.
- What?
Huh?
- Everybody down on the floor!
- I need backup... now!
- You can't park here, mate. -
Just give me a second, mate,
yeah?
Get up, over there.
Get in the corner. Get on
your knees. Go. Look around.
You can't know who owns this
place. You wouldn't be here.
You're insane!
Move it or I'll have it clamped.
I said just give me
a fucking minute!
You all right, mate?
Open it.
Charges set.
Keep your heads down
and nobody gets hurt.
Face the wall.
Sorry, sweetheart.
Naughty, naughty.
Wildcat!
- You good? - 100 grand and a
big bag of diamonds.
Thank you very much, Mrs Vine.
No one turn around or
they fucking get it.
Fucking finally!
All those
diamonds, it's gonna work.
Roman, it has got
to fucking work.
Oh my God, that is a talent.
You can just reload like that.
One after the other. It's
amazing.
- Why, you want to go again?
- Can you go again?
Can I ask you something?
Have you been thinking
about it at all?
You want to talk about
changing our lives now?
I bet you want a family.
- We are a family.
- I know we're a family, just...
If we are on two totally
separate paths, I do... I do
need to know.
And how do you think your
brother's gonna handle an
addition to the family?
Imagine how he'd be
if we had a child.
Oh, don't make this about him.
You know, I've got...
A brother with a paranoid
personality, whatever they're
calling it this week.
And I'm his big sister.
So I am responsible for him.
If I'd been braver, or...
Helped him earlier,
then maybe he wouldn't be so...
- How he fucking is!
- Listen to me.
How many times do I have to tell
you, this is not your fault.
You gotta find a way to... let
yourself off this fucking hook.
Roman, I've never lied to you
about who I am or what I want.
It is now or never.
Because I'm running out of road.
I don't know if I can
bring a kid into this world.
The job that we do is dangerous
as shit. What if I'm not around?
What if I can't be
there to be a dad?
Well then we'll
quit, we'll get out.
Ada, our work is who we are.
Ah, fuck that.
No, it's not. It's what we do.
Does that mean that
every time you're here with me,
that your mind's
just somewhere else?
I love being with you.
It's beautiful. It's quiet.
We have fun, me and you.
So why can't we just
have more fun? More quiet?
Eventually, Ada, that quiet
is going to become so deafening,
it's going to make
my ears bleed.
I... I don't know how
to respond to that.
- Just...
- Go.
So friendly.
What's his name?
- Poppy. She's a girl.
- Poppy, lovely.
- Roman?
- Are you kidding me?
How long... It's been
such a long time.
Years! I can't believe it's you.
What are you even doing here?
I'm doing this
private security job
with Curtis, actually.
And who might you be, angel?
This is Charlotte.
Charlotte,
this is Mummy's friend, Roman.
We used to work together.
Yeah, he does!
She says you look
like a Power Ranger.
- Oh, did she?
- Yeah.
I see we've both
picked up a new skill.
No wedding ring, I see.
Jumping right in there
with the big questions, then.
I'm just... wondering if
anyone's gonna mind if I ask you
to dinner tonight.
I can't go out
tonight, I'm sorry.
But...
If you fancy joining me and
Charlotte for chicken nuggets...
Chicken nuggets?
Uh... Chicken nuggets
are my favourite food.
- You're the Chicken Nugget Man.
- That's what they call me.
Well, you made a good choice
there. 'Cause they're shaped
like dinosaurs.
What an amazing kid. -
Looks smarter and tougher than
her mum.
And what about
dad? He not around?
- Not letting that one go, are
you? - Just curious.
Let's just say I'm
a terrible judge of character.
Well, your terrible judge
of character bodes well for me.
Hey, hey, hey, at ease, soldier.
That's a bit fast for me.
Yes, ma'am.
- How long are you in town for,
anyway? - A couple more weeks.
Right. Yeah.
Well, I...
guess I should get going, then.
Yeah, yeah.
- Thank you for dinner.
- Of course.
And for letting me spend time
with Charlotte.
- Yeah.
- I really enjoyed it.
I'm glad.
Oh, Roman.
Coat.
- It's good to see you.
- Yeah, you too.
Look at her.
Look at her!
Get her out of here.
Look at your
baby brother, Ada.
Your little girl is
coming with me, Ada.
Frasier Mahoney is
gifting you one day.
6 AM tomorrow.
Kailash's flower market cafe.
Bring half a million in cash.
If you're late... You
really don't want to be late.
I'm so sorry.
- What the fuck?
- Ada, I fucked up.
- I fucked up.
- What have you done?
I fucked up, Ada, please,
you gotta believe me, I
I had no idea that you and
Charlotte would get dragged into
this.
- Why Charlotte?
- Because you're my sister.
I can't pay the
money that I owe!
- Well, I haven't fucking got it
either. - Ada, they know.
They know what you are.
They know about
your special forces background.
And they figure that with you,
I've got half a chance
of getting the cash.
I didn't... I didn't know.
I didn't fucking know!
Ada. I'm glad you called.
I've been thinking about you.
- They've taken Charlotte.
- What?
Hold on.
What are you talking about? Who?
- Can you come?
- I'm on my way.
Bring guns, Roman.
Bring a fucking arsenal.
- Come here.
- Oh, God.
We're gonna take care
of this, all right?
Whatever it is,
we're gonna fix it.
Brought some backup.
Curtis!
I owe you, Ada.
I'm here to return the favour.
You've all heard about this war
brewing between Mahoney and Mrs
Vine.
Two biggest gangsters in London
fighting for the number one
spot.
Only needs a spark
and there'll be fireworks.
Exactly, so if we take down
Vine's jewellery store,
make it look like
it was Mahoney...
They'll be busy fighting a war,
not looking for us.
Are we even sure there's
gonna be enough in the safe?
I have a guy on the inside
who's pretty convinced,
enough to give us this
information and risk his life.
Sorry, how the fuck
are we gonna get.
Mrs Vine to believe
Mahoney ripped her off?
Cia.
Information's her currency.
And she's the most trusted
source of it in London.
If we can convince Cia,
our plan's gonna work.
Cia fucking hates you!
All right, it's complicated.
After that, we see
Finlay the Fence
and we flip the
jewels into cash.
Huh.
Then we'll use the cash
to pay Mahoney...
And get Charlotte back.
All by 6 AM, that's
going to be tight.
Finlay's given us
a time and a place.
Mushka Estates.
Are you crazy, man?
I'm not going there.
You fucking idiot.
You really think
you're coming with us?
You're a fucking idiot...
- Curtis!
- Look at me. At me.
They've already got my baby.
I can't risk letting
anything happen to you.
They've only got
Charlotte because of me.
I got you into this mess and I'm
gonna put my life on the line to
get you out.
I know you would.
Everybody down on the floor!
Minute!
It's gonna work.
Finlay the Fence said
to call him from
a landline phone
in the Mushka Estate.
There's a payphone
around the corner.
Fucking hell. Mushka Estate.
Why the hell would
anybody want to meet here?
Finlay likes the location
because the cops hate it here.
Is he still only
taking landline calls?
Has to be a landline. Has
to be in the next 20 minutes.
If we're late, the deal's off.
- What the fuck?
- Who the fuck is that?
Help! Help!
Edward, why is there
a parking geezer in the boot?
You fucking idiot.
What's the matter with you?
It's not a big fucking deal!
Hey, what the fuck
are you saying, man?
Hey, you lot really fucked up
in the wrong ends, you get me?
- It's an accident, OK? Just
calm down. - A fucking Yank!
Rah, man. Pussyhole's
proper lost, innit, bruv?
What, you banged your head in
the crash, bitch? Stepping at
me?
- This really hurts. - You think
man looks like a fucking doctor?
Nah, I think you look like
a bitch who lives with his mum.
And you might need a doctor.
What's happening, treacle?
Hey, yo, they got
some serious machine, bruv.
Back the fuck up. Go
on, the pair of ya.
Drop the knife, baby boy.
You ain't the only one in
this estate strapped, you know.
I'm the only one
in this conversation, innit?
I said, back the fuck
up. You too, sweetheart.
Come on then, big man.
Hey, yo, fuck this, Rico, man.
Let's cut, yeah?
I'll be seeing you.
Go on. Ta ta. Fuck off.
Hey, don't get
comfortable, yeah?
Come on we've got to get out of
here. They're gonna come back.
You can fuck off and all.
We gotta get this parking geezer
out the boot.
Will you stop kicking
the trunk, please?
You don't want to do that.
There's explosives in there.
What the fuck are you doing, Ada?
You need to wake up!
Wake up!
Ada! Ada!
Oh, God.
Edward? No, no, no.
You're bleeding. Are you hurt?
No, I'm... I'm fine.
Are you all right?
I'm fine. Fine...
- Is the traffic guy...
- No, he's not.
Look, we have to go right now.
Jesus Christ,
we've killed somebody innocent.
Well, I'm sorry.
I didn't know what else to do.
We can't think about it
now. We need to focus on
Charlotte.
So why the fuck
was that geezer in our boot?
- He was a traffic warden.
- Yeah, I caught that.
Why the fuck was
he there, you twat?
Please try
and chill, Curtis.
Well, he wanted
me to move the car.
So you put
him in our boot?
What, you'd rather
I'd moved the fucking car?!
I'd rather you'd removed
the explosives we rigged
to torch the robbery car
rather than put a traffic
- 6 o'clock.
- What?
Mushkas. Looks like
they're waiting for backup.
Can't open fire. There'll
be an army on us in no time.
- Where is this pay phone?
- Just up here.
- It's all right, Ed. Stay calm.
- Yeah, I'm fucking trying to
keep calm.
- Too late. Cover!
- Get him inside.
Get up there,
Ed. Move, move.
Move!
There has to be a way
through to the other side.
Then we can get a car.
- 98.
Guys, they're moving in.
Curtis, take my
brother. Find a way out.
- Get a car, now.
- We need firepower here.
That's an order.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Almost out! Moving!
Let's go.
Moving!
That's the police. Cops are
fighting with the Mushkas.
Now's our time to move.
I'm on your heels. Go.
Over here on this wall.
Wait here. Do not fucking move.
Oh, fuck, I can't feel my hands.
- Just chill out. - I'm trying,
I'm trying, I'm trying,
I'm trying, I'm trying.
Calm yourself
down. Deep breaths.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Roman, Roman, Roman!
No, no, no.
Where are you hurt?
- Only my feelings.
- Fucking hell!
You scared the shit out of me.
You've been waiting to do that,
haven't you?
I ain't got Roman's
patience with you.
- I'm here...
- Because Ada saved your life.
And now she gave you a fucking
order and you need to follow it.
If anyone's got a pass to freak
the out right now, it ain't
fucking you, mate!
- I can't breathe. You don't
understand. - No, you don't
understand.
Have you got any idea what
Mahoney will do to Charlotte?
- Snap the fuck out of it! -
Alright, Curtis, fucking leave
it.
Go on.
- I can't breathe! I can't
brea... - You can breathe.
What you're feeling's
an illusion.
Where are we gonna go?
- The, the churchyard.
- That's right.
We need to move.
We can't leave him like this.
Look at me. Come on, mate.
You got your anchor.
Touch it. Hold it
in your hand really tight.
- Jesus fucking Christ!
- Listen,
he's not gonna respond if
you treat him like that.
He needs to man the fuck up,
wrap his head around
what he's done.
We're gonna have a massive
fucking problem
if you don't leave him alone.
You wouldn't say that about
a soldier with PTSD, would you?
- What the fuck is wrong with
you? - Nothing.
She shot me.
Well that fucking tracks.
Hey, haven't we got
that fence guy to call?
Oh, my God. We've got
eight minutes to phone Finlay.
I've got a mate on the estate.
He's only a couple of minutes
drive away.
We need to go. Now.
- Nana! Nana!
- What's the matter?
Another nightmare?
Caden, look at Nana.
What did I say?
- Come on, poppet.
- I don't need to be scared.
That's a good boy.
Now, Mr Tiny's gonna
look after you.
And if you need me, you know Mr
Jenson's just outside the door.
Just yell, Nana
will come running.
Now, go back to sleep.
Sweet dreams.
Thank you, Mr Jenson.
An area of East London
infamous for a high level of
gang activity
is descending into a war zone.
Armed response police officers
are flooding the area,
but don't seem to be able to
bring the situation under
control.
And it's being reported that
armed officers and gang members
are exchanging gunfire.
- What happened to her?
- Scared to death, Mrs Vine.
Literally.
I didn't even electrocute her.
Gentlemen, my sincere apologies
for the interruption.
Now, help me understand.
You are attempting
to convince me
that three thieves caught you
completely unawares
on the very day I coincidentally
had over £2 million
worth of jewels in my safe.
They were smart enough
to blow the cabinets
because they knew by doing so,
the police would be alerted
and I would have to spend hours
dealing with the law
before focusing my full
attention on capturing those
audacious enough
to steal from me.
Is that an adequate summary?
Mrs Vine. Please,
I swear on my life.
I don't know who did
this to you, or what...
I want to emphasise
the need for honesty.
I trust the point is made.
I swear I had nothing to do with
this. If anyone's involved, it's
Brady.
Brady seems to disagree.
Please, if I knew anything,
I would tell you.
Please. No, please.
Please! Please!
I sincerely hope his
theory was correct.
I'm sorry. I was in the military
with Roman Cutter.
He's the one who hit your store.
I was desperate.
I knew nothing about the 2
million in diamonds. Neither did
Cutter.
But if you let me go, I will
bring him to you on a fucking
plate.
Send someone to see
Finlay the Fence.
Of course, ma'am. But if Roman
Cutter's working independently,
I mean, you really think he'd
try and fence your jewels
locally?
I don't want to think, Lennie.
I want to know.
It's a very short list of fences
with a bandwidth for such a
transaction.
- Finlay is at the top.
- Yes, ma'am.
Brady, my darling, why don't
you start by enlightening me
as to who exactly Roman is?
Cutter was a part of a
Special Ops International unit.
Elite force. He's involved with
off-the-book shit these days.
- You have a way of contacting
him? - No, he's gone dark.
He said he would reach out to
let me know where I can collect
my cut in a few days
but look, I can track him down
for you, ma'am. I can kill him
for you.
You're clearly not a match
to the man you described.
No, I can track him
down. No, wait, no!
Find Mr Cutter.
I want him sat
trembling in front of me
before sunrise.
Yes, ma'am.
An altercation between
the Mushka street gang
and the Metropolitan Police
has descended into a riot
which is spreading
across East London.
The riot is believed to have
been started within the past
hour
when gunfire was exchanged
between armed officers
and the Mushka gang.
The police are mobilising
emergency reinforcements,
but local residents are being
advised to remain indoors...
- Fucking hell! - Till the
situationhas been brought under
control.
We're hoping to bring
our news helicopter
in close enough
to verify reports.
That fucking thing
nearly landed in my living room.
- Street gang members - and the
Metropolitan Police. -
Tensions in the
City of London...
Shit! Shit...
Nicky?
Oh, thank God. Curtis!
- The fuck, man?
- Still got that landline phone?
Yeah, Nice to see you too, bruv.
Been a while.
Sorry, who are these... Hello!
- No. No.
- All right. Not my type anyway.
I just need a solid tonight.
Have you been
caught out in this madness.
Wars with the police, gangs,
cars, fire, guns. Fucking
Parisian, bruv.
- Really need that landline.
- I wish you'd have called.
You gave me a right shock. I
thought it was my giant cunt
neighbour
from downstairs.
Sorry, mate, I've only got the
burner on me. Didn't have your
number saved.
Well, why didn't you call this
geezer on your burner, then?
He only accepts landline calls.
What kind of mediaeval fucker
only accepts landline calls?
Please, no, Curtis.
Don't tell me he's dodgy.
Trust me. He's cool.
Just chill. Let us do our...
Roman Cutter. I have
a window I'd like to redeem.
Sorry, Finlay, we had
a little bump in the road.
- We're on in 30 minutes. - That
doesn't give me enough time to
get to Cia's club.
- We can't dictate the timing to
Finlay. - Sorry, what is all
this?
I will handle Finlay,
and you go to Cia.
No fucking way. I
have to be there.
- Roman, we have a problem. -
Ada, I will handle it. Trust me.
Please, someone explain to me
what the fuck is happening here.
- Roman.
- What is it?
The detonator is in the car boot
cunty bollocks over here blew up
along with the parking geezer.
- You blew up a parking geezer?
- Yes, I fucking did.
Edward, for fuck's sake!
Jesus Christ!
My man's waving a
hand cannon in my
I got neighbours, man.
- There's a WhatsApp group
and... - Hey, hey. Fuck you.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- Is that my gun?
You said I could trust you.
Calm the fuck down.
- Give me the gun.
- He's being a bollock.
- You're being a fucking
bollock. - You're being a
bollock.
Don't touch my gun.
- Can you pull a rabbit out of
your arse? - Detonator?
We've got enough C-4 left over
from the heist.
- But we've lost the detonator.
- Maybe.
I have to make a couple
of calls. It'll cost.
What about getting it delivered?
- No, no, stop.
- Is this custom?
- Also...
- You want me to babysit?
Well, taking him anywhere
without me right now...
- Bad idea. - Yeah, and I can't
take him to Cia's.
- I'll see if I can get it
dropped off. - Drop what off?
A pizza? Oh, no. Let
me go out on a limb
and guess it's something
a little bit naughtier.
- Wait, I just need you to
chill. - Chill?
You're fucking
outrageous. - This is never
gonna work.
Man was chilling.
Man was watching
Apocalypse London on the telly.
I need to hold here for a couple
of hours. It's no big deal.
- Just you, though, right?
- Well, me and...
- You and Looney Tunes?
- Oi!
I have a very serious
personality disorder
that's brought on
by stressful situations, OK?
Oh, well, tickle
me reassured, then.
'Cause there's nothing fucking
stressful about this situation,
is there?
No, bollocks to this.
You lot can all piss off out
of my yard right fucking now.
Five grand, there.
Tea, coffee?
Don't leave that
lying about, bruv.
Yeah, I'll tidy it up
before my fucking
maid gets here.
It's just like you said.
If Mrs Vine believes Mahoney
took her jewels,
she'll start a war with Mahoney,
and we're home free.
And you're the only one who
could convince Cia that's what
happened.
- I can't take a weapon in to
Cia. - Give it here.
I'll meet Finlay and get
the jewels turned into cash.
Trust me.
- Edward?
- I won't do anything.
- All right?
- Be a good lad.
He's being a fucking
idiot, though.
Why is she hugging him like
they're never gonna see each
other?
Just shut up for a second,
will you, mate?
I'll just shut up for a second,
shall I? Only my house.
Rude!
- 98.
90 fucking 8.
Right, so which one of you
bellends is gonna explain to me
what the fuck is going on here?
Attention...
Roman.
- If I don't see you again...
- What are you talking about?
See you in 90 minutes.
You are instructed
to leave the area immediately.
Failure to comply
may result in arrest.
This is the police. You are
present at an unlawful assembly.
Please go home. This is
theMetropolitan Police
Department.
You are ordered
to leave the area immediately.
I don't give a
fuck how old you are.
You're getting a
crunch on the nose,
you carry on
chatting shit to me.
Oi. Hey!
What's a nice girl like you
doing out on her own?
You're lost.
Let me walk you home.
- I don't
have fucking time for this.
Hey, where are you going?
Come, come, come. Oi!
Darlin'! Oh dear,
oh dear, oh dear.
- Slow down, babe. - Wasn't very
bright coming down here,
was it?
Babe, where are you going?
Show us your tits, love.
Alright, you've picked the wrong
tits, lads. First and last
warning.
Ooh!
She sounds like
she likes it rough.
You've got no fucking idea.
You got spirit and
a filthy mouth, eh?
Maybe I should teach you
to be a real lady.
- I mean, I do like to learn new
things. - Oh, yeah?
I did warn you.
Yeah?
Fucking bellends.
I got your text.
What the fuck is going on?
Take a seat.
No, I won't take a seat, Rouben.
What the fuck are
you playing at, Edward?
I'm not... just fucking
piss off, Curtis.
I'm trying to regale my story
here and you weren't there, all
right?
Look, we got Galloway
into this madness.
The least we can fucking do
is tell him what's going on.
Yeah, Uncle Nut Nut here is
right. I do deserve to know
what's going on.
I'm trying to make
an important phone call.
Fucking hell!
Who pissed in his salad?
I'm just a delivery driver.
I don't know anything.
I don't see anything. I keep
my head down. That is the job.
You think this crap
is going to get you out of this?
You were the one that said that
no one would find out
if we took a little taste.
Well, somebody found out.
Rouben, who the
fuck have we been working for?
Frasier Mahoney.
Frasier fucking Mahoney!
Are you having a giraffe, bruv?
- How are you even a blip on his
radar? - I didn't fucking know.
What kind of a bellend delivers
shit for people they don't know,
then steals off them?
Fuck you, you don't
get to judge me
on your shit pleather sofa.
Right, that's enough
about fucking sofas.
Chill the fuck out!
Fuck's sake.
Fine, we'll just pay Mahoney
back the money with a little bit
of interest.
It's fine.
- I'm afraid we can't do that.
- Why the fuck not?
It's gone.
I mean, it was only a few grand,
man. We'll do a couple of jobs.
It'll be fine.
How much money do
you owe, Rouben?
You know those anxiety attacks
that I used to get when I was a
kid, Rouben?
Well, I feel like
you're fucking triggering one.
So you need to tell me
how much money you owe.
400,000 plus interest.
That's the fucking number,
right there. You've fucked us.
I'm sorry, Eddie.
I did not know that this would happen.
But I didn't even fucking take
that much money!
Not even fucking close, you did!
Yes, but they know
that you steal.
- How they know I steal?
- Eddie?
- Eddie, mate.
- What, mate?
Can't you see I'm mid flow here?
No, I can see that, mate.
I think you might need
professional help.
- What?
- Your brain is broken.
Frasier Mahoney would like
to have a conversation
with you gentlemen.
- You fucking set me up. - I
just promise we both be here.
Fuck this.
Fuck this. Get the fuck off me!
Get the fuck off me!
I didn't do anything wrong!
It's not my fault!
I didn't fucking do anything!
No, no! Detonators?
Blown-up traffic wardens?
Frasier fucking Mahoney?
Yeah, and Charlotte had
nothing to do with it!
Who the fucking fuck
is Charlotte right now?
- Curtis, what the fuck, bruv?
- You're an absolute lifesaver.
Cheers, yeah, I'll be waiting.
Ta, mate, yeah.
All right?
What's the matter, bruv?
Jesus, Ada, you can't...
I'm in a rush, guys.
You jumping in or not?
We'll get the next one.
Mind
the doors, please.
Oi! Leave her alone.
Get off her, assholes.
- Who's this?
- Come swinging, man.
What is it with you
fucking Mushkas?
Get up! Fuck off!
Forgot your hat!
You know I can't
let you in, Ada.
And you know there aren't
enough of you to stop me.
Come on...
You sure? Where's Jody?
Hmm? Jody?
Come here.
Ada, what the fuck
are you doing?
I'm here to see Cia.
There isn't a chance
that you're getting in.
- Are you serious?
- Take my money and I'll go in easy.
Refuse it, I'm gonna
go in pretty hard.
- Give me two minutes.
- You've got one.
You rob the second
biggest gangster in the city
to pay back the first
biggest gangster in the city.
You fucking wanker.
You're as mental as he is.
Now my... my sister,
she's always looked after me.
- Calm down. Do the anchor
thing. - I'm calm.
Where's your pebble, Eddie?
Pull your pebble out.
No, no, no, no, no. No
one's pulling out their pebble!
- It's a calming technique,
dickhead. - I don't give a fuck.
No one's pulling out
their pebble in my yard.
He's not actually...
Are you all right?
I'm your rock.
I'm your big sister
and I will always protect you.
I love you.
She's not all that strong.
She... She fucking hurts like
hell.
You're all right.
She... she...
She learned to fight in secret.
She did. She did. She used
to steal to pay for lessons.
Just so that
she could protect me from him.
She killed that bastard for me.
She fucking killed him.
This is how I fucking repay her?
By getting her
fucking daughter kidnapped?
You fucking idiot, Eddie!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Stop stamping on the floor!
If downstairs comes
up, we're fucked.
They call him
Nicky-Never-Lost-A-Fight.
And if Looney Tunes
don't stop stamping on my floor,
he'll be up here not
losing another one.
Curtis!
Right, stop. You're taking
the piss now. Sorry, Ada.
So if that was an option, why
didn't you do that a half hour
ago?
Shut up.
Hello. Hi.
- Um... here for Finlay.
- Who?
OK.
Sit down. Shut up.
Where is she, Tony? You've got
no idea how important this is.
You know how this works. Because
you made the fucking rules.
Calm down. Cia said
she'll see you now.
Good.
I got a taxi for Roman Cutter.
Hey, hey,
hey, hey. Hold on.
- Where's Finlay?
- I'm taking you to him.
What do you mean?
That's not how this works.
Get in or get out. Up to you.
- Oh, now we fucked.
- Get out here, Galloway!
Open this fucking door!
Hey, Nicky. Oh, mate, I'm
really sorry about the noise.
It's just... It's my boy, he
gets carried away with Pro Evo.
Ah, fuck! Curtis?
- Ow.
- You guys want to fuck with me?
No.
- Told you.
- Oh, fuck.
Oh, my days!
I'm going to fucking kill you!
Shut the fuck up, Curtis.
Just let the man finish.
Oh, that's fucked!
Curtis!
Fucking hell.
Get over here.
On your fucking knees.
Now!
The number you have dialled
has not been recognised.
Please check and try again.
Hey, Nicky.
I hope we can move past all
this, being neighbours and all.
Sorry, mate.
If you ever come back
anywhere near this place again,
the last thing you'll ever see
will be my raging eyes.
All right, I'm leaving.
Go on, fuck off.
Fucking hell.
Don't you upset her.
- You understand me?
- I think so.
Rioting
descends across East London
and Ada Williams comes to see me
for the first time
since quitting my employment.
What a night.
Looks like business
is going well.
It really breaks my heart.
The only reason you're here
is because you must need
something from me.
Oh no, I've got
something for you.
Not what I'd like, no doubt.
Well, no, not that. But trust
me, you're gonna want this.
Trust... you?
How much further to Finlay?
In a few hours, you're
gonna find out that
someone's robbed
one of Mrs Vine's stores.
- Old news, Ada.
- I know who did it.
What do you want for this?
I just want peace. I want
you to forgive me for quitting.
I've left the life
and I just don't want
any burnt bridges
for me or for my daughter.
- That's it?
- That's it.
Get out.
Finlay, what's with
all this cloak and dagger shit?
The Machiavellian nature of
our unique business
forces me into the
inexorable position
of doing said business
in a unique manner.
Hmm.
You say you want peace.
I say you need to be certain
that your information gets to
the right destination.
And there is no chance
on earth you'd be here
if I wasn't the best place in
London to buy and sell
enlightenment.
If you want my
guarantee, then...
Fucking handcuff yourself.
That's the price. Trust.
Fine.
This doing it for you?
Please, let me do the other one.
Go for it.
Wow.
I've tamed the
untameable.
You must be...
Desperate.
One must be either asinine
or a criminal genius
to rob Mrs Christina Vine.
You still using that
word-of-the-day toilet paper?
I have a library card.
I'm sorry, did you say
someone robbed Mrs Vine?
Presumably nothing more than
a coincidence, then.
Hmm.
Just like this Mushka riot,
escalating out of control.
There's a lot going
on in London tonight.
Maybe I could take
you to the realms of
pleasure,
or pain...
that you couldn't even imagine.
Or...
You have friends right next door
that would actually kill
for an opportunity like this.
Imagine the kind of money
we could make.
500,000. These diamonds
and what's in the pouch.
Satisfied with that amount
for these jewels?
Just gonna take my asking price?
Not gonna haggle or anything?
I must have bagged a few
more jewels than I expected.
- I'm a man of my word.
- You are a man of many words.
Open the window, please.
Feel free to count it.
Fuck this.
I need you both out of here now.
- You know we can't leave. - I
ain't giving you a choice, bruv.
- This doesn't need to get out
of hand. - Out of hand?
Out of hand's a spec
in the rear view mirror.
This shit is next fucking
dimensional. Now, fuck off.
We come from fuck
all, me and you.
No family, no help.
We've carved out an existence
for ourselves the best we can.
I know.
And I wish I could help you,
I really do, bruv, but...
But I ain't built for this.
I'm scared. So I need you
both to leave my fucking house,
right fucking...
Fucking hell!
Fuck!
- Who's fucking shooting at us,
Curtis? - Shut the fuck
up.
Throw out the money
and we let you live.
Shit.
Shit! Fuck it.
Coming on then, you slags.
This deal is time
sensitive, Cia.
You can really be a
drag, Miss Williams.
How much pressure
would it take to.
shut
off your gas? Hmm?
This much, or... this
much?
You haven't taken air in
15 seconds.
You must feel the
euphoria, right?
- I do now, you twisted bitch. -
Oh, Ada, Ada, you haven't
changed.
I want more.
Jody!
Ahh the burn!
- Fuck's sake.
- Oh, call them off.
I still can't fathom why
you won't protect me any longer.
Let's watch this show.
Once again, you
leave me breathless.
Frasier Mahoney robbed Mrs Vine.
Wants to show how vulnerable she
is.
Mahoney thinks the move will
give him the neutral street
support,
because he wants a war.
Fucking love that bitch.
Fucking hate that bitch.
Come here!
- Fuck you.
- Fucking die!
Curtis?
The fuck is happening?
Get a lighter.
98, yeah?
Fucking hell, man.
Is that Nicky guy dead?
Fuck.
Jesus Christ, Curtis. Curtis!
Tell me what to do, mate.
You need to check for an exit
and cauterise the wound.
- OK.
- Open it. All of it.
Fuck. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, shit. Shit. Fuck!
I'm sorry, mate. I'm sorry.
Oh, there's no fucking exit
wound, Curtis. Tell me what I
do.
Gotta get the bullet out.
- Get me a mirror. Gimme a
mirror! - No, mate. I'll do it.
I'll do it, Curtis!
Please, mate. Look at me.
Look at me. Trust me.
I've got this.
Don't fuck it up.
Now, this is going to hurt
a little bit, all right?
Do you need to wait
till you feel the metal?
Sorry, mate. Oh, I got it. I got
it, mate. You're gonna be all
right.
Well done, Ed.
Maybe you're not
such a dickhead after all.
Curtis?
Curtis? Curtis, wake up, man.
Curtis, mate, wake up!
Oh, fuck, Curtis, please.
Fuck.
Looks good to me.
- The jewels, please. - How long
did it take you to learn sign
language?
You see, I learned
with an old battle buddy of mine
when we were running
ops in Helmand.
After that blast...
Well, he couldn't hear shit.
I think there's been
a misunderstanding.
There's no misunderstanding.
- Talk to me. - You asked me
to track Finlay.
He's currently in a car with
this Roman Cutter. What shall we
do?
Fuck it.
- Do them all.
- Yes, ma'am.
Lennie, love,
We're going to Cia's nightclub.
- Wake the boys up.
- I'm all over it, ma'am.
Trying to tell me
I don't look after my kids?
I look after my kids!
Bro, let me call
you back. Babes!
Holy fu... Let me call you back.
Let me call you back.
Yeah, you. Come here. Come here.
Damn!
Fancy the night of
your dreams, babes?
- Is this your car?
- You like it, yeah?
- Yeah, I really like it.
- So what are you trying to do?
I was thinking maybe I'll take
the car and we'll call it it
quits.
Take the car where?
You were gonna kill me
and you were gonna sell these
jewels back to Miss Vine's
for a little bit of
a discounted price.
Does that sound about right?
- Ambush!
- Drive!
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
What the...
What are we gonna do, Roman?
A minute ago, you were
trying to kill me.
Now we're a fucking team?
Shit!
I'm out. Give me your gun.
- I don't have one. - What kind
of gangster doesn't have a gun?
My driver has one...
on the passenger seat.
Not bad.
Get to the taxi.
- Move!
- Oh fuck! Fuck, fuck!
- Keep your head down.
- What are you gonna do?
Explosion in three, two...
Not a fucking word.
Come on out and we
can make a deal.
Ro... Roman, we can make a deal!
- You make a deal, then.
- No, fu...! Oh, shit!
Put it in neutral. Neutral!
Fuck!
What are you doing!?
Don't go fucking towards them...
Oh, fucking hell!
Fuck!
Are you fucking crazy?!
Ro... Roman? Roman!
Fuck it.
Oh fuckers!
No!
Ah! Fuck!
Fuck!
Come on.
- Who the fuck are you?
- I don't want no trouble, fam.
I was just told I had to give a
detonator to a man named Curtis,
that's it.
All right. Drop it and leave.
Jesus Christ.
Fuck's sake...
Oh, no, no, no. No, Curtis!
Oh!
I'm so fucking sorry.
Edward?
Edward?!
In here.
Oh, thank God. Are you hurt?
- What the hell happened?
- I am so sorry.
No, we're gonna get Charlotte.
We're nearly through this.
All I have ever been to you,
Ada, is... is a burden.
- That's not true.
- Oh, we both know that it is.
I mean, even when we were kids,
all you did was protect me.
You looked out for
me and you loved me.
All I've ever done is... is
throw that love back in your
face.
That is absolute bollocks.
Never, ever say that again.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for everything
you've ever done for me.
You don't need to thank me, you
arse. I'm your big sister. It's
my job.
Look
I promise I'm gonna
make it up to you.
There's nothing to make up for.
- I love you so much.
I'm so glad you're all right.
No!
You remember when we met?
First day at the
joint force exercise.
Our instructor was
the best of the best.
And he used to say:
"The body... the body
consumes calories
to be able to keep
burning at 98 degrees".
Yeah, that's right.
You keep yourself and the men
and women that stand beside you,
- you keep them burning at
ninety... - eight degrees.
Yeah.
He called you Wildcat.
You remember that?
'Cause you never give up, Ada.
No. Matter. What.
But Edward!
Edward is gone.
But Charlotte's still 98.
Let's go get her back.
That's right.
What an unexpected surprise.
You reached out to my people,
asked to talk urgently.
After years of doing business
it's the first time
we're face to face.
I hear you have
some food for me.
Caviar has a price.
It's met.
Frasier Mahoney was behind the
heat on your jewellery store.
He wants to make you look...
Weak.
Thinks that it would win him the
neutral support in the street
if war were to break out.
If I tip the server,
can I meet the chef?
I can't divulge on how or where
I obtain my ingredients.
- What I can do is serve you the
meal. - I never much liked
caviar.
Too salty.
My restaurant will still
require payment, otherwise...
Our kitchen will remain closed
to you in the future.
You've walked a
remarkable tightrope.
Building an operation
such as this in my city.
Not just a pretty head
on those shoulders.
You really flatter me, Mrs Vine.
Lennie, love.
Settle the bill.
Ma'am.
Hello, sweetheart.
You know, I've never been
very good at real talk.
You're still afraid of a normal
life without all the noise?
Nothing scares me more than
losing you again, Ada.
We're gonna get Charlotte back.
I promise.
Roman, I have to
tell you something.
Is it Charlotte?
She's ours, isn't she?
I had a feeling.
I love you, Ada.
- Is my daughter here?
- Take a seat.
Where's Charlotte?
Characters... Running
a riot up and down my city.
We're on the news
all over the world.
Enterprising little wannabe
gangsters thinking it's their
time to shine.
Wild times in which we live, eh?
Do you know that my wife
passed away last year?
My sincerest condolences.
She was a remarkable woman.
She really was.
Kind of woman to make
an impression, you know?
Christ alive,
she was a bona fide head turner.
Not just because
she was beautiful.
Fellas looking at
her and all that. No.
Didn't matter what
she looked like.
- She had this energy. - She
sounds like an extraordinary
woman.
I'll let you in to
a little secret.
I wouldn't be the man I am today
if it weren't for her.
What's that saying?
Fuck's sake...
You know, behind
every great man is a
there's a wonderful woman.
I believe it's true.
I'm a feminist, you see.
And I know if a
woman wants to get
to the same place as
a man in this world,
then she's got to
work twice as hard.
Can you pass the marmalade?
Hmm?
I want to see my daughter.
People used to say things,
on the quiet, people would say,
Martine, that was her name,
Martine, my wife,
Martine... pulls
the puppet strings.
I've got what you want.
The money my brother owes.
- Is Charlotte here? - Yeah,
yeah, we'll come to that.
No, no, no, no, no.
We're there now.
I didn't mind people
talking. That's fine.
The problem wasn't geezers
chatting. The problem was...
My wife started to believe
all the shit they were saying.
Now, the power went to her head.
Fucking woman stopped listening
to what I was saying.
She even undermined me
on more than one occasion.
- Couldn't fucking believe her.
- Look, if you want the money,
bring me my daughter right now.
I killed Martine
with me bare hands.
Wrung her neck like
a fucking chicken.
That taught her a lesson.
No woman should ever
get above her station.
Not in my presence.
I've got half a million cash
that I would like to give you
in exchange for my daughter.
Do you know the most
valuable thing in the world?
Do we have a deal?
Information.
Take you, for example.
I never knew you existed
till a few days ago.
And now here we are, cozying up
together over breakfast and a
cup of coffee.
You're a dangerous female.
It's information I wish I'd
known a long time before now.
If you think I'm gonna make some
kind of vendetta after this,
you're wrong.
My only agenda is Charlotte.
And your blood?
No baby brother here to witness
whatever tune I might play?
My brother's dead.
Hmm.
Well, you've had
a stressful time.
Your limit's been
pushed, that's for sure.
Mr Mahoney, is Charlotte here?
Yes, she is.
Can I see her?
Allow me
to throw you a piece
of information.
If you've harmed my
child in any way,
I will rip out your liver
and I will fucking eat it!
Relax!
It's a gift. Open the box.
Cia...
Of course, re-gifting
is hardly polite.
But on this occasion,
I made an exception.
Thought Ada might enjoy
the surprise as much as you.
You're
a true sweetheart.
Do you want to invite
Roman Cutter to join us?
I assume he's somehow listening.
Motherfuckers!
I hope your colleague also has
my jewels. Finlay certainly
doesn't.
Best laid plans, Ada.
Hello. Hi. Excuse
me, coming through.
If any of you poor
bastards are just here
for your cup of tea
and your beans on toast,
well, now's your
chance to fuck off.
No one. Really? Well, I'm not
surprised. You've been warned.
Thought it might be a good time
to enlighten you,
Mr Mahoney and Mrs Vine.
Part of our plan
went quite well...
Well, actually, amazingly well.
You wouldn't believe it. We
brought your 500 grand, and
this.
What's in the briefcase?
Be my guest. Have a good look.
Open it or I click me fingers
and your baby girl loses three
toes.
All right!
Yeah, we don't want
some stupid cunt
setting off the
stuff that's in here.
No, we don't.
- Is that a bomb? - No, that's a
rectal thermometer.
It is a bomb.
But I wouldn't be so much
worried about this
as I would be...
The detonator. It's
a dead woman switch.
Once I put my thumb
on the trigger like that...
If I let go, great big boom.
The thing is,
it does take
a very special kind of hate
to kill a family member.
Doesn't it, Mr Mahoney?
I didn't enjoy killing my
father. But it had to be done.
Because, and you'll
understand this as a feminist,
you can't let a man get too far
above his station.
Especially in my
fucking presence.
Why don't we all just calm down
and lower the guns?
Probably a good idea, because my
thumbs do get quite sweaty
around guns.
- Bring the girl.
- Thank you.
Easy.
Hi!
So... You just walk out of here
and then what?
We get to a safe distance.
I disarm the bomb,
everyone walks away alive.
Have I got "cunt"
written on my forehead?
I think the term
"Live to fight another day"
has never been more apt.
Let her go.
But
understand this.
If anything happens to me,
the wrath of my people
will come down on you.
Well, we'll be leaving now.
Oh, and if anybody decides to
fuck about with the case or have
us followed,
they'll be peeling
your arseholes off the ceiling
for the next three weeks.
Enjoy your breakfast!
You understand, of course, I'll
be taking that money in exchange
for my jewels.
Yeah, fuck it, it wasn't me
who ripped you off.
The fuck do you
think you're doing?
Take your gun off Mr Mahoney,
right fucking now.
Am I in Mexico?
Feels like a fucking standoff.
Oh fuck... No, no, no, no.
- Hey, what are you saying, fam?
- Are you kidding me?
Remember me?
You one of Mahoney's or Vine's?
I know they're both in there.
The feds are done out here. The
Mushkas are running the streets
now.
- Hey, dick splash. Look at
this. - Fucking shoot her!
- Fuck is that? - We have left a
fucking massive bomb in there
with enough explosives
to take out the whole postcode.
- Fucking drop it, then. - If I
fucking drop it, then we all
die.
- You're chatting shit.
- You wanna gamble?
Looking for me, boys?
Keep your head down, kid.
- What you think? - I don't
think we have a choice.
Come here, cover her.
Ada!
Ada.
- Are you OK?
- She's OK. Come on.
Ah, she's bleeding!
I took these.
This is to make sure
that you can give Charlotte
the life that she deserves.
Well, we can.
Yeah.
Maybe we should get
the fuck out of here.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
I think that that's smart.