Downloaded from
YTS.BZ
Official YIFY movies site:
Hello
"Palestine Red Crescent
Emergency Call Center"
"Ramallah, West Bank"
"84 kilometers from Gaza"
Apply pressure to stop the bleeding
Cover the wound
Palestine Red Crescent, go ahead
Palestine Red Crescent
Go ahead, how can I help you?
Okay, the ambulance is on its way
- The nearest ambulance is coming
- Stay calm
I can't hear you clearly
Okay, okay
You are now at the end
of Nazareth Street
Then you will see
the roundabout, correct?
Yes, at the roundabout
go straight ahead
Keep going straight
I see you, don't be afraid
I see you, I see you
Keep going straight then turn right, I...
I see you, you are a red dot
on the screen
- The ambulance crew is not responding
- How are you holding up?
Do you need any assistance?
Yes, this is the report
Great, thank you
Are you okay?
Is everything all right?
- Everything is fine
- Okay
- Rana
- Nisreen
Why are you still here? Weren't you
supposed to leave early in the morning?
I just need to tie up a few loose ends
I am extremely exhausted
I can't wait to go back home
Rock, paper, scissors
- Rock, paper, scissors
- Five to three
- Five
- Six to three
- Five to three
- I'm beating you
Come on, one more time
Wait, we have an emergency call
Hello, Red Crescent Emergency
Ramallah, West Bank
I'm Omar, go ahead
Hello, are there any phone
lines left in Gaza?
No, there are no phone lines
left in Gaza
All calls are being redirected here
after it was bombed
Slow down, slow down
Where?
- North of Gaza
- In Gaza?
Yes, but it shows that you're
calling from Germany
Okay
Okay, I'll send you a message
Send me your brother's car location
- and his phone number
- Okay, I'll text you that
Okay, thanks
Mahdi
- Yes, Omar?
- We might need an ambulance
- in northern Gaza
- In the north?
Yes, there is a gas station
I'm not entirely sure, wait a moment
"They're at Fares Gas Station
in a black car"
At Fares Gas Station
What's the nature of the emergency?
Bashar Hamada
with his wife and children
- evacuating from Tel al-Hawa in their car
- Tel al-Hawa
About 400 meters from their home
they were targeted near
Fares Gas Station at 1 PM
- At one o'clock?
- Yes, at 1 PM
It is 2:35 now, so this happened
an hour and a half ago
That is correct
So, are there still survivors
in the car, Omar?
I don't know, I spoke to his brother
who's in Germany, he knows nothing
He doesn't know if they are still in the car
or if they managed to escape on foot
The man is beside himself with fear
He is not getting any information
The gas station is located
in the besieged zone
The army has closed off this area
since this morning, Omar
"Fares Gas Station"
"They're at Fares Gas Station
in a black car"
"This number will definitely answer
0567022508"
We just received their phone number
Okay, try calling them
- I will, stay on the line
- Okay
It's ringing
Hello?
- Hello, dear
- They are shooting at us
- Hello?
- Yes, they are shooting at us
The tank is right next to me
- Are you taking shelter?
- Yes, we're in the car
and the tank is just right there
Are you inside the car?
Hello?
Omar
Is she still on the line?
Hello?
Omar
Omar, you need to talk to Rana
She is your supervisor
Omar
Omar was talking to a girl in Gaza
There was gunfire
then the line went dead, but...
I see
Omar
Are you okay?
Do you need psychological support?
Should I call Nisreen?
No
They killed her
What was her name?
We don't know, she didn't have
time to say her name
Omar
Hello, Omar
How are you holding up?
We hang these up in the office
When we don't have a photo
or even a name
of the people who died
while we were on the phone with them
Once we receive their real photos
we hang them here
To honor their memory
and show our respect
This way, you find closure within yourself
So you will be ready again
to receive new calls
Thank you
Omar, if you need to talk
to someone, I'm here
My door is open to you
You can come and let it all out
Deal? Don't be shy
- I need to get back
- Okay
I need to go
Do you need anything?
- Thank you
- Go get some rest and recharge
A six-year-old girl
is still alive inside the car
"Can you call her?"
Rana, come here, quickly
- What's wrong, Omar?
- There is...
Her uncle sent a message saying
there is a six-year-old girl
still hiding inside the car
Okay, call her
Omar
Come on, you've been trained
You know exactly what to do
Go ahead, call her
Okay, I'm leaving
- Hello, uncle
- Hello, my dear
Stay with me
Listen, sweetheart
Focus, focus, stay on the line
Tell me what happened there...
- Yes
- Hello?
There's no time
What? Are you hiding?
- Quickly
- Hello?
Hello?
What's your name?
- There's no one with me
- What's your name?
There's no one with me
I can't hear your name clearly
I'm Omar, what's your name?
- My name is Hanood
- Hanood?
What's your name?
- Hanood
- Hanood?
- What's your sister's name?
- Come get me out of here
- Okay, where's your sister?
Okay, I'll come to get you
but where's your sister?
I don't have a sister
- Mahdi
- Yes, Omar?
A six-year-old girl
is still hiding inside the car
hiding inside the car?
- Yes
- What about the others?
The others? I don't know
She said she's alone in the car
She's on the line
- Who's on the line?
- The girl
Is she one the Hamada family, Omar?
- Yes...
- Ask her
- Hanood
- Yes?
What's your last name?
What's your full name?
Hind Rajab Hamada
- Hind Rajab Hamada?
- Yes
- Okay, all right
- Rana
Hide under the seats
Don't show yourself at all
Stay on the line with her
- Deal?
- Okay
Where are your mom and dad?
They are not here
Okay, stay where you are
- I'll call you back shortly
- No, come get me out of here
They are shooting
- Mahdi
- Yes, Omar?
Any updates?
I'm waiting for details about
the available ambulance crews
She doesn't have much time left
Please, call them and get them moving
Omar, it won't help
if you call them again
They need to gather the information first
then they'll get back to me
- Hanood
- Yes?
Stay with me on the line for a bit
I'll come back to you, dear
Okay
The problem is there's only
one ambulance crew left in the north
Call them directly
Omar
Please go back to your call with the girl
and let me do my work
Call Zaino now
Ibrahim is the coordination officer in Gaza
He decides whether to call them or not
and that's what he is doing now
They are shooting at her
They will kill her just like the other girl
Please, tell Rana to come
and take Omar out of here
Mahdi, they are shooting at her
Here he is
Yes, Ibrahim?
Okay
- One moment
- Tell me...
Just a moment...
The crew, Youssef Zaino
Youssef Zaino
He is my favorite guy
- The driver
- It's Madhoun, there's no one else
Ahmed Al-Madhoun
- Type of the ambulance
- Savana
- Three
- One, zero, seven
- Four
- Five, five
- Okay
- Call Zaino immediately
Okay, okay, I'll start coordinating
Coordinating?
She doesn't have time, man
I'll call Youssef Zaino
to see if there is another way
There is no other way
Who told you you're allowed
to talk to Zaino?
Why would you talk to him?
Are you a supervisor?
I'm not a supervisor
but I'm trying to save the girl
- The girl...
- The girl is stuck in the car
It's not your job to save the girl
It is my job to save her
Your job is to sit
and stay on the line with her
and keep talking to her
while we try to coordinate her rescue
Don't let me see you again
without a Red Crescent vest
- What's going on here?
- I'm trying to start coordinating
but Omar isn't handling this calmly
Coordinating? I hope it won't
take nine hours this time too
Come with me, Omar
I hope so
- Hind?
- Who is speaking?
My name is Rana
and you're Hanood, right?
Yes...
Hello?
- The number you're calling...
- Zaino isn't answering
Omar, I told you
calling Zaino is my responsibility, dear
I'm just telling you there is no signal
Sure there is no signal, the army
is jamming all communications in Gaza
Hello, the Red Cross?
Vanessa, yes
We need a secure route for our ambulance
from the Saint Porphyrius Church
to the Fares gas station
in Tel al-Hawa, northern Gaza
Is it an emergency? A rescue?
- Yes, okay, thank you
- Okay, I'll call you back
That's Zaino, yes, Zaino?
How are you my friend?
Are you at Baptist Hospital?
- Hand me the phone, Omar
- Are you at Baptist Hospital?
I will connect you now
to the head of coordination
The chief negotiator, the martyr
the prisoner, the hero
Mahdi Al-Jamal, go ahead
Hello Zaino, what is going on?
Are you with Al-Madhoun at Baptist Hospital
and not at Porphyrius Church?
Okay, you are eight minutes
away from the rescue mission
Please Zaino, I need you
to wait for my instructions
- Understood?
- God willing
Thank you
Yes, my friend
I have a mission impossible for you
Hello, Ibrahim
I have started coordinating
Do not worry, I will not sacrifice
our last ambulance crew in the north
My dear, I will secure their route first
and make sure it is safe
before their mission
Hello, Hind
We have been talking to Hind
for eight minutes
If you sent the ambulance, they would
have taken her out of the car by now
Hind
Hello, my dear Hanood
Yes...
My dear, I will stay with you
on the line, okay?
Until someone comes for you, okay?
- Okay
- Where are you hiding now
Where are you taking shelter
at the moment?
In the car
You are inside the car
not outside, right?
- That is right
- Okay
Is anyone nearby who can
see you or talk to you?
- No
- Okay, my dear
Who were you with?
With my whole family
Who?
How many are there?
Do you know their names?
Can you tell me?
No
- Were your mom and dad with you?
- No
The army just shot at you
right my dear Hanood?
My little one, my dear Hanood
Come take me
My dear, calm down
and listen to me
I...
My dear, I want to ask you
a few questions
Focus with me a bit, okay?
- Hanood
- Yes?
Okay, listen to me
When they shot at you
who was with you?
- Your father...
- Everyone
Were your parents with you
inside the car?
- Or near the car?
- No
My mother is not dead
How many siblings do you have?
I only have one brother
How old is he?
Three years old
My brother is at home
with my mother
- What is your brother's name?
- Ziad
- Ziad?
- Yes
Ziad
- What is your sister's name?
- I do not have a sister
- Who was with you in the car?
- No one
- Are you alone?
- Yes
Are you alone?
Is no one with you at all?
No
I am here without mom
Without dad and without a brother
There is no one except me and Sarah
- Sarah? Where is Sarah?
- Sarah is next to me
Is Sarah with you right now?
Who is Sarah?
Yes
My dear Hanood
Sarah spoke to the uncle first, right?
- The person who talked to you before
- No
Can Sarah talk?
Yes
Is Sarah injured?
Is there blood on her?
Yes, there is blood on her
Is she right next to you
or in the front seat?
- What?
- Is Sarah next to you now?
Yes
Can Sarah talk? Talk to her
Can she talk?
But Sarah is sleeping
- Sarah is sleeping?
- Yes
Someone is calling me
Hanood?
It is her uncle, he is calling me
Give me the headset, I will talk
You have to hang in there
What else can we do?
We are in a state of war
We have taken...
- Mahdi
- We are in a state of war
You have to be patient a little
Do not even ask me
if I have made any progress
I will tell you as soon
as I get an answer, okay?
Okay, drop the subject
- Yes?
- Enough
Go back to your desk
There is no other way
- Go back to your desk
- Yes, yes
Go back to your desk
I have not left this office for two months
I have not gone home
and I have not seen my children
And you cannot hold on for 24 hours
We are trying to send an ambulance
Yes, we are trying
to send an ambulance
I want to ask you
Who is Sarah?
Okay, do you have a photo of her?
Okay
Okay, I will stay in touch with you
Thank you
What did he say?
He said a family member spoke
with Lian and Hind on the phone before me
Everyone was martyred
except Lian and Hind
- Who is Lian?
- The girl I spoke to on the phone
She is Hind's cousin
In the car are her uncle, his wife
and their four children
There is no one left but me
Are you the only one awake?
No one else is moving
and blood is covering them all?
Yes, blood is covering them all
Please do not leave me
If I am not mistaken
in the car, there are...
Your uncle, his wife
and their four children, right?
They are sleeping
- So, they are with you?
- Yes
Hanood, let them sleep, okay?
Do we not say at home...
we should not make noise
while others are sleeping?
Let them sleep so they can rest
The trip must have worn them out
The girl is stuck in the car
with six corpses
Can you call the Red Cross
and tell them that?
Mahdi, she thinks they are sleeping
It is true they were shot
It is true they are bleeding
but they look very comfortable
because they are sleeping
Let us agree they are sleeping, okay?
I said they are dead
They are all dead
- What did you say, my dear?
- They are dead
They are dead?
Yes
They are dead
They are all dead
My whole family
They all died
My whole family, they are all dead
Send the rescuers
What is your problem?
What will happen? Call them
They only need eight minutes to save her
Without coordination those eight minutes
can cost them their lives, Omar
Mahdi, these men are highly skilled
They have saved many lives
Please, call them
This isn't their first mission
Omar, you are going to be
the death of me
- "Humanitarian Martyrs"
- Do you see all these people?
Take a good look
Do you see them?
This one had two children
And this one had four
Three girls and one boy
She had just gotten engaged
I knew these people, they had
ambitions, dreams lives and families
Just like us
They were bombed
We lost them all
They were the best paramedics here
I promised myself that if another
photo goes up on this wall
I will resign
Omar, we need to secure
a safe route for them
approved by the army
so they can carry out the rescue
How can you coordinate with the army that
killed your colleagues and all these people?
Are you kidding me?
You know I never coordinate directly
with the army
We coordinate with the Red Cross
and with the Ministry of Health
here in the West Bank
- How did they attack you?
- They shot at us
Are they targeting you from houses
or while walking or from an aircraft?
- No, from the tank
- They shot at you from the tank
Yes
What do you like?
How were you at school?
I was at the top of my class
- Do you have water in the car?
- No
- Do you have food?
I do not have anything
Talk to her about something else
What grade are you in?
- Tell me, Hanood
- I am in the Butterfly Class
- Yes?
Are you in preschool?
- Right, Hanood?
- I cannot hear you
- I'm asking you, are you in preschool?
- Yes
At which school?
What is your school's name?
Esaad Al-Tufoula
- Esaad Al-Tufoula?
- Yes
Are you a good student?
What is your favorite color?
- I do not like anything now
- What is your favorite color?
I do not like anything
- What color are your clothes?
- I cannot hear you well
I can hear you
I can hear you, speak
Give it to me, it is easier for her
to talk to me, let me speak to her
- Wait a bit Hanood, wait
- I am all alone
You are alone?
I know you are alone
But remember, our Lord
Glory be to Him is with us
- Stay with me
- I am with you
I am with you, my dear
I will stay with you
until someone comes for you
- I will not leave you alone
- Stay with me until someone comes...
- What?
- Don't go before someone comes
No, I will stay with you
I will stay with you
even if the army comes, God forbid
Stay on the line
I will stay with you
Okay
- Hanood, my dear
- Yes?
I want to talk to you, okay?
But I want to ask you something
I want you to look out the window
of course only if you are able to
If you cannot and you are hiding
stay where you are, okay?
Now...
Can you see what is around you
from the window?
- They are shooting next to me
- What did you say, sweetheart?
They are shooting at me
They are shooting at her
Mahdi
Alright, tell me
what do you like?
Please, come get me out of here
I am scared
- Let us pray to God
- Oh, God
- Lord, protect us
Shall we recite a verse
from the Quran together?
Okay
How about we recite some
Qur'an and supplications?
- Alright
- Okay
In the name of Allah
the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful
All praise is to Allah
Lord of all the worlds
The Most Gracious, the Most Merciful
Master of the Day of Judgment
You alone we worship
and You alone we ask for help
Guide us along the straight path
The path of those You have blessed
Not the path of those
who have incurred Your wrath
Nor of those who have gone astray
- Amen
The Almighty has spoken the truth
Well done, you have it memorized
Can you come get me
out of here, please?
Okay, don't cry
Shall we continue with prayers?
The tank is right next to me
- Where is the tank?
- It's right next to me
- Is the tank near you?
- Yes
Is it moving or standing still?
Did anyone get out of it?
It's moving
- It's moving?
- Yes
Is it moving next to the car...
or is it coming from behind the car
or from in front?
It's in front of the car
- Is it coming towards you from the front?
- Yes
- Is it very close?
- Yes, very close
- Is it moving?
- I told you the tank is next to me
Please, I'm scared
Get me out of here
Hanood
The line is breaking up
I'm calling her again
No, please you have to do something
you have to push them
I know, I know, I...
Waiting for the green light
to send the rescuers
- We will keep you updated
- Please, please
They are coming
- Very close
- And is it moving?
I told you the tanks are right next to me
Please, I'm scared
Very scared
- And is it moving?
- I told you the tanks are next to me
Please, I'm scared
Very scared
What happened?
I'm trying to call her again
How much time has passed?
Sixty minutes have passed
since we spoke to her
All we need is eight minutes to save her
Excuse me...
A man named Mohammad Hamada
is calling nonstop
He wants to speak to the head of
coordination, I transferred him to line two
Talk to him, he's her uncle
Hello?
It's not allowed
I know this is taking longer than it should
Because our ambulance needs
eight minutes to reach the girl
We first need to communicate
with the Red Cross
- In Geneva?
- No, not in Geneva
They have an office in Jerusalem
and the Red Cross will contact COGAT
COGAT is...
It's a military unit at the Israeli
Ministry of Defense
The Occupied Territories
Activities Coordination Unit
No, not the military unit in Gaza
but another coordination unit
The military unit at the specific location
sends the route our ambulance
can take without being targeted
but it doesn't send it to us directly
It goes to COGAT
and COGAT passes it to the Red Cross
and the Red Cross sends it to us
Receiving the route map, however
doesn't mean we have the green light
to dispatch the ambulance
Because approval is
an entirely separate stage
I am obligated to follow all procedures
and follow instructions
because if we make a mistake
or cross any line
our ambulances might be targeted
And we would be accused of violations
I understand that
I understand that an ambulance
can go anywhere in the world
but what can we do?
Our only option is to go
from house to house
Yes, between the walls
Picture yourself as Spider-Man
It's a forty-minute
to an hour walk, give or take
- Always be sure to...
- Thank you, Madhoun
Don't move a muscle, Madhoun
stay put until I say so, those are orders
- What do you think you're doing?
- What are you doing?
- Why would you do that?
- Do what?
Those men could save a million souls
why are you throwing a wrench in the works?
Because I'm just following orders
why are you making a scene?
How can you even ask me that?
These men are heroes
you think they're cut from the same cloth?
Hiding like scared rats behind desks?
- Am I a coward?
- To heck with the green light you awaited
and to heck with your coordination
- This is genocide, plain and simple
- What? People are dying
- People are dying
- And you're too sensitive for your own good
You know, people like you are the reason
we're still under occupation
No, no, no...
No, no, she didn't die
She's alive
Nisreen, could you come here, please?
Let's step outside for a minute
let's go get some fresh air
I couldn't save her, Nisreen!
I couldn't do it
I feel you, I really do
Let's have some water
Drink some water
Just breathe
Look at me, look right at me
You did everything in your power
Breathe
Rana, Rana
You did everything you could
Come on, let's go outside
to get some fresh air, come on
Come with me, my dear
- Give me a cigarette
- It's not allowed
Hello?
Yes
Not yet
Thank you for calling me, but...
This is no longer necessary
We lost the girl
Rana
Come here, sweetheart
I was on the phone
with a woman in labor
The poor woman
was trapped alone in her house
under siege, with no one by her side
except her little sister
She was only ten years old
So I got a doctor on the line
and he stayed on the phone with them
He guided the little girl through every step
and I stayed on the line with them
for five long hours
until the baby was born
And the moment
I heard that cry, Nisreen
Not only I felt I mattered...
I can't explain how I felt
I put on a full face of makeup
What was I thinking?
"Can you send me
her mother's number?"
Hello?
- Are you Hind's mother?
- Yes, I am
I'm calling from the Red Crescent
Can I ask you something?
Just listen to me for a moment
One question, you're shouting
will you please just listen?
I need to ask you, when...?
When was the last time
you spoke to Hind?
Just now?
Right before I called you?
Alright, goodbye, goodbye
- Come quick, she's still alive
- What?
- She's still alive
- Hello?
- Hello, Hanood
They are shooting at me
- Hello?
- Get me out of here
- Don't hang up, stay with me
- Give it to me
Here, take it, talk to her
- Hello?
- Hey, Vanessa, how are you?
The girl is still alive
I'm glad to hear that but unfortunately....
No, please
re-establish coordination, please
- Did she apologize? Why?
- But why?
It's getting dark
- What is it?
- It's getting dark, I'm scared
Can you speak up a little?
It is getting...
I know all of Gaza needs help
- Call the army back
- Omar
- Please, Mahdi, let me speak to her, please
- Stop it
Hello, no, no, no...
Listen, listen, listen
they're shooting at a car
with a little girl inside
surrounded by dead bodies
Can you imagine that?
Who talks to these people?
You do, huh?
So do something
Damn you! Damn you!
- Don't say a word
- Omar
- I'm starting to lose my grip
Omar
What is going on?
The Red Cross refuses
to coordinate again
So what's the holdup?
Talk to the Ministry of Health
they have resources too
Hello, Doctor
this is Mahdi from the Red Crescent
Could I please ask for your help...
to coordinate safe passage
for our team to reach the girl?
The girl is in the car, surrounded
by her family's bodies, and...
There are tanks and shelling
all around her
You know this area is under siege
We need to coordinate
Thank you, Doctor, thank you
I'll await your call
I'll send all the details
Our team is standing by
- Thank you
- What did he say?
- What, are we starting over?
- What?
- Back to square one, we're at it again
- Okay
- Can you hear me?
- Yes, my dear, I can
- They're shooting at me
- I can hear the gunfire
Come get me out of here
- Please
- My dear...
I'm all alone!
I swear, sweetheart
I'd be there if I could
Ask your husband to bring you to me
Ask my husband to take me there?
Yes
My husband is at work, my dear
He can't take me there
- Call him
- Should I call him?
- Yes
- Okay
I'll call him and ask him
to come get me out of here
- Any progress?
- We're in touch with the ministry
- No progress yet
- We're waiting
Dear, my husband is very far away
It'll take us time to reach you
We live in a very far place
- What time is it now?
- What?
What time is it?
I'm telling you it's getting dark
You were saying that
darkness is falling, right?
But there's still a little light left
We still have some time
I've called everyone I can think of
I even spoke to an ambassador
I need your help
I need the number of someone
with real pull, someone at the top
I know the offices are closed
I don't want an office number
I need a personal line
I understand, ma'am
I swear I do, in fact...
I understand perfectly
Alright, ma'am
Believe me, my colleague is trying
to talk to her and keep her calm
But how can she...?
It's the girl's mother, talk to her
I can't take it anymore
Hello?
Is your son with you?
Thank God, thank God, we hope
we could bring Hind back to you
so you can be a family again
God willing
It's dark now, please come
Don't leave me alone, please
You need to calm down, Rana
You have to keep your cool
so she can stay calm too
- Get me out of here
- I'll send someone for you, my dear
but I can't come myself
Come
I swear I want to take you
but it's not my call to make
But, as I told you before
we're coordinating
and we hope to pull it off
What is that?
- What is coordination?
- Yes
- Tell her it's like a big family
- Hanood
Didn't I tell you
that in the Red Crescent
we're all brothers and sisters?
We have a father
and the soldiers in the tanks
they have a father too
So our father has to talk to their father
so we can send our brother
to rescue you
without them opening fire on him
But they're shooting right now
They're shooting now?
Yes, I know that
I can hear the bullets
Call someone to come
and get me out of here
Call someone, call my uncles
Ask them to come get me out of here
Who do you want to come for you?
- Hanood?
- Please, Nisreen
Listen, give the recordings
to Layla to post online
we need to get them out
on social media
and to the press
Of course, of course
Come with me
and catch your breath
Quickly, Layla
I need to call the girl back
Is there another headset?
- The headset is fine, it's working
- It's not working
I think, I think the phone
is out of her reach
- Let me talk to her
- No
- Nisreen, let me talk to her
- I want to talk to her
- Let me speak to her, Nisreen
- You'll break it, give it to me
- No, no
- No, Rana!
- Step away from here
- That's enough, Nisreen
- You can't talk to her like that
The girl is under enough pressure
and you're adding fuel to the fire
I don't need to calm down
- what we need is to save her
- It is necessary
No, it's not necessary, enough
I wish I would die
- Rana, take a deep breath
- I want you...
- Why are you screaming, my dear?
- Focus
What's is going on?
I was hit in my eye
- Your eye?
- Yes, my eye
Hanood
- Hanood
- Yes?
- I was hit in the eye
Hanood, my dear, my sweet girl
Talk to me slowly, my dear
so I can hear you
Don't hang up, stick with me
Okay
- My dear
- Take it easy
My dear, I need to ask you something
Does your eye hurt?
They shot at me
and hit me in the eye
What's the matter?
Your voice isn't clear
So please speak calmly to me, Hanood
- So I can hear you
- My eye hurts
I can't hear what's your name
My name is Omar, and you?
Don't forget the English subtitles
- Yes, of course
- My name is Hanood
- They're shooting
- Hide under the seats
I'm scared
They're shooting at me
I'm so scared
- She's scared, she says she's scared
- Hanood
I've been hit
Who was hit?
- Hanood
- Come take me
Did she say she was hit?
- She was shot
The girl is bleeding, she was shot
- Do something, please
- Post it, post it quickly
and mention that
she's injured and bleeding
Yes, that's a stroke of genius
Don't forget to write in English
She's bleeding...
She's injured
What? Really? You don't say
Check out the social media
Look, look, look here
There are children torn to pieces
lying by the roadsides
Do you think the voice
of a frightened child...
will move the needle
or mean anything to anyone?
She needs an ambulance
An ambulance
Please, Omar, we are all
at the end of our rope
Please
Yes, Hanood, my dear
- Were you injured?
- Please put it on speaker
Come take me
Hanood?
I called Mom to send me a doctor
A doctor?
You want a doctor?
Yes, we need a doctor
to get us out of here
My dear, I spoke to the doctor
to get you out of there
But I need you to stay put
where you are, okay?
- She is injured
- She doesn't sound injured to me
I think the blood on her
is from the bodies in the car
Hanood
Do you know the way home?
- Omar
- I know where the house is, I know
What?
I know where the house is
come take me
Don't move, stay put my dear
Stay inside the car
I cannot...
What did you say, my dear?
I cannot get out
Come rescue me
They are all around you, if you step out
who knows what might happen?
The line went dead
Get up, Omar
Hello?
Doctor, any updates?
Is this a call from the Ministry of Health?
Yes, yes
I spoke to the ambassador
I know the protocol, authorizing
one intermediary at a time
but that conversation was not official
The girl is injured and bleeding
and we are at our wits' end
Did we get the green light?
- But...
- Hand me the phone
Hand it to me
Hello, doctor
Doctor, it seems the coordination
will take all night
So, let me suggest a better idea
Can you contact the army?
Tell them a girl needs help
they should go and rescue her
All they have to do is go
and get the girl out
Let them take some photos
for their propaganda machine
and let the girl live
She knows the way home
I swear, if I were an Israeli soldier
I would have done the same thing
I don't know what world you're living in
Do you think they don't know
she's in the car?
You know their tanks
have infrared sensors
Thermal imaging doesn't show
the bodies of the dead
But she appears as a bright red figure
That is, if they can't hear her too
There is no sound
- There's no sound
- No
Wait
- She's breathing, she can hear you
- Okay
Okay
Do you know that I tried
to contact you...
over the phone...
because I wanted to check on you?
But Mr. Omar spoke to you himself
By the way, Mr. Omar
always beats me to the punch
He's always on the ball
Did we lose her?
Yes, it would be more convenient
for you this way, right?
Shut your mouth
Hanood?
Do you know that when I have a daughter
I will name her Hanood?
Talk to me if you can hear me
- She can hear you
- Hanood, did you mute yourself?
- Move
- What do you want?
What are you hiding?
Move! Move away!
- Turn on the laptop
- I don't want to turn it on
- Move away from the laptop
- I won't move and I won't turn it on
Mind your own business, come on
Hello?
Hello, doctor
Yes, I received it
Thank you, thank you
Turn on the laptop and move
- Enough, Omar!
- Move!
- I don't want to move
- No, you will move
- I won't move, I won't move
- You will move
- So turn on the laptop
- I don't want to
What are you hiding from us?
Turn on the laptop, please
Finally
- Please call the paramedics
- No, the girl isn't speaking at all
The girl is still alive
She was bleeding
and now she isn't speaking
Everyone, the girl can hear us
but we've made her many promises
that she no longer
believes what we say
She is breathing and is still alive
Please, talk to them
Even if she's alive
I can't send paramedics
- I need to get the green light
- Okay, I'll show you the green light
- Give me the phone, give it to me
- Don't interfere, it's not your concern
- I don't want to...
- Give me the phone, Mahdi
I won't give you the phone
What will you do?
- I want to speak to them
- Lower your hand
- Give me the phone
- Lower your hand, step back!
Didn't I tell you my brothers
and sisters at the Red Crescent...
are coordinating things?
- Come on
- We're doing everything we can
- Calm down
- We need to coordinate to reach you
Rana?
Rana, my dear, let me talk to her
Let me talk to her
Let me try, it's okay
Take a break
Give me the phone
Okay
I know your spirit is strong
A fighting spirit
that loves life
I want you to take a breath
Take a very deep breath
Picture yourself...
smelling a rose
We smelled the rose
We hold our breath...
Hold our breath in
Now we've held our breath
Then, we will imagine ourselves
blowing out a candle
Just like that...
we will inhale...
and exhale
Inhale
Exhale
Take a very deep breath
As I told you, we'll take a breath...
Smell the rose
Then blow out the candle
Close your eyes
Remember the sea
Remember the sun's reflection
on the sea's surface
Remember yourself
How you used to swim
at the beach
and how you used to play
by the water and sand
Remember that
Close your eyes for a moment
and imagine that, my dear
Think of Gaza's beach
Gaza's sand
The beauty and softness of the sand
The comfort one feels
when walking on sand
Walking barefoot on the sand
Hello?
- Yes, my dear?
- It's her, it's her
Yes, Hanood
I hear you, my dear
- Hanood?
- Hello
Yes
Yes, Hanood
- Who is speaking?
- It's me, Nisreen, my dear
I am Rana's sister
I am Nisreen
Tell them to come, tell them
What did you say, Hanood?
Save me
Okay, I'm right here
with you on the line
until you see a member
of the Red Crescent team, okay?
We will save you, my dear
- Do you hear me, my dear?
- Okay
Hello, Doctor?
We are still talking to the girl
and she is begging us
Any updates on getting the green light?
Come get me out of here
I am so happy
to hear your voice, my dear
What?
We are still awaiting the green light
Why don't they send everything at once?
What do you want me to do?
Do I make the rules?
I don't
I've told you time and again
no ambulances move without a green light
Mahdi, the girl's mother
is screaming over the phone
- Should I take the call?
- Mahdi, we must save her, please
We've been telling her for three hours
we needed eight minutes to save her
- Come on, get it done
- Mahdi
- Please, hand me the phone
- Enough, enough now
- I'll talk to them, give me my phone
- That's enough, take the phone
Give me my phone, Mahdi
I'm chasing you like a child, come on
Mahdi
I won't budge an inch
without the green light
Give me the phone, please
Mahdi
Come on, Mahdi
Join me in the game
Great
Excellent
Come on, get me out quickly
We will come to you
We are coming quickly, sweetheart
Come and save me
Okay, sweetheart
Okay, okay, my dear
Just like I promised
Please, I'm dying
My dear
You are fine, you are alive
You're breathing and talking to me
I am dying
it feels like I'm dying
- Rana, Rana
- Rana
Rana
Are you okay?
You are okay
- Rana
- Breathe, breathe
Come on, alright
- Wait...
- Please, hand me the phone
Okay, okay
We got the green light
We got the green light, Mahdi
Hind, Hanood
- Yes?
- We're coming to take you
Yes, Zaino, I hear you
Alright, dear...
I'm at street...
Gamal Abdel Nasser Street
that's correct
Then turn left
- Now, as soon as they move...
- You'll get the girl out in minutes
- You got this
- Okay, ma'am, ma'am
- Pay close attention
- The ambulance has departed
I'm putting you on speaker
she can hear you
Um Hind, she can hear you
and you can talk to her
- Hind?
- Yes
I love you, I love you
Our thoughts are with you
You are alright, aren't you?
- Yes
- Stay safe, dear
Okay
Alright, stay where you are
It will be over soon, dear
They are on their way, darling
We're on our way
We're on the way to you
We're almost there, it's almost over
There's not much left
They will be there shortly
- Okay?
- Yes
I lost the connection
What happened?
Mahdi, they're not moving
He stopped
There's no signal
The network is down
Call anyone, I don't know
- Call Madhoun instead of Zaino
- I am calling
Hello, you cannot reach...
Madhoun is also not answering
The network is down
- Could it be...?
- No, no
Zaino, why aren't you moving?
Okay, stay put, don't move
until I get back to you, understood?
Okay, okay
Wait for news from me, brother
- What did he say?
- The road is blocked
A bombed-out building
collapsed onto the road
- A change of course is necessary
- So they are here
Do you think the city resembles this map
The city has become featureless
This map is old and the city
doesn't look like this
- Hanood, my dear
- Yes?
We are on our way
and need some time
We need 10 minutes
but because the road...
- Hello, Doctor
- is rugged
The road is extremely rugged
Doctor, the ambulance is stuck
at the Dahshan and Al Senaa intersection
There's no street left
The guys...
We have to change the route
- Hello, Doctor, yes
- Hopefully
Hanood, Hanood
No, they are waiting for instructions
from the army and will not move
- Yes?
- Don't end the call
Yes, I can hear you
Don't end the call
Honey, sweetheart
Zaino?
Listen, there's been a slight
change in the route
Yes, yes, it is from the army
Turn left five meters
from your current position
That's enough, no more than five meters
Stop there
Then turn left and you will return
to the original route
Thank God, here they are
- Here we go
- Hanood, dear
The car will arrive in one minute
but it's moving very slowly
- That's the best news from Mr. Omar
- What?
We are in a tight spot
but we'll head...
I'm on this street
and I'm going to turn right
Hanood
You mean the Arab League street, right?
- Correct
- Turn right, turn right
400 or 500 meters at most
Um Hind, Um Hind
They are behind her
At a distance of half a kilometer
or 400 meters, they will reach her
Hanood, don't worry
They will be there shortly
Did they point a green light at you?
- Wonderful, they recognized you
- Thank God
Are you coordinating on security?
Safety comes from God, my dear
yes, we're coordinating
- What did you say?
- No, we're talking to the family
There's coordination, Um Hind, we've been
trying to achieve this for three hours
- Don't worry, my dear
- It is Fares Station, right?
Yes, Fares Station
Where are you now?
We are nearly there
We're next to the Station
The girl is there, right?
The girl inside the car
that was under gunfire
My dear, do you hear the sound
of an ambulance? They've arrived
Should I go down
to check on her or no?
Stay on the line
Can you see the car?
No, I cannot see anything
Are the sirens and lights on?
The sirens...
either the lights or the sirens
There she is
Hello?
Hello, you cannot reach
the requested number at the moment
- The guys are gone, it's over
- No, no
No, no
Please, try calling them back
the connection was simply lost
Ask her if she heard gunfire
Did you hear the sound
of gunfire, Hind?
Is there gunfire near you?
Yes
Don't be afraid
Was there a sound of gunfire or not?
She says there is
I feel like she's saying yes by default
Please, make sure of it
- This information is extremely important
- Were there gunshots?
- Yes
- My dear Hind, Hind
- Don't be afraid
- My dear, Omar is speaking
- Hello
- My dear Hind, Hanood
- Yes?
Alright, try to focus a bit
like you did this morning
- Yes
- Okay, come on
Just now, did you hear the sound
of gunfire just like this morning?
- Yes
- Are you sure?
Yes
Were there gunshots?
She said she heard
Did she hear the sound of gunfire?
Yes, she did
Ask her if anyone has reached her
I would like to ask you, Um Hind
Ask...
Ask Hanood
Did any of the guys reach her?
- Has anyone reached you?
- No
- Didn't anyone approach you?
Oh, don't be afraid, my dear
My daughter...
Don't worry, my dear
- Did anyone speak to you?
- No
Has anyone spoken to you?
- It seems to us...
- They are close, very close
The ambulance is very close to her
- But it seems they didn't give them...
- The connection is lost
They are waiting for approval to move in
but they are around the corner near her
We see them on the laptop
But we are trying to get
back in touch with them
- The connection...
- The number you are calling...
God willing, in a minute or two...
- She will see them, God willing
- God willing
Any updates, Doctor?
The girl is still waiting
They are very close
and have become at...
League of Arab States Street
I hope we make it
Don't worry, don't worry
It's almost over
It's almost over but she must
follow Mr. Omar's advice
- Hide between the seats
- Hide between the seats, lower your head
Lower your head
She's a good girl and she knows it
My dear daughter
My beloved daughter
My sweet daughter
From that moment on
all contact with Hind was lost
Every day...
I would go to the Baptist hospital
and wait anxiously for my daughter
I was absolutely certain
that my daughter was alive in the car
accompanied by the paramedics
or perhaps the army took her
They didn't tell me just one story
but countless others
I used to say that my daughter
was alive and well
"Ahmed Madhoun"
"Youssef Zaino"
"Hamada Family"
Hind loved going to the beach
She thought of it as her companion
She used to say, I hope the war ends
so we can go to the beach
I don't need anything
just take me to play in the sand