- ...we're gonna try--
- Be quiet. Be quiet.
Clear.
Slim.
It's about time.
Wow, wow, wow!
You play,
we'll be back in one hour.
Then we can talk about how
to deal with your old partner.
-Make it 3.
- Mm-hmm.
And I want you guys
throwing away good money.
Ladies.
Come on.
Go, go!
Wait!
Leave!
Who the fuck are you?
Who sent you?
Look, look, look, look!
Whatever it is.
Whatever you want,
just name it.
And it's yours.
And whatever
they're paying you,
I'll double it.
No, no, no, no, no!
I'll go triple.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
The man is an artist.
He Basquiat with the 45.
Bang, just ain't put that
brother in the ground.
He seizes, he captures
and contests mortality.
Talent like this.
You don't learn it.
It's gifted to you.
It's a gift.
Fucking beautiful.
Christ!
Shit, you see that?
You believe that?
Wow!
Check it out, boss.
That's a fucking finale.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait!
Yikes.
Très beautiful, Bang.
Très beautiful.
Um.
See?
Tsk!
Good work, Bang.
Bang!
Dinner tomorrow night.
What do you say?
20 acres, baby backs.
My treat.
I'm free.
Great.
Excuse me, do you work here?
Hey, baby!
I missed you.
Let's get out of here.
I'll be over later.
Oh, can't wait.
Yes, it can't. Or can it?
Where is April?
Is she live right now?
Okay.
April! What the fuck?
Oh, hey, Bang!
How's it going, man?
You-- you're good?
Sorry, Simon!
Come on man, she's live!
Two here!
Ah, my two favorite customers.
How're you doing tonight,
April?
Real good.
-There is a line!
-Regular?
- Sorry.
- You know it?
Get me out of the rain.
We've got some celebrating
to do, Bang.
Champagne, please.
DJ is getting married.
Is that so?
Ya, tell him.
Next month, Jasmin's father's
got a little place
down by the beach.
And just some family and--
Jesus! Dad!
Shut the door.
Shut the fucking door.
No!
Fuck!
What am I gonna do, huh?
You tell me, what am I--
What am I gonna do?
He's been talking for a month
that he's gonna get married,
go to a beach and retire.
Who retires?
You don't retire.
It was Emperor Nero said
to the famous philosopher,
Seneca, his teacher.
When Seneca wanted to retire,
"Hey, Seneca,
you want to retire?
I've got a good idea."
"Go kill yourself!"
Retire.
What happens if he's cooking
burgers with some friends,
all of a sudden,
mouth's soft, gets drunk.
Somebody says, "what did you do
in your past life?"
Huh?
What's done is done.
Be a prince and clean
this up will ya?
Thank you.
Good evening, sir.
Anything you'd like?
What time do you get off?
Midnight.
12:30.
My place.
Take one of those fat
Dominicans for yourself.
I don't smoke.
Oh, I know.
You're a nasty boy.
Yeah, so what?
Let me help you with that.
Go, go, go!
He's lost a lot of blood.
Pressure's forty and holding.
Intubate him, get an X-rays
to see what the fragments are.
Get OR to get a room prepped.
Taylor.
Taylor, more gauze.
More gauze. Control
the flow. Control the flow.
Hey, who's in charge here?
Um, of what department?
The whole fucking hospital,
who makes all the decisions?
Excuse me,
you can't just barge.
Dr. Kristine.
You know who I am?
Yes.
I've got a friend of mine
in this hospital,
very good friend
in your operating room.
I'm sure we're doing
everything possible.
He's been shot.
A lot.
Uh, I'm sorry.
You will be if he doesn't live.
You understand what I'm saying.
Good.
More gauze. Perfect.
Stand-by.
Gauze.
Alright. Where we're at?
How're you feeling?
It hurts.
Well, that's normal.
One second.
My name is Dr. Kristine.
I'll be taking care of you
during your post-op.
Good.
How come I'm not dead?
Managed to find a working heart
from the L Graft.
Organ donor.
And implanted it.
Um.
Just had one lying around, huh?
It was an accident same time
you came in.
A young couple were coming here
to deliver a baby.
Mother and baby made it.
Husband was killed
and now you have his heart.
What was his name?
I'm sorry, that's...
strictly confidential.
Cute kid.
Is that your son?
Yes,
Mrs. Delaney is in room 324.
You can send flowers to her
address, care of that room.
Thanks.
Daniel?
Daniel.
Daniel!
Well, five weeks on your back,
there's a joke there
but I'm too classy to say it.
-How's the engine running?
-Fine.
Well, I'm not too classy to say
that April would be
a good judge of that.
But before you go play
spin the bottle,
I got a quick stop to make.
Quick stop.
Quick.
Okay?
Let's go.
-Alright, Pop?
-Yeah.
Gonna take one...
One minute.
-Surprise!
-Yay!
-Welcome back!
Woah, woah, woah!
Take it--
take it slow!
Take it slow!
He's still in a testing state.
We got a surprise for you, Bang.
Reveal!
1, 2, 3! Open it up!
Ta-dah!
-Woo!
-Ta-dah!
You treated me with respect.
As long as I'm alive.
You and your family
will be taken care of.
You recognize that, schifoso?
That's the succhia cazzi
tried to do you, Bang.
I told you I'll get him.
And I did.
What do you think?
I only got two words.
Batter up!
Maybe later.
Maybe later, yeah.
Ok, Chad. You're up.
You're okay? What's up?
Funny.
Funny. It's funny, okay?
Let's talk.
what's going on? You pissed off?
What's up?
I just had seven bullets
fished out of my chest.
I don't feel like playing
head hockey right now.
Fair enough.
I'll let Momo take you home.
B...
...I need you back on the horse.
-I got it.
-Good.
-Momo!
-Yes, sir.
Yeah? You like that?
You look tired.
I can get you something
and drop it off.
I'm good to go, man.
Thanks.
I don't understand
the e-mail you sent.
It says my balance
is paid in full.
That's right.
Your bill's been paid.
But how?
Being a heart donor
is a big deal.
Listen.
You have a healthy baby boy.
You don't owe
the hospital anything.
This is all a win.
Go! And enjoy your life.
Well, if it ain't
the invisible man,
Where the fuck have you been?
You're done.
Hah!
Wow, do you look terrible.
Maybe you could just use
a touch of this shit
around the eyes, huh?
I'm fine.
You know, you don't call.
You don't come around.
You don't spread no love.
What's up?
Wanna drink? Smoke?
No, I gave it up.
Gave it up?
Son, I've been around
long enough to realize
there's some shit about
which I'm just clueless.
But this one item
I do know about,
and it is this...
you go to the mountain top
to pray all you want,
but right here
in the physical world,
in the marketplace,
there's only one thing
that brings a man
out of his darkest hour.
And it ain't alcohol, drugs,
cigarettes, or sex.
It's work.
Work puts a man in action,
and the mind
is the rest in action.
Work is liberating. Rewarding.
I'll tell you something else.
Some people, very few,
are born with a gift,
and it ain't acquired.
People start playing piano
at 3 years old,
play it till the dirt nap
and they're not gonna be
a Mozart.
You've got that gift, Bang.
If the gift they don't used,
the gift they're gifted with,
they're gonna sleep, slow down,
and blown out off.
They're useless to themselves
and everybody else.
Yes.
Good.
Go to work.
Oh, God!
Bang, Bang, come on.
You don't have to do this, bro.
Come on, man.
Shit, baby.
This is divine, man.
I don't know
why I was worried about you.
Watch!
I've got a date.
- A date?
- Yeah.
Fair enough, goodie!
I'll see you Thursday.
I'll see you.
Thursday.
You guys need some help?
Oh, yeah.
We're looking for a piano
for apartment.
Uh huh.
Louis, can you help
this happy couple here
find what they're looking for?
Congrats on your new apartment.
-Great, thank you.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
You brought the cash?
It's all here.
Yeah.
We're all set?
All there.
This fucking place's all yours.
Good luck.
My key doesn't work.
I've changed the lock.
Why?
Cause I wanted to.
What the hell's wrong with you?
I'm good and I'm tired.
Hey!
I took a day off to spend
with you.
I could've been making bank.
What's this?
Go.
Bang!
I don't know what they did
to you in that hospital,
but your gears
ain't working right.
Hey!
Do I know you?
From the hospital.
Thank you.
It's the least I can do.
You didn't have to.
I wanted to thank you.
I'm just glad that some good...
Well, it's nice meeting you.
Hey!
I don't even know your name.
It's William.
William, um...
Well, we're heading to the park,
do you wanna come?
Yeah, I'd like that.
He sleeps about
4 hours a day, so.
It's not so bad.
What about you?
It's just me and Sam right now.
I can't really afford
any help, so.
Tell me about you.
What do you do?
Uh...
I sell antiques.
What?
You don't look like
you sell antiques.
Yeah.
It's a step above
ladies' shoes.
Trying to get out.
Of selling hand me downs?
Yeah.
Well, what do you wanna do?
I don't know, uh...
Got a second chance.
Seems wise I should use it.
Hey, why did you need
the transplant?
I had a bad heart.
Something I was born with.
It's that time again.
He needs to go down for a sleep.
You guys come here a lot?
Every day.
Well...
Maybe I'll see you around?
Okay.
Hey!
Sam has my husband's eyes,
but you've got
the best part of Daniel.
So, whatever you do just...
take care of it, okay?
I will.
Hey!
Sit, please!
Please.
Coffee, wine, what?
Nothing?
You look great.
Looks great, right?
Sleeping well?
Like a baby.
And April?
What about her?
I don't know, you getting
your pipes cleaned?
Yeah, it's all good.
Good.
Three words you don't
wanna hear from a wife.
And another thing...
The accountant?
Yeah.
Get it done.
You've got the gift, Bang.
If the gift they don't use,
the gift they're gifted with,
they're go to sleep, slow down,
and blown it off.
They're useless to themselves
and anybody else.
Yes.
B.
Johnny.
Where's your sugar daddy?
He's out.
Something different about you.
I noticed it.
BANG
Yeah.
But you notice
those kinds of things
about other men, huh?
Don't worry about it, Johnny.
I won't tell daddy.
Hey, fuck you, Bang.
Oh!
Chariya!
Johnny?
Oh, sorry!
I just wanna wash my hands.
I thought you're going
to the club this afternoon.
Yeah, I just wanna get changed.
Don't let me interrupt you.
Yeah, I got to the gym
late today.
Yeah, because you usually
shower there, right?
Sometimes.
Yeah.
Alright.
I'll see you later.
Bang!
Come here, come here, come here!
Have a seat.
Okay.
The work is top-notch.
Contract's getting fulfilled.
No heat, no blowback.
Complimenting.
Thank you.
Good.
I got something I don't think
you're gonna like.
Yeah?
Momo...
Has stepped way out of line.
I told my father,
this is my problem.
-I'll take care of it.
-You do nothing like that.
I said I can take
care of it, Pop.
I can handle this.
I--
You'll take care of it.
Good?
I want it done.
Yeah.
Good.
Come on, I walk you to your car.
I've got a skin scrub
in about an hour.
You like that one?
-It's good.
-Yeah?
Why don't you get me a drink?
Sure.
It skipped.
You can do better.
What?
How did you get so good
at skipping rocks?
I was a boy scout.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Hey,
I don't really know about you.
I mean, what do you think about
art and music?
I don't know, I just...
I like what I like and...
that's about it.
And what do you like?
There is a Dutch painter.
At the end of his life,
he painted, uh, the wheatfields.
And these demons hiding
in the trees
look like torches on fire.
Van Gogh?
Yeah, sometimes I feel like
I'm living in that place.
Hey, um...
Me and Sam are
having pasta tonight.
Maybe you wanna join us.
Sure.
Okay. Good.
I'm drenched.
You want showing off.
Hey.
Here, Sam.
Do you not like the balloon?
No? No? Okay.
Kay-kay! It's okay.
- Maybe he wants a rock.
Good.
Thank you.
Does it still hurt?
No.
Hey, Santa!
-Ho, ho, ho!
-Oh yeah, I did.
If I forgot something,
I'll have someone drop it by.
What are you doing?
Come on, Bang!
We've trouble before,
let's work it out.
It was different then.
Jesus Christ!
What the hell's got into you?
I know about you.
Yeah!
I know what you've been doing.
What have I been doing?
You're screwing that bitch
with the baby.
Take care, April.
You know what I think?
Good riddance.
I've seen them before
at the hospital.
-Hospital?
-Yeah.
The night Bang got hit.
Her and her husband were
in some kind of accident.
That's how we got his new heart.
Huh!
So, she thinks
there's a little piece
of her husband inside of him.
He's up to something.
I don't know what it is.
Remember how I told you
he threw all that stuff
in the garbage bag?
Yeah.
I found this in there.
Must be in that drawer
or something.
- A Venezia.
- Yeah.
Must be where he goes
and disappears
for days at a time.
What have you got?
Yeah?
Hey, it's Momo.
We've got a problem.
Bang.
How many jobs has he done
since he's been back?
Ten hits maybe, I don't know.
How about no hits?
Zero! Not a fucking one!
All the kills, he stashed them
in an abandoned development
2 hours out of town.
He faked every
fucking kill, Pop!
He faked them.
Every single one, look!
You like pictures?
Look at them pictures, huh?
Them fucking pictures, huh?
Them pictures!
I took these tonight!
That motherfucker's
been taking us for fool, Pop!
I knew I shouldn't have
trusted that son of a bitch!
I should have fucking put him
in the ground ages ago.
You let him
in the fucking family
and this is what he does.
That piece of shit!
Alright.
Go clean yourself up.
What is this?
Chicken blood.
Okay, wake up.
Was that good?
How does this end?
It's not the weight
that breaks a man's back.
It's how he carries it.
You know what we gotta do, Pop?
We gotta do this guy. Now.
He's part of it all.
All his hits.
People he's supposed to kill.
They're gonna be on their way,
the cops,
Interpol and the crews.
Done.
We're not done.
I'll take care of it.
Johnny.
I'm sorry.
Hey, can I come in?
So, when you say we're in
danger, what do you mean?
- Maybe I should call the cops.
- No!
You can't.
You don't sell antiques,
do you?
Listen, do you have somewhere
you can go?
- It's Christmas Eve.
- Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry.
For how long?
I don't know.
Here.
It's 50 grand.
You figure out
where you're going.
I arrange for you to get
some more, okay?
You should get packed.
It was for you.
I remember you telling me
about it in the park.
Wait!
Those men that are after you,
what are you gonna do to them?
Excuse me, can I help you?
Excuse me!
Get out!
They're coming.
Go out, go out!
-Everybody out!
-Don't stay here!
-Come on, we gotta go!
Let's go, let's go!
Quick, everybody!
-Move, move!
-Let's go, let's go!
Come on, come on! Let's go,
let's go! We don't have time!
- Let's go, let's go!
- Run, run, run!
Come on, out, out, out!
Come on, out!
Move, move, move!
We're here.
Okay, we're going to the bridge!
Going hard!
Fucking take them all out!
Johnny, what was that?
What the hell was that?
They knew we would be coming.
I'll call you later.
Bring it.
Ya! Put it there!
Well, what-- what are we--
look at here?
What is it?
- It's the live-feed, boss.
- Okay.
Fuck.
Alright, split into 2 groups!
I'm gonna double the salary
of whoever hills him.
Fuck.
Johnny.
He's still alive, Pop!
I want him dead.
Dead!
Or don't come back here.
I got this, Pop!
You understand me?
I want him dead!
Or you do not come home!
Don't kill me, Bang.
Please.
Say goodbye to your father.
What?
No, fuck! No, no, no, no!
Turn it off!
Don't let him see me like this.
Please, Bang!
Please!
Johnny...
Ah, fuck!
God, I'm so sorry, Dad!
I'm so sorry!
Yeah?
Help me out here, Bang cause'
I treated you like a second son.
I'm sorry about Johnny.
You're sorry you killed Johnny?
Well...
What the fuck?
Doesn't matter anyway.
Because I've got something
you want.
I've got something you want.
I got the girl.
And the kid.
That's right.
I got the girl.
And the kid.
Hey, you don't want her.
You want me.
So, listen to me,
you son of a bitch.
So, this is how
this is gonna go down.
We've gotta go. Come on.
He's on his way.
Sorry about this, April.
I was gonna give you
the honors but...
Now that that bastard
kills my only boy.
Whatever!
As long as I get the fuck up
this bitch, it's all good.
What about her, Boss?
Take her out to the carport,
toss her in the trunk
when April's done with her,
bury her in a landfill.
You said you'd let us go.
I lied.
Hey!
Goddammit!
What the hell is going on
out there?
He's inside the fucking grounds,
boss.
And he brought help.
And what the fuck are
you doing here? Go get him!
Please.
No, no, no!
Please, please, please, please.
Please, please.
Baby!
Bang.
Ah, that was sweet.
You fucking nutless gonad.
Man can't use the gift
he's gifted with,
then he's no use to himself
or anybody else.
I'm gonna cut that fucking
useless heart right out of you.
Ah...
I wouldn't...
You kill-- kill me.
You're okay! You're okay!
You're okay!
-You're alright.
-It's alright.
Where's my son?
-Bang's got him.
-Where's my son?
Bang's got him.
It's alright.
-Sam!
-Wait! Wait!