We're here!
What's up, y'all?
Welcome back.
Thank you
Thank you.
Ava!
You think he's too afraid
to talk to her this time?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa.
I'm not afraid.
Sure, whatever you say, bud.
What?
Ava?
Hi.
-Hi.
-How are you?
Oh my God!
- Hey, everybody!
- Hey, yo!
Who wants to beat my meat?
Yeah, y'all like that?
Oh my God.
This is so you guys.
What can I say?
How can I compete
with a dick that big?
Oho, how clever.
So clever, dude.
How did she not see
how clever you are?
I'm gonna go take a piss.
Did he say piss?
- Hey, Connor.
- Your big dick is so funny.
You're like exactly the kind
of guy I'm into.
Hey, Connor.
I'd sure like a turn at smashing
your nuts with a big stick.
Uh, hello?
Uh, are you another one
of Connor's surprises?
Are you here for the party?
What?
Did I get it?
What's going on?
Move.
Eric?
No, no, no.
No, no.
What are you doing?
Do something!
Help him!
What are you doing
just looking at him?
Do something!
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and ghouls, it's that time
of year again.
Halloween night is upon us,
a night filled
with thrills and chills.
I'm your host, DJ Jack,
and I'll be your guide through
the spine-tingling lineup
we've got prepared
for you tonight.
So light your candles,
grab your broomsticks,
and settle in, 'cause
we'll be spinning
these spooky vintage tunes
all night long.
Can I help you?
All right.
I want you to pick
a card for me?
Thank you.
So, um, how's--
how's your night going?
Oh, what's this?
Is it your card?
Dang it.
No, it's not.
Hi-ya, iya, iya, iya!
What you doin'?
What are you doing?
Looking for my nunchucks.
They're not in here.
Did you check your nightstand?
No.
Why do you look like that?
Uh, we're going
trick-or-treating.
- I'm going with Lindsey.
- Zoe, we're late.
- Oh.
- Let's go.
Zoe, wait.
Zoe.
Zoe, where's your bag?
Max, have you seen my keys?
I swear that I--
You going out?
Oh, I thought I was going
with you guys.
Oh, sweetie.
Don't you think you're getting
a little bit old?
I don't know.
You know, what if a boy
from school saw you in that?
What's wrong with it?
Mom, I'm ready.
Look, I have to take your
sister to go pick up her friend.
Why don't you just meet up
with some of your friends?
'Cause she doesn't have any.
Zoe.
Of course, where's your jacket?
Look, why don't you just...
Watch some scary movies
or something?
Okay?
I'll be back later.
Come on, Zoe.
Let's go.
Come on, Max.
Please.
Please I haven't done
anything.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I haven't done anything.
Please.
Help!
Good evening, ladies and gents.
I'm your humble host, DJ Jack,
and it seems
the Halloween festivities are
in full swing all over town.
Just a little friendly reminder
to all my ghouls and goblins
out there, stay safe out there,
friends.
You never know who among us
can be trusted.
If you're scared
of ghosts and ghoulies
♪ Bumpy, bumpy in the night ♪
Have you been helped yet?
Um...
I can come back
if you're still deciding.
Okay.
Do I know you?
You go to Westwood High?
Yeah.
Thought you looked familiar.
So what can I get for you?
Trig class.
What?
Nothing.
Sorry.
It's just we're in the same
trigonometry class.
Right.
You're the quiet girl
who always sat by herself.
-Max.
-Max. Right.
Like how old are you?
- 15.
- Damn.
A sophomore in a senior class?
Must be pretty smart.
I don't know.
This uh, this your costume?
Yeah.
I-- I made it myself.
Yeah. I could tell.
Can I get you anything?
Um,
a cheeseburger?
One cheeseburger for Magic Max.
Thanks.
I-- I made it myself.
Oh, I know this.
It's face up.
Here.
When you had me put the card
back, the deck was upside down
with only the top card
flipped over.
That way when you
spread them out,
my card is the only one face up.
It's really cool.
But normally, you do the flip
while holding the deck
behind your back.
That means you would have had
to do it really fast to flip
that top card back over.
And with gloves?
That's really good.
Sorry.
Um, can I show you one?
I'm Max, by the way.
It's called
the "Jumping Gemini".
Have you seen it before?
Uh, it's really just a lot
of sleight of hand
and memorization.
I've-- I've been practicing.
You're so stupid.
I mean, come on, what was
I supposed to do, fight him?
- Smash it,
- DISCO DUDE: Ew, look at this.
I want to see its guts.
Ugh, all right.
You being a little baby?
Whoa, that was sick.
I mean, come on,
where were you guys? Huh?
I mean, this costume isn't
doing you any favors.
-Hey, whoa.
-Get it, get him. Get him.
Hey, fuck, fuck you.
Oh, that was good.
Uh, okay, so is the house over
this way or...
do you guys know
where we're going?
Yo, touch him.
Touch him.
Don't mess with him.
Shh. Shut up.
- You won't.
- Let's see what we got here.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, God.
Christ.
- He's alive.
- Oh my goodness.
Sorry, dude, I, uh...
- Uh...
- Weird.
Hmm.
-Hi.
-Oh.
- Oh.
- What's up?
Happy Halloween.
Ooh, a magic trick.
- You pick one, you pick one.
- Oh.
Oh.
Let's see.
Hmm.
Pick a good one.
-All right.
-Okay, okay.
Let's see what you got.
Just woke up,
ready for a magic trick.
Should we give him a drum roll?
Dun-da-dun.
- No way.
- Moment of truth.
- Oh.
- Ooh. Not it.
-Yeah, you need some practice,
dude.
-That's not the one.
Yeah.
Are you a real magician?
Uhuh, yeah.
Uh-huh.
Second time's the charm, right?
All right.
-Nope.
-It wasn't it again.
I told you,
I told you guys he was drunk.
I told you.
I mean, he was asleep
on a bench.
- You're going for it again?
- Oh. Oh.
- I don't think this is how the--
- Okay.
Oh.
Uh, still not it.
Uh, maybe we should get going.
Uh, yeah, let's just go.
Come on.
Have a good night, sir.
Sorry for, uh, waking you up
or--
- Yeah.
- Whatever.
- What the hell?
- I have no clue what that was.
Come on.
That was very freaky.
He's a weirdo.
Where is this party?
Whoa!
- Jake, Jake.
- Jake! Jake!
- Oh my God! Jesus!
- Yeah. Oh my God!
Oh my God. Stop! Stop.
What are you doing?
I keep struggling with it.
I either drop the card
going into the front pocket
or put the wrong card in there.
I can't get it.
Goddamn thing.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah, it's just that,
I don't know--
- Whoop, I got it.
- I got it.
There she goes.
See?
Huh, so maybe I'm not filling
up as many balloons these days,
but dammit if that thing still
doesn't come in handy.
Mm, I'm sure it'll pick up
again.
Ah, that's okay.
No one ever said a magician
was a popular profession.
But it's an honest one.
A magician promises
to deceive you...
And then they do.
You can get the trick, Max.
The problem isn't the trick.
The problem is you thinking you
failed before you even started.
Okay.
What is it?
What's what?
I'm an illusionist, Max.
I am not a mentalist.
But I'm pretty sure
the bike tire
isn't the only reason
you came by.
Come on, kiddo.
What happened?
It's just some kids from school.
Yeah?
What was it this time?
Just the bike.
Just the bike, huh?
You know, I remember
when you made that costume.
You were very proud of the hat.
The hat which is now
suspiciously absent.
Was that them, too?
No.
That was me.
I just...
I don't know what I'm doing
wrong.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
I just don't fit in, and I
don't know what I'm doing wrong.
The things they do sometimes,
it just...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I feel so stupid.
Don't say that.
Don't.
What is this?
Tell me.
It's a magic wand.
It's a piece of wood.
Right?
I mean, who are we kidding?
It's a piece of wood.
No magic.
Nothing extraordinary.
I guess.
It's not until it's in the
hands of a magician
that it becomes something more.
Those kids from school,
in their hands,
this would just be
a piece of wood.
That's all they'd ever see.
But in your hands,
it can truly be magic,
because you, Max,
are extraordinary.
Now, let's get you out of those.
Well, where the hell
did I put it?
You're getting too good at that.
You know, I remember
teaching you sleight of hand.
I do not remember teaching
you to be a pickpocket.
Enjoy your night, kiddo.
Thanks. I will.
Be safe.
Oh.
Uh, I threw it away.
For what?
No.
No, thanks.
- Wait, wait.
- No, no.
No, please.
-No.
-Just give me a minute.
Just give me a minute.
What's up?
Thank you.
Hey, where are my flowers?
What? I'm just asking.
What the hell?
Stop!
Well, now I know why you drive
such a big truck.
Fuck off!
Please, please, please.
No.
Um, come on,
I think we forgot something.
How did you do that?
- Trick or treat.
- Be careful, Ethan.
Ethan, slow down.
No, I-- I don't know them.
Do I wanna go trick or treating?
Oh, I don't know.
I think I might be getting
too old.
Go trick or treating with you?
Well, hello.
Look at you two.
Trick or treat.
Okay.
Um, can I show you a card trick?
Go ahead, sweetheart.
Uh, okay.
Um, just tell me when to stop.
Stop.
Very good.
I think instead we need
to do trick and a treats.
You earned it.
That was so good.
Run.
One more street
and we'll go home, okay?
Is that cool?
All right.
Help me!
Please help, he's after me.
Sweetie, it's okay.
Slow down.
There's a man? Where?
Honey, it's gonna be okay.
Um, did someone attack you?
I-- I don't understand.
Hurry up, Dad!
Ethan, stop!
Look, sweetie, it's-- it's okay.
It's gonna be okay. Um--
Ah, Dad! Dad!
Ethan!
Oh, I told you to be careful.
Oh, let me see it.
Here, let me see it.
My arm!
What is this?
What is happening?
Am I dead?
Excuse me.
Hey!
We need to be able to talk.
We're never gonna get anywhere
if you can't tell me anything.
Here.
Please try.
Are you going to kill me?
Then what do you want from me?
Why?
You are...
No!
No, I am nothing like you.
I beg to differ.
Don't be afraid.
Pleasure to meet you.
W-- w-- who, who are you?
Simply an entertainer
misunderstood,
cast out like you,
until the day I was visited
and found...
my soul was to be collected
by the Great Deceiver.
I offered a deal,
my soul for a trick for him,
and my soul stays.
And you did?
That's it?
To cheat death, y--
you just do a trick?
Mmm, if only.
Unable to accept his defeat,
he failed to mention
a condition.
I must trick four souls
each Hallows' Eve
before sending them to him,
all before the candle burns out.
Only then will the offerings
be accepted.
So, y-- you have to perform
a trick on someone
before killing them.
T-- to four people
before the candle burns out?
Very astute, Max.
Is-- is that why you--
Was he one of the offerings?
Some are just for fun.
O-- okay.
But what do I have to do
with any of this?
Max, don't you see?
You tricked me.
Me,
the one who tricked
the Great Deceiver.
Me, the soul he desires most,
but cannot collect.
Me, the one who has sent him
more souls
than you will ever meet.
And you tricked me!
It is you who must perform
the tricks to the observer.
Only then will the offerings
be accepted.
I-- I-- I didn't know.
I-- I was just trying...
I'm sorry.
You are like me, Max, superior.
Consider the power you now have
over those
who have ridiculed you.
No, I-- I-- I can't.
Hmm, unfortunate.
Why?
Why unfortunate?
That's what happens to you
if you don't finish
before the candle goes out?
You inherit the task,
as well as the fate
and endless suffering
reserved especially for us,
far worse
than the simplicity of death.
Apologies.
No.
No, not them either.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
It's you.
What?
Come to tell me how much
of an asshole I am?
Hmm?
All right, fuck it.
Go ahead.
Been a shitty night
so far anyways,
so say whatever you gotta say.
Can I show you a magic trick?
Pick one.
About earlier, I uh,
just wanted to say, uh,
say sorry...
...for the bike.
It's fine.
You need to pick a card.
Okay.
Do I show it to you or--
No.
I don't even know why I did it,
you know?
Just trying to make those girls
laugh, I guess.
You can put the card back.
I just feel so fucking stupid!
Don't say that.
So what's next?
No, uh--
What's the rest of the trick?
No, it's okay.
I-- I don't--
No, come on. I wanna know
the rest of the trick.
Just-- just tell me what to do.
Nothing.
You don't have to.
Do--
do I just pull another card?
No!
Holy shit.
This actually was my card!
You're pretty fucking good
at that, you know?
No!
No, stop.
Please, I changed my mind.
Not him, okay?
Not him.
No!
Put those away.
Please!
Hey!
Are you fucking kidding me?
Please, let's just go.
We'll find someone else.
You ruined my night, asshole.
Now it's time to ruin yours.
What the...
What the fuck?
Ah, fuck!
Stop it!
I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
Do something!
No!
To all my freaky fans out
there listenin',
I hope you're enjoying
this All Hallows' Eve.
We've received several tips
here at the station tonight,
some hoaxes and some not.
A report that a woman was
fatally attacked in her home
has turned out to be true.
While there's no further
details at this time,
let's all take it as a reminder
to be cautious
and to keep
those front doors locked.
Stay safe out there, friends.
No.
Evenin'.
Whoa.
That's some intense makeup.
You two out havin'
a little fun tonight?
Have either of you seen anyone
out here recently, by chance?
We got several calls
for suspicious activity
and we were wondering
if you'd seen anything.
I know.
Unheard of on Halloween, right?
Either of you wouldn't happen
to have a cellphone on you,
would ya?
You don't have a phone.
Would you mind takin' off
the mask, please?
What about you, sweetheart?
Do you have a phone?
Hey, whoa.
Hands behind your back.
Run!
Stop!
On the ground or I will
fucking drop you!
On the ground now!
Help me!
Hey.
What's wrong?
Hey. Hey, it's okay.
Take it easy.
Are you uh, are you okay?
I need to get out of here
right now.
What for?
Where are you going?
There's-- there's a man
coming after me.
He kidnapped me.
The police came,
but I barely got away.
I don't know what to do.
-Someone kidnapped you?
-Yes.
Please, I need to get out
of here right now.
He'll find me.
Okay.
All right.
Get in.
Come on, I'll drive you
to the police station.
You'll be safe there and then
we can figure out what to do.
Okay?
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is DJ Jack
with an important update.
Earlier this evening, the body
of a 17-year-old boy was found
dead at Riverside Park.
-Due to the--
-Oh, thank you.
-Yep.
Concerning condition
of his body,
as well as the earlier
fatal attack on 41-year-old
Marissa Stevens
at her own front door,
local police are now
enforcing a mandatory curfew
for all residents.
You don't need to be hearing
that right now.
So what's your name?
Max.
It's a boy's name.
So, uh, how old are you, Max?
15.
Uh-huh.
Where's your mom and dad?
How much farther
to the police station.
Well, it's not far now.
Is that your Halloween costume?
Yeah.
What are you?
A magician.
A boy magician?
Hey, I just think that you
could've dressed more lady-like.
You already have a boy's name.
Why are we stopping?
Why didn't you want to dress
more like a lady?
You're old enough now.
I think that if you did, you
could look very, very pretty.
Hey, Max.
I'm not gonna hurt you, Max.
I promise.
I wouldn't want to hurt you.
So be it.
No.
No. No.
No! Help me!
Help me!
Help me, please!
15 medical.
You think we'll break
the record tonight?
Wait for the 4th of July.
Hey!
Fucking Halloween.
Oh, shit.
Just gonna put this on
your finger, okay, ma'am?
Hey, ma'am, how are we feeling?
Run.
Say that again, ma'am.
Run!
Fuck!
No.
You might think you have
this hold over me,
but the truth is,
you can't do this without me.
You can't force me to do it.
And I say I'm done.
I-- I realize what that means
for me,
but I accept that fate
if it means you'll suffer
the same.
The world will be a better
place without you.
Mom?
For God's sakes, Max,
it's about time.
Mom!
Shh!
Your sister's sleeping.
Do you have any idea
what time it is?
Where have you been?
I've been waiting.
You know that?
Sorry, I'm just really happy
to see you.
That's not gonna get you out
of this, Max.
You're grounded.
Okay.
I just don't know what's gotten
into you.
I'm sorry.
I just...
...just wanted
to say I love you.
You're going with that, huh?
Look, I don't have the energy
for this right now.
I need to get to bed
and so do you.
-Mom?
-Shh!
-I'm sorry.
-I don't want to hear anymore.
Bed!
Are you okay?
Yes, Max.
My leg just fell asleep.
Probably because I was waiting
up for you all night.
Okay.
Goodnight.
Goodbye, Zoe.
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Hi, sweetie.
Mom, no. No!
Enough!
You listen to me now.
You killed her.
She was dead before
I even got back.
And I'll do the same
to little Zoe.
No, please!
Finish, Max.
Finish and you both live.
Refuse and I take Zoe with me
before the candle burns out.
Four.
Four tricks, four tricks.
Yes, Max.
one remains.
One remains.
Tick-tock, Max.
Before the candle burns out.
I can do this.
Promise me.
Promise me if I do this,
you'll leave her alone.
That's not how this works, Max.
I made the only promise
you're gonna get from me.
Now, do you want to be
the reason
the rest of your family dies?
Good.
You tried to be so noble,
forfeiting your life for others,
even after seeing the worst
that they had to offer.
That's why you're not going
to win this, Max.
You're only allowed what
I decide to give you.
I-- I'll do it.
Now!
I have someone in mind.
Bitch.
Eat my ass, Rick.
Fuck!
Hey, Darren.
Max, what the fuck
are you doing here?
Do you wanna see a magic trick?
What?
No.
I'm going home.
I know.
But me and my friend wanted
to show you a-- a trick.
Just one trick, and that's it.
Why?
Because...
I like you.
One trick?
Fine.
One trick.
Okay.
All right.
Uh, pick a card.
Got it?
Yeah.
Is that it?
Come on, Max.
I must perform the trick.
What?
I must perform the trick
to the observer.
Only then will the offerings
be accepted.
That's what you said.
Four tricks, four souls.
I can do this.
One soul remains,
yours.
Whoa.
Hey, back the fuck--
Darren!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I never meant
for this to happen.
Oh, excuse me, sir,
this is an active crime scene.
-Please step back.
-I'm sorry, I-- I got a call.
I was told to be here.
You're who the girl called?
Hey. Mmm.
Hey.
Hmm.
Kiddo.
Hey.
What happened?
I finally got it right.
What?
The trick.
I got it.
Four tricks, four souls.
Every year.