A TIME FOR BRAVERY
- What's up, fellas? Everything cool?
- All good.
Come on.
On time, just how it's supposed to be.
Look.
What about the van?
Fucking great.
Smooth at 110 kilometers.
The wheel stays steady.
And that thing?
- Here.
- You swapping it out for a full one?
Kind of.
And nobody's gonna find out?
Hopefully not.
- Take it away.
- Hopefully.
- Move it.
- Montero!
Get over here.
Evening. Can we?
Sit down.
- Thanks.
- Did you guys eat?
Yeah, grabbed something on the way.
With the van loaded?
Yeah, no worries.
We kept an eye on it through the window.
- So everything's good?
- All good.
Not even our wives know.
Told them we were going
to pray to Saint Jude.
Nobody will find out about this,
here or at the plant, right?
No one, no.
We did it clean, plenty of time.
Casasola here got transferred, what?
About a month ago.
Came from Bajío,
and had a copy of the keys.
All clean, no noise. Just how you like it.
All right then. So everything's solid.
Right on.
All right, boys.
Payment clears next week.
Thanks so much.
And you?
Did you tell anyone?
You seem quiet.
- I haven't told anyone.
- You sure?
Yeah.
You didn't tell anyone
how much you're making. Nobody?
- Nobody.
- Not a buddy? A coworker?
Some girl?
No.
Perfect.
Relax.
Relax, it's all fine.
Take a deep breath.
Breathe.
I just need you to tell me
if anyone knows.
Nobody knows, Solares. Nobody.
Why don't you say someone does?
'Cause nobody knows!
See, I want you to lie to me.
Lie to me.
Look what happened to your buddy.
He said nobody knew.
So what happened? He died.
But nobody knows, Solares.
I swear on my kids.
On my children.
Please, I swear!
What I want you to understand
is that if you tell me nobody knows,
killing you ties up every loose end.
But if you say you told someone,
then I can't kill you.
You get it, right?
Yeah.
I did tell someone.
- You did?
- Yeah.
I don't buy it.
No! Solares, don't!
Please! No!
Come in.
Morning, Commissioner.
- Until now?
- Hell of a match last night, huh?
Don't be a suck-up, Montijo.
What do you got?
Not much. Three stolen cars…
- Skip the obvious.
- Sure.
Some guys broke into a lady's apartment,
cleaned her out.
- Was she hurt?
- Not so much.
Give it to Gómez.
At a nightclub in the Historic Center,
two goons beat the hell out of a minor.
Sadly, he died last night
from internal bleeding at Xoco.
Oh my God.
The club owner pays us off every month.
He wants to talk to you.
Give it to Jiménez,
but he must check in with me first.
Lastly, the wife of a military employee
filed a missing person report.
Apparently, the husband went to
Saint Jude Thaddeus temple with a friend.
He never came back.
Talk to Ugarte... There he is. Ugarte!
- Sir.
- Montijo here will give you a report.
A disappearance, two military employees...
Excuse me, Chief.
Is Díaz getting anything?
- Why?
- You haven't heard?
Heard what?
Díaz is a wreck.
Last week,
he found his wife with another guy.
She's been cheating on him for six months.
So, if you could give him something…
You know, occupational therapy.
Of course. But is he in any shape to work?
He's taking sleeping pills,
but maybe we could do
what we did with Gómez when his kid died.
Have a psychologist tag along.
I'll talk to the judge,
see if there's one available.
We'd agreed on something else.
Yes, I know.
Didn't the judge say I could give talks
at Colegio de Bachilleres?
Or working with kids with disabilities?
Thanks.
Well, police stations are dangerous spots.
People get kidnapped there.
They do kidnap people. It's a jungle, sir.
Sure.
So, community service helps me
with the conditional suspension.
I fulfill my duty by giving back
to the community through my profession.
That's how I clear the criminal case.
- Why the police?
- I don't know.
- Nerve-racking. What do they want?
- No clue.
Treat a detective or something.
They'll explain.
Don't stress.
I'll find a way to get out of it.
Hey, your mom called
to confirm if we're going today.
- Going where?
- For Pesach.
Oh, it's Pesach?
Time flies, Diana. Give me a second.
If you want, I can order something
and we eat here together.
- Oh, okay. Sure.
- It's fine if you don't want to.
- I do want to.
- No, you don't.
Look how you said it.
- Babe, relax, I do want to.
- But you don't feel like it.
Babe, I really want you to order food
and for us to have a nice time, okay?
Don't worry, it'll be fine.
PUBLIC SECURITY SECRETARIAT
Well, Dr. Silverstein,
you were sentenced for having…
I ran over a woman.
Well, actually, what happened was
that she threw herself under the car.
Her kids sued me. Nothing happened to her.
They took my car, my registration,
my license. Everything went wrong.
Anyway, the judge ruled
that you have to do community service.
Yes. I'd just like to know exactly
what you have in mind.
Look, Doctor, one of our agents
is going through a rough patch.
A few days ago, he found out
his wife was living a double life.
With another man.
No, she was dressing up at night,
fighting crime.
Yes, she had another man.
A coworker of hers.
- He followed her and caught them together.
- Right, a...
The idea is for you
to work with the detective
and help him get back to work.
- A kind of...
- Occupational therapy.
Listen, Officer,
I have a friend
who's an extraordinary couples therapist.
- She'd be perfect for this kind of...
- No. This is one-on-one, Doctor.
And don't you think… we could find
another solution to this problem?
Are you bribing me, Doctor?
No…
Because we can add more hours
to your community service.
Ever heard of the Xochiaca dump?
Lots of trash to pick up there.
Absolutely not.
I'd never suggest anything like that.
I meant something else, okay?
Look, the thing is,
Díaz is the son of one of my best friends.
He was my com padre,
so I'm taking this one personally.
And is he aware you're assigning me?
I mentioned it.
Look, there he is now. Díaz!
What's up, champ? How are you?
How are you, Commissioner?
- How are you?
- Seeing you, just incredible.
- Montijo.
- Hey, Díaz. Everything okay?
Yeah, all good. I think.
Díaz, I want you to meet Dr. Lieberman.
Silverstein.
- Nice to meet you.
- Pleasure.
- Anyway, Silverman here...
- Silverstein.
- It's Silverstein.
- Right.
He's a local.
Anyway, he's a psychologist.
The idea is for him
to accompany you in your tasks.
- Montijo will give you a file with...
- Wait, what do you mean, accompany him?
You're saying I'm supposed
to ride with him in the patrol car.
That's dangerous.
Not inherently.
Just routine work.
- Díaz is one of our best men...
- Chief?
It isn't necessary, he's right.
- This is ridiculous, honestly, I...
- Of course.
I'm fine.
He looks fine.
Relax, okay?
We'll find a solution for this, okay?
Look into my eyes.
There's no tragedy when there's a way out.
The moment we realize
there's a way out ahead,
the present stops feeling so tragic.
I think there's already
good chemistry here.
All right then.
Shall we begin?
Care to tell me what happened?
My wife.
We've been together almost four years.
She's been seeing another man.
Fine. What's the problem?
You never cheated on her?
A couple of times, yeah.
Did you tell her?
- No.
- Why not?
- It's not easy, is it?
- Of course not.
But that's why I want you to tell me
how all this makes you feel.
How does it make me feel? Anxious.
Red light.
Fuck your mother, asshole!
Did you at least
call her every name you could think of?
- No.
- How about that? Why not?
What's the point?
Because there's no point, or out of fear?
Fear? The worst already happened.
If it has already happened,
you should be able to sleep.
With no pills,
since the worst has already happened.
But if you don't mind me saying so,
you look to me like a man in panic.
- You know what panic is?
- What?
Panic is the feeling
that what you fear most
is just about to happen.
Hey!
Yeah? And what is it I fear most?
That's exactly
what we need to find out together.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- How are you? Morning.
Over there.
How are you? Morning.
- Thanks for seeing us.
- Officer.
Just three questions.
- You're sure they went alone, right?
- Yes, totally.
They couldn't have gone off
with other women? Friends? Lovers?
Montero's a quiet guy.
I barely know Casasola.
He was transferred from the Bajío.
- And you're in contact with the factories?
- Of course.
- For work.
- Anything you hear, any lead could help.
- Fine.
- Any side business.
- Missing weapons, explosives, anything.
- Good, very good.
I'll leave you my number in case…
Darn. You got a piece of paper?
- Yeah, of course.
- Something to...
There you go. Thanks.
Cross out my number, please.
Excuse me?
What did you say?
My number, right there.
- In case you need to reach us.
- Thanks.
Everything's there.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
General Valdés will see you now.
Very well.
- Thanks for everything...
- Santos.
Santos.
Here's the thing. Casasola told his wife
they were taking Montero's car,
and Montero told his wife
they were taking Casasola's.
Both cars are parked at home.
Did they have access
to any military vehicle?
No.
MILITARY SUPPLY DEPARTMENT
They had no military vehicle access.
Everything okay?
Excuse me
Any connection to arms trafficking?
I beg your pardon?
A few days ago, I read in La Jornada
that in Mexico, many military men are
tied to arms trafficking.
Not all, of course.
Just some, that's all.
No. No connection to arms trafficking.
Goddamn! Pay attention, for fuck's sake!
Any unusual behavior? Any… strange calls?
No strange calls.
Good.
And that Nazi
was staring me down, judging me.
And you left me totally exposed, right?
Looking like an idiot.
You were right.
- About what?
- That I hadn't insulted her enough.
That's it. I hadn't insulted her enough.
Now I feel better.
And why do you think
you hadn't insulted her enough?
Why did we say
the worst hadn't happened yet?
Because she cheated,
but she didn't leave me.
If I insult her, she might leave, right?
And panic's directly tied
to fear of abandonment.
What does that connect to?
What childhood event do you link that to?
That my mom
left my dad after he got fired?
Well, there you go.
That's a key point, Díaz.
We've made real progress.
What did your father do?
- He was a cop too.
- How about that? Why'd they fire him?
He got caught reselling
a shipment of confiscated appliances.
They accused your father of corruption.
How old were you at the time?
About 13, 14 years old.
Now that's something.
Puberty hits, that stage of development.
And right when you're about
to become a man,
your father collapses as a man
under the disapproving gaze of whom?
- My mom?
- A woman, Díaz!
"No woman will ever love me now."
"I'm worthless as a man."
And if you add to that
the usual male ghosts…
"She left me because
the other guy's better in bed."
he lasts longer than I do."
"She left me because
his erection's firmer than mine…"
No!
You son of a bitch!
You hit my car, asshole!
Stop right there, you fucking idiot!
Díaz, you just hit someone's car.
- It sounded worse than it was.
- No, Díaz, you slammed into that car.
No, it's fine. Relax. Cool.
Whatever you say. You're the cop.
Okay. Well, thank you very much, Díaz.
Thank you. I can finally get some rest.
Actually, I was gonna give you my card.
Look. Here's my number.
If you ever need anything, call me.
I'm usually up late.
- Hope I'm not too much trouble.
- Don't worry.
Is that your dad?
Yeah.
Very touching.
Okay…
I remember being embarrassed by him.
After he got fired,
he'd sit around in sweatpants, unshaven.
I'd argue with him constantly.
- Right.
- Because I wanted to change him.
What I should've done was make the most
of the time I had with him.
Unfortunately, we have to wrap up, Díaz.
But there's clearly
something important here.
I never asked, where do you live?
Me? In Satélite.
Yeah, I'm not going there now.
I'm staying in a hotel in Tlalpan.
I don't want to go back home.
- Right.
- Not after everything I said to Mónica.
Right.
- So, see you tomorrow.
- Get some rest.
Where are you having dinner?
Hello there!
- Hi!
- Hi, honey.
- How are you?
- Okay, this is my partner, Diana.
This is Detective Díaz.
You didn't tell me your name.
- Cameron.
- Cameron Diaz.
Oh, you…
No, it's a joke.
It's a dad joke.
- Alfredo.
- Alfredo, this way.
- Nice to meet you.
- Make yourself at home, Alfredo.
It's a 19th-century house,
integrated office.
Make yourself at home, please.
I had to invite him to dinner.
He's going through a rough time.
- We'll do something another day.
- Shit, Mariano, why do you do this?
Don't be mad.
And don't be too affectionate with me.
He's in a fragile place, hypersensitive.
I don't want him to get depressed.
Love you.
Do you like classical music,
or should I put something else on?
- Whatever you usually listen to is fine.
- All right. Come in.
Come on in.
- Excuse me.
- Of course.
What's this?
That's Peña de Bernal.
I took it on our last trip.
What was it, three years ago?
Three years. I really love rock climbing.
Looks dangerous, but it's actually only
about a meter and a half off the ground.
He pretends to be brave,
but he's my baby teddy.
Shall we eat?
Careful, that one's bitter.
It is bitter.
We eat it to reminisce about
when we were slaves.
In World War II?
That too, but no, in Egypt.
Four or five thousand years ago,
when we built the pyramids.
- We didn't build them.
- Yes, we did.
- There is no proof.
- We're not arguing about that.
- Don't bore him with history lessons.
- I'm not. History is fascinating.
- Right, Díaz?
- Matzo ball?
Yes, thanks.
Thanks.
- Delicious. Thanks.
- I'm glad.
Thanks.
Who would've thought
we'd get this crossover?
I can say I've got a cop friend,
you can say you've got a Jewish friend.
There's a lot of prejudice
against cops, right?
Tons. I wouldn't call it prejudice so much
as there's a lot of corruption, right?
Diana.
There are all kinds,
but with the salaries they pay…
Doctors and teachers also make little
and don't get corrupt.
- Diana.
- They don't carry guns.
If I were a leader,
I'd raise salaries first.
You don't want
someone unhappy with a gun, right?
- Right.
- These balls are really good.
- Right?
Thanks. I ordered them.
What did you do today, honey?
Nothing.
I went to the dentist.
How was it?
So-so. I need a root canal.
Oh, no. That's really painful.
Then I looked for a job.
The company Diana worked for
closed a few months ago.
- She's an accountant looking for work.
- Yeah, well…
You okay, Díaz?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I set up a padel game
with Sandra and Alexis for Thursday.
You sure you're okay, Díaz?
You seem a little stressed.
No.
Your wife is cheating on you.
What? What do you mean?
That. Your wife is cheating, Doctor.
What? How is my wife cheating, Díaz? No.
- You cheating? Yes or no?
- I don't know what…
- What are you saying, Díaz?
- Well, are you?
Calm dow... Hey, what's wrong with you?
Are you crazy, Díaz? Calm down.
Are you cheating?
Whoa! Hey! Okay, Díaz, calm down.
Díaz, let's calm down, okay?
Díaz. Hey.
Look into my eyes.
You're projecting.
You're not talking to her,
but to your wife.
- Díaz! Hey!
- No.
- No…
- Díaz!
- Put the gun down.
- Are you cheating?
Answer! It's easy!
- Put the gun down.
- It's easy.
- Put the gun down!
- Easy to answer.
Are you cheating? Yes or no?
- Yes or no?
- Yes!
- What?
Yes!
What do you mean, yes?
It's true, but I love you. I swear.
- What do you mean, Diana?
- Just that.
- I didn't mean to, forgive me. I didn't...
- Why are you cheating on me?!
Speak clearly. It's like a tongue twister.
I thought you were with someone else!
When would I even have time for that
if I see patients all day?
In literature workshop,
we were analyzing Madame Bovary.
And the professor said
she was a very brave woman.
She was brave because
she lived in another century, Diana!
Women were repressed then
and didn't cheat on their husbands.
Today, all women cheat.
So guess what? You're average!
- Wait, no.
- Oh, yes.
Are you stupid or what?
How could you do something like that?
Who's the guy?
The teacher of a literature workshop
this dumb woman… is taking.
And how did you find out?
She took too long
to answer a very simple question.
And she's not wearing her ring.
They always do that.
We are not married, Díaz.
We don't have rings.
Get me out of here, Díaz, please.
- Mariano…
- Don't talk to me.
What a bitch.
I don't understand, how...?
- I was an idiot too.
- Why so?
I neglected the relationship
over the last few years.
I was wrapped up in my work, you know?
I went to like 20 conferences alone,
and she's right.
- She's right.
- Do you think so?
I mean, she cheated on you.
So what?
I've done my share, and I don't think
it's terrible or earth-shattering.
Why would I act macho?
No, sure, but for her,
your share would seem terrible, right?
Yes.
That's why, if I have enough maturity
and take some distance,
this shouldn't be a tragedy, right?
That's what you think, not what you feel.
Yes, but what truly matters, Díaz,
is what you think, not what you feel.
And the truth is…
I don't know what I feel, Díaz.
There you go.
There it is. Let it out.
That's it. Cry it out!
Cry, son. Cry like a man!
- What a bitch.
- Yeah, a real bitch.
What a bitch.
Díaz, you copy?
- Here, Díaz. Dispatch, I copy.
- What a bitch.
We have two bodies in a van in Tláhuac.
Maybe the men you're looking for.
Understood. I'm on my way.
FORENSIC MEDICAL SERVICE
Here, sir.
Here.
They're your guys, Díaz!
We should tell their wives
their drinking days are over.
Commissioner.
Look, they dumped it in the deepest part.
Those bastards knew what they were doing.
If it weren't for the cleaning of this...
What's this called?
- Hyacinth.
- What?
- Hyacinths.
- We wouldn't have found it.
- Watch it.
- Sorry.
What do you think?
Maybe they tried
to strip the van and failed.
Or they sold weapons on the black market.
Who knows?
How are things with the doc?
Good. He helps me to keep it together.
How do you feel about
continuing the investigation?
Me? Perfect.
Commissioner!
What else do we know about the car?
It had no plates,
but we've ID'd the engine number.
They're checking records.
See? That's not the original lock.
It's stolen.
We need to call Dr. Apolonio Ramírez
to send the report tomorrow.
Anything you know,
or any leads would help.
Sure.
LUXURY SUITES
Okay.
A clean bed, fresh sheets.
A shower, and rest, huh?
Good evening.
- Your keys.
- Thanks.
- Who's this?
- A colleague.
Damn cops.
Here.
Take one of these.
Take both at once.
Up. Come on.
With that, you'll sleep deeply.
Good night.
Good night, Díaz.
In half an hour, I'll have
the coroner's report. Wanna come?
Isn't that too much?
No. You'll love it.
The bullet enters the occipital region,
exits through the anterior of the neck,
and finally grazes
the inside of the left calf.
In Casasola's palms, there were particles
of a ferrous material, iron or lead.
He'd probably been handling
something heavy for a long time.
Our buddy Montero was shot
against the wall or the floor.
The projectile enters the right temporal
and finishes its path at the second molar.
The casing was damaged.
I sent it to Ballistics.
They'll have the report at 10:00.
You're new, aren't you?
No, he's a buddy who's a little depressed.
We brought him out for a walk, right?
If it comforts you,
you have fewer problems than these two.
Next!
Good morning.
Morning. I'm here to pick up
the Casasola and Montero report.
MISSING CAT - LOLA
They brought it half an hour ago.
This isn't a photo studio.
Hang tight.
Okay.
Outside?
QUIET - RESPECT THE SHOOTER
I should be with some patients.
Feeling like this,
I don't want to see anyone.
Maybe I should call them
just to let them know, right?
Or not call them, let it all go to hell.
They're always falling apart,
and today I'm falling apart.
Want to try?
Me?
No way, you're crazy.
Gee, I feel like I'm in Lethal Weapon!
- Isn't that right?
- Yeah!
Okay, .40 caliber.
Eight rounds, automatic.
Accuracy to 35 meters
and effective range up to 120 meters.
- Perfect.
- Loaded magazine inserted.
- Right.
- Safety off.
Chamber a round.
Right hand on the grip.
The other hand supports it, elbows bent.
Finger off the trigger just in case.
Ready to shoot.
If I fall, I don't shoot myself and die.
- Right.
- Good.
- Aim at the enemy.
- I have no enemies...
- Oh, wow.
- Yeah.
I'll help you.
Okay, your turn.
Very well.
Loaded magazine inserted.
Safety off.
Chamber the roof...
- The round.
I put my hand on the grip and hold.
I bend knees and elbows in case of a fall.
I fire.
Three hits on the cardboard.
- One on the target. Good start.
- Very good.
You're drifting left. See?
That's an easy fix.
Where do you drift?
- What?
- The shot.
Where's the other shot
which isn't on the cardboard?
No, it is there.
They just hit the same place twice.
- Weren't you two here for a report?
- Yes, sorry!
Shall we?
CUAUHTÉMOC BOROUGH
Firearm, .38 Smith. Right.
- Makes sense. A .38 special.
- Why does it make sense?
What happens when you fire a gun?
Casings eject. What are casings?
Evidence.
You don't want to leave evidence.
With revolvers, they stay in the cylinder.
It's harder to trace.
But you've got a good lead, right?
There are around 750,000 folks
with a .38 special.
On the black market,
you can find them for under 3,000 pesos.
- Díaz, you copy? Díaz.
- Coming.
- Copy, Montijo.
- You were right. The van was stolen.
It went missing
in Chabacano two weeks ago.
- Which side?
- Not sure. Where Eje 3 starts.
That goes to the Historic Center.
Was it taken while parked,
or was it an armed robbery?
- What does the report say?
- While it was parked.
Day or night?
- Day, at 3:00 p.m.
- Thanks, Montijo.
You're welcome, Díaz.
- Where are we going?
- Tepito.
We're visiting a friend.
How are you? Feeling better?
- We'll see.
- Okay. Let's see then.
- You smoke?
- No, thanks.
What are you doing?
Smoking.
Yeah, but it's marijuana.
- So?
- You're a cop, Díaz.
So?
Marijuana's illegal.
So you've never smoked pot.
It doesn't matter if I did or not.
It's not about that.
I'm in a police car with a cop,
and it's important to set an example.
So, you're setting the example.
Excellent.
How do you know I never smoked pot?
You don't even know me.
You wouldn't be so judgy.
Okay, give it here. I'm devastated anyway.
This is crazy, really. In broad daylight.
You've got to swallow the smoke
and hold it for a bit.
You're a real piece of work.
You run red lights, you smoke pot.
- How long?
- As long as you can.
Then exhale slowly.
SUCK-A-BELLY TEA
They think we're dumb, right?
"Suck-a-belly."
A tea that sucks your belly.
It's crazy how advertising
tries to trick you, isn't it?
Think about this.
Your wife cheats on you,
but you don't want
advertising to fool you.
Both of us.
This stuff does nothing to me.
I'm really starving.
What's up, man?
Hey. We still have pending business.
- Long time no see!
- Hey, skinny.
Mega cheap. Get pineapples!
- I'm hungry, Díaz.
- We'll see my friend and grab something.
- Who's your friend?
- A car thief.
A car thief?
If you know he's stealing cars,
why isn't he in prison?
If he were in prison,
he wouldn't give us info.
I won't put my friend behind bars.
There?
What? Trust me, man. Trust.
You'll bust your hand.
Keep your guard up. Throw a jab.
Then finish with the hook.
All right? Hit it.
Okay, good.
- Yes?
- I'm here to see the Accountant.
- There ain't no accountant here.
- Wazowski, don't start any shit, open up.
- They'll fuck me over.
- Who the fuck's that?
- Hey.
- No way!
- No, man!
- Get over here, asshole.
Where the fuck are you going?
- Get back, prick!
- Enough!
- That's it.
- Come on!
- Boss!
Calm the fuck down!
He's a pal. Lower your guns.
Come on, down.
- Okay?
- Keep walking.
I just wanted to talk.
All right. Over here.
Can't believe it.
This dumb-ass moved the balls.
Don't worry, they were right here.
I clearly checked before I grabbed them.
There.
Want a soda? A beer?
Can I get a Tehuacán, please?
Water's fine for me.
Who's this guy?
- My shrink.
- Excuse me.
Look, man.
So, a Kangoo van went missing
two weeks ago over on Eje 3 by Chabacano.
I've been working only
with imports for two years.
Just imports.
Yeah, right, play dumb.
- Push me. I'll throw your ass in a cell.
- I ain't playing.
You know how much they pay
for a van like that?
And how much they flip it for?
1,000% markup.
- And the grease you gotta give the cops.
- Yeah, I know.
So who the fuck boosted it
in broad daylight?
The Colombians. Those motherfuckers.
We stomped their asses three times
and they keep coming back like lice.
Wait. Chucky!
Find out who jacked a Kangoo
from Chabacano, Eje 3.
Move your ass!
Who should I ask?
How should I know?
You've been hustling since you were 15,
and you don't know who to ask
about a damn van?
Come on!
Hey, sweetheart.
Why don't you shove your fingers
up your own ass?
- I'm fine, thanks.
- What?
Oh, these were yours.
Sorry, didn't notice.
You didn't notice?
- I'm here with Díaz.
- Who gives a shit who you're with?
Why do we have to be so antagonistic,
when we could all be… buddies?
What's up? It's Marcos. Chucky.
'Sup, Chucky?
The Accountant wants me to find out
who jacked a sand-colored Kangoo, man.
- Where?
- Eje 3 and Chabacano.
Gotcha. Hold up.
When was this?
Who told you the van
was sand-colored, asshole?
He said it. Wasn't it sand-colored?
Yeah, but I didn't say anything.
He didn't say the color.
How can I know something I don't know?
- Trying to make me look like an idiot?
- Come on, boss.
For three years, this hand
has been feeding you, asshole.
And now you're opening your own shop?
Ungrateful little thief.
What, your hand feeds me?
You get 50 grand for a van
and you toss me 10,000, man.
Cheap-ass old fuck.
You think I can pull miracles?
I take the risks, man.
Who the hell are you calling cheap-ass?
I didn't mean to lie.
That dude's been my client
before I started with the Accountant.
It was a quick job, a van.
- They paid fast, cash.
- How do I recognize him?
His name's Óscar.
We only deal by phone.
He's the one who calls.
I don't even know what he does.
Why be a nosy prick?
- Where'd you leave the vehicle?
- I just changed the lock and ignition.
He told me to leave it in a lot over
on República del Salvador and Bolívar.
Across from a military building?
I dunno, man.
República del Salvador and Bolívar.
Then what? Did he pay you or not?
Yup, when he hired me.
Then I didn't see him anymore.
Where didn't you see him, Chucky?
Nowhere. I said I didn't.
No, dude, you said,
"Then I didn't see him."
So you saw him before. I'm asking where.
What, man? I don't get it.
Son of a fucking bitch!
Don't play dumb, okay?
I don't know you, but you seem kinda slow!
Don't disrespect me.
Where did you meet before taking the job?
At a seafood place, man.
- I guess you saw him there a few times.
- A few times? Wh...?
- No!
- Hey! Enough.
Cut it out, man!
Why don't you just arrest me
and take my fingerprints?
Then you go back and find the guy.
I don't know shit.
- Move it, Chucky.
- "Move it, Chucky."
In other countries,
they put you in witness protection.
They sweeten the deal.
A chick, a house, a nice family, man.
You see him?
- He's not here, boss.
- Well, then… we can wait, Chucky.
What's wrong, Chucky?
- I'm just…
- You okay?
I'm cool, bro.
Thanks, sir.
What?
Good afternoon.
- Yes?
- Can you spare a moment to talk?
Sure, why not?
Thanks.
- How are you, sir?
- Good afternoon.
I'm an agent with the Federal Police.
I'm on a lead about a stolen van
we just found in Tláhuac.
Two bodies in the trunk.
And that lead brought us here. To you.
Oh my.
And why's that?
- Exactly what we want to know.
- I have nothing to do with it.
- It's okay, we're not in a hurry, right?
- No.
We'll sort this out together.
What do you do?
Right now? I'm having a coffee.
Right. Coffee's good here, isn't it?
In general, what do you do in life?
- I'm unemployed.
- No way.
- What's your name?
- Carlos.
Let me see some ID, please.
- I don't have my wallet.
- No? Nothing?
In that case, you're coming with us.
Oh my, why?
- You're not cooperating.
- On the contrary.
Anyway, you two
should identify yourselves.
Of course.
Look.
INVESTIGATIVE POLICE
There you go.
"Alfredo Díaz…"
- And you?
- We're the ones asking the questions.
What's your relationship
with the kid sitting back there?
- Which one?
- Back there, at the bar.
- None.
- Funny, huh?
He's a car thief who just ID'd you
as the buyer of the van we found.
Yeah. What's this?
Oh God.
Yikes. How are we gonna handle this then?
Lisandro Prada.
What's this Camarasa thing?
Weren't you unemployed?
He won't talk.
So you're not talking?
I am.
Go back to your work.
Let me drink my coffee in peace, okay?
Excuse me?
- Are you a cop?
- Díaz, let's go.
What are you up to? Tell me. Drugs? Guns?
- What's Camarasa?
- Beat it.
- I'm doing you a favor.
- Who are you?
One more question and you'll eat lead.
I could justify you in a heartbeat.
- Díaz, let's go.
- I just wanna know.
Who are you?
One more word
and you'll leave here in a body bag.
You're under arrest
for contempt of authority.
For disrespecting me.
Move it. Stand up. Easy.
Let's go.
No funny business.
Hands where I can see them.
Don't you do anything stupid. Come on.
Spread your legs.
Let's see what you got.
What do you have here?
Look. A .38 special.
Did I say what they used
to kill the Tláhuac guys?
Oh, dear.
- Police!
Police!
Arrest this man!
I'm a federal officer!
- Agent Díaz!
- Listen to me!
Get on the ground!
National Intelligence Agency!
On the ground!
Hey! Where do you think you're going?
Hands behind your back!
Let him go!
He has nothing to do with this!
- All three come with me for questioning!
- I'm a cop!
- There's my badge, goddamn!
- Stop!
It all happened so fast
and it was so violent.
Thing is, the guy never identified himself
as an intelligence officer, okay?
He refused to ID himself.
If you ask me, he acted like a criminal.
He threatened Díaz, knowing he was a cop.
"Keep asking questions,
and your wife could turn up in a trunk."
Stuff like that, he said.
Agent Sosa was doing
undercover intelligence work
on a case that, for obvious reasons,
we can't give you details about.
It almost certainly connects
to the two dead men.
And Díaz
is inside a network we're investigating.
The Federal Police
are rotten with corruption,
and the government is pressuring us
to clean up before the elections.
We've been onto Díaz for a while.
He's not the only dirty cop on your team.
Commissioner.
Wholesale corruption, extortion,
kidnappings, a prostitution ring.
Chop shops.
In fact, Díaz's informant
works in a major organized-crime cell.
But don't worry.
We'll question him and let him go.
It's more interesting to see
where he leads than to lock him up, right?
What I will ask, Commissioner,
is that every case involving Díaz
be handed over to me.
Forensic reports, ballistic reports…
You'll have them first thing tomorrow.
Tonight.
- No problem.
- Very well.
I suggest we release the doctor
from his community service.
- I can talk to the judge.
- No, I'll handle it, don't worry.
Fine.
You may come to my office
to escort two people out. Thanks.
Right away.
Doctor, tomorrow
we'll summon you for a full statement
about everything you've seen
and heard these days, okay?
Sure.
Fine.
Gentlemen.
Commissioner, Doctor.
It was a pleasure.
The commissioner's not a problem,
but we must look into the psychologist.
I want you to tap his phones,
keep close to him.
He knows nothing,
he doesn't understand. He's lost.
But if you see anything suspicious,
make it look like an accident.
RESTRICTED AREA
Access granted.
Any more questions
about the cooling pools…
Good evening, Díaz.
I'm Mr. Gerardo Solares.
You're in the restricted area
of Special Affairs Division, which I run.
So we've got some privacy here.
I don't want to waste your time or mine.
I'm a busy man, and I've got things to do.
Let's cut to the chase, Díaz.
For some time now,
I've been putting together
the special ops we're running tonight.
I just need to know if you've said
or done anything that could hinder it.
I know nothing about any operation.
- I only stole a van, man.
- Don't say anything.
- I don't...
- Shut this clown up.
- Please!
- Hey! Let him go!
Let him go!
You're gonna kill him!
Goddamn.
Díaz.
Anything I should be worried about?
Diana! You scared the hell out of me.
Where were you?
- Why didn't you answer my texts?
- Because I was mad.
And my phone died.
Were you with someone else?
Camarasa…
Were you with another woman?
No, Diana, I wasn't with any woman.
Then can you explain that hickey?
It's not a hickey, babe. It's a bruise.
A cop subdued me. Threw me on the floor.
Enriched uranium
is kept submerged in pools
under strict safety rules…
- Where did you sleep last night?
- In a hotel.
CAMARASA IS GRANTED
WASTE RIGHTS FOR LAGUNA VERDE
- Don't you love me anymore?
- How could I not love you?
You're still mad.
Yeah, still mad.
Look at me when I talk to you!
- I am.
- Stop ignoring me, please.
- Stop ignoring me.
- I'm not.
You always ignore me!
- You are. You always ignore me.
Look me in the eye
and tell me what you're thinking.
I don't know.
I don't know what I'm thinking.
I don't want to think anymore.
I want to feel.
Okay.
Okay, so…
then tell me what you're feeling.
I don't know, like…
Nothing major, really, but maybe that…
Maybe we aren't…
Right for each other.
Maybe we're just not
two halves of the same fruit.
Maybe you're half pit a ya
and I'm half a kiwi.
I don't know.
It must be that Santos guy.
He's been calling all afternoon.
- Who?
- Santos.
- Yes?
- Silverstein?
- This is him.
- It's Santos.
We spoke yesterday about supplies
at the military building.
- Yes, tell me.
- I spoke with a friend.
He's over at the Bajío factory.
About what you asked yesterday.
Someone took an R-22 cask.
The ones made exclusively
for the Laguna Verde Power Station.
"R-22 cask."
They're lead. Manufactured in accordance
with international safety standards.
Used to transporting uranium.
You messed with the wrong people.
Uranium?
You know what uranium is worth
on the black market?
With 500 grams,
you can make an atomic bomb.
Atomic…
What do you mean an atomic bomb?
Don't say I told you.
I hope you find those bastards
who killed the guys.
Hello?
Who's that guy, Diana?
- Who?
- The one over there, looking in.
Hold on a sec.
Can I help you?
What can I help...?
Don't move. Stay there, Diana.
Yeah?
Hello, Doctor.
I'm Agent Barrera
from the National Intelligence Agency.
What do you need?
Can we talk for a second?
What's going on?
Can I come in for a sec?
I won't take long.
Right. We're about to have dinner.
I was told I'd give my statement
at the National Intelligence Agency.
Yes, of course.
I was assigned this case today.
Look, it'll just take two minutes.
No, that won't be possible.
I'd rather you call me tomorrow
and we set up a time.
All right?
Sure.
Of course.
Excuse me.
Good night.
Diana, calm down
and grab something to tie this guy up.
Tell me who you are.
Diana, what? Aim at him.
- What do you mean?
- Tell me the truth.
- How long have you been lying to me?
- What?
- How long have you been a spy? Tell me.
- Diana, I'm not lying to you.
You've been lying for two months.
What the…
Diana, what's wrong with you?
That's why you didn't pay attention to me.
What?
I don't even know what's real anymore.
Tell me who I'm living with!
Everything's real.
Calm down, okay?
Look me in the eye. Breathe.
Let's breathe.
Give me the gun.
Slowly.
Barrera.
Do you copy?
Barrera, do you copy?
Let me… let me answer.
I'll answer.
Doctor, more agents will come.
Hear me out.
You will repeat every single word I say.
Any wrong word,
any pause a little too long,
and you'll leave in a bag.
Shut up, for fuck's sake!
Barrera, do you copy?
Sorry, okay?
Copy.
Any problems?
Negative.
And the doctor?
Having dinner with his wife.
Nothing unusual.
How about you guys?
Who's this?
Who's talking?
Fix this shit for me.
It's Barrera.
Chucky has left the toy store.
And the cop?
He won't make the night.
Copy that.
"Copy, affirmative, negative"?
This isn't war, Barrera.
Keep me posted, yeah?
Keep walking.
Go, mister.
- Faster.
- I can't.
Shut up. Move it.
Keep walking.
- Whoa!
- Shut up.
Bachelor party. You know how people get.
Keys. Open the trunk.
- Open the trunk.
- On the front.
- The front.
- Where's your wallet?
It's there.
Get in the trunk. Go on.
- You okay?
- Yeah, he's fine.
Here's what we'll do.
Call an Uber
and go to your parents' house.
You won't use the phone.
You won't talk to anyone.
You won't try to reach me, okay?
Everything's fine.
You're at a peak of stress. It'll pass.
Do you understand
what you have to do? Repeat.
- I'm gonna call an Uber.
- And then?
- Go to my parents'.
- Exactly.
- I've gotta go now.
- No!
Who are you? You're not like this.
Yeah, well…
What can I say, honey?
I'm not the same guy anymore, okay?
I'm… not like that anymore.
I've gotta go.
I don't want any reaction, understood?
Díaz is under a sensitive interrogation.
Nobody interferes, nobody asks questions.
- The case is with Intelligence.
- Hey!
I tried to stop him, but he ran in.
- Step back, López!
- We must help Díaz.
They'll kill him.
We need to go to Intelligence right now.
Relax, Doctor. Díaz is well guarded.
- Nothing's gonna happen!
- He's not well guarded.
This man is in the trunk of my car.
He tried to break into my house
and kill me.
They're tying up loose ends.
They killed Chucky. They'll kill Díaz.
I heard it on the guy's walkie-talkie.
- Two things, Doctor.
- Okay.
This case is being handled
by intelligence services.
And your connection to this office
is now over, Doctor.
Intelligence services?
They're criminals, for God's sake.
Criminals acting covertly.
They're going to steal uranium
from the nuclear plant.
Montero and Casasola
stole a cask and handed it over.
An R-22 one, used to transport…
Uranium, okay?
These casks are made by the military.
That's why they killed them.
They knew exactly what they were doing!
Keep talking and I'll have you arrested.
Why, if I'm telling you
they're going to kill Díaz?
Arrest him!
Wasn't it personal? Didn't you tell me
Díaz's dad was your com padre, your pal?
I'm telling you they'll kill your friend
and you're not doing anything?
Arrest him, I said!
Anyone who interferes
will be discharged immediately!
Understood?
Individual matters don't mean shit here!
FOR YOUR SAFETY, LOCK YOUR LOCKER
I've got an operation underway.
Will I run into any surprises?
You stubborn son of a bitch, Díaz.
Answer me so I can shoot you.
Who are you waiting for?
Your Prince Charming?
This is wrong.
- Good evening.
- Yes?
I'm Officer, uh, Vargas.
I come from the mayor's office.
Someone brought this to the station.
Someone found it on the street,
and we believe this person works here.
I don't know.
- Lots of people work here.
- Sure.
- Leave it. I'll take it to reception.
- Unfortunately, it can't be like that.
I have to deliver it personally.
I was also asked to get a signed receipt.
- Hold on a sec.
- Yes, very kind of you.
Dispatch.
I'm here with an officer asking…
It's been a full 42 years… well lived.
There were many happy moments.
Many professional goals reached.
- I found love… I thought I did.
- You may go in.
Thank you very much.
This is wrong.
Good evening.
Let's see.
Yes, he works here.
- My colleague will deliver it tomorrow.
- Fine.
- I'll sign.
- Pardon?
- The guard said I had to sign a receipt.
- Ah, yes.
Okay.
So where is it?
Sign any piece of paper.
Just write, "Received ID,
number X, from Officer Vargas."
Today's date. CDMX.
Here you go.
- How's the match going?
- It's from last year.
You're watching it on YouTube?
Who's playing?
It's the clásico.
Ah, yeah, Chivas.
Anything else you need, Officer?
Do you think it'd be possible for me
to quickly use the restroom?
No.
- No?
- No.
Why not?
Why won't you let me through
if I'm a Federal Police officer?
This is Intelligence.
You have no authority here.
It's very late. It's all closed, okay?
I really need to use the restroom,
so couldn't you show a little empathy?
- I must ask you to leave, Officer.
- How can you not let me go?
Let him use the bathroom, you rude jerk.
Juan, I can't. Authorized personnel only.
Don't be such an asshole.
If he says he needs the bathroom,
you let him in.
Fine. This is on you.
- Thanks.
- Come on, man. Leave your gun there.
Right.
Go ahead.
- Thanks a lot.
- Nothing to thank for.
You work all night for pocket money,
risking your life,
and look how this punk answers.
Anyway, it was a nice gesture.
I never meant
to cause trouble for your job.
- Relax, man. It's no big deal.
- Okay.
That's very kind of you.
Nice restroom.
There's no toilet paper.
- No problem. I'll bring you some.
- Thank you.
He doesn't know anything.
He would have already talked.
I'll handle it.
Good evening.
Seen anything weird around here?
No. What happened?
That's exactly what I'm asking you.
What happened?
I don't know.
You don't know what happened?
No. What happened?
Is the detainee still around here?
Around here where?
Where? Where else?
I don't know.
- In the restricted area?
- Exactly.
The restricted area.
I didn't know you had detainees there.
- Besides, I don't have access.
- Why would you?
- Right.
In a serious country, you shouldn't
even know where the restricted area is.
It does have a sign.
- The one on the third floor?
- Oh, no, I mean the eighth.
We're talking about different things.
I'll ask you to get back to work.
Officer?
González, you copy?
González?
- González?
- Copy.
At the agreed time, at the rendezvous.
On our way.
RESTRICTED AREA
Kid, do you have the keys?
What keys?
The service bathroom keys.
- No. They're lost.
- What do you mean lost?
They're lost.
Access denied.
"If you do community service,
you'll save yourself a lot of trouble."
Sure, dumb-ass lawyer.
Stop! Everyone stop.
Animal?
- Seal.
Five points. Color?
Intruder alert.
An intruder?
Are you blind?
The cop in the service bathroom.
Where is he?
For color, I wrote "sage." Twenty points.
Fuck.
The balls of this guy.
- Hello?
- Mr. Solares.
Morales at reception.
An intruder got into the building.
He's wearing a police uniform,
but we suspect it's fake.
- Everything good over there?
- All good.
Keep me posted, okay?
Yes, sir.
Hi.
How are you doing?
I've worked 35 years in Intelligence
and I've never,
never seen anything like this.
- May I come in?
- By all means.
Sorry.
- Should I close?
- Yes.
Right.
Look.
I'm a pacifist, okay?
All I want is for you
to release Díaz, please.
Barrera...
I forgot to tell you I have Barrera, okay?
But he's in a safe place.
AUTHORIZED VEHICLES ONLY
TOWING IN EFFECT
If you release Díaz,
I'll tell you where Barrera is, okay?
Let's negotiate.
Yes.
Where is Barrera?
I would really need you
to release Díaz first, honestly,
because I don't trust you much, really.
Wise choice.
That's a very wise choice.
- Good evening.
IDs, please.
Sectors F2, F6 and F8, toxic waste.
Okay, Officer.
No, what are you doing?
Let him go, please.
Listen, let him go.
I'll stay here as long as you want.
Your problem is with me.
He knows nothing, he's not involved.
He's harmless, damn it!
Harmless?
Someone who bails on his custodian,
compromises the security of the building
and climbs through the fucking window
of a restricted area is harmless?
You'll be in a lot of trouble
if anything happens to either of us!
You will never know where your agent is.
And second, I know very important people.
I'm a member of the Rotary Club,
so it'll be damn hard for you
to cover something like this.
I've installed and removed presidents.
You have no idea
how easy this'll be for me.
CAMARASA
SPECIALISTS IN HAZARDOUS MATERIALS
LOCKED/UNLOCKED
Díaz, we have to get out of here.
You know what uranium
in the wrong hands means.
- There's no hope. They'll kill us.
- They won't. Don't start.
We have to think,
that's what we have to do.
I've been thinking for six hours here.
There has to be some way out of here!
Where's the AC duct?
There isn't one.
Well, then, we have to get these cuffs off
and take those bastards on, right?
We can't get the cuffs off!
- Why can't we?
- That's what they're made for.
So they will…
They're gonna kill us.
I'm totally fucked.
- I fuck up everything I touch.
- Don't say that. You're not…
- You're a good man.
- No, what good man?
- I mess everything up.
- No.
I'll tell you something.
I charge 3,000 pesos per session.
I spend my days listening to that.
"I ruin everything, I fuck everything up."
And…
I promise you, if you get me out of here,
I'll introduce you to Dr. Moya.
He's a brilliant psychologist,
and he can help you.
And you?
You and I are friends.
Call me if you want to grab a bite.
Hey!
No, please!
- No, please!
- Shoot me! Don't hurt him!
- Don't, please!
- Don't hurt him!
- Yes?
- Agent Morales, sir.
I brought you some cake.
- Cake?
- Yeah.
It's my birthday.
I brought you cake.
Come on.
'Sup?
Go in.
Quiet, motherfucker.
Gentlemen.
Good evening.
Move forward!
- Move!
- Let's push forward! To the right!
Move.
You could retire tomorrow, boys.
Your kids wouldn't have to work.
My son's been a lazy bum for 19 years.
You think he'll get a job?
Hey! Wait, this is the guy who let me in.
Move it!
Get in!
Go inside!
This way. The elevator.
Damn. Move.
Let's take the stairs.
EIGHTH FLOOR
No. That way.
It's your word against mine, isn't it?
And even if you get out,
you won't get to the plant before us.
Díaz.
HELIPAD
Go! Move.
Doctor.
Sorry, guys.
Go!
Move!
Go in!
- They're coming.
- Doctor, on the back.
Oh God.
Get in.
Okay, let's go.
Díaz. You sure you know how to take off?
"Helicopter Flying Basics"
is an elective in the police entry course.
Pedals control the tail rotor.
The lever controls the main rotor.
Right.
- Now!
- Moving in!
Look what I just found, motherfucker.
Do you know how much these beauties cost?
They make us pay for our own bullets.
- Does this have a safety?
- Here.
- How do you start the engine?
- Button should be…
It's an American model. Here!
There you go!
Remember, turbines can't
exceed 600 degrees.
600? Not 800?
- Weren't you in that course?
- No, I took Computer Basics.
They taught us programming.
- Quick!
- Move!
I started digging into the deep web.
When no one knew about Bitcoin,
I managed to buy up to 10,000.
But I lost the password to my wallet.
Interesting.
Díaz, we could also turn him in.
- Yeah, right. Chill.
- Here they come!
There it is!
- Doctor!
- Yeah?
Look, you load here.
Unlock it and pull the trigger.
Okay? You only have 24 rounds per second.
Check that out.
The good thing about these is,
if you miss your aim,
you can correct as you go.
- Right?
- Right!
- Okay?
- Okay!
Okay.
What are you looking at, asshole?
Slowly.
Start decontamination sequence.
I've got another one here!
How many men are in the plant?
Sosa!
Freeze.
- Freeze?
- I'm just following orders.
They told me to shoot if you moved.
I know very dangerous people
all over the country.
Very dangerous.
One day, you'll be out on the street
and get hit by a truck.
Or one morning you'll wake up
crushed on the subway tracks.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you saying these things?
I pay my taxes right on time, okay?
I pay property tax,
where your paycheck comes from.
And you come at me like that,
using that passive-aggressive tone.
- With that thug face of yours.
- Passive-aggressive?
Why don't you just
breathe and relax, baby?
Hey, that can't be left like that.
It's dangerous.
It's so frustrating to turn on the TV,
the news, and it's the same every day.
Corruption here, corruption there.
You think,
"How can all these people be like this?"
It's not possible that
all of these people are such assholes.
Then you meet them,
and they really are assholes.
Why can't you step up?
Imagine what this country would be like
if you went to work and did things right.
DANGER - RADIOACTIVE MATERIAL
Let me go, and if you want…
No, shut the fuck up!
Either shut that fucking hole you've got,
or I'll put one in the back of your head!
Then I'll bury you 200 meters under.
I've got a lot of friends in the police,
and together we'll bury you.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Stop the fucking van!
Run!
Stop, motherfucker!
DANGEROUS INTERSECTION
Shoot him!
- What?
- Shoot him!
- For the news, dude.
- And let's see what my folks say.
Commissioner.
Sir, I just found out what's happening.
These officers acted on their own.
They disobeyed orders.
Let's give them an exemplary punishment.
Excuse me, sir.
Come on, inside.
Thanks to these men,
a dangerous international-level operation
was stopped, Commissioner.
I've always told my boys
to follow their gut.
A good cop must know
how to follow his instinct.
No, everything's in order. Yes.
We should just pick a day. Sure.
- Excuse me. Are you Díaz?
- Yeah.
Everything okay?
Yeah. Well, weird, but okay.
- Weird how?
- What do you think?
This guy's been in Intelligence
for over ten years,
and now he's putting together
a new international security outfit.
So, he made me tell him,
in excruciating detail,
everything that happened,
and he couldn't believe it.
He asked, "Wouldn't you like to join?"
Join what?
He's recruiting people
from different fields
to make independent cells
of two or three people.
That's where you and I would fit.
They'd give us
six to eight months of training.
As agent?
Yes.
I'm really happy for you, Díaz.
It's clearly a big opportunity
for your career.
But I've got a life.
A bit of a mess right now, sure.
I've got nothing to do with this.
Training for what? Shooting?
Shooting, yes, and everything else.
Martial arts, languages,
diving, parachuting.
Those international agencies are always
behind the darkest stuff in every country.
But they'll keep existing anyway.
Somebody's gotta do the job.
Wouldn't hurt to have
a couple of guys like us on the inside.
I've never been able to skip stones.
Can you believe it?
It's all in how you hold the rock.
Yeah, between your index finger and thumb.
Index and thumb.
What?
Nothing. This guy asked me
if maybe you were CIA or Mossad
because the way you climbed that building,
slipped in through the ledge and window,
and handled that submachine gun
didn't quite add up.
So once you finish the training,
do they give you a mission or what?
You're not, are you?
- What?
- A spy.
Come on, Díaz.
No, I mean, if you did all this
to catch those bastards,
respect, man.
- But I need to know the truth.
- What are you talking about?
Are you an international
intelligence agent? Yes or no?
Yes or no? Are you or are you not?
Yes or no?
Not yet.
How did you say to hold it?
Index and thumb.
Subtitle translation by: Francel Diaz