Downloaded from
YTS.MX
- Previously
on "The Rainmaker"...
- John would have been
a great lawyer.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
- So will you.
- When do you take the bar?
- Six weeks.
What's your name?
- Kelly.
- Donny Ray's doctor
is a recovering alcoholic.
His nurse is
a homicidal maniac.
- He had
Jackie Lemancyzk's address.
There's a genuine dispute
as to how Donny Ray died.
- No deal.
- You were really great today.
- She has a relationship
with this Baylor kid?
- Out of respect
for your father,
I'm gonna do you a favor.
- I'd say you owe him
a lot more than that.
- ♪ I'm here for the action ♪
- ♪ Whoo ♪
- ♪ I'm here for the whole
pie, not a fraction ♪
- ♪ G, A ♪
- ♪ Yeah, the road's rough,
but I'm moving with traction ♪
♪ Ain't nobody surpassing,
moving fast ♪
♪ Can't nobody come at 'em
or try to combat 'em ♪
♪ We get deep up
in these waters ♪
♪ You better tread lightly ♪
- ♪ Hey, hey ♪
- ♪ I can't be beat,
I go the hardest ♪
- ♪ Go the hardest ♪
- ♪ 'Cause it ain't nothing
like me ♪
- ♪ No, it ain't
nothing like ♪
- ♪ I'm always ready
for the showdown ♪
- ♪ Showdown ♪
- ♪ Now I don't run and hide ♪
- ♪ Run and hide,
run and hide ♪
♪ I'm showing up,
and I'ma show out ♪
♪ ♪
- Hey, Pop.
- [scoffs] You look like shit.
Sleeping okay?
- Well, I got one
against Leo Drummond.
- How's your case?
- It's a fish.
- So settle.
What's the problem?
- When Leo was working me,
he made it a point
to mention you.
- Me?
[scoffs] Why me?
- Clearly, he thought it
meant more than the money
he was offering.
Why is that?
- Listen, Bruiser,
you need to settle the case,
whatever Leo is offering.
- I need to know
everything you did for him.
- In 22 years, I did plenty.
- I'm not settling.
- That's a mistake.
- You already ate
this case for him.
What's he got on you?
No more riddles.
- Jocelyn, I'm free in a month.
Don't go making trouble.
- Well, if you won't talk
to me, maybe Prince will.
- You don't talk
to Prince about this.
Understand?
- I don't work for you anymore,
Pop--I can help you.
- Guard.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Just remember--
everything I ever did
was to protect you.
- From what?
♪ ♪
[door buzzes, clanks]
[country rock music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Ice cold,
know I'm on the way ♪
♪ I can feel a change,
ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ I know it'll come around ♪
♪ So I double down,
ah, ah, ah... ♪
- Are you serious?
Come here.
- Hi.
- Not bad, Plankmore.
- ♪ My sweet time,
ice cold... ♪
- Your parents got you this?
- Well, the firm did.
But, um--
- Tinley Britt
bought you a house?
A first-year associate?
- I mean, it's just a rental,
but, um--but I made mimosas.
Come here. I want to show you
the bedroom.
- The bedroom?
- "Step into my parlor,"
said the spider to the fly.
♪ ♪
- Wow.
- Mm-hmm.
You like it?
You can leave a toothbrush here
if you want.
- I only have the one.
I'm just kidding.
- Mm.
Wait, I have a surprise.
♪ ♪
- What's this?
- Open it.
- Sarah--
- Just--just open it.
♪ ♪
So it should fit like a glove,
but I figure you could wear it
to your first deposition.
You know, announce
your presence with authority.
As they say, you know,
dress for the job you want,
not for the job
you have, right?
- Right.
♪ ♪
- You hate it.
- No.
No.
No, I love it.
I-I mean, it--it's just--
it's nice.
I can't afford
clothing like this.
- Yeah, I-I know.
I know, but I can.
Just let me do
something nice for you.
You don't have to dress
like them, Rudy.
- [scoffs] "Like them"?
- Look, this is
all just temporary.
You're gonna work
your way back.
- To what? To Tinley Britt?
I doubt it.
- No, to a big firm doing
what you were meant to do.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
- Try it on.
- Now?
- Yes, please.
Try it on. Fashion show.
I'll grab the mimosas.
[footsteps departing]
- Hi, I'm Daniel,
and I'm an alcoholic.
[all greeting]
I finally saw
my daughter today.
Most of you know,
it's been six long months.
I got to play with her
while that goddamn woman
from the court watched us--
my own daughter.
Not too close, of course.
- [whispering]
We shouldn't be here.
- [whispering] Anybody
can attend these things.
- It's called
Alcoholics Anonymous--
key word being "anonymous."
It's secret.
- It's not like it's church.
- We are literally sitting
in a church.
- That's semantics.
both: Shh!
- Yeah, shh.
- He liked to say addiction
was the disease of relapse.
Well, so is parenthood.
And I relapsed.
I want to be her dad again.
[applause]
- Would anyone else
like to share?
- Thank you, Daniel.
- Hey.
You're new.
- Yeah.
Just feeling
this thing out, you know?
- Any questions, hit me up.
- You know,
I was kind of wondering,
as a doctor,
can you tell someone's high
just by looking at 'em?
- It depends on the person.
- Really?
So, I mean, if I were
on smack right now,
you might not even know.
- I never said I was a doctor.
- Did you not? I could--
Did he not?
- Wait, no, I-I thought
I heard you say that, too.
- Assholes!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Hey, take it easy, okay?
- You're the lawyers
for the hospital?
- No, we're--
I am a lawyer.
- Right, from Tinley Britt,
the leeches who do
the hospital's dirty work?
- Hey, listen, listen,
there is no reason
to get physical here, right?
We are in a church.
- I told your colleague, that
icy bitch in the suit and tie,
that I haven't seen Jackie
since she was fired.
- The truth is Jackie's been
a little hard to reach.
- Right.
- We were just hoping
you might be able to steer us
her way.
A recent address maybe?
- How would I know?
She wouldn't give me the time
of day, let alone her address.
Why don't you ask
her ex-boyfriend?
He's all she'd ever talk about.
- Of course, the ex.
He's, um--[snapping fingers]
What's his--
- No, it's, uh--
You know what?
I left my notepad in the car.
- Charlie Stern.
- Right.
- Now get the hell out of here
before I call the police.
- All right, relax.
Come on.
Good luck with your daughter.
Jackie was one of two nurses
who treated our client's son.
It's important
that we find her.
- What's Jackie mixed up in?
Is she in trouble?
- It's just
a lawsuit, Mr. Stern.
We're, uh--we might need her
as a witness.
- It must be one hell
of a lawsuit
because this is the second time
someone's knocked on my door.
- Is that right?
Who knocked first?
- Well, she didn't give a name.
She just said she was
an investigator or something.
- Kind of icy,
in a suit and tie?
- [chuckles] That's her.
- You know, uh, Jackie moved
out of her apartment,
but she didn't leave
a forwarding address.
Do you guys know where
she might have moved to?
- Well, like I said
to that woman,
I haven't heard
from Jackie in weeks.
- You stayed in touch
since you split up, right?
- Yeah, we stayed friends.
Yeah.
- Friends, my ass.
She may as well have slept
between us.
- Amber.
- Don't "Amber" me.
Jackie's not my problem,
and she is not yours either.
- Amber, I swear to God--
- Look, we really need
to find Jackie,
but we don't want
to cause any trouble.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
That's Jackie's job.
- Jackie, uh, she took Amber
and my marriage pretty hard.
I tried to be her friend,
but she's--
- Whiny and pathetic.
[slurping]
- Okay, so you guys--
you have our card.
- If you hear from her,
will you pass along our info?
- Sure, yeah.
- Great.
Thanks a ton.
- We done?
- Yeah.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- Jackie, what have you
gotten yourself into?
[horn honking, cars passing]
- I've done a ton
of mock depos.
- "Mock depos."
Stop, my nipples
are getting hard.
- I don't understand. Why--
- Because the doctor is
at the heart of our case.
Because a multimillion-dollar
lawsuit hinges
on what we get out of him.
So he will definitely not be
the first person
you ever depose.
- Okay, when was he born?
- Who?
- Donny Ray Black.
When was he born?
- November 29, 1994.
- So you know he was born
with a heart murmur?
- Is that relevant?
- Oh, it shouldn't be.
Disappeared when he was 5.
But the other side, they will
try to hammer us with it.
- Okay, great, so you know
a couple things.
I'll get up to speed.
- I'm sure you're aware that
Donny was a straight-A student,
starting forward
on the Jackson High
basketball team
till his senior year
when he broke his wrist.
His doctor prescribed Vicodin,
then reupped him six times,
no questions asked.
That's probably what led
to his first addiction.
Admitted to North City General
the day he died
at 5'9", 160 pounds,
red blood cell count,
5.9 cells per microliter,
resting heart rate, 85 BPM, and
blood pressure, 80 over palp.
But you know all this, right?
[footsteps departing]
- Now my nipples are hard.
[door opens]
[dramatic music]
- I swear, I'll pay you back.
- All these people
asking questions, Jackie--
what did you do?
- I was trying to do
the right thing.
- Why didn't you go
to the police?
- I-I wanted to. I just--I--
- Well, you still can.
- You're the only one I trust.
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry.
If Amber finds out--
- I know. I-I'm leaving.
♪ ♪
Thanks for everything, Charlie.
[door opens, closes]
♪ ♪
- You again?
- Dr. Mulvaney.
- You know each other?
- He's the asshole
you people sent
to spy on me at my AA meeting.
- Yeah, he's opposing counsel.
- You said you were
with Tinley Britt.
- You've got to be kidding me.
- We never actually said that.
- No, we didn't say that.
- I wonder if the man
who bought that suit
would approve of your behavior.
♪ ♪
- It's my brother's suit.
[door closes]
- Okay.
You just let Drummond
into your head.
Look at me.
You cannot be thinking
about anything
other than
what you're here to do.
Got it?
- Got it.
- Come on.
♪ ♪
- The tox screen
I ordered came back positive
for morphine.
- Did you or anyone
on the nursing staff
give Donny Ray morphine?
- No, the only way this patient
overdosed on drugs
is if he came into the hospital
with them already
in his system.
- How could you possibly
know that unless you were
in his room every minute?
- Common sense.
- Well, how often did
you check on Donny Ray
after he was admitted?
- Three times.
- And how many patients do you
usually see during your shift?
- Typical night, 60 to 70.
- That's a lot of bodies
to keep track of.
- That's the job.
- How's Karen Horton doing?
- Who?
- Karen.
She came in with head trauma
from a car accident.
You don't remember her?
- Objection, relevance.
- This isn't a trial.
He still has to answer
the question.
- Is that true?
- Yeah.
- Um...
yes, now I do.
- Um, what did you do for her?
- I ordered her an MRI.
- You recall doing that?
- Yes, absolutely.
- I'm sorry.
See, I've got this wrong.
It says here
all the--all the victims
were brought
to Charleston General.
She was never
a patient of yours.
- Dirty trick.
- I agree.
Bruiser, can you please
get control of this?
- I think he's doing
just great.
- I can't remember
every patient
who comes through those doors.
- The azaleas.
- Am I deposing him,
or am I deposing you?
- I remember your client, okay?
He had azaleas in his room.
I'm allergic.
Every time I went in to see
him, I couldn't stop sneezing.
- You know you can just
stick your hand up his ass
so you can operate
his mouth easier.
- That's good.
That's on the record.
- Doctor, what time
was Donny Ray Black
admitted to the hospital?
- 6:00 p.m.
- Two of the nurses
who treated Donny Ray,
ER Nurse Melvin Pritcher
and ICU Nurse Jackie Lemancyzk,
no longer work
for North City General.
Do you find that curious?
- Objection, leading.
- Again, he has to answer.
- Critical-care nurses
suffer a high burnout rate.
Ever have someone's life
in your hands?
- Is that why Nurse Lemancyzk
was fired?
- I wouldn't know.
- No?
I have one more question,
Doctor.
Do you require supervision
treating your patients?
- What?
- A court requires it when you
visit your own daughter, right?
- Okay!
We're finished.
Nice job, Bruiser.
This circus...
[door opens]
- [exhales sharply]
- Nice job.
They have a credibility problem
with that doctor.
I wouldn't be surprised if they
came back with a bigger offer.
Why'd you ask what time
Donny Ray was admitted?
- The azaleas.
Dot wasn't told her son was in
the hospital until he was dead,
and even if she was,
the fact he wasn't admitted
until 6:00 p.m.--
- The azaleas weren't his.
- So he must have had
a roommate.
- And a roommate is a witness.
- The hospital will never give
us his name--HIPAA violation.
- You know who's
not bound by HIPAA?
Florists.
[upbeat rock music]
All right.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Make a big racket
and cause a scene... ♪
[line trilling]
- Hey, how you doing today?
Uh, I was a patient
at North City General
the week of August 25th,
and my roommate had this
amazing arrangement of azaleas.
You don't sell azaleas?
Sorry for bugging you.
One down.
- ♪ Long, long road ♪
[distant telephone ringing]
- Mary, hi.
- Sarah, don't you look lovely.
Sorry to bother you
in the middle of your work day.
- Oh, no.
No, no, no, don't be silly.
- I was in the area
and thought I'd surprise Rudy,
but the receptionist couldn't
find his name in the system.
- Yeah, yeah, well, she's new,
um, and the system--
it's a little glitchy.
So all this money,
you'd think we'd have a better
internal directory, right?
[chuckles]
- Mm. So where is he?
- He's in court...
like, all afternoon.
[door opens]
- Oh, that's a shame.
[door closes]
- Yeah, I know, he's gonna be
upset he missed you.
- Hello, Sarah.
- Brad, hi.
- Hello, I'm Brad Noonan.
I work with Sarah.
- Mary Baylor.
Pleased to meet you.
- Baylor? You're not related
to Rudy Baylor?
- Yes, he's my son.
- He seemed like
a fine young man.
We were sorry to see him go.
[serious music]
♪ ♪
- Well, I should be going.
- Very nice to meet you.
♪ ♪
- I'll--I'll tell Rudy that--
- I'll tell him.
♪ ♪
- Oh, good.
Come in.
- I brought my notes
from the depo.
- Sit down.
- Your, uh...
boyfriend likes
to play fast and loose.
- I was just
as surprised as you.
- Clearly.
- We don't talk about work.
- I guess you must find
other things to discuss.
Close your eyes.
- I'm sorry?
- Close your eyes.
Okay, picture this.
You're a senior partner
handling an incredible
workload,
managing a team
of extremely talented lawyers.
"The National Law Journal"
calls.
They want to make you
Lawyer of the Year.
Naturally, there's a dinner
to which you invite
all the people
you most respect and admire
to join you at that table.
♪ ♪
Here's the question.
Is Rudy Baylor beside you?
♪ ♪
- Of course.
- If you say so.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[footsteps approaching]
- Your mother came
by the office today.
She thinks you still work
at Tinley Britt.
- [sighs]
Shit.
- I was planning
on telling her.
I wanted to get
through the bar exam.
- It was awful.
- You want to talk about what
happened at the deposition?
- [scoffs]
Definitely not.
We both just need
to pass the bar tomorrow.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry you don't like
your suit.
♪ ♪
[footsteps departing]
- The first session
of the bar exam
is a mix of constitutional law,
civil procedure,
torts, evidence, contracts,
real property,
and criminal law and procedure.
Then a one-hour break
and return
for another three-hour session.
♪ ♪
You may open your laptops now.
[clock ticking rapidly]
[ticking slowing]
[vehicle tires screeching]
[loud crash]
♪ ♪
[haunting piano music playing]
[plays off-key]
- This is the one
Dad gave you, right?
- I-I can't.
It's yours.
- Now it's yours.
Go on.
[haunting piano music playing]
♪ ♪
- "A woman employed
"by a federally funded
educational institution
filed a retaliation complaint
under Title IX."
♪ ♪
[music stops]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- Hey.
The, uh--
the civil-procedure question
on negligent maintenance...
- They couldn't retry
because of res judicata?
Please say yes.
- Yeah.
[upbeat rock music]
- How long till we got to go
back in?
- ♪ See you comin' for me,
I'm not... ♪
- 20 minutes.
- ♪ I'm an expert
at this part ♪
♪ Not my first time
at a rodeo ♪
♪ Where I've rumbled
with the best ♪
♪ Come out on top ♪
♪ You're gonna wish
we hadn't met ♪
- Wait.
How did you answer the
fertile-octogenarian question?
- Really?
- ♪ You shouldn't mess
with me ♪
♪ Because I'm dangerous ♪
- Wait, what--what do you mean
you never deliver
to North City?
You're--you're called
Flowers Everywhere.
[line beeps]
Yeah, I just want to clarify.
You're--you're called
All Flowers,
but you don't sell azaleas.
Okay.
Well, maybe you should just
be called Some Flowers.
Not--no, no, not Sunflowers.
You don't sell those either.
♪ ♪
Hey, how you doing?
Quick question--
do you guys deliver
to North City General?
- Can I help you?
- We're looking for Bruiser.
- Really? Well, I'm sure
you guys don't sell azaleas.
You do?
Great. Well, how good
are your records?
- Take a seat.
♪ ♪
Hey, I think
I found our florist!
- You've got visitors.
- I can see that.
- They're FBI.
- I can see that, too.
♪ ♪
- Agents.
- Cistulli.
She's Cutler.
- Can I get you anything?
Coffee, water, shot of bourbon?
- Thanks, but we've got
something for you.
[liquid pours, glass clinks]
- You know who that is?
- [inhales deeply]
Rosalie Sutton.
She's the reason
my father's in prison.
- Your father's in prison
because he arranged
for her to leave the country
before she could testify.
- So I've heard.
- Did you ever meet Miss Sutton
prior to her disappearance?
- The transcripts
are freely available
if you want to read
my testimony.
Never met her.
- Would it surprise you
to hear that she's dead?
- We got a credible tip that
Rosalie Sutton was murdered.
- I also have a credible tip.
Unless a U.S. Marshal serves me
a subpoena, we're done here.
- [clears throat]
You need to get out of this.
- I only need three things--
Kentucky bourbon,
a bloody steak...
and a man
who won't spend the night.
Try it, Agent Cutler.
It might loosen you up
a little.
[door opens]
[dramatic music]
[door closes]
♪ ♪
[knocking on door]
- We have to talk.
- Uh-oh.
This sounds serious.
- It is.
- I got a fresh pot of coffee.
- Sure.
- So...
it's about the kid?
- Oh, no,
Rudy's doing just fine.
[coffee pouring]
It's about my father.
- I see.
- FBI's been sniffing around.
What'd you two get me
mixed up in?
- Look, your father's in prison
for witness tampering.
Now, everything you need
to know came out in that case.
- Yeah, then why
are they in my face?
- Look, if they had something,
they'd be in my face.
- Prince...
where is Rosalie Sutton?
- You don't want to say
that name out loud again.
- Where is she?
- Bruiser, I'm gonna
answer this one time
and one time only.
I don't know.
Now, that's the God's honest.
I have no idea.
And that's the end
of this conversation.
You know I love you, Bruiser.
I always have, always will.
[indistinct chatter]
[light music]
- Hey, um, I'll--
I'll catch up with you.
Hi.
- Did we just do this?
- Yeah, we just did it.
- How'd it go?
- Uh, good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Who's your friend?
- Um, she's a--she's
an associate at Tinley Britt.
Um, look, a bunch
of us were gonna go out
for drinks to celebrate.
You want to go?
- Yeah, come on.
Hey, you know what?
I'm, uh--
Do you mind?
I think I'm just gonna go home,
grab something to eat,
and pass out.
- Are you sure?
- Totally.
I'll call you, though, okay?
- Okay.
Only if you're sure.
♪ ♪
[softly]
Are we okay?
♪ ♪
- Yeah, of course.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
- ♪ Everyone I love ♪
♪ Holds me down ♪
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Thanks.
See you guys tomorrow?
- Yeah.
- ♪ Are my plans too hip? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Did I hold you
long enough? ♪
♪ Did I not seem real? ♪
♪ ♪
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- What do you mean? I just--
- What, are you following me?
- Following you?
No.
I was driving by.
I-I saw you.
The bus sucks.
[distant engine revving]
- Okay. Thanks.
[door rattles]
- Sorry, hold on.
It always does that.
[door rattling, opens]
You laughing at my ride?
- I don't even have one.
- You do now.
[car door closes]
So...
what is that place?
- It's a spa.
[radio clicks on,
pop country music plays]
♪ ♪
- It's old-school radio.
- I took the bar exam today.
- How'd it go?
- Yeah. Good.
♪ ♪
I think, I mean...
you never know, you know?
- So you're a lawyer now?
- [knocking on dashboard]
Hope so.
♪ ♪
- That spa says it's open
till 2:00 a.m.
- Can you drop me off here?
- I'm sorry.
It's really not my business.
- It's not that.
I just need to get out here.
- We're just a few blocks away.
- I know.
♪ ♪
- You don't want your husband
to see me driving you.
♪ ♪
[brakes squeal]
- Thanks for the ride.
- Kelly.
- Night, Rudy.
Cliff?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[lock clicks]
[zipper opens]
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
- What the hell?
You want to get the hell
out of my place?
- I wanted to see what you see
when you're watching my wife
through your window.
- I'm not watching.
These apartments are close.
- If I ever see your face
in that window again...
♪ ♪
You're a dead man.
- ♪ Lord, yeah ♪
[upbeat rock music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, I miss that smell
of sex and vomit.
- You have food on your face.
- I do?
Oh.
This is why I buy them
off the rack--
just a little tip for you.
Hey, Ross. Hey.
Thanks for coming down.
Appreciate it.
- No worries, man. Who are you?
- Hey, uh, we represent
the family of Donny Ray Black.
You shared a room
with him, right?
North City General,
night he died.
- Sorry, I-I really don't know
anything about that.
- Hey, whoa, wait.
Donny Ray was just
a little older than you.
And his mom--she's a mess.
She needs closure.
Anything you can tell us--
it'd mean a lot to her.
- [sighs]
All right.
Look, I was really out of it.
I was coming down
from anesthesia after surgery.
- Yeah, what'd you, uh--
what'd you have surgery for?
- A condition called torsion.
It's no biggie.
- What, you mean
testicular torsion?
My second cousin had that.
He had to have one of his...
balls removed.
- You know what--
- Well, hey, sorry.
Right? We're very sorry.
- Yes, we are very sorry...
- Sorry.
- About your ball.
- Your hospital roommate...
we just want to ask you
about what you saw.
Can you show him Donny?
- Yeah.
- You recognize him?
Yeah, except he wasn't smiling.
He was messed up.
- Yeah.
Do you remember anyone else
coming into the room
that night?
- Sure. Doctors and nurses
came in all night long.
- Any names?
- No names, but, uh,
there was a nurse
who kept waking me up
to take my temp.
- This her?
- Yeah, yeah.
She came in four or five times,
checked on me and your guy.
- Right.
- Anyone else?
- There was a douchebag doctor
who wanted the flowers that
my mom sent out of the room.
- Yeah, we, uh--
we know that guy.
- This guy?
- Yep. Yeah, yeah. That's him.
- Yeah. Yeah, now did you see
him give your roommate
any meds?
- No, not him, a-another guy.
- Wait, what?
You saw another doctor
giving him meds?
- Uh, a nurse, a male nurse.
He came in and started
changing his medication.
- How did he do that?
- He injected something
into his IV bag.
- You got to be very clear
with us right now.
You're sure about that?
It was not the flower hater?
- No, man, a nurse--
like, a bigger guy.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, that's him.
I, uh, heard him whisper
to your guy...
"It's okay, I'm a nurse,"
which... [scoffs]
Creeped me out a little,
if I'm honest.
[chuckles]
- Thank you, Ross, truly.
We really appreciate it.
- Thank you.
This isn't
a negligence suit anymore.
It's murder.
- So your theory is--
Pritcher waltzes
into Donny Ray Black's room
and injects him with morphine?
- He wasn't even supposed
to be upstairs.
There's no reason
for an ER nurse
to be anywhere near
admitted patients.
- Boss, we got this.
Dial M for murder
and Maserati--
as in the one I will be buying
with our settlement dough.
- Well, you might want to dial
another M for maybe,
which is our chance
of actually proving this.
Did you get the security cams?
- No, the hospital wipes
the footage every 72 hours.
- So we will just bring in...
- Ross Cho.
- Uniball to testify.
- We're gonna need a lot more
than an anesthetized teenager.
Drummond will turn him
inside out on cross.
- How about a suspicious
heart attack?
If we can tie Melvin
to Roberta Caracas--
- Yes, Jackie Lemancyzk's
neighbor, right?
If we can tie Pritcher
to her death--
- That's quite a leap.
- Guys, we got to call
the police
before he kills somebody else.
both: No.
Not yet,
not until we can firm this up.
- Deck, see if you can get
the neighbor's autopsy results.
- "Autopsy"?
We don't have time for that.
We're looking at homicide.
You don't think that's
why Drummond is so eager
to make this case disappear?
His client is guilty
of criminal conspiracy.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- [singing along]
♪ And just like the pavement ♪
♪ After a hard rain ♪
♪ ♪
[car rumbling]
♪ Don't worry about nothin' ♪
♪ A new day keeps comin' ♪
♪ ♪
- Shit.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
[cell phone beeps]
[brakes squealing]
♪ ♪
- I've got a flat.
Would you mind giving me
a ride?
[sinister music]
- Sure.
♪ ♪
- [sighs, scoffs]
- I wasn't gonna come,
but I thought...
for old time's sake,
I would hear you out.
- I had a visit from the FBI.
- Hmm.
- But, of course,
you knew that.
- How would I know that?
- Whatever you think
you're doing, it won't work.
- I'm not doing anything.
But, uh, if I were, the fact
that we're both sitting here
would suggest that,
in fact, it is working.
- I'm gonna bail you out, Leo.
- Really?
- For old time's sake.
I'm willing
to settle this case.
- Good. I think it's a very
generous offer.
- Oh, no, you misunderstand me.
I have an offer for you.
Call off the FBI,
and I'll convince my client
to settle with the hospital...
for $80 million.
- [scoffs]
Did you drag me out here
to play games?
- Melvin Pritcher's
a murderer.
He killed Donny Ray Black, and
you and your client know it.
$80 million.
- That Sarah tells a good lie.
You'll want to watch out
for that.
- She was just trying
to protect me.
What the hell is this?
You're smoking again?
- I guess we both have secrets.
- I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you,
but I needed to figure out
my next move first.
- What happened?
- I, uh...
I got into it
with a senior partner.
Mom, it was stupid,
but I'm still a lawyer.
I'm just starting out
at a different kind of firm.
- This firm...
they reputable?
- Yeah, they have a reputation.
- [scoffs] I see.
What kind of law?
- Do you remember that case
I told you about--
lawsuit against the hospital?
That is real.
It's my case. I brought it in.
I found it.
It's actually something you
might be quite interested in.
It's a mother
fighting for her son.
I just didn't want
to let you down, Mom.
Ever since John died--
- Uh, stop right there.
You don't get to use
your dead brother
to squeeze out of a jam
you made yourself.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Is Hank not in?
- He's gone.
- "Gone"?
- I kicked him out.
And that's that.
♪ ♪
[waves crashing]
[knock at door]
- Prince.
It's the middle of the night.
- Look, your father needs you
to watch someone
for a few days.
- Absolutely not.
♪ ♪
- Bruiser,
say hello to Rosalie.
[baby toy jingles,
baby cooing softly]
♪ ♪
- Right now...
I just need you
to get real loose.
Get comfortable.
[hissing]
♪ Go on and do the two-step,
then cowboy boogie ♪
♪ Grab your sweetheart
and spin out with 'em ♪
♪ Do the hoedown
and get into it ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Take it to the left now
and dip with it ♪
♪ Go on, throw down,
take a sip with it ♪
♪ And lean back,
put your hips in it ♪
Let's have some fun.
♪ To the left,
to the left... ♪
[sinister music]
♪ Now take your left hand
and put it on your side ♪
- ♪ Put it on your side ♪
- ♪ Go on,
roll your shoulders ♪
- ♪ Roll your shoulders ♪
- ♪ Do the slip and slide ♪
- ♪ This next part
is my favorite part ♪
♪ 'Cause it's time to shine ♪
♪ Go on and do the two-step,
then cowboy boogie ♪
♪ Grab your sweetheart
and spin out with 'em ♪
♪ Do the hoedown
and get into it ♪
- ♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh-ooh ♪