Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[female voice]
We have apprehended
a dangerous threat
in one of our very own labs.
-[crowd gasping]
-Quiet!
We believe that this...
this monstrosity...
-[snoring]
-[crowd gasping]
...is the product of illegal
genetic experimentation.
What deranged lunatic would
create something like this?
[alien grunts, clears throat]
I prefer "deranged genius,"
but thank you
for the introduction.
Dr. Jumba Jookiba,
you were tasked
with safely studying
biological threats,
not creating them.
A threat?
-Experiment 626...
-[glass clanging]
...is our federation's
most sophisticated weapon.
-[growling]
-[crowd gasping]
626 is unstoppable.
Indestructible.
[laughs]
And smarter
than 100 supercomputers.
-[speaking Tantalog]
-I don't wanna play anymore!
It's an atrocity!
-Destroy it!
-I can't even look at him.
He should be exiled.
[leader] Silence!
He did not ask to be created.
Perhaps, if he is
so intelligent,
he has the capacity to reason.
Experiment 626, show us
that there is something
inside you
that is good.
[speaking Tantalog]
[clears throat]
[crowd gasping]
So naughty.
Throwing up. Throwing up.
I did not teach him that.
You have made
our decision easy.
He is clearly the flawed
product of a deranged mind.
Dr. Jookiba,
your lab will be destroyed.
Okay. Just leave me 626.
And 626 exiled.
Oh, come on!
-Bailiff.
-Wait.
No, no, no, no!
You can't do that.
No!
[grunts] Huh?
-[gasps]
-Don't get any ideas.
These guns are locked on
your genetic signature.
They're not gonna shoot anyone
but you.
[laughs]
Hmm. Oh.
Knock it off! Federation
strictly forbids being gross.
Don't make me say it-- Ew!
[guns charging up]
Uh-oh.
-[alarms blaring]
-[leader] Where is he?
He's loose on Deck C.
[officer]
Now heading for the hull.
What?
He's trying
to find the police...
[laughs, blows raspberry,
chuckles]
...cruisers.
He, uh... He took the red one.
Fire at will!
[cackles]
He's in hyperspace.
Where will he exit?
In 12 hours,
we project he will collide
with a planet called "E-arth."
That's a planet full of water.
Water increases
his molecular density.
[aliens] Uh...
He'll become heavy and drown.
Oh!
So I think we can all say
farewell to 62...
You're kidding.
-[alarms blaring]
-[all sighing]
Oh, what a pickle
we've got here! [chuckles]
If only there was
a brilliant genius around
to help you catch
that monster.
You! You're the reason
we're in this mess.
And I could get you out of it.
If you release me
and give me back my lab.
Nonsense. We'll simply
vaporize the planet. Captain.
Armed and ready,
Councilwoman.
Hold it! Hold everything!
Excuse me. Sorry.
Excuse me. Pardon me.
You can't destroy the planet!
Aw, man.
Uh, who's this?
Agent Pleakley.
Earth expert at your service.
Howdy.
"Earth expert"?
I'm an expert in that planet's
flora, fauna and fashion.
Yeah, this outfit
screams "expert."
Yeah. I'm researching
an Earth species
that's half-cow and half-boy.
-It's quite fascinating--
-Yes, marvelous.
What's your point?
Oh, uh, Earth is
a protected wildlife reserve.
We've been using it to rebuild
the mosquito population.
[sighs] Crikey. Very well.
Dr. Jookiba, you will travel
to Earth, where you will
capture the escaped
lab experiment known as 626.
Agent Pleakley,
you will be going with him.
You are deputized to ensure
he follows Federation rules.
What?
I don't need a babysitter.
This is all very dangerous,
and it's likely you'll die.
Do you accept?
[breathes heavily]
With every heart in my body,
of course I accept!
I'm going to Earth!
Hey, everyone!
-If I may...
-Thank you, thank you.
-Can I hug you?
-No.
-Can I hug--
Sorry. Permission to hug
the Grand Councilwoman?
-That's not going to happen.
-Of course. My apologies.
I do not need supervision.
You have asked...
Permission to hug
my new partner?
Brilliant. Permission granted.
So what I'm just trying
to say is, I--
It would just be better
if I went by myself.
Do not let the Earthlings
discover your mission,
or I will be forced
to intervene.
This is a dream vacay.
[gasps]
I have so much packing to do!
Well, well, well, 626.
What hideous, pathetic planet
is caught in your crosshairs?
[♪ "He Mele No Lilo" playing]
[breathing through mask]
Let's go snorkeling later.
Yeah, that's a great idea.
I know, right? So cool.
They have the best sandwiches.
Are you supposed to be here?
I'm in town
for the convention.
Cool.
You're free! Go, go!
Live your lives!
No, no, no! No! Lilo.
Not again.
They deserve to be free!
Lilo!
I'm gonna have to talk
to Nani about this.
[watch alarm beeping]
[screams] Sorry!
Sorry, sorry. Sorry.
[phone ringing]
Hey, Jimmy's Luau.
Hey, brother.
-Go, go. Hurry.
-Sorry.
Hey. You're gonna be late.
Yeah.
[dancer] Where is she?
She's always late.
[teacher]
Has anyone seen Lilo?
Lilo, thank goodness.
I thought you were gonna
be on time today.
I had to get a sandwich
for Pudge.
Is Pudge a friend in need?
He's a fish.
I forgot to tell you that.
So, you're late because
you fed a sandwich to a fish?
Yeah.
Pudge controls the weather.
[chuckles] She's so weird.
Lilo, honey, come on.
Get dressed, honey.
Oh, guys, look.
I got
a friendship bracelet too.
[dancer] That's not
a friendship bracelet.
Ew, garbage girl
puts garbage on her arm.
Girls, hāmau. Hoʻomākaukau.
Come on.
You know, silly,
it's not a friendship bracelet
if you don't have any friends.
Girls, girls, girls.
Hui! Kulikuli.
Stand in line. Get ready.
[engine sputters]
No, no, no.
Okay, not today.
She's not coming.
[audience murmuring]
-[dancer screams]
-[audience clamoring]
-Kumu!
-[attendee] Who's her parents?
Girls, go.
[attendee 1]
She acts up all the time.
[attendee 2] Somebody
needs to look after her.
She's always causing trouble.
[attendee 1]
She's just not a good fit.
Kumu, where is her sister?
That's the real question here.
[teacher] It's a delicate
home situation for Lilo.
She's not a bad kid.
She just needs--
[attendee 1]
I don't know, Kumu.
I just don't know.
[attendee 2]
She disrupts the class
and ruined
today's performance.
♪ Well, since my baby left me ♪
♪ Well, I've found a new place
To dwell ♪
♪ Well, it's down at the end
Of Lonely Street ♪
[muffled]
♪ At Heartbreak Hotel ♪
♪ I'll be so lonely, baby ♪
♪ I'll be so lonely... ♪
Lilo? Can you please
open the door?
Read the note!
[groans]
I'm sorry I missed
your performance.
-Pāpā's truck died.
-Blah, blah. Wow!
That must be
so stressful for you.
How about you just
leave me alone to die?
No, no, no. Not now, not now.
[horn honks]
The social worker is here.
You can pout later, Lilo.
That's not how pouting works.
[Nani] Lilo, open the door.
I can't hear you.
It's really weird.
Open the door
or I'm breaking it down!
Hey, what is wrong with you?
-[clears throat]
-Uh...
Mrs. Kekoa.
Hi. Um, nice to see you.
Can I, uh, help you
carry anything in?
I'm okay. [chuckles]
Can I help you
carry anything in?
Oh, yeah. Would you mind
if we just, um,
just use the back?
It's just, uh, just right--
We're in the back.
[grunts]
[chuckles]
These old houses, right?
You just gotta have the...
the touch!
Oh! Oh...
There we go! Um... Actually,
would you mind waiting here
for just a second?
-Yes, of course.
-Okay.
-Hey! Don't touch that.
-No, I don't wanna hear it.
-That's mine.
-I'm turning it off right now.
[music stops]
So, uh, what can I
get you to drink?
Do you have tea?
Course I have...
There's a lot
of unpaid bills here, Nani.
[groans]
How often would you say
you leave your little sister
home alone?
What? No. I... No.
Why would I do that? I...
I would never leave
my sister alone. [chuckles]
[Mrs. Kekoa] Smoke, Nani!
-Oh! Oh, uh...
-The alarm! The smoke alarm!
Oh, don't worry.
There's no batteries in there.
Lilo! [chuckles]
I took 'em out
because it kept going off.
[chuckles] That's not true.
Say aloha to Mrs. Kekoa.
Aloha, Lilo. How are you?
Is that blood?
Oh, yeah, I've been practicing
jumping out of my window.
Ha! She's... She's kidding.
She's actually been
very well behaved recently.
Haven't you, right?
[gasps]
Yeah,
I've been more than good,
Mrs. Kekoa.
I've been doing very,
very great at hula.
Made a ton
of new friends there,
and they all think
I'm the coolest.
I've been eating
a lot of organic stuff.
Sometimes I eat too much.
And I've been eating
five or ten times a day.
Sometimes I eat so much, I...
can't...
-breathe.
-[laughs]
That's enough imagination
for you, you little weirdie.
-[microwave dings]
-Oh, tea's ready.
Hmm. Okay, pretty sweet.
Okay, Nani, we both know
this didn't go well today.
I can see you're trying,
but you're too smart for me
to beat around the bush here.
I know it hasn't
been that long
since your parents
passed away,
but my job is to make sure
that Lilo is in
a stable environment.
And I can't say that
in good conscience right now.
Listen, I know this is a lot.
You're practically
a kid yourself.
[māmā] What happened
to knocking?
[Lilo and Nani] We decided
it was a surf day!
-[family cheering, laughing]
-[māmā] A surf day?
Look, you seem like
a goal-oriented person.
We have a new director coming
into town next week,
and I would really,
really love to tell him
that you girls
have turned the corner.
So, why don't we come up with
some goals to achieve by then?
Yeah, yeah.
All right, here.
Three things.
First, I want this house
cleaned, including laundry,
-and a fully-stocked fridge.
-Perfect.
Second, pay all those bills
I saw in the kitchen.
Yes.
And third,
file for health insurance
for you and Lilo.
Got it.
If you do those three things
by Friday,
I might be able
to give you some more time.
Thank you.
Okay.
It was Capri Sun, yeah?
-Yeah.
-I figured.
[Mrs. Kekoa] And
don't forget the insurance.
[Nani chuckles]
Yeah, yeah. You got it.
You're gonna need
that health insurance
for when I kill you!
[screaming]
[Nani growls]
Oh, yeah.
We took out
the smoke alarm batteries.
I'll show you "can't breathe."
Come here!
-[screams] Let go of me!
-Yeah, no.
Ow. Okay.
No, no, no.
Why didn't you wait at hula?
Because you weren't there.
Do you want them
to split us up?
Because that's what's
gonna happen
if we don't get it together.
Hey! Did you just lick me?
Stop pretending you're my mom.
Oh. At least I don't tell
the social worker
I like jumping out of windows.
It's better
than listening to you.
Go to your room!
I'm already in my room!
-[muffled screams]
-[screams]
[goat screams]
Hey, Alvin.
[Nani groans]
[ATV engine revs up]
There she is, Miss Aloha.
Yeah, not today she's not.
Meeting never go well.
I never liked
that government lady anyway.
Why is she always so smiley?
Give me the creeps.
Yeah, well,
our future is in her hands.
Ah, ah. None of that.
Your future is in your hands.
And you're gonna have
a very bright future
'cause of that
akamai brain of yours.
What?
Your acceptance letter
to your dream school
magically taken
out of your trash
and appearing in your bag
at your place of work?
Ooh, that's a sign, girl.
Will you stop with this?
That school is the best school
in the whole world
for that bionic magnets.
Bio... Marine biology.
Marine biology.
And they already
let you in once,
and they wanted
to give you for full ride.
Yeah, I know, but, Tūtū,
there's no way.
Lilo needs me here.
You ever ask Lilo
what she wants?
She's six, so, no.
Sorry, Tūtū.
Had to catch a few extra ones.
The swell was... Hey, Nani!
What are you doing here?
[Nani] I live here.
We're neighbors.
[chuckles] Yeah. Yeah,
that's... that's good. Uh...
The waves were crazy today.
You know, I was like,
"Nani should be here,"
'cause you're always, like,
shredding waves,
and I miss shredding you.
I mean, I miss...
I miss seeing you
shred waves, so...
Yeah.
I've always loved
watching you.
-Not to say that--
-Well said, David.
-Well.
-[David] So, like, when...
when are you gonna go surfing?
[Nani]
Maybe when Lilo turns 18.
Enjoy the surf.
Bebeh.
Now, make up
with your sister, yeah?
You need anything,
you just ask, okay?
We're not just neighbors,
you know.
We're ʻohana.
[ATV engine revs up]
-Yeah, I mean, if you want--
-No, no!
No, David, you've said enough.
[speaking indistinctly]
[space ship rumbling]
-[alarm beeping]
-[computer] Warning.
-Check engine.
-Hmm? [grunts]
[beeping stops]
-[alarm beeping]
-Warning. Check engine.
[beeping stops]
-[computer] Warning. Guidan--
-[grunting]
[chuckles, sighs]
-[alarms blaring]
-Guidance not functional.
Warning. Guidance not
functional. Warning.
Warning.
Guidance not functional.
Crash imminent.
Prepare for impact.
[speaking Tantalog]
[screams]
[knocking on door]
Hey. Think I might've nailed
those kalua sliders you like.
Here.
[groans]
You don't have to eat it.
Nani, am I bad?
What?
That's what everyone says.
Nobody says that.
Maybe some teachers
and school security guards.
Look, you're not bad.
You just do
bad things sometimes.
Just like me earlier,
when I yelled at you.
We just have to learn
from our mistakes.
I shoved Mertle Edmonds today.
I know.
You wanna tell me
what happened?
People treat me different.
[sighs] Baby, they just...
They just don't know
what to say.
But you...
you didn't mean what you said,
did you?
No. Of course not.
You're my sister.
And I'll always be here
for you. Okay?
You got that?
No more tickle town.
Yes, tickle town.
-Tickle town!
-I don't wanna go!
[Lilo] Will you still
be able to visit
when you join the Marines?
[Nani chuckles]
It's not the Marines.
It's marine biology.
Anyway, it's not
gonna happen anymore.
I'm staying right here.
Remember when we put up
those constellations?
[Nani] The Three Sisters.
That one's you. That's me.
And that one means,
"time for bed."
I like you better
as a sister than a mom.
Ouch.
[Lilo] A shooting star!
[gasps]
Oh, my gosh.
I have to make a wish.
You, out!
-What? Why? Whoa.
-Out!
You can't be here.
It won't come true.
Gravity is increasing.
-No, it's not, sister.
-Oh.
I wish a wish upon a star,
even though it's very far.
I hope and pray, hope it might
send me my wish tonight.
All I wish is a friend.
A real friend.
Someone who won't tease me.
Someone who won't run away.
Like a best friend.
[crashing, rumbling]
[whispers] Send me an angel.
The nicest one you have.
Please.
[speaking Tantalog]
[laughing]
-[toad croaking]
-Huh?
[speaking Tantalog]
-[toad croaks]
-[grunting]
[device beeping]
Huh. What does this thing do?
Give me that back! You're
not authorized to touch that.
Why? Does it eject you
from the ship? That'd be nice.
[screaming, grunting]
It's connected
to his tracking collar.
[scoffs]
That's never gonna work.
You might as well
give him a mood ring.
That collar tells us exactly
where he is at all times.
[screen beeping]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[electrical humming]
[electricity crackles]
[power cuts off]
And that's why
our mission cannot fail.
[computer] Mission failed.
Oh, no!
You know, I am right so often,
I don't even enjoy it anymore.
The novelty
has completely worn off.
[strains]
Whoo-hoo! [groans]
[♪ pop music playing,
Mark Ronson "Uptown Funk"]
[sniffing, gasps]
Mmm.
Oh, this is bad. This is bad.
Will you relax?
I know his every move.
Yeehaw! [laughing]
What the hell?
[laughs, screams]
[grunts] Hmm.
-Huh?
-[screams]
[speaking Tantalog, laughing]
[bridesmaid grunting]
-[gasps]
-[crowd clamoring]
-I saw it over there.
-Where did it go?
-Huh?
-[guest screaming]
How are we gonna find him?
We just have to follow
the path of destruction.
I got him!
-[speaking Tantalog]
-[gasps] It talked to me!
[crowd gasping]
[sniffs] Huh? Ah!
Ooh! [grunting]
[exclaims]
[Jumba] There.
Jumba! No,
you can't fly this close!
-Seat belts, please.
-Or else--
The humans will see us.
[crowd clamoring]
[belches]
You're jeopardizing
the mission.
-We can't be seen.
-I'm in charge now.
Partners are supposed
to share.
-Oh!
-[brakes squeal]
-[bus horn honking]
-[gasps]
[♪ distorted music playing,
Mark Ronson "Uptown Funk"]
-[tires screech]
-[passengers scream]
[passengers murmuring]
[♪ Hawaiian music playing]
[Pleakley]
It's called "vacation."
Once every solar year,
the human migrates
to go see a sunlight
and drink celebratory poison.
What are we doing here?
We've gotta find 626.
We will, after we blend in.
How are we gonna do that?
With these. And this.
It's a Federation-certified
cloning device.
What? Who are we gonna clone?
Ugh, this is never gonna work.
[Pleakley]
Just be cool and normal.
[Jumba scoffs]
They look like a bunch
of Slim Jims with googly eyes.
[Pleakley] No, not those two.
[Jumba] Look at their
disgusting Popsicle bodies.
Human, what a downgrade.
[Pleakley gasps]
Look at these two.
They look like best friends
just like us.
They're perfect.
[Pleakley]
I'm so sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Here, I will hold you up.
[device whirring]
[Pleakley] Apologies.
What a nice arm you have.
-[Pleakley grunts]
-Okay. Are you guys--
[Pleakley] And I thank you.
[Jumba] I feel like
I'm walking on chopsticks.
My legs feel a little wobbly.
[Pleakley] I know.
Don't worry. They're fine.
You watched
the video I sent you, right?
The walking video?
Yeah, but I didn't know
it was gonna be like this.
One foot
in front of the other.
[chuckles, grunting]
[both grunting]
[Pleakley] Cool and normal.
-Aloha.
-How are you?
-I'm good. Thank you.
-I would like to check in.
-Okay.
So, how many nights
will you be staying with us?
I don't want to stay with you.
I would like my own room
with a door.
Oh, and a hot tube.
I would like a hot tube.
Uh, a hot tub?
-Yes, that's how you say it...
-[chuckles]
-...down here.
-Okay.
And where are
you visiting us from?
-Earth.
We both grew up in Earth.
Earth. Okay,
that should be about it.
Marcus, could you help him
with his bags please?
Yes.
[door closes]
What is it?
Gotta be some kind
of a dog, right?
[worker] What kind of dog
has six legs, bro?
[sighs]
Oh, nice. That went
better than I expected.
[Jumba] Which part, falling
down? It was embarrassing.
Hangers.
[Jumba] Humans.
Disgusting.
They're really
simple creatures.
Every time an asteroid hits,
they start life all over.
It's quite adorable, actually.
You know what I'd really
like to do while we're here?
Sneeze. Humans do this thing
where they blast juice
out of their nose.
What are you doing?
I'm finding him.
We only have 48 hours.
Wait! No! Wait, wait, wait.
Humans have never seen
a portal before.
The Grand Councilwoman
was very clear
not to draw attention
to ourselves!
What about that guy?
-[device beeps]
-[screams]
Listen,
I majored in Earth studies
and minored in human textiles.
-Wow!
-Trust me.
-We need to blend in.
-[elevator bell dings]
[woman] Fourth floor, please.
[Jumba] Can you stop that?
[on TV]
Aloha, I'm Stephanie Lum.
Breaking news on a
strange situation last night.
A local tour bus ran over
an unidentified wild animal
who terrorized a wedding.
The creature is recovering at
the Nā Mea Ola Animal Rescue.
-More on that at 10:00...
-Bingo.
...and hear from
the wedding photographer.
Tūtū, can I go
into the animal shelter?
Please, please, please.
Nani lets me do it.
Okay. But no wander.
I'll pick you
after I pau shopping, okay?
-Yeah!
-Hey, hey, hey, hey!
If anyone tries anything,
hit 'em in the eyes with this.
Whoa! Cool! [laughs]
Ho ho.
[Lilo laughs]
Whoa. Okay.
[groaning, gasping]
[gasps]
[speaking Tantalog]
[barks]
Uh, no, no.
[speaking Tantalog]
[groaning]
[dog whimpers]
[Lilo] Can I pet
the dogs again?
-Hi, AJ.
-Okay.
But you know you can't feed
the dogs candy again, right?
[sighs]
Lilo.
[candy rustling]
But it makes them happy.
It makes them have diarrhea.
Hmm? [sniffs]
Huh?
[gasps, speaks Tantalog]
[panting]
[grunts] Huh?
[Jumba] Nighty night, 626.
Jumba?
[pants, grunts]
[Pleakley screams]
[Jumba]
Will you please stay still?
Ow. [groans]
I'm gonna get an earful for
these ferns we trampled on.
Not to mention if we actually
hurt any of the humans,
-then we're really-- What?
-[shushes] Quiet.
He's listening out for us.
Who's listening?
Oh. How good's his hearing?
[gasps] That's really good!
[Jumba] Yeah,
they're called super ears.
[♪ electronic music playing]
Yeehaw!
[♪ electronic music
ends abruptly]
[groans, speaks Tantalog]
-Huh.
-[dogs barking]
Hey, Bailey.
-[Bailey whines]
-Look who's back.
What's the matter?
Is it bath day today?
Man, the mood in here
is very depressing.
[grunting]
Sorry, guys.
AJ took all my candy.
[dogs whimpering]
Are you guys okay?
[grunting]
[Pleakley] The Grand
Councilwoman was very clear.
-[Jumba] I know the rules.
-[626 groans, gasps]
[Jumba] I know I could catch
him if I used my blaster.
[Pleakley] It's too risky.
The Grand Councilwoman
was very clear.
You can't hurt the humans.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[speaking Tantalog, grunting]
Whoa. This one
must've been a good one.
-[dog barks, whines]
-Huh?
[gasps]
-[breathes heavily]
-[Lilo gasps]
[groans, pants]
[screams]
[gasps] Um...
[pants] Hi.
Whoa.
Um...
[groans] Um...
[door swings open]
Auē, what is that?
-A dog, I think.
-[grunting]
Looks like some
kind of baby bear
that come out of the trash.
-I like him. Come here, boy.
-[straining, gasps]
[AJ] Yeah,
let's put this one back, Lilo.
-Come here.
-Sweetie.
You know, we do have
better dogs. Like, way better.
Not better than him.
He can talk.
Say, "aloha."
-Alo--
-Dogs no can talk.
-[AJ] Dogs can't talk, Lilo.
-[imitates dog barking]
[Tūtū] Nah,
we can come back later.
[grunting]
[Lilo laughs]
You sure you like this one?
[Lilo] Yep.
-He's perfect. [laughs]
-[grunts]
[Jumba] Oh,
look at that genius.
He's using the mini human
as a shield.
Got you.
Wait, you can't shoot!
That's your fault.
[chuckles]
[grunting]
[laughing]
[Nani] What?
An animal?
What were you thinking?
-Was it her idea?
-No.
-She just said...
-Did she put you up to this?
[exhales sharply] Uh...
You have to be polite.
You're our guest!
-It was my idea.
-What?
Tūtū, are you kidding me?
Why on earth would you...
[blows]
It's been hard
for that girl, no?
Hey, take that off him.
And for you too.
And a pet might bring joy.
Remember,
we don't hurt chickens, okay?
Like me and Alvin.
[phone dings]
[sighs] I forgot I'm covering
Maya's shift today at work.
Lilo, I need you two
to keep yourselves busy, okay?
I've gotta clean the house
before work.
Are we gonna keep him?
-Ah! Just today.
-Yeah!
But we are taking it back
first thing tomorrow morning.
And, hey, I need you
to listen to me, okay?
He is your kuleana, okay?
Your responsibility.
You have to be a big girl
about this. Got it?
We promise.
[clears throat]
Special Agent Cobra Bubbles,
there's no sign of a pilot.
No tracks. No trails.
Nothing since the incident.
Who says it walked?
Sir?
Sir, you're not implying
this is extraterrestrial?
-Hmm...
-[woman] Sir,
second team intercepted this
from a nearby dog shelter.
You were right.
[man] I'm sorry. Sir,
what division are you from?
[Cobra] When things fall
out of the sky,
you're the public's
first line of defense.
I'm the last. Often the only.
I need to find out what kind
of threat we're dealing with.
[people on TV screaming]
Okay, just stay put.
I'll be back in a second.
[creature roars]
[mimics roaring]
Hey, Mertle, look,
I got a new dog.
Oh, no, not Lilo.
[girl]
That's the weirdest thing.
Just like you.
[Lilo] Hey, give that back!
[Lilo] Give that back!
Stop it!
-Lilo plays with dolls.
-Be careful with her!
[626 grunts]
[Mertle] Lilo,
what is up with your dog?
What is up with you?
Wait for me.
Why are you doing that? Lilo!
I don't know.
Blame it all on him.
What are you doing?
[626] Ah-ha!
How long
does this thing last anyway?
[626 giggles]
Isn't that them?
Hurry. Hurry. Hurry.
[Jumba] He'll stop at nothing
to get away from us.
He will likely head
for a big city
for maximum destruction.
But he's gonna
find out real soon,
-he's stuck here.
-Huh?
[grunting]
Don't you love being on
an island with no big cities?
It's just miles and miles
of water.
-[gasping]
-[Lilo sighs]
[screams]
[Lilo] Come on. I'm gonna take
you to my favorite spots.
You're gonna love it.
Come on. Come in the water
with me. It's so fun.
[giggling] It's just water.
Ready? Fetch.
[grunts, screams]
[both straining]
Come on. Animals like water.
[panting]
[roars]
[Lilo] Oh, so
you like trouble, huh?
Come on, boy.
[howls]
[both howl]
[slurps]
[hotel worker on PA]
Lilo, we can see you.
You know
you shouldn't be here.
[Lilo giggles]
Go, go, go.
[626 giggles]
-[626 babbling]
-[Lilo giggling]
[Lilo]
Get down. Get down from there.
[626 straining]
-Oh, my God. Control him.
-I'm trying.
-[squealing]
-[grunting]
[Lilo giggles]
Ah, no.
Did he just...
[626 chuckles]
[car horn blares]
-[giggles]
-No.
No. Stop.
-Did he just--
-[seat fabric rips]
Great, Lilo.
Now I have to stitch that up.
[sniffing]
-[screams]
-What? What? What? What?
That's his name. Stitch!
[sighs]
Lilo, you can't
just do that, okay?
Seriously. I thought
I almost hit something.
-[both scream]
-Huh?
Oh, I...
I am so, so sorry.
Is... Is... Are...
Are you guys okay? I...
-[Stitch growling]
-[Nani chuckles]
Lilo, lock your door.
[Lilo] Was he dragging another
man across the street?
Nah-nah. He-he.
See you later. [snickers]
[car horn blares, beeping]
Get over yourself.
Just give me a second.
[sighs]
-[car horn beeps]
-Okay. Come on. Come on.
Let's go. Let's go. Come on.
Why do I have to
be at your work?
I'm six.
[Nani] Because someone
got kicked out of hula.
Stay here.
It's so boring here.
And no dogs on the table.
-Why not?
-Because people eat off them.
Nani.
Who cares? They're already
covered with bird poo.
Lilo.
[boss] Nani!
[grunts] Come on.
[Stitch exclaiming]
Stay here.
We don't have time for you to
babysit your little daughter.
No, no, it's fine. It won't
happen again. I promise.
I'll go get the table.
Hey, Lilo. How's it going?
Look, David, I got a dog.
[clears throat]
You sure that's a dog?
Mmm. Yeah.
Mmm. [barks]
Um, hey.
You know, your sister.
Have you noticed she's been
a little tense recently?
Don't worry.
She's always like that.
But she said that she likes
your butt and fancy hair.
She told you that?
Nope.
But I read her text messages.
Oh.
Okay. Uh...
Stitch? Oop.
Stitch?
[Stitch speaking Tantalog]
There you are.
We have to stay at the table.
Stitch.
[speaks Tantalog]
No.
Stitch, put it down.
-[speaking Tantalog]
-Yes.
[speaking Tantalog]
-You.
-No, no, no.
[speaking Tantalog]
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam!
And then... [whimpering]
-No.
-Ah.
I'm gonna give you
to the count of three, Stitch.
[growls]
One.
[gasps]
[chuckles] Ah-ha!
[Stitch chuckles]
[phone cameras clicking]
[boss] Wait!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, get back to work.
[both chuckling]
-[Stitch babbles]
-[both chuckle]
Cake! Cake!
Are you guys staying
out of trouble?
Yeah. Of course.
You hungry, boy?
[growls]
[chuckles]
[chuckling]
Stitch? [gasps]
[chuckles]
-[Lilo] Stitch!
-Hey!
[guest] Fire!
[both chuckling]
[Stitch chuckles]
I wish it could've worked out.
[chuckles]
Not right now, Stitch.
[car engine sputtering]
[sighs]
[Lilo sighs] Here you go.
626, you little scoundrel.
What a piece of work you are.
Hello, human. Fellow human.
Hello, hello. Ooh, look, fire.
[Jumba]
Look, look, look. We're close.
Wait, it's moving.
Come on. Come on.
-Let's go. We gotta go.
-[device rings]
[Pleakley] Oh. Oh, look,
it's Grand Councilwoman.
-Don't answer that. Not now.
-It's Grand Councilwoman.
Your Majesty.
Aren't you just
looking delightful today?
It has been 24 hours. Have you
captured the creature?
Start.
Start traveling, please.
We've captured his attention.
Oh, his attention. Good.
There's no...
There's no instruments.
There's nothing here!
And are you
enjoying the hotel?
[Pleakley] I'm so glad
you asked. I mean--
I'm obviously being sarcastic.
-Go! Systems go.
-Hey!
Engage.
-Oh, no. Other way.
-What you think you're doing?
Find the creature.
And remember,
you must use discretion.
-Discretion is my middle name.
-How do I stop this thing?
Oh, brilliant.
Is it too late
to vaporize the planet?
Finger's always
on the trigger, ma'am.
No, no. I'm joking.
What an adorable
little psychopath.
[Lilo, Stitch grunting]
[Lilo] You know,
you didn't even like that job.
I don't wanna hear it.
And I cleaned the house
before work,
-so please don't make a mess.
-[sniffing]
[Stitch] Aah! Ooh! [grunts]
[Nani] Lilo,
he's getting water everywhere.
[Lilo] I'm giving him
a bath right now.
[Nani] Yeah,
we're not really equipped
to handle a pet
right now and--
[animal rescue worker]
We have it down here
that it was a black Lab, no?
No, I didn't say it was black.
I said it was blue.
[straining]
-[Lilo] Stitch!
-What's going on in there?
[Lilo] Everything's fine!
Stitch,
you need to listen to me.
-[Stitch yells]
-No, no, no, Stitch!
[groaning]
Stitch, get back here.
We're not done.
[Nani] Get him back
in the bath now.
Where did he go?
[chuckles]
[Lilo gasps] There!
Be careful!
[record rewinds]
[Elvis Presley] ♪ Ain't
Nothin' but a hound dog ♪
♪ Cryin' all the time... ♪
Do not go in my clean kitchen.
[Lilo] He's exploring
his new house.
♪ And you ain't
No friend of mine ♪
That's it.
[grunting]
Ew! [groans]
[Lilo] He's just curious.
[Nani] Lilo! Help me.
[Lilo] He's a puppy.
[Nani] It's not a puppy, Lilo.
I'm not even sure it's a dog.
Ooh!
-[Lilo yelps]
-No, no, no.
-[Nani] Get down.
-[Lilo] Stitch, stop.
Fire.
We are taking it back.
First thing tomorrow morning.
[Nani] Why are you so strong?
But I wished for him,
and he came true.
We said one day.
That was our deal.
What does that say?
On the 'fridgerator.
We are not keeping this thing.
-"ʻohana." means family.
-No.
-Family means...
-Dude. No.
...nobody gets
left behind or...
Or forgotten. I...
[Stitch chuckles]
[Lilo] Why are you
trying to go
against what Māmā
and Pāpā said?
Because we were left behind.
Look,
I know all that stuff
sounds so nice.
It sounds really nice
to me too,
but that is not reality.
This is reality.
And I need you
to start living in it with me.
-[banging]
-[Stitch exclaims]
[sighs]
Look, can you just
get control of your dog?
[scoffs] And I don't
even wanna think about
what social services
is gonna do.
Agent Foster,
get me the social worker.
I'm going undercover.
[Lilo] You've got to stop
causing problems, Stitch.
You can play with Scrump,
but be nice.
She was my best friend
before you.
Hey, stop it.
Bad dog. Bad dog.
Don't pull on her head.
She's recovering from surgery.
Hey, that's my favorite photo.
Stop it.
This is kapu, okay?
That means "off limits."
Don't ever, ever touch this.
Now be good.
Be good for one second.
She was smartest
in her whole class.
That's a board.
That's how you surf.
Oh. This is how she trained.
She was great at it.
And she has a whole room
fulled with trophies.
We used to go
to the beach all the time.
She used to be fun.
I wish you could have
met her then.
[slurping]
I don't think
you're supposed to drink that.
Huh?
[continues drinking]
-[burps]
-Did you have a family?
Fa... Fam...
-Family?
-Family.
-That's close.
Like Māmā and Pāpā.
The people at home who give
you lots of hugs and kisses.
And they're there for you,
even when...
No.
No family.
Is that why
you act bad sometimes?
It's okay.
Maybe my parents talked
to your parents
and they sent us
to each other.
Yeah.
[speaking Tantalog]
Oh, that's hula.
Uh, hula?
It's a Hawaiian dance.
You wanna try?
-Mākaukau.
-Hmm?
Now, follow what I do.
♪ Aloha ʻoe  ♪
♪ E ke onaona ♪
♪ Noho i ka lipo ♪
♪ One fond embrace ♪
♪ A hoʻi aʻe au ♪
♪ Until we meet again ♪
[Lilo sighs]
I'm so glad I found you.
Can I kiss your nose?
[sighs]
[Lilo] Nani, Nani!
-You have to see this.
-Hmm?
Okay, just like we practiced.
-What are you doing?
-Watch this.
[Nani] I'm excited.
Go. I'm watching.
[Elvis Presley]
♪ We can't go on together ♪
-♪ With suspicious minds ♪
-[Nani chuckles]
-I love that song.
-[song stops]
-[song continues]
-[phone dings]
[Lilo] Did you even see?
-Oh. We're gonna be late.
-[song stops]
[song continues]
Come on. Turn that off.
Go get your shoes.
[Lilo]
That's like a superpower.
-The superpower I have is...
-Come on. Let's go.
...sometimes
when I run too fast, I fart.
[blows raspberries, chuckles]
[both laugh]
[Mrs. Kekoa] Nice to meet you.
I appreciate someone with your
seniority coming to help us.
[Cobra] Well, this is
my top priority. Wha--
-Okay, come on.
-Stitch!
-Let's go. Let's go. Hurry up.
-Go, go, go!
We're already late.
We gotta go.
Mrs. Kekoa.
[Mrs. Kekoa] This is
our social services director.
-Hello.
-Hi. [chuckles]
I thought you weren't
coming in until next week.
[Mrs. Kekoa] No, Nani.
Your case has been elevated.
So, this is Lilo.
And who is this little friend?
[Lilo] That's my new dog.
Nani, I heard
what happened last night.
Can we talk for a second?
Yeah. Sure.
-His name is Stitch.
-Oh, Stitch.
If he knew what was happening,
you would lose Lilo right now,
that's all I'm saying.
[Nani] It shouldn't have
happened in the first place.
-So that was a lot.
-Yeah, and you lost your job.
[yelps, grunts]
Hey! What are you doing?
You don't look
like a social worker.
I'm a special rank.
[Lilo]
Your knuckles say, "Cobra."
-You can read, huh?
-Yeah, I can read.
I'm reading you like a book.
[Nani] That's how
I'll get health insurance.
Don't even worry about it.
You said I had until
the end of the week, right?
Lilo, Stitch,
let's go find a job.
Gotcha.
But I do want to know
a little bit more about you.
Okay, what would you like
to know about me, Pleakley?
Where'd you get
the name Jumba?
It's a family name.
-[Pleakley] Are you related--
-There's the truck.
[Jumba] Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
We have to catch him today.
Why did you choose
this foolish method
of transportation?
[Pleakley]
They're eco-friendly.
[Nani] Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Hop to it.
-Okay, this is it, Lilo. Okay?
-Let's play Simon Says.
This is our last shot.
If I don't find a job
by today...
Simon says wiggle your butt.
...then we are going
to be separated.
-Simon says wiggle your legs.
-Hey. Listen.
For real.
I need you and him
to be on your best behavior.
Okay? Yeah?
Okay, wish me luck.
Okay, Stitch,
Nani's counting on us.
So let's get to work.
Ready? Sit.
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[Lilo] Okay, class, listen up.
This is your badness level.
It's unusually high
for someone your size.
-But we'll fix that.
-[grumbles]
So, lesson number one.
Lend a helping hand.
Or a paw.
-[chattering]
-[Lilo] This is how you clean.
First, use this.
-Okay, we gotta get closer.
-Okay.
That's not...
[Lilo] Lesson number two.
Don't wreck stuff.
It's really fragile,
so you can't break it
every time when you--
[glass tinkling]
Now, it's your turn.
[sneezes]
[Lilo giggling]
[glass squeaking]
[Jumba] You can't just say,
"Let's get scooters,"
-and that's a plan.
-I've been trying to be--
-[sneezes]
-Oh!
A sneeze!
[shushes]
[Pleakley] Can you
tell me how you did it?
[Jumba] I have no idea.
I looked at the light.
Lesson three. Make amends.
[Stitch grunting]
There you go.
-[grunting]
-[Lilo] No. Hey.
-[screams]
-No. Hey. Hey.
-Good job, Stitch.
-[Nani] I'm excited.
You know what I mean?
How did it go?
-Not at this hotel.
-Wait. Well...
-Uh...
-Mm-mmm.
Hmm.
[gasps] Nani, Nani, Nani!
[Nani] Okay.
Maybe you can do
something you love.
Go! Go! Go! And pop!
[Lilo, David cheer]
Yeah, Nani!
[David] Yeah!
[groans]
[chomps]
[gasps]
[exclaims]
[grunting]
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[Stitch exclaiming]
[chuckles, grunts]
[sighs]
[exclaims]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
Hey!
What are you doing?
[air squeaking]
-Why'd you make him so quick?
-[Stitch grunting]
[screams]
Get off, Stitch.
[laughs]
[screams]
-[gasps] Lilo?
-[Stitch gasping]
Nani!
Lilo? Lilo?
[beachgoer] ...drowning!
-Lifeguard!
-Lilo!
Get off of her!
David, help!
Stitch is pulling her under.
Code 51. I repeat, Code 51.
Send an extraction team now.
[superior]
Cobra, my hands are tied
until the sample is processed.
Someone's after it too.
The next chance I get,
I'm catching him.
You're good. You're good.
You're good. David, help.
[Stitch groaning]
-Help, help, help.
-You got her?
Okay. David, help, help.
-Lilo, can you hear me?
-Baby.
Up, up, up, up, up, up.
Call an ambulance!
[groaning]
Well, folks.
She asked if she could ride
in the MRI machine.
I told her
I would check with you.
[sighs] She's fine.
[chuckles]
-[Stitch sighs]
-She got lucky.
A few more seconds,
it could've been much worse.
But, overall...
Is that a--
It's a service animal.
Okay.
And you can see the front.
They'll run your insurance.
Okay?
Mahalo.
Uh-oh. What?
[Nani] No. No. Absolutely not.
It's not just the bills, Nani.
It's time for you to think
about what's best for Lilo.
There's a way that the state
will pay for all of this.
But...
it means that you have
to officially relinquish...
guardianship of Lilo.
What would that...
look like? Um...
Well, we take our lead
from you.
You tell us
how you want to proceed.
It's really about making the
transition easier for Lilo.
[Mrs. Kekoa]
You'll still get to see her.
It'll just be different.
You can prepare a bag,
a few toys,
things that comfort her.
And at that point,
we would leave you
some time alone to...
Say goodbye.
No.
We don't say goodbye.
We say a hui hou.
[Mrs. Kekoa]
Until we meet again.
I really thought
they could make it work.
[whimpers]
[Jumba] Why would he
protect her like that?
[Pleakley] You don't think
they're kind of cute together?
He's not a pet.
He's an experiment.
And a dangerous one at that.
I just think he's a lot cuter
than you think
he is dangerous.
He has sharp teeth.
He has claws.
I designed him
to be dangerous.
Dangerously cute.
-[device rings]
-Do not answer that.
Pleakley, don't answer that.
[device ringing]
[whispering]
Pleakley. Pleakley.
For me.
Your Majesty,
Agent Pleakley here,
not ignoring your call.
We just intercepted
a call from human authorities.
Do you realize
what you have done?
-Nope.
-Play the recording.
And take off
that ridiculous hat.
[Cobra Bubbles] Code 51.
We found something. Confirm.
And not only have you alerted
the humans to our existence,
but you still haven't
captured 626.
Grand Councilwoman,
with all due respect,
I'm not sure you know
what's going on with 626.
We have found, um...
a... a glitch.
Which is making it
a little harder
to get him off this planet.
But don't worry.
I'm sure I can figure out...
-We just need--
-A glitch?
You're a glitch, you buffoon.
I have had enough,
Dr. Jookiba.
You have exhausted
my patience.
Consider our deal terminated.
-What?
-No tantrums.
Agent Pleakley
is hereby deputized
to detain you
under Federation orders
and escort you
back to Turo immediately.
Uh, hello?
Now? Like now?
No, later. What do you think?
You cannot do this to my work!
This is not a debate.
A Federation detail
is on its way
to clean up your mess.
-[Jumba scoffs]
-Did she hang up?
[breathing forcefully]
[Pleakley] Jumba?
Yeah, the Federation has
always kind of been that way,
overreacting all the time.
But work's work,
and we gotta follow orders--
[device beeps, whirs]
-What?
-Aloha and mahalo.
Oh, you're learning the--
[shrieks]
I really thought
we were getting closer.
[Jumba]
It's time to do this my way.
Oh, no.
Hey, boo thang.
Hey.
What are you doing, silly?
Oh, I'm just playing with my
dolls that I made at Tūtū's.
-Aw, cute.
-Pizza!
[Nani chuckles]
[chuckles] Um...
So, remember that time
that I went to the North Shore
that one summer?
Yeah.
And we were on
opposite sides of the island,
but we could, you know,
go and visit
anytime we wanted, right?
We just weren't together
all the time.
But we could call.
You would tell me about all
of your fun little adventures
with Alvin and Tūtū
and stuff like that.
And we could talk a lot,
just not all the time.
You know?
Is this... [sighs]
Is this connecting at all?
You're going back
to surf camp?
No. No.
It's just that with Stitch
and everything this week,
things have gone
from bad to worse, so...
we're gonna have to make
some changes.
And...
You know... I...
I have to get some air.
[sighs softly]
Remember when Pāpā
took us camping out here?
-[chuckles] What?
-Yeah, remember?
I had s'mores.
And you also did too.
Pāpā didn't take us camping.
They were fumigating.
We had termites.
Mmm. I went camping.
We had fun.
They were really good parents.
Hey.
I changed my mind.
What's that?
Hmm?
I like you as a mom too.
Come on. Do it. For me?
Okay.
♪ Haʻaheo ka ua i nā pali ♪
[grunting]
♪ Ke nihi aʻela i ka nahele ♪
[groans]
♪ E uhai ana paha i ka liko ♪
♪ Pua ʻāhihi lehua o uka ♪
[sighs]
[frog croaks]
♪ Aloha ʻoe  ♪
♪ E ke onaona noho ♪
[both singing] ♪ I ka lipo ♪
♪ One fond embrace ♪
♪ A hoʻi aʻe au ♪
♪ Until ♪
[dog whimpers]
♪ We meet again ♪
[Nani] I want you to know...
whatever happens,
I love you very much.
[sighs]
[whimpers]
You ready?
Yeah.
It's gonna be okay.
I promise.
[Nani sniffling]
[Nani sighs]
Um...
She's not here.
What do you mean,
"She's not here"?
I... I don't...
Maybe she's
at the neighbor's house.
Go, go, go, go.
What?
Where'd he go?
Stitch?
Stitch!
I thought I lost you.
S... Stitch break f... family.
It was a accident.
Like a mess-up.
But Stitch...
[sniffs] ...bad.
Stitch is bad.
You're not bad.
You just do bad things
sometimes.
ʻOhana means family.
And sometimes
family isn't perfect.
But that doesn't mean
they aren't good.
[portal burbles]
[Lilo gasps, screams]
[growls]
[dogs barking]
[growling]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I didn't come here
to hurt anybody.
I'm here to help.
This animal belongs to me.
He's not an animal.
He's my friend.
Do you have
anything else to say?
[whimpers]
[growls]
[grunts, laughs]
Hand me that.
You don't know how to use it.
I'm gonna count to three, and
then I want you to drop it.
One...
two...
three! [screams]
[screaming]
-Come on!
-Cool.
[Lilo]
You're a genius, Stitch.
[Jumba] I made him.
I'm the genius!
[Lilo screams]
First rule
of stranger danger is:
Find an adult.
Nani!
Nani?
-Lilo!
[groans]
This is all my fault.
[motor whirring]
Hui.
[screaming]
[grunts]
Ugh! And now I have a wedgie.
[pizza clerk] Wait. Why would
I know where you sister is?
I don't know. This is the only
phone number I could find.
Do you wanna order
a pepperoni or what?
[gasps] Never mind.
She's back.
Nani!
[gasps]
Stitch, stop.
[shushes]
Ow.
Okay, 626, very clever trick.
Funny. I got to stare
at my own derriere.
I've always wanted to do that.
[Lilo] What are you doing?
-[Lilo gasps]
-Okay, listen.
I... I just wanna say...
the Federation
doesn't exactly appreciate
what you've done here.
I know you're in there.
Come out, please.
I've got huge plans for you.
I mean, for us.
Go away, hairy potato!
Did you just call me
a hairy potato?
That's not nice.
Window, window, window!
-[shrieks]
-Wait! Come back!
Hey! You're gonna run?
You're not gonna run away
from all this.
All these memories.
Humans are so attached
to each other.
To their things,
to the alien experiments
they've stolen from me.
[Stitch] We gotta go!
"Attachment" means you care.
-[Stitch] Hurry!
-Oh, no.
[gasps] Lilo! Hurry!
We go now!
And caring causes people
to make very stupid decisions.
Who is "May-May"
and "Pay-Pay?"
That's Māmā and Pāpā's room.
Oh! That makes
a lot more sense.
Stop it, or else.
Or else what?
What are you gonna do?
[Stitch] Yoo-hoo.
-[chuckles]
-[Jumba] There he is.
Aloha! [chuckles]
[shrieks]
[panting]
-I'm sorry.
-[screams]
[screaming]
My eye! My eye! My eye!
Why would you do that?
[shrieks]
Hey, stop it.
I'm only trying to help!
[groans]
626, playtime is over.
[screams]
Ow!
Ah!
[slurping]
Okay, okay, okay.
What's the plan, 626?
Say you escape the Federation.
You think you're gonna
just stay here with her?
Live happily ever after
on Earth?
You're built to destroy, 626,
and you have.
Look what's happened
since you got here.
Her family is falling apart.
Let's just be honest.
The only reason you picked her
at that animal shelter
was for your own protection.
Is that true, Stitch?
See, I don't think that's bad.
I don't think anything
you do is bad.
I think it's genius.
If you care about
this little girl at all,
you'll leave her here.
[sighing]
Stitch?
[portal burbles]
Aw.
This is for the best.
Lilo, run!
David, Nani, meet me
back at the house.
[Jumba] You know,
you made the right choice.
The Councilwoman
was gonna exile you.
She was gonna waste
all my brilliant science.
But I'm gonna do something
even better.
-[device beeps]
-[gasps]
And turn you into 627.
[gasps]
-[David] Lilo?
-Lilo!
-Not in here.
-I'm gonna check the back.
-Okay.
-What happened?
-I don't know.
-Where's Lilo?
She's not here.
Actually, she's on a ship
headed away from the--
[all screaming]
Oh, my God! Okay, okay.
That was a really
impressive throw.
If we can all...
No, come on.
Not that again. I actually...
Agent Cobra Bubbles, CIA.
-[Pleakley] What?
-Wait, what? CIA?
Wendell Pleakley from the
United Galactic Federation.
I'm a fellow
government worker.
What you doing here?
-Yeah, where is my sister?
-Great news.
She's alive and well.
Well, actually,
I don't know if she's well.
This only tells me
the velocity
of them moving away
from the planet.
Enough! I'm taking you out,
and that's that. Let's go.
You know, seeing you with that
little girl made me realize
you're not the heartless
monster I thought you were.
But once I remove
your capacity for love,
you'll be perfect.
And then, with 627 by my side,
the Councilwoman
won't be able to stop me.
[laughs]
Oh, don't look so sad, 626.
We have each other.
I'm your "o'hannah,"
just like your friend Lisa
used to say.
Was that her name, Lisa? Lily?
Limo? Limo... No.
-What was her name?
-Lilo!
Oh, yeah, that was it. Lilo.
Horrible name. Let's get
off this planet, huh?
[spaceship voice]
Initiating hyperspeed.
Ready to launch
in two minutes.
You need to tell me
what is going on.
-Where is my sister?
-Not now.
The priority is reporting
this incident
and getting this thing
into custody.
People need to know what
kind of threat they're under.
Uh, I'm not really a threat.
I'm kinda quite harmless,
actually.
But you shouldn't be
that concerned.
This is actually
my first mission
in the field,
so I wouldn't really
-be that concerned. Okay.
-[Nani] Wait, wait.
Aren't you supposed
to protect us?
I took an oath to protect
the American people.
Hey. What you think we are?
[Agent Foster] Cobra, you were
right. The lab results are in,
and we've never seen
anything like this.
Please.
There is something big
at play here.
Have you found any
additional evidence?
[Nani] She's my sister. He's
the only one who can help.
-Hmm.
-Okay.
Also, I took off
your bracelets.
They were uncomfortable.
Yeah, it just comes down
to having a vision.
That's all science is.
-It's the ability...
-Red button.
-...to see what others can't.
-Push. Go.
And I'm guilty of that.
The Grand Councilwoman,
for example...
No. No, no, no.
...she couldn't see the future
if it were standing
right in front of her.
Oh, I wouldn't say that
to her face.
[groaning]
[power whirs]
Hey! What are you doing?
Hey, 626, don't touch
those wi--
Hey!
Do not touch another wire.
-Blah, blah, blah, blah.
-[Jumba] Please.
I mean,
it's really frustrating
to have this relationship
with you.
I say something,
you ignore it.
When we get back,
there's gonna be
some real changes.
Not so fast, pizza face.
[buzzing]
Huh? What the...
[wipers squeaking]
[gasps] Lisa.
[chuckles]
Let me guess, you don't know
how to work a spaceship.
You little...
♪ You've got to get on down
Get on down ♪
[gasps]
♪ Everybody ♪
What?
Why do you have party lights?
[Jumba] Well, that's none
of your business.
Why don't you just admit
that your little friend
is a dangerous,
freakish monster?
-[beeping]
-[gasps]
Also, cute and fluffy!
What?
[spaceship voice]
Hyperspeed. Ready for launch.
[electricity zapping]
Time to go home.
Hey! What are you doing?
No, no, no!
-[straining]
-[Lilo screams]
Look, look, I had a pretty bad
"o'hannah" growing up.
That's not an excuse.
I just thought,
give it a little context--
A hui hou, hairy potato.
[Jumba] Can I just propose
that sometimes
we need second chances?
And that's just what I...
Trust me, I know.
-[screams]
-[voice] Pull up. Pull up.
Pull up. Pull up.
[Stitch gasps]
They're descending quickly.
Can you go any faster?
[Tūtū] David, faster.
You're driving like a grandma.
[Stitch grunting]
[speaks Tantalog]
-[grunting] Jump!
-No!
There's no way! I can't!
Gotta jump.
Safe together.
Yes! Yeah.
-[Lilo] My photo!
-[squeals]
[yelling]
[Nani] Lilo!
[David] Nani!
[grunts] Lilo? Lilo?
Lilo.
[grunting]
[gasps]
-Lilo!
-Nani! Over here!
-Stitch!
-Over here!
Lilo!
-[Lilo grunting]
-[Stitch groaning]
[♪ "Aloha ʻOe" playing]
[Stitch whimpers]
[Nani] Lilo!
-Are you okay?
-He's still down there!
-[Nani] No! Lilo, no!
-Stitch is down there!
-He saved me. Let go!
[David] We need to go.
Let's go.
[Nani] Listen to me.
-Get on the board.
-We have to go save Stitch!
He's still down there!
Go save him!
-I'm sorry!
-Please!
-I can't. I can't.
-Let's go.
-Go get him!
-I need you back.
-David, we need to go.
-[David] We need to go, Lilo.
We need to get you safe.
[Nani] We need to get
out of here.
[exclaims]
-Please! Go save him!
-No, Lilo.
But what about ʻohana?
What about nobody
gets left behind?
[Nani grunting]
Lilo, no!
[defibrillator charges]
[David] Come on, buddy.
Yeah. We need something
more powerful.
-Like what?
-[Pleakley muttering]
[Nani] Try it again.
Try it again.
[defibrillator charges]
Come on.
Okay. We try that.
[Nani] Come on. Come on.
[engine starts]
[engine revving]
[Cobra]
Everybody back! Back up.
[David] Lilo,
get out of the way!
[electricity surging]
[surging stops]
Stitch.
[Nani]
We did all that we could.
[Lilo] We were supposed to
grow up together.
[Lilo sobbing]
I am sorry, baby.
I'm so sorry.
[Stitch groaning]
Lilo?
-[Lilo gasps] Stitch!
-[Nani gasps]
The dog talks?
[Lilo] I love you, Stitch.
-[coughs, groans]
-Oh, gosh.
Ew, let it... Let it go.
[Stitch retches]
[retching, coughing continue]
It's the family picture!
-[Nani] Aw!
-Good boy, Stitch.
[chuckles]
Okay. We're gonna
wash that after, yeah?
Auē. It never ends.
[aircraft whirring]
[soldiers clamoring]
[Nani] Uh, just...
Stay behind me, Lilo.
-Just get back. Get back.
-[Pleakley] Don't worry.
They're just scanning
for deadly parasites.
We're here to retrieve
this dangerous experiment.
Soldiers,
take 626 into custody.
No! Hey! Leave him alone!
Let him stay!
I'm afraid I can't allow that.
This creature poses a threat
to your species.
We are sorry
for what transpired here.
Rest assured those responsible
will be brought to justice.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
How dare you treat
a scientific genius like this!
Hey, Grand Councilwoman,
can you-- Oh! Ow.
My precious brain.
As for experiment 62--
-Stitch.
-What?
My name Stitch.
Stitch then.
-Will be--
-Can Stitch say goodbye?
Yes.
Thank you.
[Lilo] Come here, Stitch.
We're gonna miss you.
Who are these people?
This is my family.
I found it all on my own.
It's little and broken,
but still good.
Yeah.
Still good.
[Pleakley] Grand Councilwoman,
can we leave Stitch
with his new family?
Absolutely not.
The Council would
require supervision.
And who would possibly
want to stay
on this dilapidated
mosquito farm?
-Me, me. Me! Me!
-[Grand Councilwoman] Ha!
Ridiculous.
I cannot risk the global panic
that would ensue
if this were to become public.
[Cobra] What if it didn't?
Oh! Oh! Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
He's CIA. He's very good
at keeping secrets.
Our reconnaissance said
you were going to tell
your superiors about this.
How could I ever trust you
to keep it a secret?
[Cobra] Your Highness...
you have my word.
[Grand Councilwoman] Hmm.
You have all shown me
that there is good
in this creature.
However, I cannot reverse
the council's decision.
Experiment 626 has been
sentenced to life in exile.
A sentence that will be
henceforth served
here on Earth.
[Tūtū, Nani gasp]
[Lilo chuckling]
Yay! [chuckles]
Lilo.
[gasps] I'm so happy.
Permission to hug
the Grand Councilwoman?
-Still no.
-Of course. Yeah.
We will be checking in
now and then.
-Let's go home.
-Yeah.
-Come on, Stitch.
[hammer banging]
[David] Hey,
look on the bright side,
there were a lot of good
memories in this house.
-Some good.
-[glass shatters]
Some bad.
This one's kind of bad. Yeah.
At least
you got the wind chimes.
That's crazy.
Um, David?
[David] Hmm?
Read the room.
[Stitch, Nani chuckle]
He is right though.
[Mrs. Kekoa] Nani.
Hey, baby...
I need to talk to you
about something.
I know. This doesn't
change our agreement.
Well, actually...
Oh, no. What's wrong?
[Tūtū] Nothing.
Well, actually, plenty.
Your house is destroyed.
Your dog is an alien.
Our baby about to go
to another ʻohana.
But that's what
we've been talking about.
What if Lilo came
to live with us?
Ooh.
No, Tūtū, that is
way too much.
-That is...
-[shushes]
Smiley already said yes.
It is usually
a much easier transition
in these foster situations
if the family, hanai
or otherwise, are involved.
[Nani] I mean...
Tūtū, that would be amazing.
I mean, after we rebuild...
You'd be right next door.
Really?
[Lilo] No.
You're so smart, Nani.
I think
you should join the Marines.
[chuckles] Baby,
it's marine biology.
No. I, uh...
It's a lot more complicated
than that.
But I want you to go.
And plus, that's what Māmā
and Pāpā would like too.
They told me so.
[sighs] Yeah, but, Lilo...
it's my kuleana
to take care of you.
Nobody gets left behind.
[Tūtū] It's also your kuleana
to make sure
you no leave yourself behind.
Look at what
your parents gave you.
A good head on your shoulders.
A sense of place.
Pride. An akamai brain.
A creative spirit.
But most important,
you get each other.
ʻOhana.
-[Stitch sighs]
-Use them.
Make us proud.
[Nani chuckles]
-Come here.
-I love you.
[Nani] I love you too.
[gasps] Nani, maybe college
can teach you how to cook!
[Tūtū] Okay, okay.
Come on, Smiley.
-[Nani] Come here.
-[Tūtū] Get in here.
♪ Lord Almighty,
I feel my temperature risin' ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ Higher, higher ♪
♪ It's burning
Through to my soul ♪
♪ You see now
Girl, girl, girl ♪
♪ You're gonna
Set me on fire ♪
♪ My brain is flamin'
I don't know which way to go ♪
♪ You know
Your kisses lift me higher ♪
♪ Like a sweet song
Of a choir ♪
♪ And you light
My mornin' sky ♪
♪ With burning love ♪
[plane departing]
[Lilo] Cobra comes
by sometimes
to keep an eye on Stitch.
He's a little scary.
[both chuckling]
Aw, I miss that cute face.
-I miss you.
-Yeah? You do?
-Yeah.
-Well, speaking of that...
Uh, hold on one second.
[Lilo] Is that your dorm bed?
How come it has bars on it?
-Are you in jail?
-[Stitch snoring]
That's not good.
-Hello?
-[Stitch exclaims]
Nani? Nani? Hello?
-Sup, nugget?
-[screams]
-[chuckles]
-[screaming continues]
Whoa! [grunts]
[all chuckling]
I missed you too, Stitch. Aw.
Hey, Double-O-Seven, go check
on Lilo before you go.
[snoring]
[Cobra] Doesn't sound
like sleeping in there, Lilo.
-Get the gun. Go.
-[Stitch grunting]
Nice.
It's jammed.
The trigger's not working.
Try again. Hurry up, Nani.
Better not be up
learning another one
of those tick tack
dances again.
[grunting] Go, go, go!
[Cobra]
Golly, you're getting big.
[chuckles]
[door closes]
Good night, sister.
Goony-snissers.
♪ Your kisses lift me higher ♪
♪ Like a sweet song
Of a choir ♪
♪ And you light
My mornin' sky ♪
♪ With burning love ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah
Burning love ♪
♪ It's coming closer ♪
♪ The flames are now burnin'
My body ♪
♪ Won't you help me? ♪
♪ I feel like
I'm slippin' away ♪
♪ Oh, it's hard to breathe ♪
♪ It feels like
My chest is a-heavin' ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ Lord, have mercy ♪
♪ I'm burning a hole
Where I lay ♪
♪ You know
Your kisses lift me higher ♪
♪ Like the sweet song
Of a choir ♪
♪ And you light
My mornin' sky ♪
♪ With burning love ♪
♪ I'm just a hunk
A hunk of burning love ♪
♪ I'm just a, just a
Just a, just a ♪
♪ I'm just a, I'm just a ♪
♪ I'm just a hunk
A hunk of burning love ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ You gotta burn it up, baby
Whoo ♪
["He Mele No Lilo" playing]