Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[♪ Gipsy Kings plays
"Volare [Gipsy Kings Version]"]
[song continues with lyrics
in Spanish and Italian]
[crowd cheering]
[groans]
[cheering continues]
[Noel] And with approximately 140 tons
of overripened tomatoes,
La Tomatina remains the world's
greatest annual food fight.
Throwing it back to you at the studio.
We'll ketchup later.
Ooh. Ouch.
- That was painful.
- What?
All right, that wasn't my best tomato pun,
but it was vine.
Wasn't it, Francis?
You know, boss, you don't need
to give a fake broadcast.
[over earpiece] You know
we're on a mission, right?
Okay, easy.
You have your process,
I have mine. Simple.
Now let's zip it and keep
our eyes peeled for Gradov.
Seriously, Coop, the "ketchup"
line was strong, yeah?
Noel, as your oldest friend,
I can definitively say
that was not punny. [laughs]
That's why I don't go big game hunting
without you CIA boys.
Speaking of, we got a lion
in the crosshairs.
Gray hat and jacket,
pink shirt, heading southwest,
matching the target's description.
Walk faces and run it.
Okay, pink shirt, pink shirt.
Okay, I got him.
But I can't confirm it's Gradov.
Cho, you got anything?
That's a negative.
No-go for facial recognition.
[cheering continues]
Wait. I think I'm staring right at him.
20 feet from me, right below you, Coop.
What?
Ah, shit.
Guys, we got two potential
Gradovs on site.
Three.
[Noel] Shit.
He's got decoys in play.
Stay on your mark, Jacks.
Talk to me, home base.
Still no facial recall.
It's like they know
where our cameras are positioned.
Get me gait analysis.
We'd have to request a patch to Echelon.
Then request the patch!
[analyst] Director Adams?
We have a request for a real-time patch.
It's a joint MI6-CIA capture
of a high-value target.
- How high?
- NSA priority.
Russian arms dealer Viktor Gradov.
First sighting in over two years.
[Coop] Noel, target one is still
in the southwest corner.
[vehicle horn honks]
Coop, I don't like this van.
Field, you're authorized
for a 60-second link
to Echelon's servers.
All the time I need
to pin the real Gradov.
It's a VW T5, Spanish plates,
registered to a rental company in Madrid.
What are you?
[silenced gunshot]
[cheering continues]
- [gunshot]
- [crowd screaming]
[Noel] Field team, abort!
We've been set up!
[gun racks]
[panicked screaming and clamoring]
[rapid gunfire distorting,
slowing to a stop]
[muffled voices clamoring]
[tense music playing]
- [typing]
- [laptop beeps]
[both grunting]
[grunting]
[Noel shouts]
Done.
[laptop closes]
Don't move.
Drop it.
[calling whistle]
[pensive music playing]
[device beeping]
♪ ♪
[engine starts]
- ♪ Sugar ♪
- [phone vibrating]
[ringtone playing "Sugar, Sugar"
by The Archies]
♪ Oh, honey, honey ♪
- ♪ You are my... ♪
- [music and vibrating stop]
[sighs]
[over TV] U.S. President Will Derringer,
amidst soaring popularity
at home and abroad,
touched down in London yesterday.
Derringer has stopped
in the U.K. for a brief visit
before he heads
to a NATO summit in Italy...
[newswoman] ...president will be attending
a press conference
in his first face-to-face meeting
with the increasingly embattled
Prime Minister Sam Clarke,
now serving his sixth year in office...
[Mario Lopez] ...Derringer smashed
worldwide box office records
playing the Venom in Denim
with his Water Cobra franchise.
[distorted yelling]
He then went from
bullets flying to tears flowing
with his heartfelt baseball drama
- Sliding into Home...
- [somber music playing]
We did it, son.
Made Mom proud.
[Lopez] ...earning him
a Golden Globe nomination...
[Chuck Todd] After only
five months in office,
Derringer is enjoying
historic polling numbers
- and voter confidence.
- [crowd cheering]
With your help,
we did it at the box office,
and now we will do it at the Oval Office.
- No.
- [crowd chanting over TV]
[groans]
[sighs]
[secretary over earbuds] Good morning,
Mr. Prime Minister.
Here's your brief for Thursday the 29th.
The economic minister will announce
record low unemployment.
The refugee crisis in Poland
continues to intensify,
with numbers growing into
the tens of thousands.
Your early-morning meetings
have been cleared
for an urgent briefing
on a classified intelligence op
in Spain that ended in tragedy.
Seven CIA and MI6 operatives
have been killed.
Sam, I regret to say
that team leader Noel Bisset is missing
- and presumed dead.
- [exhales sharply]
I'm so sorry.
Families of the fallen
are being notified...
- [voice fades]
- [panting]
You okay, boss?
[pensive music playing]
[crowd cheering]
And while the royals play host
to the American president and his family,
record crowds are gathered,
hoping for a glimpse of Will Derringer,
proving he's as loved abroad
as he is at home.
[majestic music playing]
I just don't understand
what tornado has to do with anything.
[laughs] Not tornados.
NATO, okay?
It's like, um, a-a group of friends.
Let's say, in this case, countries.
They-they get together,
and they make a pinky promise
if they ever see a bully,
let's say this guy,
and the bully attacks one of them,
they all got to join in
and stand up to that bully.
And that's when they start
dropping warheads on foreheads.
[stammers] Hey, what?
Who let her watch Water Cobra?
- I saw it at Janey's house.
- Oh, you did?
Hmm. Okay, well, Janey's mom is now
- under federal investigation.
- Sir.
Scoot.
[chuckles]
What time's the lecture at Cambridge?
[Cat] Not till 4:00.
Meet you at Trieste in the morning?
- Yeah.
- Enjoy this.
And use it as a bonding opportunity
with the prime minister.
Please.
Don't tell me you're still mad
about the fish and chips thing.
He endorsed my opponent
in the heat of the campaign.
He had lunch with the guy.
It's hardly an endorsement.
Wasn't just lunch. It was fish and chips.
Look, you got off on the wrong foot.
- Sam's not a bad guy.
- It's not about bad or good.
He doesn't respect me.
This is where you're supposed
to say, "Yes, he does."
- He respects you.
- Way too late.
Is a man who got 83 million votes
from the American people
not feeling properly respected?
See you tomorrow.
Did you look over your speech?
Yeah. It's solid.
I'll hit it with some fireworks.
It'll crackle.
It's gonna be a good morning.
Won't be that simple.
Tell me.
Sideways op, Spain.
- Who was the target?
- [Quincy] Viktor Gradov.
Russian-born arms dealer turned extremist.
Right. Black market weapons developer
who got his hands on enriched plutonium
a few years back.
Yeah, that's when we took him
out of business.
Destroyed his manufacturing plant
with the help of a NATO task force.
We launched an air strike,
destroyed his whole facility.
After that, Gradov went off the grid.
[Simone] Spain was our first chance
to move on Gradov in two years.
Where is he now?
In the wind.
NSA is scraping border entries
and airport screenings for noise.
[Quincy] Intelligence and Research
didn't have the chance
- to do their usual analysis.
- Bloody hell.
How many times I've got to say it?
We do not leapfrog intel.
About Noel, if you want to talk...
I don't.
[Derringer] We should warn Clarke's team
about Jack Gordon.
Jack always goes for the jugular,
and he will fry us over this Spain thing.
Did you tell
the president's comms director
that he must stick to the script?
- Yes.
- Good.
Hopefully he doesn't start writing checks
that we can't cash.
He still hasn't figured out
the difference between
a press conference and a press junket.
Oh.
- Mr. Prime Minister.
- Mr. President.
Yeah. We finally meet.
You know, it was a shame
that you missed the inauguration.
It was a hell of a show.
- Sure it was.
- Yeah.
Well...
Shall we?
Uh, wait, wait.
We should savor this moment.
I mean, this is... it's our debut duet.
- Duet?
- Yeah.
It's like I'm Dr. Dre and you're Eminem,
and we're taking that stage
for the first time together.
I'm Eminem?
Listen, um, about this terrible situation
- in Spain.
- Mm-hmm?
If it comes up out there,
I'd just steer clear of it.
- Let's just punt it.
- Punt it?
- Yeah.
- To where?
Well, to later.
Today's about NATO,
clean energy, light and bright stuff.
Light and bright. Okay.
You want to warm up together?
Do some breathing exercises?
I'm already breathing.
- Roger that. Well...
- Yeah.
[laughs] Let's dance, I guess.
Hey, uh, just do us both
a favor out there.
No questions from Jack Gordon.
My guy.
- [cameras clicking and beeping]
- And as of today,
thanks to this revolutionary
new technology
developed by both of our great nations,
we are now partners in energy.
The pebble-bed reactor is not just
an investment in clean energy.
It's also an investment in security.
Energy security is national security.
It is also an investment in job creation.
A whole lot of jobs.
And we no longer
have to deal with the Russians,
the Saudis or the Venezuelans on oil.
But we are keen to present
this global initiative
to our NATO partners in the coming days.
Okay. Questions?
- [reporters clamoring]
- [man] President Derringer!
Uh, it's just been announced
that Water Cobra
is being expanded
into a cinematic universe.
Any chance you'll be making a cameo?
Oh, folks. [chuckles]
I promised the first lady
if I ever dressed up
as the Venom in Denim again,
it'd either be in the Oval boudoir
or for the White House
Correspondents' Dinner,
and you're only invited to the last one.
- [laughter]
- Prime Minister Clarke.
- Yes?
- The Daily Mail have photos
of the duchess and a new beau.
Any comments about your ex-girlfriend's
latest escapades?
Okay. Who has a real question?
Hey, hold on a minute.
Now, who else is tired of seeing
the prime minister as a single man?
I'll tell you what.
How about we get him
his own season of The Bachelor?
- Who's with me?
- [laughter]
- [excited chatter]
- [man] Yeah! Let's do it!
Jack Gordon.
There are six dead British and Americans
in Spain this morning.
Can you comment on speculation
this is the result
of a failed covert operation to capture
known arms dealer Viktor Gradov?
Covert operations are covert for a reason.
That's all I'm gonna say on that.
That and Gradov's gonna wish
we caught him yesterday.
Because when we do get our hands on him,
he is going to be forming
a special relationship
with the concept of retribution.
We should also be using this
as a collective moment of introspection,
find out what went wrong
and learn from it.
Leaks indicate that Echelon
was accessed during the op.
Are you ready to acknowledge the existence
of a top secret surveillance program
which monitors all of our emails,
video conferences, phone calls...
Tom.
There's only so many times
I can say "no comment" to that.
I'll comment.
Our enemies should be afraid.
We have the tools
and we have the technology
to find and destroy them
if they challenge us.
[Clarke] We aren't making
any promises except that
we will work tirelessly to get results.
Well, we are.
The United States of America
is promising results.
[Gordon clears throat]
President Derringer,
do you have a message for the families
of the men and women killed in Spain?
I've spent a lot of time
with Special Forces.
Trained with them, learned from them.
And what I have to say is
we must do better.
We will do better.
When you say, um, "trained with them,"
- that was for an acting role, yes?
- [light laughter]
Yes, but, uh...
I mean, y-you've never served.
As someone who did serve
in the British Army,
as most of you know,
if I did have something to say
to the families,
I would say it to them directly.
I do not salute heroes through you, Jack.
To be clear, you never saw combat.
[Gordon] But with all due respect,
gentlemen, you're politicians.
You don't equate yourselves
[chuckles] with actual heroes, do you?
Well, that was a shit-bath.
Socials are lighting up.
Hashtag "commanders in beef" is trending.
Goddamn it!
You knew Jack Gordon was trouble.
I warned you.
My town. I'll call on whomever I want.
Let's take five.
[Clarke] You know,
I'm not afraid of the press.
Not all of us have a compulsive need
to be liked by everyone.
With all due respect...
I know you like to fight
his battles for him, Simone.
[Clarke] Your presidency is in diapers.
You're on a learning curve.
- I've been on this slog for six years.
- [Derringer] You?
I fight my own battles.
You, you want to talk numbers?
Your approval ratings,
that's a great place to start.
[sighs]
Unlike you, I'll take results
over likes on Instagram.
You-you clearly don't care
about what people think.
You called for a collective moment
of introspection?
Let's just say I'm more concerned
with how people pay their mortgages
and send their kids to university.
Oh, for sure, 'cause God knows
there's nothing the public loves more
than politicians giving them homework.
Is this about the fish and chips thing?
'Cause if it is, just say it.
I am not mad about the goddamn
fish and chips thing.
Enough. Neither of you were
at your best today.
[Quincy] Agreed.
We need to give this a short shelf life.
He's right. Change the narrative.
Turn this into an opportunity.
To show that you guys are united.
[Clarke scoffs]
I've got it.
You fly to Trieste together
on Air Force One.
I don't know if we have enough room.
No, I'm good, thank you very much.
And besides,
I have to be in Warsaw tonight.
Hear me out, all right?
You both do 35 seconds
on the airstairs here in London,
waving and smiling, pit stop in Warsaw.
You'll be in Trieste by breakfast.
By that time,
pictures of you on those airstairs,
a vision of solidarity,
will be on the front page
of eight out of ten newspapers
all around the world.
[sighs] Quincy.
Bradshaw.
I am the President of the United States.
I don't share the stage with anyone.
Hitch a ride? Is that your solution?
It's a guaranteed
three-point bump in the polls.
Look, we are in the early days.
You've got to show you can make friends.
Right now we need him
more than he needs us.
Sam, take the win.
Take the flight.
Will you be there?
I'll go with the advance team.
Quincy and I will foam the runway
with the press in Trieste.
[sighs]
Mr. Prime Minister.
Would you do me the honor and fly with me
aboard Air Force One?
[gunshot]
I'll be honest.
It kept me up all night.
How is it that I hire
the best sniper money can buy
and he misses the one shot
meant to protect
the most important man
in my entire operation?
Yeah, thanks,
but we're all just doing our part.
Pieces of a puzzle, patches on a quilt...
[sniffs]
[Gradov] I assumed
it was faulty equipment.
But now I know it was human error.
Like you say...
[speaking Russian]
[chuckles softly]
"Everything that happens
happens for the best."
Yes.
[gulps]
Come.
Sit down.
My mother was very fond of that phrase.
Yes.
She was a gadalka.
A fortune teller.
- She read tea leaves.
- [pours drink]
She could see the future.
She saw mine and said that one day
I would be served a great injustice,
and it would be my mission in life
to punish those responsible.
And nothing or no one would get in my way.
[tense music playing]
[screaming, gurgling]
[man gagging]
[grunts]
- [crowd cheering]
- [The Star-Spangled Banner playing]
[reporter] It's been over
a decade since a U.S. president
has hosted a British prime minister
on Air Force One,
making this trip
one for the history books.
Check her out.
Fresh off the assembly line.
30-foot wider wingspan
than the previous model.
Can break Mach 1,
oh, and corners like an F-15.
Surprised you didn't paint flames
on the side of it.
Ah, you're just jealous 'cause your plane
sucks and doesn't have a cool name.
Fellas.
[chanting] We love Will! We love Will!
[chanting continues]
- [cameras clicking]
- [crowd cheering]
[excited chatter]
[engines powering up]
[majestic music playing]
Mr. Prime Minister.
I heard you like rye.
This one comes
from my hometown in Kentucky.
Mmm.
Now, that is American exceptionalism
in action.
Thank you.
Enjoy, sir.
[door closes]
[pensive music playing]
♪ ♪
There he is. Come on.
Say hello to Prime Minister Clarke. Hey.
Be nice to him, Sawyer.
He's besties with Harry Styles.
Well, I don't know about that,
but next time he's in Washington,
I'll see if I can get you some good seats.
- Thank you.
Nice to finally meet you,
Mr. Prime Minister.
Now, honestly, just-just call me Sam.
I'm so sorry we missed each other.
You two take care of yourselves,
and go easy on him, Sam.
We're still learning the ropes.
I'll try and keep him out of trouble.
Okay, hey.
Love you guys. Talk to you tomorrow.
You're good at that.
Good at what?
Being normal. Ish.
Uh, thank you?
You should show people
that side of you more often.
Start by ditching the bachelor status.
World leader who's unmarried?
Freaks people out,
leaves too much to the imagination.
What are they imagining?
I don't know, Eyes Wide Shut parties
or by night you're some masked vigilante
into some weird, unsettling shit.
Look, people want clarity.
Marriage gives them clarity.
It softens the image.
I'm confused. Are you giving me advice
or are you pitching me
on one of your shit rom-coms?
All right, I get it.
You don't like my movies.
I've never seen your movies.
Because Sam Clarke is the man
who does not like to be entertained.
No, it's 'cause I like actual cinema.
Come on.
You don't think I wanted to work
with Wes Anderson
or Bong Joon Ho? Of course I do.
I'm classically trained.
Did you know I once did a play
with Edward Norton?
Mm.
But the universe keeps telling me
I look cool with a gun in my hand.
A toy gun.
What is it with you?
Walking around, thinking
you're better than everybody else.
First, thought it was a British thing.
Then I realized it's a you thing.
- I know Paul McCartney, okay?
- Wow.
He's put a whole lot more wins
on the board than you,
and he is cool as shit!
[mysterious music playing]
- Want me to take it up?
- I got it. Thanks.
And you know what?
I'm not gonna apologize
for wanting to be liked or loved.
We're blessed with two
of the most extraordinary jobs
ever created, and part of that job
is to instill hope.
It's to make people feel good.
Yeah, well, based on my experience, okay,
hope is just delayed disappointment.
Doesn't put food on the table.
Doesn't put a roof over anyone's head.
And if you want to focus
on making people "feel good,"
then you're never gonna understand
how to help them.
You are the commander in chief.
You're not some DJ in Vegas.
I don't need to be refreshed
on my job title.
Let's be clear about that.
♪ ♪
[military radio chatter]
Don't tell the captain
I snuck you his stash.
Thanks.
[men grunting]
[dramatic music playing]
[screams]
[switch beeps]
Move to intercept.
Just know,
once this honeymoon period is over,
there is only disappointment
in your future,
because this job, my job,
is about suffering.
Yeah, Nostradamus?
When that day comes,
maybe then you and I can sit down
and talk about it
over some fish and chips.
I knew the truth would come out.
There it is.
Oh, great. You did it, Agatha Christie.
You cracked the case.
Let's give Scooby Snacks to everybody.
Will, let it go.
You took my opponent for fish and chips
in broad daylight
in the middle of "Liester" Square,
and you knew photographers would be there!
First of all,
it's pronounced Leicester Square.
And, no, bollocks, he's an old friend.
I took him for lunch.
You knew there were
political implications.
Not all of us have some posh
Cambridge Mafia in Parliament
helping us get elected!
I busted my ass to get to where I am.
I was born in a housing estate
and was never given anything
on a silver platter.
I worked three jobs to pay for Cambridge,
and then to the Army,
and then to community organizing,
and then Defence Attaché,
and worked my way up through Parliament.
Now, not all of us got our political start
because some commercial agent
decided they like
- our G.I. Joe jawline!
- Watch it!
No, no, no! You went from modeling
your underwear to being on the red carpet
to having your finger
on the nuclear button,
all without doing a single day
of public service!
So, yes, mate, when I see you
play the role of president,
it makes me sick to my stomach,
because you know your lines--
oh, yes, you do--
but you're not believable in the part.
And if I could've endorsed
your opponent, yes, I would've,
because at least there'd be a real leader
in the White House
and not some embarrassing,
bullshit, popcorn president!
- What's that?
- You heard what I said!
No, what's that?
[dramatic music playing]
Sirs, secure yourselves in the office.
♪ ♪
- Fasten your seatbelts. Sir.
- [man] Yeah?
[flight attendant] Take your seat, please.
- What's happening?
- Unidentified aircraft,
you're in restricted airspace.
Pull away immediately
or you will be fired upon.
All radios are out.
Comms are fried across the board.
[alarm buzzes]
- [door opening]
- [alarm blaring]
[devices beep]
[Crasson] Dear God.
- Ready the weapons.
- Yes, sir.
Oh, shit.
[tablet beeping]
Uh, gentlemen.
- [alarm beeping]
- [man] Multiple inbound bogies!
Open fire!
[men grunting]
[yelling]
Mr. President! Sir!
What the hell's going on?
Shit. We got to get
to the back of the plane! Go!
- Go! Go!
- [panicked chatter]
Stop shooting the drones!
Shoot the goddamn plane!
[panicked chatter]
[screaming]
Hold on!
[straining]
Initiating emergency descent to 10,000
for cabin pressure stabilization.
[screaming and clamoring]
[screaming]
Let's go!
There are parachutes in the back!
[copilot] Here comes another wave.
We lost engine two.
Gonna lean into it.
[grunting]
[gasps]
[Crasson] Come on, we got to jump!
That way! Through the door!
[Clarke yells]
Come on, sir! Move!
- We're leveling out.
- [alarm beeping]
[screaming]
They're finished.
Let's go home.
[grunts]
[Crasson] Let's go!
Come on! Let's move! Quick!
These two should be intact.
Shit!
We're going down in Belarusian airspace.
You'll need to get
to our safe house in Poland.
Rip it hard once you're out.
The chute'll do the rest.
We can double up.
Not a chance. Too risky.
What about all these people?
We all have our jobs to do.
Yours is to survive.
Get to Golden Mountain Mining Company
under the Gdanski Bridge in Warsaw.
Let me hear it, sirs.
Golden Mountain Mining Company.
Gdanski Bridge!
It's been an honor, Mr. President.
[both screaming]
[grunts] Oh, shit.
[grunting]
[grunting, groaning]
[screams]
We have just received devastating footage
of Air Force One going down
over Western Belarus.
President William Derringer
and Prime Minister Samuel Clarke...
are presumed dead.
[sobs]
[reporter] We're awaiting word
from the Pentagon
on the potential cause or suspects.
No groups are claiming responsibility
for this tragic loss.
An emergency session of Parliament
is convening
to discuss succession strategy,
while moments ago
V.P. Elizabeth Kirk was sworn in
as acting president in Trieste, Italy.
...where gathering NATO leaders
are offering their condolences
and unyielding solidarity.
What was meant to be a celebration
of the North Atlantic Alliance
is now a time of unprecedented
shock and mourning.
[birds chirping]
[gasps] Oh, geez.
You okay?
Yeah. You?
How the hell'd they get on my plane?
With the help of someone on the inside,
that's for sure.
The Polish border
is about 15 miles that way.
On foot, we can be at that safe house
by morning.
No. The cavalry's coming.
Cavalry's not coming, mate.
Belarus will want to control
the crash site.
Won't be letting any planes
into their airspace,
and there's no way our guys
are sneaking across enemy lines
to retrieve corpses.
They have to assume
there are no survivors.
Shit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
Calling my wife.
I'm letting her know I'm alive.
No. No, no, no, no.
No. No phones.
All right? Do as I do.
[water splashes]
We just survived
the worst security breach in history,
so you have to assume
whoever wants you dead
is listening to communications, okay?
I'm calling my family
to let them know I'm okay.
And we should let
the world know we're okay.
News flash: We're not okay.
All right? If we fall
into the wrong hands,
best-case scenario:
they use us as a political football.
Worst-case scenario is... [grunts]
they make an example of us.
Now put that down!
You know what happened to the last guy
who threw a shoe at a sitting president?
You're not sitting. You're hanging.
All right?
You know what? Piss off.
You want me to piss off?
- Yeah.
- Okay, I'll piss off.
I'll piss off all the way to Warsaw.
Enjoy living the rest of your life
as a bird sanctuary.
[grunts]
All right, don't piss off.
Would you just help me down
for Chrissakes, please?
There you go. Look at that.
An American action hero
asking me for help.
Even in his most noble moments,
he was still petty and mean-spirited.
I'm gonna drop you on three.
Three!
[screams, grunts]
[birds squawking]
[Derringer panting]
You all right back there, Derringer?
I'm fine.
Hearing a lot of panting and snuffling.
I don't snuffle, okay?
Besides, don't concern yourself
with how another man breathes.
Boundaries, guy.
Nothing to be embarrassed about.
Endurance is tough for guys like you.
Guys like me?
Guys like you. You know, gym strong.
- Gym strong?
- Gym strong.
As opposed to?
- Strong strong.
- Want to see gym strong?
I'll rip a tree out of the ground
and beat you to death with it, huh?
- Go on, then.
- What?
Rip that tree out
and beat me to death with it.
That's what I thought.
Silly thing to say, really.
Picked the biggest tree.
[pensive music playing]
Dear God.
Think he's had the day off.
[Derringer] Who the hell did this?
[Clarke] We got a lot of enemies.
Right now we got to get home alive.
That's our job.
No, our real job is to find out
who did this and make them pay.
Look, I want to get them
just as much as you do,
but these things don't happen overnight.
We got to pick our moment.
Took us ten years and two wars
before we got bin Laden.
I'm not waiting ten years.
One thing for certain,
whoever did this got some big balls.
There's no reason to think
this wasn't just phase one.
[dramatic music playing]
[Kirk] Tell the Pentagon
to move DEFCON status up,
and inform Russia, China and Iran
this is not a moment to get adventurous.
Don't challenge us
and don't think we're distracted.
- Yes?
- Echelon is standing by
- for system security update.
- Please.
This is Kirk.
This is Echelon Director Adams.
Please confirm voiceprint
and retinal scan.
Alpha, Echo, Bravo, Alpha, Charlie,
Zulu, Tango.
Voiceprint confirmed.
[scanner trilling]
Biometrics confirmed.
Commence continuity
of government protocol.
[Hammond] Sir.
[sighs]
What's happening?
They're rebooting the system.
In three, two, one.
[computers whirring and beeping]
Almost there.
[alarms blaring]
[analysts murmuring]
Someone's inside the system.
[phone vibrating]
Uh, wh-what's happening?
[laptop beeping]
We are now in control of Echelon.
Now we're talking.
There's our ride to Warsaw. [chuckles]
[♪ Hard Bass School and RebMoe
plays "Discoteka v Garazhe"]
We can't just walk down
and ask them for a lift.
I'd agree with you, but you're wrong.
We can.
We're two of the most recognizable men
on the planet.
Ha. You're not even one of the most
recognizable British people.
You get my point.
The point is we need help,
we ask them for help.
What part of "keep our heads down"
don't you understand?
- You got a better idea?
- Yeah, I do.
I say we move fast,
creep along that tree line
and hot-wire that car over there.
♪ ♪
[donkey brays]
Since when do you know how to hot-wire?
I don't, but you do.
You got busted at 16
for stealing your neighbor's Camaro.
Where'd you hear about that?
I vetted you.
You vetted me?
I'm the President of the United States.
You don't vet me. I vet you.
Well, did you vet me?
- Not the point.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
- [Derringer] Come on. Come on.
- [chickens clucking]
[engine sputtering]
Yeah, there he is.
Boys.
[song stops]
[spits]
- [engine sputtering]
- Oh, no.
We have incoming.
I'm going to talk to them.
- They'll give us a ride.
- [hushed] No, no, no.
You're gonna start this car,
and we're gonna get out of here.
Trust me. I poll really well
with young men who drink beer.
I speak their language.
Except you literally
don't speak their language.
Cinema is the international language.
- Watch the magic.
- Will. Hey.
Hey, fellas, how's it going?
We got a little turned around.
We could use some help.
It's me, Will Derringer.
You know, Water Cobra.
[yelling wildly]
Huh, still nothing?
Nice watch.
- Huh?
- I think you should give him the watch.
Let me try it on.
This is a gift from Keanu
when we wrapped Carnage 2.
Yeah, well, I hope Keanu gifted you
some kung fu lessons,
'cause we're about
to get our asses kicked.
Man, read the room.
["Discoteka v Garazhe" resumes playing]
See?
[speaking Russian]
That's enough! [grunting]
On your right!
- [grunts]
- [shouts]
Oh, sorry.
[song continues with lyrics in Russian]
Don't.
Stop!
I said, stop!
[song slows, stops]
[groans]
What have you done?
- [man panting]
- [chickens clucking]
You are dead men.
["Discoteka v Garazhe" resumes playing]
[grunting]
[man yells]
[distorted yell]
[chickens squawk]
[screams]
- Hey!
- [yelling]
[groans]
[pained groaning]
Ah, God.
You okay?
[both groaning]
[song continues with lyrics in Russian]
[man yelling]
[shouting in Russian]
[screaming]
[grunts, sniffs]
[confused grunt]
[men yelling]
[song stops]
Get your asses home!
You half-witted cretins!
[men shouting in Russian]
Yankees?
No, no, no. Canadians.
Why'd you say Canadians?
Everybody loves Americans.
Americans love Americans.
Today we're Canadians.
Trust me.
Where you go?
Across the border to Warsaw.
Papers?
No papers.
Okay.
I take you.
I have great ride.
[♪ Dave Van Ronk sings
"Hang Me, Oh Hang Me"]
♪ Hang me, oh, hang me ♪
♪ I'll be dead and gone ♪
♪ Wouldn't mind the hanging ♪
♪ but the laying in the grave so long,
poor boy ♪
- ♪ I've been all around this world ♪
- [sheep bleating]
Eh, it'll be great for our memoirs.
"Chapter 14.
It was exactly like when Churchill met FDR
for the first time,
just with an added splash of sheep shit."
Could be worse.
We're experiencing
the kindness of a stranger.
We're en route to safety.
Shortly after we get there,
we'll make our enemies feel
[dramatically] the ripple of our wrath.
Is-is that the...
Battle cry of the central character
in one of the most seminal
action franchises
in the last decade? Hell yeah.
What?
What do you Brits know
about slogans anyway?
[mockingly] "Keep calm and carry on."
You know,
that-that's actually like saying,
"Do nothing and continue
to do nothing," right?
Yeah, we don't all fetishize taglines
to the same degree.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Well, here's what I don't get, okay?
If life is such a Möbius strip
of failure and futility,
why would you want to lead
an entire nation?
I just like sitting in musty old rooms,
arguing with boring old men
about tax code.
- Okay?
- That's a good one.
Seriously.
Why would you want to run
for highest office in the land?
[Clarke scoffs]
Yeah, fine. Me first.
Did you know I didn't travel
outside the U.S.
until I was 28 years old?
First Water Cobra press tour.
And it was there I realized,
man, there are awesome people everywhere.
But the world is so damn fractured.
So I figured if I could use my celebrity,
even just for a little bit,
to bring people together,
wouldn't that be a good thing?
[chuckles]
Okay. What's your excuse?
Certainly not about believing
you'd deliver people to better days.
I believe in better days.
In fact, this day has got me believing
in better days
more than any other day,
because any day would be better
than being stuck in the muck
with you and a bunch of...
You having a rough one, huh?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Take it up with your security detail.
Or my security detail.
Or anybody on that flight.
[pensive music playing]
Down, down, down, down, down.
- [dog barking]
- [men speaking Russian]
Passports and documents for the livestock.
Kill the engine and get out.
[engine shuts off]
[sheep bleating]
Maybe we could make a deal?
What?
["Hang Me, Oh Hang Me" resumes]
♪ Went up on the mountain ♪
♪ There I made my stand ♪
Think I'm ready to write
those memoirs now.
♪ There I made my stand ♪
♪ Rifle on my shoulder ♪
♪ and a dagger in my hand ♪
♪ Poor boy,
I've been all around this world ♪
[trolley bell ringing]
[gearshift clicks]
[song ends]
Thank you.
Take this.
It was my pleasure...
Mr. President.
Good luck to both of you.
- [gearshift clicks]
- [sheep bleating]
[doorbell rings]
[intriguing music playing]
[door buzzes]
[Hammond] Sir, Echelon intercepted
security footage
from a CIA safe house in Warsaw
that just buzzed in two guests.
With all due respect,
we got what we needed
when we took down Air Force One.
Quiet your mouth.
And we kept our footprint tight,
- so who cares if they live?
- [phone dialing]
They die because I say they die.
[phone beeps]
[helicopter whirring]
They're alive. Warsaw.
Warsaw! Let's go!
[pilot speaks Russian]
♪ ♪
You're alive.
Oh.
[sobbing softly]
Okay. Hey.
- Are you crying because of me?
- Hell yeah, I am, man.
I mean, sir.
I'm sorry. Marty Comer.
Oh, well.
[Comer] Station agent.
A huge fan.
Patriot.
Sam Clarke, British prime minister.
- Can we come in?
- Yeah.
Yeah, of course, of course.
- [chuckles]
- Like, now?
- Yeah, now.
- Thank you.
Right this way.
Okay, so I know this sounds,
uh, bonkers, but...
What's the playbook on this?
For this?
[stammers, chuckles]
Th-There is no damn playbook.
I mean-- And we got lots of playbooks.
Ones that account for pole shifts,
computers becoming self-aware,
space monkey attacks,
- all kinds of hectic shit.
- [desk thumps]
But, uh, none that contemplate
you two sauntering in here
after dying in front of
the entire planet's eyes.
So no playbook?
Let's make one.
They say never meet your heroes,
but to them I say:
You've never met
President William Matthew Derringer.
- Your initials are WMD?
- [keypad beeping]
Yeah. Pretty bitchin', right?
Follow me, gentlemen.
Your timing's great, by the way.
The ambassador just recalled
all in-country personnel to the embassy.
It's a real nut punch
in a Ziploc bag out there.
And it ain't exactly a coincidence,
if you ask me.
W-Wait, what's not?
Well, first you two go down,
and then someone rolls a political grenade
into that NATO conference.
You guys didn't hear?
No, we've had a pretty busy day.
[sighs] Well, apparently,
Echelon servers were infiltrated.
Two hours ago,
a tranche of classified documents
were leaked,
exposing decades of covert activity
amongst NATO members:
industrial espionage, economic sabotage
and the influencing of foreign elections.
And the real pisser?
These weren't acts committed against
enemy nations but against each other.
These were friends against friends.
I'm talking some real Monica and Rachel
season two shit.
I mean, tomorrow's summit's
gonna be a monkey knife fight
in a telephone booth.
Germany just found out
France embedded journalists
to influence their last election.
The Czech Republic wants Italy
kicked out of the building
for trying to tank their economy.
All while we're locked out of the most
powerful surveillance tool on this planet.
How many files are we talking about?
20,000 and counting.
It's the most damaging leak
of state secrets in history.
Someone is using Echelon
to tear at the very fabric of NATO.
Sounds like NATO has been
tearing at the fabric of itself.
Bet you're dying to say "I told you so."
Excuse me?
You ran your primaries on "America first."
Simone, I am allowing you to be
in this room out of respect for Will.
Allowing me?
But please don't ever insinuate
that I'm not all in on this alliance.
If NATO falls, there's no more backstop
against despots and dictators.
They run unchecked.
It could set off a series of events
that-that would
destabilize Europe
and the rest of the world.
We are talking about the potential
for increased conflict, chaos
and the very real threat
of war on a global scale.
We put our heads above water.
Call the embassy.
Let them know you have us.
No, we have to assume
all high command posts are compromised.
Bullshit.
We are in a secure U.S. facility.
You guys want a hit of these Pringles?
Last time I was in one of those,
we got shot out of the sky at 40,000 feet.
- Hmm?
- [chip crunches]
Make the call.
- Mm-hmm.
- Don't make the call.
Make the call.
- Hmm.
- Don't make the call.
- I can't make the call.
- I'm the commander in chief!
- Make the goddamn call.
- The line's dead.
[alarm buzzing]
Is that normal?
No.
[intense music playing]
Somebody really wants us dead.
We're safe, we're in a safe house, right?
[mechanical creaking]
We got this.
That feel safe enough for you?
♪ ♪
Shit.
Not in the movies now, son.
[Comer] Okay, listen up.
I'm gonna get you guys out of here,
but just in case things do go south,
best to beat a retreat
through the secondary exit.
That's a left out of here,
down the hall, make a left.
That's the bunk room.
Another right, you should see
a poster on the wall.
You punch through that poster,
you should be good to go.
[♪ Beastie Boys singing "Sabotage"]
Feed me, boys.
♪ ♪
♪ I can't stand it ♪
♪ I know you planned it ♪
- ♪ I'm-a set it straight, this Watergate ♪
- [beeps]
♪ I can't stand rocking when I'm in here ♪
♪ 'cause your crystal ball
ain't so crystal clear ♪
♪ So while you sit back and wonder why ♪
♪ I got this ... thorn in my side ♪
♪ Oh, my God ♪
♪ It's a mirage, I'm telling y'all ♪
♪ it's sabotage ♪
[beeping]
[grunting]
♪ So, so, so ♪
♪ So listen up
'cause you can't say nothing...
[speaking Russian]
All of you in here! Now!
♪ I'm out and I'm gone ♪
♪ I'll tell you now, I keep it on and on ♪
♪ 'Cause what you see...
[chuckles]
That boy's a nutter.
Maybe, but he's America's nutter.
♪ That's a mirage ♪
♪ I'm trying to tell you now,
it's sabotage...
[gasping]
♪ ♪
[bell dings]
[whooping]
[gasps]
Let's move.
[shudders]
♪ Listen, all y'all ♪
♪ it's a sabotage ♪
♪ Listen all y'all, it's a sabotage ♪
♪ I can't stand it,
I know you planned it ♪
♪ I'm-a set it straight, this Watergate ♪
♪ Lord, I can't stand rocking
when I'm in this place ♪
♪ because I feel disgrace
because you're all in my face ♪
♪ But make no mistakes
and switch up my channel ♪
♪ I'm Buddy Rich
when I fly off the handle ♪
♪ What could it be? It's a mirage...
Get out of here.
♪ That's sabotage ♪
Go!
[song ends]
[gunshot]
Come on!
No, no, this way. He said right!
Damn it!
[dramatic music playing]
No, no, Rambo! Come on!
Oh, found the poster.
Punch it.
Oh, goddamn it.
- What's the problem?
- I can't.
You having a laugh?!
Come on!
Forgive me.
[frustrated shout]
[shouts angrily]
[both panting]
I think I killed that guy.
Only thing you killed is the wall.
I have to say, though,
you do look good with a gun in your hand.
[both grunt]
- You should go.
- No, you go.
Drop your guns!
We have them.
Coming down.
- [tires squealing]
- [siren wailing]
[both yell]
[siren slows to a stop]
[pensive music playing]
Noel?
Sam?
- I thought you were dead.
How are you not dead?
You two know each other?
- We...
- We worked together. Back in the day.
How'd you find us?
[gasps loudly]
[engine starts]
[men scream, grunt]
- All right, I'll tell you!
- [Taser crackles]
- [bird calls]
- [beer gurgling]
[chanting] Hey! Hey!
[group cheering]
- [siren chirps]
- [tires squeal]
[shouts in Polish]
Long story.
Hey, where's your backup?
- There is no backup.
- [device beeps]
[coughing]
I've been trailing Gradov since Spain.
- Victor Gradov is behind this?
- The gun guy?
- Mm-hmm.
[Clarke] So you're saying
this is all payback
because we stopped him building nukes?
That way. Gradov wasn't building a nuke.
But he was a weapons developer.
He was, but his son wasn't.
Yeah, what's his son got to do with it?
His son was a scientist.
He was brilliant
and made incredible breakthroughs.
He was on the brink of onlining
the first ever nuclear reactor
incapable of melting down.
The pebble-bed technology.
Our pebble-bed technology?
The same technology I just told
the world that we developed?
- You're telling me Gradov's son
invented it?
- [shushes]
He was close.
He still needed the enriched plutonium,
which his father procured
from the black market.
Echelon picked up on that transaction.
Of course we assumed
it was to build a weapon.
So we did what one does
when faced with a nuclear threat.
You dropped warheads on foreheads?
We did.
Gradov's son was amongst the dead.
The operation was sanctioned by NATO.
We couldn't risk the chance
that he was building a nuke.
Millions of lives were at stake.
It was only in the aftermath we realized
what was actually being developed.
So with the help of Echelon,
we procured the schematics
for the pebble-bed tech.
- [siren whooping]
- Get back.
[siren wailing]
[siren fades]
So we took his son's life
and then his legacy, huh?
Which we were about to take
a big victory lap for in Trieste.
Correct me if I'm doing the math wrong,
- but we're the assholes here.
- Okay, look.
Gradov's son didn't die because of us.
He died because he's the son of the devil.
Let's keep it moving.
[Clarke] Gradov couldn't have
done all this
without top-level security clearance.
Okay, so then the question is:
Who was Gradov working with on the inside?
Got to start with the guy
who put us both in that plane.
What?
You weren't supposed to fly with me.
Somebody put that idea
in your head, insisted on it.
Quincy.
[crowd clamoring over TV]
A safe house was hit in Warsaw.
What are you thinking?
Could be Will and Sam?
There must have been something
in there worth going after.
We have to consider the possibility...
[Quincy] Did you not see what we all saw?
They went down with Air Force One.
I'm not giving up hope. Not yet.
None of us should be.
We need to focus all our energies
on this Echelon leak.
The rhetoric is heating up.
But if there's even a chance
that Will and Sam are still alive...
We put CIA on the safe house in Warsaw.
And right here in this building,
the focus is on stopping
the bleeding with NATO.
I want an audience with Italy,
Germany and France as soon as possible.
It's time these guys
stopped clutching their pearls
and get on with the business of leading.
[phone vibrating]
It's my son. Excuse me.
Hi, sweetheart.
Simone, I appreciate
how much Will meant to you.
I know he was like a brother,
but he's gone.
They're both gone.
You need to start wrapping
your head around that.
- There's no way it's Quincy.
- How can you be sure?
He's been my chief of staff for six years.
I known him since university.
The way normal people know him
or the way you know people?
[Clarke] Ah, don't start that shit again.
Does he like bangers and mash
or fish and chips?
Ah, I see what you did there.
Sneaking the fish and chips
back into the conversation.
You must be exhausted
trying to figure that out.
Stop chipping away at each other.
We need to be on the same page.
Did she just hit us with a pun?
[sighs] She loves a pun.
I tried to tell her
puns are for simple people.
- I love puns.
- My point exactly.
[hushed] Guys!
Over here.
Come on.
Look, right now
the key is getting to Trieste.
Trieste? How far away
is the U.S. embassy from here?
They can help us.
We're not going to the embassy.
Wait, why won't anyone
let me go to my embassy?
What does everybody suddenly
have against embassies?
- [men speaking Russian]
- [shushes]
[hushed] We have to presume
that all high command posts
are compromised.
Say that again, I'm gonna scream.
Not just a conventional scream,
a guttural wail.
Let's go.
Listen, I'm the commander in chief.
Okay, respectfully, sir, no, you're not.
The vice president was sworn in
a few hours ago.
And he has never been
commander in chief of anything.
The king is.
In fact, he's the only head of state
that's not an actual head of state.
Again, king.
You're just two guys
that are shit out of luck.
So let's go.
Come on.
[over headphones] ♪ Turn around,
bright eyes ♪
- ♪ Every now and then I fall apart...
- [sparks crackling]
You are now my package.
My mission.
And my mission is to deliver you alive
to the most secure location
on this continent,
and that is the NATO summit in Trieste.
And my best shot at keeping
this mission on track
is that train.
[train horn blows]
Pun, this time, not intended!
- You seem very "locomotivated"!
- [laughs]
Trying to make sure
this thing doesn't go off the rails!
Ha!
Well, that confirms it!
I died in that plane crash,
and this is hell!
♪ I don't know what to do,
and I'm always in the dark ♪
♪ We're living in a powder keg...
Come on!
- ♪ I really need you tonight...
- [grunting]
- You good?
- Thank you.
♪ Forever's gonna start tonight ♪
♪ Once upon a time,
I was falling in love ♪
♪ now I'm only falling apart ♪
[laptop beeps]
♪ Nothing I can say ♪
♪ A total eclipse of the heart... ♪
[song fades]
[Gradov speaking indistinctly]
[intriguing music playing]
[train wheels clacking]
[train horn blows]
[gentle music playing]
[grunts softly]
[snoring]
About your team in Spain.
We've all lost a lot.
Look, I-I owe you a...
Please don't say an apology.
An explanation for disappearing
after Tripoli.
What happened in Tripoli?
None of your business. Go back to sleep.
Okay, first of all,
you didn't disappear in Tripoli.
You appeared everywhere.
You were on TV, newspapers,
social media...
I was running for office.
You were running away.
Was it love?
Were you running away from love?
Can you stay in your lane?
And you could have come with me.
On the campaign trail?
Like, go on breakfast TV
and share my mom's lasagna recipe
with the world?
We would have been together.
No, Sam.
We couldn't have been together.
I'm gonna go get something to eat.
Can I get you anything, Mr. President?
I'll have whatever you're having.
You got it.
[exhales heavily]
I'm just gonna go out on a limb here.
You two did a little more than
work together back in the day, huh?
I mean, she seems nice.
[scoffs] A lot better than
that best friend chief of staff of yours
that's a sleeper spy insurgent.
We're not having this conversation.
Listen, man,
she's a little emotionally distant.
Great sense of humor, though.
Hey.
Why'd you guys split up?
And he's back. Back to questions.
Come on. What happened in Tripoli?
- Don't.
- Come on.
- What happened in Tripoli, Sam?
- Stop saying "Tripoli"!
Fine, what happened
in the capital city of Libya?
It's where I told her
that I wanted to run for office.
Are you happy now?
And why'd you want to run for office?
Oh, God, are you still going?
Why'd you want to run for office, Sam?
Because, because I wanted
to build a better world
for her and I to grow old in together!
That's...
...the most romantic
goddamn thing I've ever heard.
Yeah, well, she didn't...
she didn't see it that way.
[dramatic music playing]
- Shit!
- Whoa, whoa. We can talk this out.
I know you're both enamored
with the sound of your own voice,
but there's no more talking.
[silenced gunshot]
- [man grunts]
- [gasping] What the hell?!
[groaning]
[pained groaning]
Oh, shit.
Didn't see that coming.
[grunts]
Already short on time as it is.
- [gun racks]
- Drop it.
- [gun thumps on floor]
- [Derringer] Whoa, hey.
- Don't shoot him.
- We need to hear him out.
You want to hear him out?
Let's do it on the move.
Come on.
[grunts]
All I wanted to do
was live my days out in peace,
but Gradov found me,
put his claws into me,
made me do things I never wanted to do.
But what's happening now,
what we've set into motion now,
it's a bridge too far.
I know you've figured out
there's an insider
working at the highest levels
of government.
And, no, I...
I don't know... [grunts]
I don't know who the insider is.
I never saw them face-to-face.
But they helped Gradov get into Echelon,
and they helped him take down
Air Force One.
Then how do we find out
who this insider is?
Through Gradov's secure communications.
Communications I designed.
But you'll have to get off
this train right now.
While it's moving?
Gradov's got the eyes of God
at his disposal.
They'll have a team waiting
at the next station to kill you.
- Great.
Look, there's a building in Croatia
I operated out of before
I ever knew the name Gradov.
Get to 12 Lavaska Street in Zadar.
There's a secure terminal there
on the fifth floor.
Give me your hand. [grunts]
[grunts]
This prompt will run a program I designed
to trace communications he had with anyone
carrying compartmented security clearance.
Run the program, you'll find the insider.
You have to end this.
Gradov is insatiable.
He'll never stop.
[Hammond groans, chuckles]
Feels nice to do something good
for a change.
Shit. Okay.
Okay.
You know what? We got this, okay?
Hell, I barrel-rolled off a freight train
in Death Jumpers.
No, you didn't. Your stuntman did.
Now? Now you want to bust me
on a technicality?
Sir, respectfully, no one
is barrel-rolling off of this train.
I think it's time to raise your heads.
- We have to call someone.
- No, no, no.
We have to assume that all
high command posts are compromised.
Yes, and if we resurface now,
the cover-up begins,
we never find out who's behind this,
and they get to fight another day.
So you'd rather jump off a train
that's going 40 miles an hour?
We've been taking this on the chin
for way too long,
and I'm done with being on the defensive!
Oh! Come on!
All right, hey!
Just tuck your chin to your chest!
Sure that's gonna make a difference?
Trust me!
[yells]
I think he's okay.
Damn you.
[yells]
Man up, Derringer.
You're the President of the United States.
Stars and stripes forever!
[grunting]
[Kirk] At the CIA, we had a saying:
"The strength of the organization
is the individual.
The strength of the individual
is the organization."
The collective that sits in this room
is the living embodiment of that.
And someone out there is manipulating us.
Trying to tear us apart.
So let's send whoever's
behind this a message.
Swing in the other direction.
Double down on NATO.
Let it be known
that if you try and break this bond,
it will only make us stronger.
[German chancellor] Those are
lovely sentiments.
But what you're asking for
is predicated on trust.
And I don't trust anyone in this room.
- Chancellor...
- It's fine.
Let him walk.
He's in a campaign season. He's scared.
You know what I'm going
to campaign on in the next cycle?
Withdrawing from this alliance.
[Italian prime minister sighs]
It's okay.
We can hold this together.
The U.S. will cover the cost
of their contribution.
That's what we all need, isn't it?
I think so.
More American arrogance
shoved down our throats.
There will be a vote held in the morning
with 25 countries already on board
to disband NATO,
including Italy.
I'll see you there, Madam President.
Man, the chin thing kind of worked, huh?
All right,
enough with the bloody chin thing.
You don't have a bloody chin
thanks to my killer pro tip.
Way to go, bro. You made her mad.
[engine starts]
[tires squealing]
♪ ♪
Thanks.
[sighs] Geez, Hammond didn't have
an incredibly sexy taste in hideouts, huh?
Well, some people like to hide out
in old derelict buildings,
and others like to suck on sheep nipples.
- Who sucks on sheep nipples?
- Nobody sucks on sheep nipples!
Okay. God. Geez.
- What floor?
- Fifth.
All right.
Come on, Gym Strong.
[Derringer panting]
There's nothing here.
Hammond, that lying son of a bitch.
Led us to a dead end.
Unless...
...he didn't.
[lights clinking]
[computer beeps]
[Derringer] Well, nice.
- Okay.
- [tires squealing in distance]
Do you hear that?
[tires squealing]
That does not look like the cavalry!
Lock yourselves in the safe room.
- I'm gonna go handle this.
- [Clarke] No, no, no.
You're the only one that can
get the intel off the server.
- I'll hold them off.
- Sam...
What, do you think I've lost a step?
I know you've lost a step.
I just don't want you dying on my watch.
Just go.
We got this.
You're coming with me. I need your hand.
[breathes deeply]
[dramatic music playing]
[men grunting, shouting in Russian]
I've been shot!
[speaks Russian]
You okay?
Yep!
Hand.
Okay.
[shouts]
[metallic clink]
Oh, shit.
[grunts]
[gasps]
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's holding them off,
but we need to go.
♪ ♪
[groans]
[screaming]
Come on, come on, come on.
Okay, we're in.
Abort!
Fall back!
- I got the insider.
- Yeah, it's Quincy.
It's Bradshaw.
Bullshit.
- Tell me where it says that.
- There are dozens
of communications between her and Gradov
going back almost 18 months.
Her digital fingerprints
are all over this.
- I'm sorry.
- You don't need to be sorry.
I'm gonna grind up her world
when I get my hands on...
[helicopter whirring]
[both gasp]
[shouts]
[straining] It's stuck.
[creaking]
[both grunting]
[yelling]
[yells]
- [Noel screams]
- [Derringer grunts]
- [grunts] You okay?!
- Yes!
Okay!
Sam.
[screaming]
[panting]
We need to get out of this box.
I need you over here! Now!
[Derringer grunts]
- You see that roof?
- Yeah.
Get as low as you can, okay?
- [grunts]
- [thumps]
[grunts]
[both gasping]
Get ready.
Drop!
[both scream, grunt]
[both panting]
[car alarms wailing in distance]
[pensive music playing]
[phone beeping]
It's handled.
[phone vibrating]
She paid you extra
to clean up loose ends, didn't she?
And now I'm the loose end.
[screaming]
[panting]
[pensive music playing]
[engine starts]
[thunder rumbling]
I'm sorry.
I know how much he meant to you.
We had this...
perfectly imperfect thing...
...that didn't fade with time or distance.
Knowing that someone loves
everything about the way you are.
[chuckles] Well, except the puns.
Sam hated those puns.
Yeah.
You know, for a second there,
I thought that the universe
did all this shit,
all this horrible shit,
just to bring us back together.
And I was happy.
Pretty demented, huh?
I just found out my best friend
tried to kill me
and wants to rip the heart out
of Western democracy,
so everything's being graded
on a curve today.
Yeah.
[newsman over TV]
...with a vote on the future of NATO
set 30 minutes from now
and with world leaders
openly expressing their outrage and anger
at their allies and friends,
-it seems imminent that after 75 years,
- [phone vibrating]
NATO is on the verge of collapse.
Yes?
[Derringer over phone] Madam President.
Thanks for keeping my seat warm.
Will? How did you...
- I'm coming in.
- Tell me what you need.
I'm at the Port of Trieste.
Send the Beast.
Oh, and, Kirk, Bradshaw's behind this,
- so box her out.
- O-Okay.
Um, I-I'll hold off
the NATO vote as long as I can,
and-and just get here safe.
[uplifting music playing]
Mr. President.
You sure are a sight for sore eyes.
- After you.
- Oh, thank you.
[Derringer sighs]
[tense music playing]
- [cell phone ringing]
- [cameras clicking]
Thank you, everybody.
The meeting will commence in 30 minutes.
- [lively chatter]
- [phone beeps]
Take them to the rally point
and do your job.
Don't disappoint me again.
[phone beeps]
It wasn't Bradshaw.
It's Kirk.
Of course it was the vice president.
It's always the vice president.
[phone beeps]
Kirk has them.
Don't let them get to NATO.
But Bradshaw's communications
were tied to Gradov.
[chef] Bradshaw was the decoy.
Kirk covered her tracks.
It's called contingencies.
You have your contingencies,
- I have mine.
- [button beeps]
[♪ Mötley Crüe singing
"Kickstart My Heart"]
♪ When I get high, I get high on speed ♪
♪ Top Fuel funny car's a drug for me ♪
♪ My heart, my heart ♪
♪ kick-start my heart ♪
[tires squealing]
♪ Always got the cops coming after me ♪
♪ Custom-built bike doing 103 ♪
- [gasping]
- ♪ My heart ♪
♪ My heart, kick-start my heart...
We got company!
♪ Ooh, are you ready, girls? ♪
Shoot him!
Take the shot!
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Kickstart my heart, give it a start ♪
- [horn blaring]
- ♪ Woah, yeah ♪
- [engine revving]
- ♪ Baby...
Oh, sh-shit.
- Take the wheel!
- Okay!
♪ Kick-start my heart,
hope it never stops ♪
♪ Woah, yeah ♪
♪ Baby, yeah...
[horn blaring]
♪ ♪
Yeah!
Ha!
♪ Kick-start my heart...
[grunting]
- Sam?
Hold her steady!
Okay, no problem!
♪ My heart, my heart ♪
♪ kick-start my heart ♪
♪ Say I got trouble, trouble in my eyes ♪
♪ I'm just looking for another good time ♪
♪ My heart, my heart,
kick-start my heart...
How are you alive?!
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[screaming]
♪ Baby...
[engine revving]
[horn blaring]
[whooping]
Easy.
I just kept calm and carried on.
- [Chef and Noel grunting]
- Help her. I've got this.
Come...
Sorry, mate.
♪ Yeah, are you ready na-na now? ♪
♪ Whoa, yeah ♪
♪ Kick-start my heart, give it a start ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Whoa...
[screams] Open the door!
- ♪ Give it a start...
- [door alarm chimes]
- [screams]
- [horn blaring]
[groans] Is it bad?
♪ Whoa, yeah ♪
♪ Kick-start my heart,
hope it never stops...
- Where are we going?
- I got you.
Don't go dying on me a third time, okay?
[Derringer] Oh, there's a knife in my leg!
♪ ♪
No, wait, wait.
Maybe we should leave it in.
No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no!
- Wasn't that bad.
- Good. Okay.
[console chimes]
Sam?
Punch it!
[sirens wailing]
Get down!
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Kick-start my heart... ♪
♪ Whoa, yeah ♪
♪ Baby ♪
I'm driving blind here!
[Derringer] Here! Sat view!
Nice.
[tires squealing]
Any other toys in this Batmobile?
- [grunting]
- [keypad beeping]
[gas hissing]
Smoke! [laughs]
♪ Ooh, ah ♪
♪ Kick-start my heart...
- Turn. Turn. Turn. Turn!
- I will. I will. I will.
♪ We did all of this to rock ♪
[screaming]
♪ Whoa, yeah...
[shouts in Russian]
[tires squealing]
♪ Whoa, yeah ♪
♪ B-B-B-B-B-B-Baby...
[woman screams]
♪ Kick-start my heart,
hope it never stops...
[Noel grunts]
The fridge!
What, are you gonna kill them with snacks?
Backup blood supply.
[British accent] Take this,
you bloody bastards!
- [tires squealing]
- [grunting]
[shouts in Russian]
[tires squealing]
That's the Beast. It's the Beast!
He's got a rocket launcher!
Sam, incoming!
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Baby...
[yells angrily]
♪ Kick-start my heart ♪
[song ends]
[automated voice] You have now
reached your destination.
[horn honks]
[Italian prime minster]
Effective midnight tonight,
Italy will be withdrawing
from the NATO alliance.
On behalf of the Republic of France,
we withdraw as well.
It's with a heavy heart,
despite my most strident efforts
to hold this alliance together,
on behalf of the United States,
I withdraw our...
Hold it right there!
- [crowd murmuring]
- [uplifting music playing]
[cameras clicking]
On behalf of the United Kingdom...
And the United States of America.
...take it all down
several notches, everyone.
That's right.
You're not getting rid of us that easy.
And we're not getting rid
of this alliance that easy,
because we all have a job to do.
I get it.
You're embarrassed. You're angry.
But we need NATO.
We need partnerships.
We need to treat each other with respect,
embrace each other's differences
and lean into our commonalities.
To send a message to future generations
that we were here.
That we did the right thing.
And that starts by taking the fight
to the very real enemies we face.
There it is.
The inevitable conclusion.
The people elect a dopey actor
as leader of the free world.
Of course their country can't survive.
And you just sealed the deal.
- These people are our partners,
and we need them.
- For what?
We grow food. We pump oil.
We manufacture.
Meanwhile, we send our people
to die in their wars.
This is not a partnership.
We give, they take.
But not anymore.
The plane is going down.
We put the oxygen masks
on ourselves first.
These are all false alliances anyway.
False alliances?
That's something you know a lot about.
That's what kills you most, isn't it?
It's not that I'm a better politician
than you'll ever be.
It's that I'm a better actor.
[gunshot]
[crowd screaming]
[dramatic music playing]
Kill them all.
Everybody, down!
[rapid gunfire]
[grunting]
Over there!
Get in here!
Get down.
[panicked screaming]
Deal with her.
[man screams]
Now! We should go now!
That way!
No, no, no! That way! Go! Go!
[gun clicking empty]
[straining]
- [door bangs]
- [Noel] Gradov!
[screaming]
Guys, come on! We've got to go!
- Sam!
- [Simone] Will!
[panting]
[grunting]
[calling whistle]
[wheezing cough]
[Clarke] Noel.
Get Gradov! I got this guy.
She said she's got it.
Go.
[knife clatters]
[groans]
[men screaming]
[straining]
[ominous music playing]
[panting]
Shoot him?
Hmm?
[gun clicks empty]
- [grunting]
- [dramatic music playing]
[sighs] Get the gun.
Oh.
Whoa!
- [groans]
- [bell dings]
[screams]
Who's the action hero now, huh?
Will!
Good to go?
Try not to kill the wall.
[grunts]
I got him. I got him.
[both panting]
[pained grunt]
[pained shout]
[Noel yells]
[panting]
He's got to be in here somewhere.
[intriguing music playing]
[gun clicking empty]
I think he's out.
Let's dance.
[dramatic music playing]
[gun clicking empty]
Drop it.
Back up.
Back up!
[Clarke] There's nowhere to go.
It's over.
Not for me.
Goddamn it!
We're gonna let him get away?
We can't wait ten years to get this guy.
We're not waiting ten years.
Do you remember at the end
of Water Cobra 2?
You said you never saw my movies.
I know. I lied. I've seen them all.
They're classics.
But the one moment that
really cut through them all
is when Water Cobra sacrifices himself
to save his brother.
[♪ Elvis Presley sings
"Can't Help Falling in Love"]
You know what I'm talking about?
♪ Wise men say...
We go on three?
♪ Only fools...
Three!
♪ Rush in ♪
♪ but I can't help ♪
♪ falling in love ♪
♪ with you...
[distorted yelling]
♪ Shall I stay? ♪
♪ Would it be a sin...
[growling]
♪ If I can't help ♪
♪ falling in love ♪
♪ with you? ♪
[distorted grunt]
♪ Like a river flows ♪
♪ surely to the sea ♪
♪ darling, so it goes ♪
♪ some things are meant to be...
[clanking]
♪ Take my hand ♪
♪ take my whole life, too...
[distorted screaming]
♪ For I can't help...
- How's that for gym strong?
- [chuckles]
Hey!
♪ With you ♪
♪ For I can't help...
Everything harpoons for a reason.
♪ Falling in love...
[laughing]
♪ With you ♪
[song ends]
[Chuck Todd] Two months after
NATO nearly disbanded,
the alliance is making hopeful strides
in rebuilding trust.
President Derringer
and Prime Minister Clarke
have been crucial in these efforts,
as new transparency measures
are being implemented
and there's a restored
sense of cooperation.
- [waiter] Here you go.
- Cheers.
[quiet chatter]
Nice.
You two gonna rekindle?
Uh, I don't know.
She's halfway around the world
on some covert operation.
We'll see how it goes.
Still a bit complicated.
Well, just talk her out of the cons
and into the pros.
Maybe she'll come around.
Actually...
you might be able to help me with this.
"Congratulations on your
big bump in approval ratings.
Guess you're not as
poll-arizing as you thought."
Okay, so now we got to hit her
with a pun back.
Okay.
Uh, it's, um, it's, uh...
"That's nice,
but it polls in comparison to you."
[chuckles] You know what?
I think I'm just gonna go with:
"Thank you.
I miss you.
Hope to see you soon.
Don't get shot."
You know what? That's perfect.
Before I forget,
two tickets to a meet and greet
with Harry Styles in D.C.
It's official.
You are now the coolest Uncle Sam I know.
Thank you. You hungry?
Oh, I'm starving. What's good here?
I ordered us a little something.
Here you go, gents.
[laughing] Okay. All right.
Fish and chips.
Dig in.
You guys, um, got any, uh, ketchup?
No.
We do vinegar.
Yeah, these are fries.
This is not a salad.
Well, my country, my condiments.
- Mmm.
- Okay.
Okay. You know what?
Well, you come to the Oval Office,
we're doing ketchup.
Once you see the light,
you're gonna be stocking the, um...
What the hell's your office called again?
- My office?
- Yeah.
It's called "my office."
Boy, you guys are really afraid
of spicing things up, huh?
Oh, yeah. It's really spicy
to name things after colors and shapes.
You know what I mean.
"Hey, what should we call
this white house?
- Mm, the White House?"
- Don't.
"Hey, this office is oval.
What should we call it?
I know."
[both] The Oval Office.
- Yeah, yeah.
- That's real spicy.
Hey, you got a problem,
take it up with George Washington, okay?
He died a hundred years
before the Oval Office
- was even built.
- [reporters murmuring]
- [cameras clicking]
- [Derringer] Uh, why you gonna
bust me on a technicality?
[Clarke] Well, technically
it's not a technicality.
[Derringer] It's an insignificant detail.
[Clarke] No, it's a fact,
which is exactly what a technicality is.
[Derringer] When did you become a farmer?
- 'Cause you are milking this.
- [Clarke] Really?
Says you, the sheep nipple aficionado?
[Derringer] I don't even think
we need to talk about that.
[Clarke] You don't want
to talk about that?
[Derringer] No. No, we don't.
- [♪ Bill Withers sings "Lean on Me"]
- ♪ Lean on me ♪
♪ when you're not strong ♪
♪ and I'll be your friend ♪
[over speakers]
♪ I'll help you carry on...
[Comer] Did I take one for democracy?
You bet I did. Right in the noggin.
But who would've thunk it?
This bullet hit at the exact spot
where I had the metal plate installed
after my whole rotisserie grill debacle.
- [chuckles]
- [metallic knocking]
I mean, one nanometer either way,
I am not here sipping this Bahama Mama.
No, sir. [slurps]
Am I a hero?
Sure.
Yeah, that's what the president
and prime minister say
whenever we talk on a semi-regular basis.
And yes, there's some light chitchat
about a cabinet appointment.
No big deal.
- Yeah.
- Sure thing.
Nice try.
[sighs]
[slurping]
[Noel] I believe you.
Nice to meet you, Agent Comer.
[intriguing music playing]
[♪ Gipsy Kings singing
"Volare [Gipsy Kings Version]"]
[song continues with lyrics
in Italian and Spanish]
♪ ♪
[song ends]
[gentle music playing]
♪ ♪
[intriguing music playing]
[music ends]