Day 34 of observing Eun-seo
via the smart home system,
and behavior observation cams.
The cause of her symptoms
may have stemmed
from the panic
disorder five years ago,
after our mother's passing,
and the stress of moving
along with the stress
of practicing all day
for her audition by herself.
(Lucifer: A fallen
angel who rules Hell)
(Moloch: A demon that
devours child sacrifices)
(Beelzebul: Chief
lieutenant of Lucifer)
(Valac: A fallen angel who
became Hell's guardian)
(Archbishop: Leader
of the worshipers)
(overseeing the entire ritual)
(Worshippers:
Followers of the Devil)
(Exorcism: The act
of freeing someone)
(from possession
by an evil spirit)
(Holy Night: Demon Hunters)
All done!
Evening, Kim.
- Det. Choi, welcome.
- Good evening.
Hey, Sharon.
- Is Bow in?
- Yes, he is.
He's a client.
- Good evening.
- Hello.
You may go inside.
Boss, Det. Choi is here.
A month ago, my daughter
became unreachable,
I think she went missing.
She'd never just disappear.
Something is
definitely wrong here.
Three of my men were assaulted
while searching for her.
Two are dead, and one's in ICU.
As usual, I need
your help on this.
If the detectives were harmed,
I realized it was more serious.
So I asked him for a favor
and came to you for help.
Don't worry too much,
we'll look into this case closely.
Kim, get something to drink.
Sure, one moment.
I'm okay...
Pardon me...
Sorry about that.
Do you have any leads?
We secured a location
from a photo we obtained,
but my team got attacked
and we couldn't rescue her.
Here, Sharon.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Thanks.
- Go inside.
- Okay.
Would you like some water?
Don't worry, we'll do our best.
Detective...
Can I trust them...
You can absolutely trust us.
We may look shady,
but we're professionals.
Please find her for me.
- We'll do our best.
- Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Here's the payment,
in cash as usual.
You didn't skimp some
like last time, right?
What do you take me for?
I'm a cop.
How many clients have
I brought you so far?
For your kids.
What do you take me for?
Don't want it?
This is serious.
A lot of people have been killed.
I hear you.
All right, guys.
Let's go to work.
Murders and assaults
are taking place
by unknown assailants
across the country,
leaving the public in fear.
The police believe
that a mysterious group,
along with organized
criminals, are involved.
A special task force
has been formed,
but the criminals have
brutally murdered
officers at the scene...
In my 30 years as an officer,
I've never seen such
vicious incidents, Father.
They talk about demons and devils,
and as we witness
unbelievable events,
we can't handle this
with the police
force alone, Father.
They blindly devote themselves
to a devil worship per,
and obtained superhuman strength
by drawing on the Devil's power.
Ordinary people
can't stand up to them.
That's why we need him.
Kill them!
You vile demon.
I command you.
Return to hell!
You are Bael,
the Commander of Hell's Army.
Return to hell at once!
Return!
I command you!
Return to hell!
Return to hell immediately!
I command you.
Return to hell.
Return to hell immediately!
Let's see.
Okay.
Everything all right?
I'm fine.
No, not you, her.
The evil spirit hadn't
fully possessed her,
she'll be okay.
That's good.
Um, boss...
Things got pretty hairy earlier,
I missed some shots in the end.
What should I do?
Have another take?
Should I wake them all up?
No, we can't do that but
we need a proper ending.
You should've shot properly!
Yeah...
Is Det. Choi on the way?
Yes, he's heading over.
I got a lot better thanks to you.
I can breathe better,
thank you so much.
I'm glad to hear it.
You should still take your meds,
and I'll drop the dosage
as I monitor the progress.
Check up on her every 2 hours.
Yes, doctor.
(Exorcism)
(Patient Clip)
(Suspected of
Schizophrenia Day 142)
(Exorcism Treatment Day 7)
(The Man Who Punched
Out Four Gangs)
(and Illegal Fight Clubs)
(Are They Devils? Or Messiahs?)
Catalina, it's fine.
I'm making money to
build a Catholic orphanage.
No need to thank me.
Yeah, Catalina, okay.
Boss, I found out
who those guys served.
Who?
Beelzebul.
(Beelzebul: Chief
lieutenant of Lucifer)
Who's their leader?
I haven't found
their archbishop yet,
but I got informants
all over the place.
Ton of high-ranking demons
like Beelzebul are popping up,
a massive crisis may
be on the horizon.
I've seen them countless times,
but they still scare me.
We're scared too.
They're powered by demon's energy,
so always keep your guard up.
You still have a bright future.
And me?
Me?
Is my future bleak?
So hot today...
Excuse me.
Be gone!
My apologies, who are you?
May I help you?
Could I meet the owner?
Yes, I'm the owner,
what can I do for you?
My sister is really sick.
I came here because
I'm at wit's end.
Did Det. Choi tell you about us?
No, Father Mar...
Father Marco recommended us?
My apologies, we do
not work with them.
I'm sorry.
My sister is in danger!
If you help us, I'll do anything.
I brought money too.
Here.
If...
If she's sick,
take her to the hospital.
She should see
a neuropsychiatrist.
I'm a neuropsychiatrist!
Christ...
Please...
This contains her videos,
please give it to him.
I'm begging you.
I understand.
(Han Eun-seo)
(Neuropsychiatry approach...)
This is my sister and my home.
Jung-won and Eun-seo's home.
Let's live happily here.
- Let's never fight.
- Yeah, let's not fight.
Don't steal my clothes.
Don't use my make-up.
We moved today, so let's be happy.
Let's be happy.
- Thank you, sis.
- Not at all.
You like it?
Yeah, the air is so nice here.
As a fellow doctor,
I couldn't believe it
until I saw your sister.
Since the Church
officially prohibits exorcism,
I suggested you go to him.
Of course, as a doctor,
I know you must have had doubts...
Devil, exorcism,
I don't know about these things.
I simply want to
save my sister, Father.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Where did Sharon go?
She should be in her office.
By the way, boss,
do you want to see the footage
that pretty doctor brought?
Nah, forget it.
But if Father Marco sent her,
it could be something big.
Don't ever mention
his name to me again.
I'm sorry.
Where's Sharon, I
need to give this to her.
I'm right here.
Holy Jesus! She's right here...
Could you stop sneaking up on us?
(Sharon Kim Goon)
Here, here.
Your salary, thank you as always.
Good work.
Here.
Put it away.
Why is mine so thin?
Sharon's work is a lot tougher.
She's got to perform
rites on blades and stuff.
When do I ever do that?
Anyway, she does a lot
of really difficult tasks, thanks.
Take it.
Thank you, bud.
Wait a minute.
Demons and their worshippers
are increasing and getting bolder.
They flex in
the middle of the city.
More and more people
are dying, am I right?
And our workload
is growing too, right?
So, how about a salary bump?
It's been a while, hasn't it?
10 years already.
You haven't changed at all.
Of course, I've had
this face since I was 19.
Your sense of humor
hasn't changed either.
Dr. Han Jung-won
came by, didn't she?
I know you refused because
of me, but her sister...
I no longer want to
get involved with you.
I know you still resent me.
I struggled too, so many
lives were lost back then.
But I didn't want to accept
that Joseph was involved.
The Joseph
we knew no longer exists.
Only Lucifer, who killed
our angelic children
and nuns, remains.
The demon you raised.
I prayed with regrets and tears.
The will of God...
Those children
are all dead,
is that the will of God?
Even if you can't forgive me,
can't you help her?
Eun-seo!
(Park, Kidnapped by
Mysterious Group, Found Dead)
I came to thank you.
If it wasn't for you,
I might not have said
good bye to my son.
If only we acted sooner...
No, thanks to you,
we recovered his body,
and comforted his soul,
I'm just so thankful.
(Archbishop)
(The Domestic Activities
of Unknown Cult)
(Lucifer - Joseph)
(Catholic)
Let's not look at it.
Holy crap, Sharon!
7 years ago,
the boss saved
our lives from the demons.
Spare us!
He saved us from Lucifer,
along with Sister Catalina.
If it wasn't for him,
we'd already be dead.
What do we have to be afraid of?
Let's help that doctor.
I really want to help her too.
Observation day 34.
The cause of her symptoms
may have stemmed
from the panic
disorder five years ago,
after our mother's passing,
and the stress of moving
along with the stress
of practicing all day
for her audition by herself.
Eun-seo, med time.
Eun-seo...
Eun-seo?
Don't talk to me!
I've got a good
feeling about this.
Wish me luck.
Parcel delivery!
I'll leave it here!
Eun-seo?
Eun-seo!
Blair! All lights on!
Eun-seo?
- Eun-seo?
Where are you?
- Where are you?
Eun-seo?
Eun-seo!
- Eun-seo!
This is the police,
what is your emergency?
I...
I'm sorry.
Eun-seo, what are you doing there?
Eun-seo?
Are you okay? Eun-seo...
Eun-seo...
Eun-seo!
Eun-seo! Are you okay?
Crimes committed by
a mysterious group are increasing.
Over 30 police officers have died
in the line of duty,
and countless
civilians have either died
or have gone missing.
Kim!
Yes, boss!
Show me the footage.
I want to go home, let me go home!
I want to go home!
You idiot!
Fire will rain down from heaven,
and demons from hell
will drag people
into pits of fire...
Jung-won...
Despite all the treatments,
her deviant behavior must be
attributed to
my shortcomings...
Take a look at this.
I found another video,
there's a bigger problem.
Thank you so much.
As the landlord,
it's the least we can do.
We aren't jerk landlords!
We moved all our big furniture
into the shed out back.
It's really dusty,
and there's still so much stuff...
All done?
Yes, smart home monitoring system
and CCTV are fully operational.
Look at that.
What's happening to her
must be connected to Lucifer.
(Lucifer: A fallen
angel who rules Hell)
Joseph...
Bow grew up in the
orphanage with Joseph,
a boy 3 years younger than him.
Sister Angela raised them both
like her own children.
They were both
among the chosen few.
Bow had the physicality
and strength like a rock,
while Joseph had the ability
to draw demons out of people.
Other kids were scared of
Joseph and shunned him,
but Bow always protected him,
and they grew as
close as brothers.
Joseph chose
the path of priesthood,
while Bow used his
fists to earn money
in the underground world,
and always looked after
the orphanage and Joseph.
Bow would visit
the orphanage every Christmas...
No!
But 15 years ago, Joseph
summoned the devil,
and massacred the orphans
and Sister Angela
before disappearing.
Bow miraculously survived
but consumed by the guilt
for failing to save
his loved ones,
he began hunting down
Joseph and slaying demons.
Help me...
Joseph absorbed
the vitality of others,
to increase the evil
power inside him.
Foolishly, I didn't
want to believe
he was capable of such evil.
That's why I could not
disclose this to the Order.
During that time, he disappeared,
and Bow found out later,
and it's very likely he
rejected you because of me.
Hello?
This is Holy Night's Kang Bow.
Could we meet for a bit?
(Catholic Seoul Hospital
Neuropsychiatry Center)
The exorcism will be
performed by Sharon.
And Kim will assist
you by your side.
I didn't get to tell you earlier,
but in cases like this,
demons and their worshippers
could appear near Eun-seo,
so I need to keep them at bay.
She has a special
ability to sense evil.
She knows how to fight
them better than anyone.
Turn your eyes white, you know,
to show her we're legit.
I can't do that now.
Right...
It's a dangerous ritual,
you and Eun-seo could be at risk.
We're always risking our lives.
Are you still willing to do it?
Yes, if it means saving my sister.
Our lives are on the line too...
- Anyway, Kim.
- Yes?
Get the briefing ready.
What's certain is, a demon
has settled in her body.
Why did this happen to her?
Have any strangers
ever enter your home?
No, it's a remote house,
we don't have any guests.
It seems these people
summoned a demon through her.
We don't know who these people are
until we figure out their symbol.
They're always around us
posing as good neighbors.
We call them 'worshippers'.
They worship the devil,
obedient to demons,
cause harm to
people and spread evil.
These worshippers
are trained like soldiers
and harm people.
So-called 'Demons' are bishops
that control various regions,
and they're closer to
evil deities than humans.
They follow
the archbishop's orders
to select the sacrifice
and lead all rituals.
But why go after Eun-seo?
For thousands of years,
they've used pure and
vulnerable souls like Eun-seo
as a medium to summon
demons and reshape the world.
Anyone can be a target.
We'll have to meet her.
Eun-seo, are you awake?
Can you hear me?
Yes...
I came to help you,
could we chat for a bit?
Yes...
Aside from me, is there
anyone else talking to you?
Yes...
Who is that?
I don't know...
I can't tell you.
Could I talk to that person?
You can't.
Why not?
I'm scared...
If he responds to me,
he will leave your body.
Don't you want him to leave?
I'm... so scared...
I'll begin.
Who are you?
Answer me, who are you?
Answer me!
Do not hide behind the child,
and answer me,
who are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
I haven't done anything wrong.
Vile demon.
Reveal your name
and return to hell.
Vile demon.
Reveal your name
and return to hell.
Eun-seo...
No, doctor!
Vile demon!
Reveal your name
and return to hell!
Vile demon!
Reveal your name
and return to hell!
Reveal your name and return...
Where is she right now?
It's near the entrance.
What do we do?
She's trying to get out!
Get off me!
Get going!
Doctor!
Eun-seo!
Wait!
Jung-won!
No!
Eun-seo!
It's too dangerous!
I'll come to you,
stay right there!
Sis, I'm scared...
Eun-seo!
- Jung-won!
- Doctor!
Jung-won, are you okay?
Sir, are you hurt at all?
The demon is so deeply entrenched,
I can't tell what it is.
We must end it
where it all started.
Staying at the hospital
will put her and
other patients at risk.
Yes, let's do that.
We have to move, there's no time.
Eun-seo...
Hang in there a little longer.
Dammit!
I just can't tell where
they'll come from.
It's no use.
Eun-seo...
Mister...
Save me...
I'll save you no matter what.
There are 6 stages of exorcism.
The goal of each stage
is to make
the demon reveal its name,
and expelling it
from Eun-seo's body.
Please follow
my orders at every stage.
Once we start the exorcism,
it must not be stopped.
If it stops,
her life and ours may
be in grave danger.
(Presence)
The first stage is 'Presence'.
We force the demon
to reveal itself.
Sis, I'm scared...
Please send them all away...
I'm so scared...
Eun-seo, it's okay.
Doctor, don't answer the demon.
Kim, everything ready?
Yes.
Jung-won.
Jung-won?
I mean, I'm not a demon.
Yes?
Turn on the machine.
Okay.
Her vitals are
within normal range.
Let's begin.
You must answer all my questions.
Or you will feel intense pain.
(Jugwi: A bamboo
that wards off evil)
Do not touch me, no!
(and malevolent energies)
Tell me your name!
Tell me!
What happened?
We're entering 'Deception' stage.
(Deception)
The evil will try to deceive us.
Jung-won...
I'm so scared...
Could you untie me?
(Dongkyung: A small mirror imbued)
(with the shaman's soul)
(Taeju: An act to
convey the words)
(of the guardian spirit)
You want to know my name?
Should I tell you?
The demon isn't pretending.
Before existence,
I was the first being.
I am both one and infinite.
I am eternity and finality.
I am within you,
I am not within you.
The interior lights
are being shut off.
Something's odd.
I'll look into it,
stay on guard.
Okay.
There you were.
Dammit...
I exist everywhere, and nowhere.
You vile demon.
Reveal your name at once,
and expel from the girl.
You're too chicken
to come in here.
Come in, do it.
Petty priests like you
can never defeat us.
The demon within,
release her at once!
Expel yourself!
The demon within,
release her at once!
Expel yourself!
Hey, it's me.
Boss, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine now.
Boss, I told you once before,
always watch out for
the powder they throw at you.
It could paralyze you,
and you could even die from it.
All right, get on with it.
Okay.
Now it's the third stage,
'Break Point'.
You should use this moment
to get some rest.
(Break Point)
Jung-won?
Are you okay?
I command you
in the name of our
almighty creators,
return to the netherworld!
Return at once!
Jung-won, wake up!
Doctor, it's okay,
everything's fine.
The demon entered
your body momentarily.
They sometimes
target a family member
during the exorcism.
There's something
else in the house.
- Bud.
- Yes?
Don't read that.
Okay.
What does it mean?
I'm not sure.
It's an ancient
language called 'Igbo'.
This is why all these
unexpected events
kept happening.
There is a curse
on the entire house.
What do we do then?
We have to remove
all of these symbols.
Did something happen to me?
It felt like something
left my body.
Eun-seo, are you okay?
Feeling better?
Wait.
Jung-won...
Could you untie me?
Eun-seo, is that you?
Do you recognize me?
Hold on.
This idiot will die
one way or another.
Remember?
You let all those
poor children die.
'Voice' stage has begun.
(Voice)
Mister, save me...
Help me, Mr. Bow!
Joseph killed them?
No, you killed them.
They all died because
you couldn't stop him.
Let's go visit him together.
Then you can achieve eternal life.
If not, you'll end up
killing this child too.
Just like you
killed Sister Angela,
your mother figure.
Kill! Kill! Kill!
- Kill!
- Boss!
- Boss, boss, no!
- Kill!
Sharon!
Boss, I'm okay.
Do not fall prey to its delusion.
(Shindo: Daggers
imbued with a divine spirit)
Why are you siding with humans?
Your power did not come from him,
but from my brother!
If my power came
from your brother,
it proves he couldn't defeat me.
Do you think you can handle
that much power?
Here you go.
What's this?
A lid.
Why did you bring a lid?
You said to bring
something to cover.
I meant a coat to cover
her body, you moron.
Why do you waste your life
on these pathetic beings?
You know it eats away your body,
as you use your power.
You've felt it,
is it worth saving these humans,
who are wicked and greedy?
Be with us, sister.
Be with us.
I am not your sister.
Get out of my head!
Reveal your name!
I'll make this pain go away!
Tell me your name, now!
Tell me your name!
Tell me!
What's your name!
Jung-won, please...
Save me...
Stop it! Please!
- Jung-won!
- You can't!
It's not over yet!
The boundary...
Wait.
Step back.
She is mine now.
We're now in 'Clash' stage.
We need to find her quickly.
(Clash)
Sharon...
With your power,
we can rule the world.
Be with us, sister.
Be with us.
Boss, we're locked in!
Move out of the way.
I'm doing a lot of
home degrading today.
Wait, boss!
What is it?
It's an automatic door.
Dammit...
Jung-won...
Eun-seo, are you in there?
- Jung-won!
- Eun-seo!
Hey, hey!
- Are you okay?
- You good?
I'm fine, doctor...
Is there a room
we don't know about?
We moved all our big furniture
into the shed out back.
Shed...
Over there!
What's that?
The demon is taking
more control over her.
Eun-seo...
Doctor, no! No!
So, this is where you hang out.
Wounded soul,
why do you use the power
devil has given you on humans?
Are you Korean?
If you interfere with us,
only death awaits you.
Go, kill Sharon.
Die, die, feel the terror.
Bow! Die!
Die!
Sharon!
Boss...
Blood, you're bleeding!
What do we do, boss?
I am your Omega.
You are my Alpha.
I am the new path.
With my kingdom
created with blood of children,
I will rule you all.
Now I get it.
I know who you are.
We're in the final stage,
'Expulsion'.
After this stage,
we can save Eun-seo.
A foul deity of death
that takes child sacrifices.
Moloch!
Your time is up.
Return to where you came from!
I expel you, Moloch!
Return to hell at once!
Return to hell, Moloch!
Return to where you came from!
I expel you, Moloch!
Return to hell at once!
Return to hell, Moloch!
I expel you, Moloch!
Return to where you came from!
Return to hell!
At once, Moloch!
I expel you!
- Eun-seo!
- Not yet!
The demon is being expelled.
Defeated by petty exorcists!
I will one day shred you all!
And I am taking
this idiot to hell.
She's mine.
Eun-seo!
Sharon!
Eun-seo! No! No!
No!
Sharon!
I am the Grim Reaper!
Leave the child alone,
Valac's incarnation
is ordering you!
Return to hell!
Your time is almost up!
If you want to live,
accept the power of hell!
Return to hell, Moloch!
Eun-seo...
Eun-seo?
Can you hear me?
Jung-won...
I'm so sorry...
(Don Lee)
(Seohyun David Lee)
(Gyeong Su Jin Jung Zi So)
(Grand Opening of
Angela Orphanage)
I'm taking the photo, look here!
Everyone, smile!
One, two, three!
That's enough, kids.
Bow, please come by
when you get a chance.
- Let's move.
- Okay.
Yes, sir.