I'm not angry.
I'm not asking for
special treatment,
- I'm just...
- Begging.
You said I was one
of your best guys.
Was.
Look, if you can't hire me back,
just ask them to take
me off the blacklist.
You say that again
and I'll kick you and
your kid out on your ass.
Bringing her here to guilt me.
Look, I need to work.
- She's had a fever for the last week.
- No, no, no.
That ain't on me.
I'm not the jerk that spoke to a
union rep about radiation exposure.
One time.
You got your daughter.
Your nuts didn't fry.
Take the win.
Bye-bye.
A sick kid in my office.
You know, I didn't bring
her here to guilt you.
I brought her to stop myself from
bouncing your face off this desk.
And this is you... not angry?
Next!
Hey, you! Tough guy!
Are you man enough to risk it all?
Today is your last chance of the
year to be on The Running Man!
If you can duck the
boys in black, the public,
and McCone's
Hunters for thirty days,
you'll run away with
a billion new dollars.
Go on.
I'll give you a head start.
Catch me if you can, motherfuckers.
Whoo! Come on!
We've got the cash
if you've got the balls.
Don't miss the final
run of the season.
- The Running Man.
- Don't worry.
- Tomorrow, eight o'clock.
- Daddy's not that crazy.
It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Welcome back to Speed the Wheel
where a big-boned badass
bets bravely to bag big bucks.
Am I right, Bud?
Yeah.
And away "wheel" go!
I know, I know. Mommy's
coming right back.
Mommy's coming.
Bud, for 100 new dollars
the capital of France...
is A, Marseilles,
B, Lyon, or C, Paris?
C.
Paris. C.
Correct!
Paris for a hundred new.
Cynthia, drop a hundo in the Hammy!
Feed me!
Oh! Look at the fuzzy hamster!
Mm...
Do you see the fuzzy hamster?
- Bud, next question...
- I know, it's scary.
For one thousand new dollars.
How many lavatories does a Net-Air
Flying-V luxury jetliner have?
Is it A, four, B, five, or C, six?
- Oh. Tough one.
- What?
I'd say B, Bud.
Is it A?
It's... C, six.
Six toilets.
The rich are even more full
of shit than Daddy thought.
It's time to speed the wheel!
Oh, God.
Bud, in my hand is the question...
that could change...
your life.
- Who invented the pepperoni?
- Oh, no...
- Oh, no.
- Whoa...
Bud, we hardly knew you.
- I'm here. I'm home.
- Oh, okay.
- Mommy's here.
- Here she is.
- How's she doing?
- Mommy.
- Hey, babe.
- How's she feeling?
- She's really burning up.
- Hey. Come on.
- Mommy.
- Oh...
- Thank God you're here.
- Can I feel?
- I think she's hurting bad.
- That's not good.
Two drops.
All right.
- Wait, what is this?
- Look, I know.
Molie said he would have real
pharms. Damn it, real flu meds.
Yeah, well, your little black-market
buddy has all the stuff to kill people
but is sold out of the
things to save them.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- This stuff doesn't make her better, babe.
- But it makes her feel better.
Look, I just pulled another
double at that hellhole club.
And if it wasn't dead in the
morning, I'd still be there.
So that's what we can afford today.
I talked to him.
- You did? Who watched Cathy?
- I took her with me.
I figured, you
know... guilt-trip him.
No, you took her so you
wouldn't beat the crap out of him.
Smart.
I left my pride at the
door, I was respectful.
Maybe got a little
heated at the end, but...
by then it was game over.
They don't want us to win.
I'm sorry. I...
- I tried.
- Hey.
You're just being punished
for being a good man.
You were just standing
up for your guys.
It just didn't seem
right, you know?
I got to be a dad and they didn't.
Ben, none of this is your fault.
- Doesn't change our situation.
- No.
But we're in this together, right?
Right.
We'll think of something.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
It's okay.
Wait. Where's her sock?
Oh, Ben, those
take forever to make.
No, no, it was on when we got home.
- Hold on, it's here.
- Those are her comfies, babe.
Shit!
Where did you kick that off?
Don't worry. Daddo's gonna find it.
Get it together, girl.
Honey.
- Are you going back to the Libertine?
- I don't want to.
I thought you said that place
was dead in the morning.
It is, except for the most
desperate, wasted losers.
My friend told me how to
get tips out of these guys.
- The other waitresses do it all the time.
- No.
Look, if these jerks can
splash 50 ND per bottle,
they can accidentally
save a kid's life.
- Babe, I can't let you do that.
- Ben, she is burning up.
My friend makes
twenty new every shift,
usually from just one customer.
Hey, now you know
I'd never do that.
My friend doesn't even
let them grab her ass.
She just charms them into tipping
for something that's not on sale.
And right now it's prime
time for that kind of play.
If the wrong exec
thinks you ripped him off
you could end up in the dump
like that girl across the street.
I'm sorry. These men are savages.
If we don't get real pharms
from a real doc, she won't survive
- another night!
- Hey, you, tough guy!
- We don't have a choice!
- Are you man enough...
to risk it all? Today
is your last chance...
- Yeah, we do.
- To be on The Running Man.
Where are you going?
To get money.
Enough for her to see a
real doc before bedtime.
You'll run away with a billion...
You lecture me
about taking chances?
People on that show
never come back.
I'm not trying out for
The Running Man.
There's a ton of other shows. Look.
The lowest amount someone
won today, 75 new dollars.
I get on one of those,
we get the meds.
Oh, no, people on these games
get hurt, too. Like, really bad.
It's kids' stuff next to
the kind of jobs I work.
Hey. Look.
Promise me you
won't go on that show.
I promise... I'll get
you out of here.
Ben.
We need you.
Watch yourself.
No, I need both of those!
No deal!
♪ I know how it feels To
expect to get a fair shake ♪
♪ But they won't let you forget
That you're the underdog ♪
♪ And you've got to
be twice as good ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Even if you're never right ♪
♪ They get uptight
When you're too bright ♪
We see you. We hear you.
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I know how it feels ♪
We have eyes everywhere.
♪ You get up and
get a raw deal, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Say, I'm the underdog ♪
No gatherings. No protests.
No exceptions.
Harboring fugitives is
punishable by death.
Scanning.
State your business.
Network Building. Tryouts.
Proceed to your destination.
Loitering will be prosecuted.
♪ I know how it feels
to get demoted ♪
♪ When it comes time,
you got promoted ♪
♪ But you might be
Movin' up too fast, yeah ♪
Keeping our streets clean.
♪ If you ever love somebody ♪
♪ Of a different set ♪
♪ I bet the set
didn't let you forget ♪
♪ That it just don't go like that ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I know how it feels
for people to stop ♪
♪ Turn around and stare ♪
♪ Signify a little
bit and low rate ♪
♪ Low rate me, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, I don't mind ♪
♪ I'm the underdog ♪
♪ No, I can handle it ♪
Welcome to the Network Building,
home to the greatest
television station.
The only television station.
Eyes forward! Mouth closed!
Do not sit down! Do not lay down!
Eyes forward!
Mouth closed!
Do not sit down! Do not lay down!
Eyes forward!
Mouth closed!
Do not sit down! Do not lay down!
Eyes forward! Mouth closed!
Oh, shit.
I can still try out.
- Hey. This guy's in trouble!
- Get up and get back in line!
- This guy needs help!
- No helping! Step back!
Get him a fucking
doctor and I will!
I said step back now!
Keep moving,
people. Nothing to see!
Back of the line, welf!
Eyes forward! Mouth closed!
Do not sit down! Do not lay down!
Next.
Tap each page to confirm
the information's correct.
What's the triangle mean?
I'll read it to
you, it'll be faster.
Ben Richards, 35, married.
Employment history: Hired by
Sea-Gen, fired for insubordination.
Why is there a red
triangle on my file?
Hired by Net-Utility, fired for...
Hey, man, I asked you a question.
Insubordination.
Hired by Defense-Net,
birth of daughter.
Fired for
insubordination. Poor kid.
You mention my daughter again,
they don't make glass thick enough
to stop me from choking you out.
Elevator six. Send him up.
Elevator six.
Next.
Proceed directly to
your designated elevator.
Please stay in your allotted zones.
Hey.
Co-Op 27, right?
Yeah.
Twenty-nine, neighbor. Laughlin.
Ben.
All right, Ben.
Elevator six.
Ooh. This is us. Come on.
Catch me if you can,
motherfuckers. Whoo! Come on!
We've got the cash
if you've got the balls!
I... don't.
Right. Yeah.
I'm Tim.
Tim. Jansky.
Jansky's my last name
and Tim is short for Timothy.
Got it.
Should we all go around and
say our names and a fun fact?
We can do it later.
Ha, twinning. Let's go!
Come on!
Assessment this way.
♪ Gonna stamp out your fire
He can change your desire ♪
♪ Don't you know that he can
Make you forget you're a man ♪
♪ Gonna stamp out your fire
He can change your desire ♪
♪ Don't you know that he can
Make you forget you're a man ♪
♪ You're a man ♪
I got you!
I got you.
This is a rest period.
Assessment resumes in 60 seconds.
Thanks.
You didn't have to
do that back there.
No problem.
Wrong!
No helping, welf!
Obedience.
Never.
- Heroism.
- Useless.
Technology.
Abuse.
- Freedom.
- Nope.
- Authority.
- Burn.
- Anarchy.
- When?
- Justice.
- Hilarious.
Family.
Everything.
Next image, what do you see?
Cutest puppy ever.
What about this one?
Aw. It's my favorite
flower giving me a hug.
Final image. Tell me about it.
Infinite bunnies getting
sucked into a knife tornado
spraying blood all over the galaxy.
Um, Mr. Richards,
you are quantifiably the angriest
man to ever audition for our shows.
Well, that really pisses me off.
Proceed directly to
your next destination.
Final assessment.
Ooh...
Our jumpsuits are in here.
Wow.
You are required to change
into your assigned jumpsuit.
- You're on Bug Out.
- Spank Bank, nice.
You must wear your
designated jumpsuit to proceed.
Yo, you got a target on your back.
Yo, Richards!
I knew it would be us, man.
I knew it would be us.
Come on. Shit happens, right?
Jansky. Richards. Laughlin.
Ooh. That's us.
They say you run to
add life to your days.
Not days to your life.
I'd say both are
pretty fucking true.
Don't miss the final
run of the season.
I always thought
this was fake, but...
Hey, runners...
- I don't know.
- You can't outrun fate.
- It's feeling pretty real now.
- And you cannot hide...
- Right, guys?
- From destiny.
Feeling realiosa.
Viewer discretion advised.
And it's feeling realer
every second, y'all.
Later.
Miss Laughlin.
Hey, uh, you're the man, Richards.
I never would've
made it without you.
You like spaghetti?
I stole a little something for you.
So far, so good.
Don't worry, we'll keep
it down... neighbor.
Oh, we're going down...
Mr. Richards?
Vita non est periculum.
It is not death that
man should fear,
but never beginning to live.
Dan Killian.
Go ahead. Relax. Sit.
You know, critics
say The Running Man
represents a return to the
barbarism of the Roman Colosseum.
I disagree.
I'm not doing The Running Man.
I'm aware of your family crisis.
And I think the contents
of this envelope will help.
If we come to an
agreement, it's yours to keep.
Call it a signing bonus.
I'll do any other show.
The most anyone's ever won
on another show is 1, 000 ND.
And I know it sounds
like a tremendous sum,
but it's not enough to get your
family out of Slumside for good.
Whereas on The Running Man,
merely surviving a single week
would put the Richards in the
top one percent of global wealth.
See for yourself. Page 66.
I'm not trying to
get myself killed.
Mr. Richards, I'll
be honest with you.
I've said this to every contestant,
but this is the first
time I've really meant it.
You have what it
takes to win this game.
Our viewers have a burning desire
to see a Runner go the distance.
We've had men come close.
Twenty-nine days in season one.
But it's gonna take somebody
special to go the full thirty.
You tested off the charts,
so I looked through
your employment history
and had my assistant
shoot me your highlights.
Now, this is the most thrilling ten
seconds of video I've seen all year.
They fired me for
destroying the harness.
But you bounced back. Hired by
Defense-Net. The best wages Downtown.
The best dog shit's still dog shit.
Then why beg to be rehired?
Let's be honest.
You stuck your neck out one
too many times for your coworkers
and got your head chopped off.
Pretty gutsy, considering half the
country thinks unions should be illegal.
Well, I come from the other half.
So they can kiss my ass twice.
Right there is why
you can win this game.
You're a fighter, Richards.
The Network blacklisted you
from all the corps they own
except for this one.
You've risked your life for other
men and their families long enough.
Now do it for you and yours.
Put your boots on.
Make them pay, in cash.
Sign the agreement and
change your family's life forever.
What father wouldn't want that?
And your thumbprint.
Just press the box.
Welcome to The Running Man.
This is exciting.
Ah, there you are.
This is the fun bit.
I'm married.
I assumed you two had an
understanding, based on her line of work.
She's a waitress at a club.
I've hit a nerve. My apologies.
To mutually profitable
collaboration.
I'm Agent Dugg, your
Family Alliance liaison.
Family Alliance is the Network's
premium private security service.
It's included in your contract.
No point winning all that jack just
to get your people robbed and killed.
We'll relocate the fam.
Put them under an assumed name.
That's the one thing you
won't have to worry about.
You have one call... to the wife.
Let her know we'll be
there in the morning.
Wait, no, I need to
bring her this tonight.
I promise, I will be back
before the show starts.
No one comes back.
I got to lock you in a
really nice apartment.
Come on, man. I have a sick kid.
I'll deliver it now and
bring back a receipt.
Can you give her this, too?
Hey.
You okay?
Where are you?
I'm at the Network
Building. I'm fine.
Look, a man named Dugg, he's
gonna bring you 500 new in cash.
Take her to Uptown
Mercy. All right?
It's 24/7. Get her a real
doc, whatever she needs.
Ben?
What did you do?
I'm on The Running Man.
Listen to me.
I promise, I'll be back.
Um...
I got to go get her ready.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Bye, Ben.
We good?
♪ Americanos, Ah-Americanos ♪
♪ Americanos, blue
jeans and chinos ♪
Are those my Jilly Hoobahs?
I don't know. Are they?
I told you never, ever
wear my shoes. Ever!
Your feet smell like dead
mice! Now I have to burn them.
- You're an insane person.
- What is going on here?
Mom, she stole my shoes.
Because Elizabeth put
them in my shoe cubby.
Take off my fricking shoes.
- Are you serious?
- Take off my shoes.
Hello, America. You
know me. I'm Bobby T.
And if you want to
murder your thirst,
reach for an ice-cold Liquid Death.
The official beverage
of The Running Man.
The starting gun
fires tonight at 8:00.
Showtime.
Let's roll.
Wrist.
Here's your Running Band.
You're gonna use it for
timers, reminders, and rewards.
Good luck down there.
Are you ready to see
some Runners cry?
And are you ready
to see some Runners die?
Ah.
- You look great.
He looks great. One
minute warning! Last looks!
One minute. Come on.
Watch your backs, people!
Stand clear!
You got one job out there.
Say what's on your mind.
You're feeling angry,
violent, aggrieved.
Don't think before you
speak. That's for pussies.
Go off, curse, shake
your dick at the crowd.
It's all good Free-Vee.
Bobby T!
Daniel, you son of a bitch.
How many times I got to tell you, do
not put bluefin in my amuse-bouche?
When I pull a "mercury
poisoning" on a show night,
your bouche will
not be amused, Dan.
- Oh. Is this the one?
- Mm-hmm.
- Is this our star?
- Yep.
Oh...
I know it's weird to
see me in real life.
But you get used to it.
I'm flesh and blood
just like you are.
My robot puts my pants
on one leg at a time.
Classic Bobby.
Do not shake your dick at
the crowd. That's a bad note.
He looks great.
Twenty seconds, people!
See you out there.
Are we ready for Bobby T?
This is the kind of energy I
want all night long, everybody!
There it is!
The new Colosseum.
Bobby T! Bobby T!
Cue the intro. Five, four, three...
America,
the greatest country
in the fucking universe.
We work hard. And after
a long day of busting ass
we get to kick back and feel good.
But some don't want
to work for that privilege.
Thieves. Fraudsters. Freeloaders.
And why should they when
they can take it from you?
Welcome to the game where
we give three of these tough guys
all the freedom they want.
Biodata erased.
No scanners, no trackers.
For 30 days, all
that stands between
these men and millions is you.
Record. Report. Reward.
With over 10 million
new dollars in prizes won,
the best audience
in the world remains
undefeated!
It's The Running Man!
And now...
Yeah! Bobby!
Your tail, tenacious, trustworthy
trailblazer of the truth,
Bobby T!
- Bobby T! Bobby T!
- Let's go!
Your fury at the injustice of
the world has stopped you
from reaching your
full potential, but now?
That anger is your
superpower. Embrace it!
Our first Runner hails from
right here in Co-Op City.
Ben Richards.
A healthy 35-year-old man who
thinks he's too good to work for a living.
- Get him outta here!
- Fuck you, Ben!
Mr. Richards's last job was a
full-time position at Defense-Net
until he spilled military secrets
to a commie union he's not even in!
That's bullshit! That's bullshit!
Come on, that's
showbiz, kid. Chill out.
That's right!
He bit the hand that feeds him
because that's what dogs do.
Remember that face.
You win 3,000 new dollars...
for a verified report
and 10,000 if it leads to a kill.
We doubled the prizes for
the last run of the season.
'Cause when the stakes go up...
The shit goes down!
And the stakes be high!
Because the thousands he
wins goes to his wife, Sheila...
a night witch who only takes
the biggest tips at the Libertine.
It's fake!
- That's a lie, you sack of shit!
- If you comprendo my innuendo.
I'll fucking kill you.
Abandoned by Richards,
it's up to her now
to raise the tragic
kin of their sin.
But what's that?
I think it's time for...
Famous last words!
- Well, Mr. Richards.
- Go on, Richards!
Come on, can we hear it?
Do you have any famous last words?
Yeah.
Fuck you, Dan!
How long do you think you'll last?
Long enough to burn this
building down and everyone in it!
How small does your dick
have to be to sit out there?
Fuck you!
Holy shit! Save it for the run!
Oh, shit!
Our next contestant...
My eye for talent
remains unrivaled.
You, Mr. Richards, are
what they used to refer to
as a game changer.
Now listen. I shouldn't say this,
but when the run begins,
lay low with your own
kind. You'll last longer.
And also, in case you
missed it in your contract,
every Goon you kill
wins you a 10K bonus.
And it's a hundo per Hunter.
I don't know how yet,
but I am gonna fuck you up someday.
That's the spirit.
The Rules of the Run!
Rule one:
Running Money.
Runners get a 1,000
new dollar advance
and a 12-hour running start.
The Hunters don't hunt until
the Record and Report App
goes live tomorrow morning!
Rule two:
The Running Cam.
You must tape ten minutes
of on-cam-ham per day.
These envelopes cannot be tracked.
Drop them in a Network Drone
Xpress mailbox before midnight
- or you'll be disqualified...
- Thank you.
From further winnings,
but still hunted for 30 days.
Don't die for free.
Get your tapes in!
Rule three:
Run Far, Get Rich.
Make it to midnight tomorrow
and win 5,000 new dollars.
Awards increase by
a thousand per day
and double at the end of each week.
The grand prize for
surviving day 30 is now
a billion new dollars!
But, before they can win that,
who do they have to get past?
The Hunters!
Ladies and gentlemen,
meet... the Hunters!
Five men who fight
for real freedom.
Deep undercover where
you least expect them.
In fact, they may be
amongst you right now!
And their leader,
the ghost haunting
every Runner's dreams,
Chief McCone!
Search and destroy, gentlemen.
Look at them go!
Take a last look at these thugs.
Observe the typical disguises
their kind use to escape justice.
In mere moments,
they will walk among you
free to do whatever they want
until we stop them... together!
Let them run! Let them run!
Suck it!
On your marks!
Get set!
Run!
13th and Obama.
Whoa! Hey, Running Man!
What?
I-I was watching you
on... on the Free-Vee!
13th and Obama.
Okay.
♪ Keep on running ♪
Yeah.
♪ Keep on hiding ♪
♪ One fine day, I got... ♪
What's up, man? Hey.
- Take a pic with me.
- It's okay.
What do you mean, "No, it's okay"?
You got to be nice, man, so
people don't report you. Okay?
'Cause people will do that. Not
me, though, man. I'm a nice guy.
No, you know what, you're right.
We should pull over, pick
up one of these hookers.
She can take the pic, huh?
Yeah! Sickest idea ever, man!
Yeah!
I like the way you think, man.
Hey! Where you going, man?
Yeah, you'd better run!
I hope they burn your ass!
You're dead meat, pal!
You're dead!
Yo, Molie, let me in!
Hello?
Molie?
- Yo, Molie.
- What?
You didn't see me on the hatch?
I saw you two blocks away on
the infrared. What do you want?
Look, I need...
two I.D. cards and a gun.
Forget it. I don't do guns.
Go see Mickey on Third.
What in the hell is
your problem, man?
The Running Man?
What are you thinking?
I had you pegged for smart.
Look, I didn't have a
choice. Cathy was sick.
Do you know how much danger
you put me in, coming here?
If you want to kill yourself, fine.
But leave me out of it, okay?
You got it?
Goddamn it, Ben.
I.D.s are a hundred.
It's 30 each for costumes
and accessories.
I got a priest, I've
got a combat veteran,
I've got an exec.
And the rush order makes
it two hundred new all in.
Okay.
Go hide out in Survival.
It's aisle five.
- I'm gonna lock the incinerator.
- Oh, I already did.
You don't mind if I check, do you?
Hey, where you going?
All right, you heroes,
come and get it!
Listen to him! If he
lets go, we're all dead.
You sell a lot of these?
I can't keep them in stock.
Those TVs don't watch you back.
Come on.
Is this gonna work?
Absolutely.
Stand over here.
Okay, you ready?
One, two, three.
All right.
Let's test out those contacts.
Okay.
Can you read
anything on that shelf?
All right.
"BFE-20."
Holy shit! How do
you have Black Irish?
That's not for sale.
Yeah, like I'd put
that shit in my pocket.
Only took a couple grams to blow
up fatbergs in the sewers Uptown.
BFE. Big Fucking Explosion.
So what's your plan?
I don't know.
Lay low with my own kind?
Your own kind will sell
you out in a heartbeat.
I'd find the busiest place you can
and disappear in the
crowd. That's my advice.
Well...
you can leave the
same way you came.
Molie...
I had to do it.
No, you didn't.
I was gonna bring you on here...
sort of as a partner.
I should've told Sheila yesterday,
but I wanted to tell you myself.
Hey, too late for that now.
Well...
Godspeed.
See you on the big screen.
New York City, one way.
I.D. and cash in
the tray, please, sir.
Safe travels, Mr. Springer.
Thank you.
Mister.
Hey, mister.
Your face.
Forget you ever saw it!
You say anything, I will kill you so
fast your mom won't even wake up.
But your mustache.
Oh, shit.
So sorry about that.
Want my snack pack?
Now arriving at New
York Penn Station.
This is the final
stop for this train.
Welcome to the Brant
Hotel, Mr. Springer.
Hmm. You shaved your mustache.
It fell off on the train.
I hate when that happens.
Everything okay, Mr. Springer?
Yeah, yeah. Just, uh...
have a good night. Day.
You know what, have both.
Rules say I have to be on
camera ten minutes a day.
They didn't say which part, so...
I guess you can watch
my ass take a nap.
And he said to Him,
"All these things I
will give to Thee...
if You fall down and worship me..."
Thank you.
That thou shall worship thine Lord,
thine God, and only
Him shall you serve.
♪ Americanos, Americanos ♪
Previously on The Americanos...
- I love you.
Don't worry about it.
I just hate that...
You should have thought about
that before you spread your legs.
Mom!
One down. Twenty-nine to go.
Gah!
Fuck off!
John Springer!
Green light.
Live update! Let's go!
Our Hunters are hard at work
near a Co-Op City Netmart
where Mr. Jansky is flirting with
the clerk that just reported him.
Let's find out if he's
also flirting with death.
Do you watch The Running Man?
Uh... I guess.
I heard there's this guy on
there who kinda looks like me
and he's really hot or
something, I don't... I don't know.
- I don't know.
- I'm gonna come back
in a little bit and I'm gonna
try to ask you out again.
- Jesus, Tim.
- Yeah?
And that's Jansky!
Stepping out with
his breakfast burrito.
Green light on Jansky.
Will it be his final meal?
Come on.
The fuse has been lit.
It's just a matter of time.
Get out of there, buddy.
Better eat up, Tim.
Enjoy those last bites
before it's last rites.
Move, move. You're walking.
It's the fucking Running Man.
- Here we go.
- Oh, man.
Bang!
God!
And Jansky crosses the finish line.
That's one down and two to go!
Watch tonight at 8:00
to see if Jenni Laughlin...
and Ben Richards
are still on the run.
How long do they have
left? Tune in and find out.
Hi. I'd like to extend
my stay for three days.
I'd be happy to arrange
that for you, Mr. Springer.
In the same room if possible.
- Of course. Let me see what I can do.
- Thank you.
You're in luck.
Look like I can keep you in
the same room, Mr. Springer.
Great.
Can I get you a car this morning?
Uh...
You know what? I think I'll walk.
Attention, passengers,
this is our final stop, Boston.
Please check your personal
belongings before leaving.
Thank you for
traveling with Netbus.
Hey, brother, I need
to get off the street.
Oh, yeah?
I'm looking for a place
to rack out for a month.
Mm-hmm.
Off-Net, if you know what I mean.
Oh, is that so?
I'll give you a hundo
new for your room
and another hundo for your jacket.
A deuce hundo for
this rat-ass jacket
and that rat-ass room?
Fella, you need to
get to Jamaica Plain,
- pick up your head meds.
- Come on.
Put that shit away.
What, are you
trying to get us killed?
Let me see your face.
Where'd you deploy?
Alaska. Ate shrapnel.
You ain't seen combat.
But I reckon it ain't stolen valor
if you pay me for it.
Thanks.
Hey! I'm talking to you!
I'm talking to you!
Come back here, you little shit!
You listen to me. You
stay out of my stash.
I catch you in that basement again,
I'm gonna stomp you.
And I'ma get big bro
to take care of you!
He'll kick your cow
ass over the moon!
Beat it!
Ah...
Yeah, good luck with that.
Idiot.
Floor two.
Okay, then.
Guess I gotta make
another one of these tapes.
I've always been a guy
who followed the rules.
I showed up to
work first, I left last.
Nice.
It hasn't done much
for me, obviously.
I mean, I'm on the murder show.
But what are you gonna
do? Take on the whole world?
Sweet.
So here I am, a grown-ass man
playing hide-and-seek for money.
Please don't.
Thank you.
I think I'll just lay
low, keep it cool.
Try not to burn out.
Depraved.
Demonic. Deceased.
What havoc will the
remaining Runners wreak?
Tune in and find out.
Next up, rich and bold,
it's those Americanos.
"Hey, Jim."
"How do you like this energy wine?"
"I'm a big fan. Love it."
"How about you, Bill?"
"It's pretty much my
favorite thing, Jim."
"So, guys, you mind if I ask
you a personal question?"
"Why do we all have
the same voice?"
Relax, Ben.
Mail later.
Who am I?
Good to see you, too, Frank.
I'm the dog!
The rats!
Him!
I demand an apology!
Give it a rest, Frank.
At least you got
someone to talk to.
Damn, son.
You can't hide!
You think I don't see you!
I'm gonna find you!
Key, duh.
I'm gonna burn down your house
and everyone in it!
You're a weird guy, Frank.
We interrupt The Americanos
for a live update from
The Running Man.
Running fans,
we catch up with an
undisclosed Runner
at an undisclosed location
in an undisclosed city.
The tension is so thick,
you could cut it with
McCone's knife of destiny.
The Hunters are
currently descending
on the location.
Orders have been given.
They're entering the premises now.
Chief McCone is directing them
to fan out through the building.
Get in your fucking room... now!
Rover cams have been deployed
and are waiting for the signal
that the Hunters
have found their prey.
I'm on three.
There's no way out for this Runner.
But never underestimate
a cornered rat.
Fuck!
I need to get the bag.
I'm getting word now
the Hunters believe
they've located the room
this Runner is hiding in.
The suspense is
thick, Running fans.
I saw him! I saw Ben Richards!
He's heading downstairs!
Will this Runner even
have a chance to run?
The fuse has been lit.
It's just a matter of time.
Shit.
Our Hunters
are triangulating the
Runner's exact position.
Confirming their location.
I can reveal to you now
the Runner is Ben Richards.
I knew it.
Mr. Richards talked the talk.
We're about to
find out if he can...
walk the walk.
I need a rover on three.
Chief McCone has confirmed.
The Hunters have found their man.
Things are heating up.
Things are getting warmer.
Nowhere to run, nowhere to hide.
The Runner is trapped
inside of the building.
But what's this?
McCone's given the signal.
The rover cams have
entered the building.
Any moment now.
This is why we play
the game, Running fans.
The moment of truth when these animals
find out we live in a society with rules,
a society where actions
have consequences.
And there they are, the Hunters,
posted up outside Richards's room.
We're going in.
Here we go.
Go!
Hold fire!
Why?
He's not going anywhere.
Bravo.
Hey, buddy. You're on Free-Vee.
The Hunters are racing
to intercept their prey.
Better run, Mr. Richards.
This is why we watch, Running fans.
He's on two. Go, go!
Stop filming me!
Going down.
We got him.
He's headed for the lobby.
You have reached the lobby.
Richards,
you're going down.
I got a grenade!
Back at you.
Have the boys in black
breach the basement.
Get a backup rover online.
I want an NCG tactical team
ready at the bottom of the stairs.
Go! Go!
Get two guards in
the lobby elevator.
Report to me if he
tries to climb the shaft.
All Hunters rally at staging
one and stand by for the breach.
You heard the man! Tac-One on me!
Let's go, go, go!
Bring down the auto-ram!
Stairs are clear.
- Fuck.
- Tac-One standing by.
- Ready to breach.
- Action is go.
- Auto-ram hot!
- Hit it!
No go! No go!
- Hit it again.
- Oh, shit.
He's got a gun!
Light him up!
Oh!
Reload! Reload! Reloading!
Get out of here! This
place is about to blow!
I'm still here, you shit-eaters!
Hah!
Tragedy strikes as an explosion
at the YVA in
Fenway takes the lives
of eight Network Community Guards.
Belinda Brave coming to
you live from the scene...
of a powerful blast
that shook Boston to
its core earlier tonight.
No confirmation yet on whether
Richards's body...
has been recovered.
As far as we know,
the Runner is still at large.
A thrilling live update
of The Running Man
turned deadly...
Hey, come on out.
I know you're here.
- Come here, you little rat!
- Get off me!
- You the one who reported me?
- It wasn't me!
- I ain't no rat!
- Oh, yeah?
Let me go! I'ma get big
bro to take care of you.
You think your big bro can kick my
ass after what I just went through?
He's not gonna kick your
ass, he's gonna save it!
You need help!
Suspect at large. Curfew enforced.
We've got to get off
these streets, man.
Goons and zooms
all up in this bitch.
Everyone's looking for you.
Curfew enforced.
Hey. Hey, yo, stay
here. I'll be right back.
I got you, Richards.
Hunt him down! Hunt him down!
Thank you.
Hunt him down!
- Remain indoors.
- He's in here.
Remain indoors.
- Nah.
- Told you.
Ben Richards?
No Runner ever survived a
live update. How the hell...
Remain indoors!
Inside, inside, inside!
I can pay you.
Just get me off the
street for the night.
- Hell, nah.
- Five ND.
- Boy!
- We need street meds.
Our sister got cancer, real bad.
Make it ten.
- Get her the good stuff.
- Goddamn.
Hell of a price on your head.
How fast can you run, Richards?
Faster every day.
Just a shocking amount
of destruction here.
The NCG on tactical alert
as units pour in from
neighboring districts,
seeking justice for
their fallen brethren.
The NCG bomb squad is on the scene
combing through the
rubble for evidence.
Preliminary reports indicate Richards
set off the explosion in the basement.
His body is yet to be
found. But as one specialist
told me off the record...
Baby. It's time.
I don't get it. You could set
your grandkids up for life...
with one Record and Report.
You think the Network would
rather pay us reward money
or make up some
bullshit and arrest us?
What if I gave you enough
to get your sister real pharms?
Say 500 new.
I can get you out of Boston,
- but it won't be for money.
- Bro.
This dude ain't going nowhere.
Goons got the hood
surrounded. Reality.
Stop.
Just a little pinch and
everything's gonna be okay.
Does Richards live?
Find out tomorrow night
on The Running Man, 8 o'c...
You know, you
seem like a smart cat.
What made you sign up to be a
cog in their propaganda machine?
I'm just trying to take
care of my family.
Just like you and your sister.
June.
When my kid was sick,
I sent my wife
enough to get her well.
Now I'm trying to win
enough to get them out.
She's only two. So if I do my job,
she'll never even
remember Slumside.
Okay, Richards.
I can get you past that blockade.
But I'll need a couple days to set it
up, so hide out here in the meantime.
You know, you could go
the full 30 if you play it smart.
And what makes you such an expert?
Tune in and find out.
Welcome to the Pulpit.
♪ I don't want a lot ♪
♪ I want just enough ♪
♪ So why has it got to
be so damn tough? ♪
What goes on behind the scenes of
the biggest Free-Vee show of all time?
Welcome to The Apostle, episode 30.
"Real Rules of the Running Man."
If you dig, dupe and distribute.
The Network has three
types for every run.
Oh, my God.
Type one: Hopeless Dude.
Hopeless Dude is cursed
with a fatal misunderstanding
- of human nature.
- Enjoy your...
- Tim?
- Yup.
He usually lasts
less than 48 hours.
Come and get me.
Dinner is served, pal.
Aw... Damn.
Pa-pow! That's a take out.
- Woof.
- Oh!
He is cooked.
Type two: Negative Dude.
Negative Dude knows he
ain't got a chance in hell.
He just wants to go
out with a bang or two!
Make life greater.
Leave a fucking crater.
Bro gets smoked by
the end of week one
'cause he buys too much ass
and not enough food
with his running start.
A slave to his appetites...
he often serves
himself up on a plate.
Suck dicks in hell!
Ka-boom! Runner down!
Type three:
Yeah!
Final Dude.
Final Dude has a
fierce will to survive.
Yet he never wins.
The Network cheats.
They can find anyone anytime.
But if a Runner's getting
good ratings, they let him run.
Thirteen days.
And just like Papa always said,
"You can try, but you
can't catch a ghost."
So by the end of week
two, ratings usually peak.
Oh, shit.
The crowd wants blood,
and Final Dude becomes
a victim of his own success.
They might hide from Destiny,
but they never outrun Fate.
That's me, McCone!
I'm the Running Man, bi...
Double kill!
Rest in pieces.
That's game.
Is that supposed to inspire me?
Oh, come on, man! Don't you get it?
After that escape tonight,
live, prime time, you...
You... are...
Final Dude.
And they're gonna squeeze every
last drop of ratings out of your ass.
So you got at least until
Negative Dude flames out
to get somewhere safe.
Which gives us enough
time to set you up
for the biggest underdog
win in game show history.
So where the hell is "safe"?
I'm working on it.
Hey, pen pal. It's been a while.
You sure you know
what you're doing?
Guess we'll find out.
Got a package headed your way.
Yeah, special delivery,
as seen on Free-Vee.
Okay. I see you.
And pickup location B.
Got it.
Mama's coming, baby.
Okay, okay.
So, how does a
five-year-old get lung cancer?
Radioactive dust.
From the Rhode Island explosion.
Never heard about that.
Yeah, you never heard of it
'cause the Network owns the news.
Just like they owned
that munitions factory.
Just like... they
own the government.
So why bother complying
with safety regs, right?
That's how June got sick.
For all you watching...
not the execs, not the technicos.
If you live in a tower
Uptown, I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to the
people in the Co-Ops.
The ones who can't get
a job, the squatter tribes,
the kids getting shot for
looking at a Goon the wrong way.
There's something
you all need to know.
The Network is
giving our kids cancer
and they are covering it up.
Previously on The Running Man.
I'm still here, you
shit-eaters! Hah!
- Yeah! Richards is the man!
- Ben! Ben! Ben!
Ladies and gentlemen,
last night seven men and one woman
gave their lives to protect ours,
their love for their country only
matched by the love for their children.
Uh-oh.
Someone chose to end the
lives of these eight heroes.
And that someone was Ben Richards.
His new tape just arrived.
Let's hear what he
has to say about it.
For all you watching,
not the execs, not the technicos.
If you live in a tower
Uptown, I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to the
people in the Co-Ops,
the squatter tribes, the
ones who can't get a job,
the kids getting shot for
looking at a Goon the wrong way.
There's something
you all need to know.
I laughed my ass off
smoking those Goons.
- Whoa.
- I wasn't just laughing
at their screams, I was
laughing at their kids.
Now you know how it felt when
Daddy did it to someone else!
Damn, cuz.
I didn't say that, okay?
I made a video about the Network
giving kids cancer. It's all fake!
Disgusting!
- You got to get him out of here.
- Ma!
Tonight! Right now!
I want him gone!
Bring them all on!
What kind of world
are we living in?
Running fans,
I've just heard from
producer Dan Killian
who has personally doubled
the reward for Ben Richards.
Now 20,000 new dollars for
any confirmed Record and Report
- that leads to a kill.
- Get in, get in!
Come on, come on.
It's getting crazy out here.
Yeah, man. The
gangs are out tonight.
We got to roll. You ready?
Here we go.
Okay, keep your eyes open.
Those biker boys are on a
bounty hunt for the reward.
Got it.
- Yo, they're following us.
- I know, I know.
Stay cool.
They're on us, they're on us!
You got to be shitting me.
When we hit the alley,
yell which way to turn next.
Don't stop till we're out.
- Hang on, Richards! A pothole!
- Yo, what's going on?
- They're still on us!
- I know!
- Go right!
- Okay!
Left!
Pothole! Sorry, sorry.
There's two of them!
I see them, I see them!
They've got guns!
Give him up!
Straight! Floor it!
Go, go, go!
Look out!
- Richards lives!
- Pull over!
¡No hablo inglés!
Hold on!
- You good? You good?
- Yeah.
Karma delivery, motherfucker!
Oof.
Yeah!
Floor it!
Whoo!
Y'all messed with
the wrong brothers!
Yeah, that's the stuff!
Whoo!
Hey, Richards! We're through!
Go, go, go!
My pen pal needs a day to
prep transport to a shelter.
You can trust him with your life.
Just don't mention hot
dogs around him there.
- You say, "hot dogs?"
- Yup.
Go catch that slow train to Maine.
Less people in the sticks, but keep
your head down and don't trust anyone
but this guy.
Name's Elton. Hardcore.
Down for the cause.
You really think this will work?
Look, we know they
track the envelopes.
You pre-shoot the
rest of your self-tapes,
my man heads south,
drops them on the way
while you're safe underground.
They won't know what hit 'em.
Oh. Almost forgot.
Just in case.
Why are you helping me?
You seen the power they have.
We don't got each other's back, this
game is over before it even begins.
Hey.
Done.
What's up, America?
I was about to tell you the
Network fakes these self-tapes,
but if I did, they'd
just fake this one, too.
So...
I'm just gonna read
you something instead.
"Dear Diary: I woke
up with the blahs today.
My regular gig of
killing heroic Goons
was feeling... too routine.
Time for a 'me' day.
So I ate my favorite
breakfast in bed:
Defenseless puppies. I
could have eaten twenty.
Then I did yoga. I
blew up a courthouse.
I know, creature of habit.
But tonight...
I am gonna make
love... to an illegal...
immigrant... sheep."
You know how a sheep
tells you it's horny?
Mr. Richards thinks he's funny.
But we'll see who
has the last laugh when
McCone catches him lacking.
Now, let's see if Miss Laughlin has burned
through the last of her running money.
We're still here, you shit-eaters!
Damn, Richards, that's a
tough act to follow, but...
challenge accepted!
Yeah! Ooh!
Go off, neighbor.
Oh, my God! Look at it!
Who dies next?
Definitely her.
Laughlin? Get real.
Sheep boy's going down.
- No way.
- I got ten clams says
- Ben Richards dies next.
- Oh, come on.
- He's pissed the Network off, all the way.
- That's why he's gonna win.
- The guy's got moxie.
- Yeah, he's one of us.
Taking on the boys in black.
Giving the world the finger!
He's your final Runner.
- That's a bet.
- Damn straight.
What do you think, Reverend?
You seen this Richards guy?
No. But he sounds
like quite the character.
What's wrong with you?
He's blind, you fucking idiot.
Me again. Look,
here's the real deal.
I'm not out here trying
to fight the power.
I'm not out here to have fun.
I'm here to win and
get back to my family.
So you won't see me
throwing Molotov cocktails,
you won't see me throwing parties.
In fact,
you won't see me at all.
Just in time, Father.
The best takeout in Maine.
Bless you, my son.
Keep clear.
Keep clear. This is
a self-driving vehicle.
Hey, Father. Can I
ask you something?
Of course, my son.
So I got this girlfriend, okay?
Am I going to hell
for using rubbers?
You may well go for not using them.
I've ten brothers and sisters.
My father said he was
in hell every single day.
- Thanks, Father.
- Mm.
Have a good night.
Careful out there.
You think you're the guy
who stops me from
seeing my daughter again?
Thank you.
It's him! It's him!
There he is! Run him down!
We got him!
Get him!
I got him.
Fuck you, Richards! Die!
Die!
This is a message
for my fellow citizens.
And let me make this
clear for the cheap seats.
If I die on this show, I died
for the two things I believe in.
My wife and my kid.
Everything else and
everyone else can fuck off.
It's The Running Man!
Game on! Friday night!
Here we go!
We all know what that sound is.
We're giving Miss Laughlin
a run for her money.
She rolled the dice on a very public
appearance at the Holy Grail Casino
but didn't gamble that
our Hunters would be there.
Shit.
Move, asshole! What are you...
Oh, she's a wild one. Whoa!
She's on the run!
- Fuck.
- Oh!
Lordy, Lordy.
Looks like she went
bust. Or did she?
Go, they got guns! Go!
Fucking shitbag!
Yeah!
Suck it, McCone!
Kiss my ass!
Hold it right there.
No...
Not so fast, Miss Laughlin.
No blaze of glory for
you, just a human candle
fizzling out on a
lonely Nevada road.
Now, I know what you're thinking.
"Bobby T, you didn't get the kill."
No, we didn't.
But they did.
Meet Jeff and Jeeto.
Brave defenders of their community.
Roll the tape.
Sorry, Hunters.
All you managed
to kill was my vibe.
Remember, kids,
don't drink and drive.
Unless you're good at it.
Get her!
That's some hot footage, kids!
Beyond their cash reward,
Jeff and Jeeto will
receive a lifetime supply
of Fun Twinks cereal!
And then...
there was one.
That's right. Ben Richards
is your final Runner.
Richards lives!
If he survives till midnight,
he'll be our most successful
contestant since season one!
Richards lives!
Come on, hurry.
Hunters will be out for blood.
They hate civilian kills.
Things are gonna start ramping up.
Come on.
I wouldn't be
surprised if they fire up
the DNA sniffers tonight.
I don't want anything else.
I don't need anyone else.
What a tough guy.
Is that clear?
I'm not looking for new friends.
Don't ask for an autograph.
- Eltie! What if he's in Derry?
- He's not in Derry, Mom.
Don't worry, it's fine.
She thinks you're an actual
demon, but she's fairly deaf.
We can use our normal voices.
Kill him. Welf bastard.
Hunt him down!
She used to be a
kind, clever woman.
This is where it all happens.
Amateur lab for making
handcrafted soap, far as you know.
Some normal
non-revolutionary literature.
Wink, wink.
Copier for my harmless
community newsletter,
- if you follow my drift.
- Uh-huh.
So what's a DNA sniffer?
Black ops scanners that I.D.
highly fragmented strands of DNA.
These things are hidden in every
streetlamp across the country.
Which is why you got to
get underground ASAP.
Man, if you want to ask, just ask.
What is up with the hot dog cart?
My dad was a cop.
A good cop.
He quit in protest when the
Network privatized local police.
He believed officers
should be accountable
to the towns that pay
them, not the government.
And sure as hell
not some mega-corp.
So he bought the cart.
Busted his ass. We
never missed a meal.
Better an honorable hot dog
vendor than a crooked Goon.
But his friends who signed on with
the NCG didn't appreciate his choices.
And they let him know
every chance they got.
He made damn sure we
were safe in this house.
But every time he
took that cart out,
well... you see what
it did to my mom.
And this is what
they did to my dad.
His buddies on the force
never solved the case
'cause they're the
ones who killed him.
But you can't kill an idea.
Dad was their worst nightmare.
A free man with a conscience.
And everything they
destroyed in him lives on in me.
Like a nuclear blast...
that never burns out.
Monster?
I'm good.
Hey, Runners.
You can't outrun Fate.
And you cannot hide...
from Destiny.
That's actually not true.
Before he was killed, Dad
refurbed this Cold War shelter
he found in a nearby forest.
I have a detailed map
for how to get there.
You could survive down
there for three years.
But you'll only need
it for two weeks.
We'll pre-shoot the rest
of your tapes tomorrow.
What do you think?
Um...
Or...
Maybe just... white.
Hardcore.
Check this out.
You can be arrested just for
having The Truth in your house.
So these won't be distributed
until right after you win.
What the hell?
It's a special issue on the
Network's most heinous crimes.
What does that have to do with me?
A bomb's chemicals
hold great power.
But without an initiator to
make it go boom, it's harmless.
You know why they cheered for you
down there? They think you just might win.
And if you can survive against
those Goons, so can they.
The people have had it.
This country's ready to
blow... and you're the initiator.
I'm not the initiator!
I'm a guy trying to
get back to his family.
It's you against the
world either way, brother.
Why not be both?
Come on.
My mom thinks the bathroom across
the hall is haunted, so that's all you.
If the light in the hallway
is off, she's asleep.
Hey.
I appreciate what you're doing.
But if they find out you helped me,
those same Goons that got your dad...
they'll come for you.
One can hope.
This message is for Cathy.
In case you see this someday.
I wanted to impart
a little dad advice.
Rule one:
Take care of your mom.
She's your best friend.
Rule two: Bullies are cowards.
Hit back.
Rule three:
You can be kind and
strong at the same time.
Rule four: Don't trust
the Network... ever.
And rule five:
You remember...
your dada loves you a whole lot.
I'll be looking out for
you. No matter what.
Ha!
I knew it was you.
Devil. Murderer!
- You stay away from my Eltie.
- Ma'am?
You savage!
Wait! Mom!
You'll never eat puppies again.
Mom, no! No!
Mom, it's okay! He's a friend!
Eltie, no!
Ma'am, ma'am!
If you press that button,
the NCG will come in firing.
Okay? They will not care who
gets caught in the cross fire.
It will be a bloodbath.
We don't need every Goon in the
state coming through that door, right?
Don't.
Network Community Guard.
What crime would you like to report?
Ben Richards just
broke into my home!
Okay, stay where you are.
- Why?
- Ma saw you.
We got to get going.
I just need five minutes of fun
with these guys before we do.
Fun?
Grab your stuff!
I'll get the 'zines!
They're coming to get you!
You're not listening.
It's dangerous!
No!
Mom, get in the safe room!
No, Eltie, I want to see him die!
You hear that, welf?
You're gonna die!
They're here.
Mom!
He's here! Richards is in the hall!
- Mom!
- Kill him!
- Come on!
- No! Let me go!
No! I don't want to miss it!
I want to see!
Let's move!
This way. Come on.
Yo, dip shits! You
shot up the wrong hall!
We're over here!
Here we go.
Are you crazy? We don't
have time to play games!
Oh, yes, we do.
Fastest the Hunters ever arrived
on-scene was 4 minutes 30 seconds.
We'll be long gone by then.
Go! Go! Move!
♪ The police in New York City ♪
Yoo-hoo! Hey, big boys!
♪ They chased a boy
Right through the park ♪
♪ And in a case of
mistaken identity ♪
♪ They put a bullet
through his heart ♪
♪ Heart breaker, heart breaker ♪
♪ She stuck the pins
right in her heart ♪
I like my bacon extra crispy!
- We got to go, man!
- Follow me.
Shit!
♪ A pain maker ♪
Come on!
♪ Doo doo doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ I wanna tear that world apart ♪
♪ Doo doo, doo doo
doo doo doo doo doo ♪
Yeah!
Let's go!
♪ I wanna tear this world apart ♪
Whoo!
♪ Heart breaker, heart breaker ♪
Why are we upstairs?
♪ You stole the love
right out my heart ♪
Go! Go!
♪ Heart breaker, heart breaker ♪
Yes! Yes!
Elton! Why are we upstairs?
♪ I wanna tear your world apart ♪
For this!
You brought us up here so
you could slide down a pole?
I brought us up here so
we could slide down a pole!
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
See? Four minutes flat.
Told you we'd be long gone.
Long gone? We are still
in the goddamn house!
Not for long!
Tactical flashlight.
- Pretty powerful.
- Yeah.
Come on.
I'm gonna sever your
Achilles and drag you outside.
Chief wants to end your
run in person, on camera.
Don't let him answer that!
Still there?
- Yeah.
- Put him on.
It's for you.
Ah! There he is.
Incredible work,
Mr. Richards. You are killing it.
Killing it? People are dying,
you fucking psychopath!
If you can fake everything, why
don't you just fake the whole show?
Believe me, we have tried.
But humans bring that
special unpredictable spark.
The audience lives for
these happy accidents.
- A little advice?
- I'll pass.
Make sure my family gets the money.
Richards, don't go.
You can still win this game,
but you have to play it smart.
I just sent a rover
into that tunnel.
Now finish off that Hunter
and wait for my cue to exit.
You want me to off
one of your own guys?
It's all good Free-Vee.
Okay, on you in five... four...
three...
two...
one.
And action.
Get in!
- Floor it!
- What about the doors?
Oh, shit!
Hold on!
- Where are we going?
- Down the dirt road.
- They're all dirt roads!
- There!
- The trail!
- Okay.
Son of a... bitch.
Cross the bridge and drop me off.
I can slow them down.
Take back roads to the shelter.
Survival is the win!
This way!
Take this map.
Dad's bunker is in
the middle of the forest.
Remember, Richards...
you're the initiator.
Green light on Richards.
It's the end of your run, Richards.
Fuck it.
I am the initiator.
The thrill of the hunt.
Can you feel it?
Your heart beats faster.
Bright red blood pumps
adrenaline through your veins.
This game is no game.
Life and death are on the line.
Can you feel it, Mr. Richards?
Congratulations.
You took out a Hunter.
Now it's down to four of them.
Plus every citizen
of this great nation.
"Hundred and five
paces west of big rock.
Bunker's dug into the hill."
Well, shit.
Can you smell it?
The acrid stink of fear
as the prey animal realizes
he's surrounded by predators.
Reality sinks in as
he scurries to hide,
desperately hoping to survive.
But deep down, he already
knows it's too late, because...
this is America, goddamn it,
and we don't put
up with no bullshit!
Bloodlust is our
birthright. Set it free.
Richards chose this path,
and it's up to you to
show him where it ends.
Keep your eyes open so
you can see the terror in his,
and hunt him down!
Hunt him down! Hunt him down!
I see, yeah.
I see! Wow!
Look, it's Dada.
Yeah!
Look. Look.
I told you I'd get
you out of there.
People on this show
never come back.
This is a message for Killian.
Hey, Dan.
I'm starting to get
how this game works.
It's not about me
winning or losing.
It's about your ratings.
About how much chaos I can cause.
I'm taking this thing
all the way to the end.
And I am done playing
defense, I promise you that.
So here's the deal.
I will see my family again.
And as long as they
keep getting paid,
you can put whoever
you want in front of me.
I will run through all of them.
I know you fight dirty.
Well, guess what,
you son of a bitch.
I'm from Slumside. Let's
throw the rule book out.
Here's to mutually
profitable annihilation.
- You want a show?
- Damn it.
I'll give you a show.
Whoo-hoo!
♪ Americanos, Americanos ♪
Sing it, girl.
Yes! Here we go! Let's do this!
We interrupt The Americanos for a
live update from The Running Man.
Boring!
- Who even likes this show?
- The poors. Duh.
Zaza!
They're the only ones
dense enough to think it's real.
I know. It's so fake.
Stop!
What is happening? Are you okay?
Oh, my God!
What's happening, Amelia?
Don't hurt her, please!
Go, go! Take it off autopilot!
Drive! Take the
next back road north.
I can't. My power's on empty.
Your battery is 93% charged. Nice!
Those Goons are going to frag us
if you don't back
this car up right now!
Whoa!
They're here!
Your car is damaged.
Go, go! Keep it moving!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Left!
Jesus!
Now I see why you people
need self-driving cars.
Recalculating.
Keep it pointed north.
All the way to the border.
Go ahead. Say what you got to say.
Why?
So you can go crazy and kill me?
No.
You have one
minute to speak freely.
How do you live with yourself? Hmm?
You dare sit there
and criticize my driving?
Tell me how to operate my own car?
I am a member of society!
You disgust me!
You abandoned that starving baby,
that horrible wife of yours.
So you can what?
Kill people for money?
And you only kill the best people!
The people who protect us from...
from welfs like you!
And that's not a word I use!
That is my family.
Our number finally
came up for the park.
I watched Cathy try ice
cream for the first time.
That was the best day of my life.
So yeah, you're right.
The show is so fake.
Not the bullets. Not the death.
Just the part that
makes people like you
think you're better
than people like us.
Let me ask you something.
How much was that scarf?
Huh?
More than the meds my daughter
needed when she was dying of the flu?
The flu!
That is a human life
hanging around your neck!
But you seem to be doing fine.
Who can blame
you? It's a nice scarf.
I'm not a bad person.
No, do not start crying.
I will shoot us both
if you start crying.
Cry when it's over.
When will that be?
Shit.
Yielding for an
emergency vehicle. Nice!
- Disable it! Disable it! Do not pull over!
- I don't know how!
Yielding in 100 feet.
- 50 feet.
- Pull over!
In 20 feet.
You have successfully
yielded. Nice!
Shit.
Oh, hey, Richards.
You've been pulled over by
the Rustic Rock Mulisha Boyz.
We're here securing our homestead
in the name of the Network.
Don't worry, lady.
We're the good guys.
Just step out of the car.
You'll be safe with us.
It's him we want.
Just go.
What the fuck is happening?
The producers just killed
Network militia instead of me.
They wouldn't do that. Those men
were just trying to protect me from you.
What is it gonna take for
you to get I'm not the bad guy?
Take the car. Just drive
away. I don't want to hurt you.
You think they're gonna let
you walk after seeing that?
- You're on the show now.
- No, I'm not!
Richards lives. And this
time he's got a hostage.
Amelia Williams, a 27-year-old
realtor from Bangor, Maine.
Help me! He's got a gun!
Welcome to The Running Man.
Help me, please!
The crisis continues,
as Miss Williams's gray Alpine heads
north on Rustic Rock Siding Road.
The hostage situation has triggered
the NCG to go into full tactical alert.
Help me!
- Turn it off.
- He's got a gun!
Just turn it off!
Miss Williams was
carjacked and kidnapped by...
Richards lives! Whoo!
Yeah!
Richards lives! Richards lives!
Go, Richards!
- Unbelievable.
- Goons ahead!
Watch yourself!
Yeah, it's a circus all right.
So they're just gonna
keep filming us?
If a Runner gets good
ratings, they let him run.
- Richards lives!
- Oh, God.
Is that a blockade?
Oh, shit. All right. If we play
our parts, they'll let us pass.
Oh, shit, shit, shit.
Richards lives!
Okay. Just keep driving.
They're not gonna shoot.
How do you know?
'Cause they're gonna wait
for the show to start. Do it live.
- Do what live?
- Kill me.
- Richards lives!
- Open up!
They're waving us through.
Yo, Richards! We got you, man!
Why are they cheering for
you when I'm the hostage?
Unbelievable.
Amelia?
Will you give me the gun?
Why not? You're obviously the hero.
Trust me.
I don't think we're
gonna need this anymore.
Record and Report.
State your claim.
Oh, my God. I just
saw Ben Richards.
I'm sorry, wait. I am Ben Richards.
If you don't want to be
the reason Amelia dies,
get this message to Killian.
Do what he says, please!
You heard the lady.
Richards lives! Richards
lives! Richards lives!
Richards lives! Richards lives!
Go, Richards!
Before you murder us, make up
some bullshit why it had to be done,
look at all these people
who know the truth.
Are you willing to kill all
of them? Because I am.
I'm holding onto this
bullhorn with my right hand.
My left hand is in my front pouch,
wrapped around twelve
pounds of Black Irish.
When I used to work
in Network Public Utility,
you'd get these two-ton fatbergs,
take less than a
gram to blow those up.
Twelve pounds.
It'll vaporize everything
in a half-mile radius.
Bull... shit.
BFE-20 is the most highly
regulated industrial explosive.
And you haven't even set
foot in a state that sells it.
I guess Molie didn't
tell you everything.
I got my finger stuck in the
detonator ring and it's on half-cock.
So...
I want one of those big
fancy Flying-V airplanes.
I want two autochutes handed to
Amelia at the bottom of the ramp.
If the chutes are sabotaged,
if you make any sudden moves,
if you don't back those trucks up
and let me on that
tarmac right fucking now,
you won't even hear it go boom.
I'll just see you in hell
and laugh in your face.
You got one minute.
Shouldn't take long.
He's got a direct line to the boss.
Last chance to run.
No.
You made me feel
like I'm the bad guy.
Now I have to prove I'm not.
Why do you give
a shit what I think?
You're not the one
I'm trying to prove it to.
So what's our plan?
Let him through.
I'm gonna convince them
your handbag is a bomb
long enough to bail
out over Canada.
They'll never let me win,
so I'm gonna slip out the back
door and wait out the clock.
We just have to keep
the audience entertained
until that jet crosses the border.
What if they call your bluff?
You make sure they know
it's real. Get scared, freak out.
Curse, scream, call me
the worst names possible.
Just remember, everything bad,
it's all good Free-Vee.
Act terrified when McCone
hands you the chutes.
I won't have to act.
He grabs his gun, you'll
know it's time to go off.
So, you think you're the guy
who stops me from
seeing my daughter again?
Show starts at 8:00.
Get on the plane.
Only if you take your mask off.
Audience will love it.
Keep dreaming.
- Do what he says.
- No copy.
Do what he says. Take it off.
There he is.
Come on, show starts at 8:00.
Welcome aboard, Mr. Richards,
to the Net-Air Flying-V
Luxury Jetliner,
the ultimate in private travel.
With state-of-the-art
safety features,
this is first-class
comfort taken sky high.
So sit back and enjoy the
most relaxing flight of your life.
Oh, welcome aboard, Mr. Richards.
I'm Captain Holloway.
You'll excuse me if I
don't shake your hand.
That's First Officer Duninger
and Navigation Officer
Donahue to your left.
Looks like you're missing one.
Hey, Captain, how many
lavatories are on this rust bucket?
- Four.
- Six.
Why don't you check
them all for stowaways?
Anyone sneaks up on me,
it's gonna be a real short ride.
So, where are we headed tonight?
Plot a route over the richest
homes from here to Canada.
Fly as low as you can.
Let me know when we're
ten minutes from the border.
As you wish.
The seat belt sign is now off.
Feel free to move about the cabin.
Hey, Richards. Six
minutes to showtime.
You should get that last meal before
they clear me to blow your head off
in front of a couple
billion people.
Oh, yeah?
You should really put some
makeup on before the show starts.
Fuck the show! Let's go.
- You want to go? We can all go right now!
- No, no, no! Just stop!
Do it! Do it, tough guy!
- Why are you doing this?
- See if I twitch.
Show him the bomb!
Show it to him before he
shoots you and kills us all!
- Ma'am...
- No, just show it!
'Cause I don't want to feel like this
anymore! Do you fucking hear me?
- I'm done!
- Let's calm down.
- Calm down.
- I'm fucking done!
All right, Richards, what if I offer
you an amnesty deal and an exit visa?
You're nothing but a
Halloween costume.
You can't offer me shit!
Too true, Mr. Richards. He can't.
- But I can.
- How about I offer you a deal?
You tell your
Hunters in the cockpit
to do what I tell them, otherwise,
I blow up this jet
and everyone on it!
Ben, I admire your
commitment to the bit,
but we're short on time, so...
I'll be blunt.
We know you're bluffing.
The Flying-V Mark 2 has
scanners built into the doors.
It's been wildly entertaining.
But you can give Amelia
her lovely handbag back now.
Evan.
Evan, don't.
That's game.
Safety that weapon, sir.
Evan, are you insane?
The show hasn't even started.
Hand over your gun and
go to the back of the jet.
Thank you.
You can remain there
until I say otherwise.
I need a moment to have
a word with Mr. Richards
to discuss a sensitive matter.
Let's keep this between us.
You know, it wasn't too long
ago that someone with my job
thought it was more
important to force some
hypocritical moral message
down society's throat
than to simply entertain them.
They forgot about the power
of illusion, the power of the star,
which is what you are, Richards.
And this is why we want
to offer you your own show.
Now picture it.
A former Runner redeemed
through righteous vengeance,
turns his life around
to become a lethal force for good.
They call him...
The Hunter.
The board has authorized me to pay
you 5 million new dollars per season.
There's only one condition.
Sit back, watch the intro
and when Bobby cues you,
kill every Hunter on that jet.
Condition met, I'll remote-pilot
you back to the studio jetport,
where the president
of the United States
will induct you as
"Hunter Number Six,"
another title idea
I'm playing with.
The data says the revenge plot...
Revenge?
Revenge for what?
Who is gonna root for a guy
who kills your national heroes?
I call bullshit, Dan.
Let me worry about the creative.
No deal.
The truth, then.
Revenge for your wife and child.
Why would I ever believe you?
Because, if they were still alive,
I'd hold them at gunpoint and
force you to do whatever I want.
And torture them
right in front of you.
I didn't want to show you this.
But I'm out of time
to save your life.
The Hunter you killed
was part of a tight crew.
McCone and the men in that cockpit
flew to Co-Op City
to Sheila and Cathy's
secret Uptown location.
- No.
- They badged their way
past the Family
Alliance agents and...
I'm sorry, Ben.
Not all accidents are happy.
No.
We want you to win.
The audience is
already on your side.
Once I show them footage of
McCone and his men killing your family,
they will follow you into hell.
Think of what this
does for your narrative.
Thirty seconds to showtime, Ben.
You'll find a gun by the
coffee station in the galley.
But if you don't sign before
the theme music ends,
I'll order the bastards that
killed your family to kill you, too.
What's happening?
Tune in and find out.
Everyone, everyone, please settle.
Now, now.
Running fans!
We start today's episode
with a heavy heart.
We here at The Running Man
believe in following the rules.
So it pains me
to tell you that one of
our most important rules
has been broken by the very
men we entrust to enforce them.
Chief McCone and his Hunters.
And that rule is
we protect the Runner's
family from harm.
No one would play if we didn't.
We thought it only
fair to let Richards
administer the penalty
for this grave infraction.
As we go live to Richards,
we pray he has what it takes.
Hey, Richards.
You making coffee?
Yeah.
How do you take it?
Altitude alert.
Remote pilot engaged.
Disengaged.
Altitude alert.
Remote pilot engaged.
And then...
there was one.
Three Hunters down.
But the deadliest among them
is still somewhere on this jet.
He took the other
parachute. I couldn't stop him.
Strap that on.
Keep your head down.
The prey has become the predator.
McCone is trapped.
Nowhere to run. Nowhere to hide.
Mr. Richards is checking all of
the Flying-V's executive toilets.
That's four.
The fuse has been lit.
It's just a matter of time.
Okay, here we go.
The moment of truth.
Six, bitch.
Uh-oh.
That's got to be disappointing.
The tension is higher
than ever, Running fans.
It all comes down to this.
Ben!
Whoa!
No!
You want to know who's stopping
you from seeing your kid again?
You!
That had to hurt!
No!
Oh, no.
Richards has taken a savage blow...
Shut the fuck up, Bobby!
If this is how they fire me, what
do you think they'll do to you?
Chump.
You think you're the only
Runner ever got offered a deal?
You think surviving two weeks
and change makes you big shit?
Try 29 days.
What's more likely?
A. I killed your family.
B. Killian sold you just the right
lie to get a bloodbath season finale.
Or C. You're too fucking
stupid to figure it out?
Take it from someone who took the
deal to be a Hunter instead of the hunted.
The only time you'll
ever see your family again
is when they torture
them in front of you.
Fuck with your head enough to
make you wanna kill it all away.
You're full of shit.
You're all full of shit.
The truth is...
I'm doing you a favor.
Cabin pressure compromised.
Emergency doors disarmed.
Hey, Killian!
You think I need a
gun to waste this loser?
You outran Fate.
You can't hide from Destiny!
This is my show now!
Do it, tough guy! See if I twitch.
That's game.
Can I borrow your scarf?
Uh-huh.
Emergency doors disarmed.
Cabin pressure compromised.
Let's get you back on the ground.
Door two unlocked.
The chute should open on its own.
But if it doesn't,
just let her rip.
When you get on the
ground, just run like hell.
Don't look back.
When I tell you, you're gonna
pull that down all the way.
I'm sorry they did this to you!
I did it to myself.
It's a sign! I'm not supposed to...
Stop fucking filming me!
Assholes!
Richards lives,
ladies and gentlemen!
Keep going, kid! You've got this.
Ben Richards, you are the man.
We have command of the jet.
Our best trauma surgeons
are already on the tarmac,
ready to patch you
up as good as new.
But wait!
Making his Free-Vee debut
with a special message,
the creator of Running Man,
super producer Dan Killian!
Mr. Richards, we
here at the Network
believe you embody the raw strength
and salt-of-the-earth, moral
backbone this country stands for.
And we want... no...
we need to see more.
This summer, Ben Richards is...
Hunter Six!
Congratulations, Ben.
And welcome to the Network family.
I already got a family.
Did you kill them or not, Dan?
Fuck you, Dan!
Give it up for Dan Killian!
Come on, Ben.
We're live.
How many times do you get to tell
two billion people how you really feel?
How does it feel to be a hero, Ben?
Nothing I've done on the
show makes me a hero.
I tried to be a hero once,
and they blacklisted my ass.
My daughter got sick.
And this is the
only job I could get.
Seems like the whole
point of Free-Vee
is to make us hate each other
so they can keep stealing from us
while we fight in the mud.
You want the truth?
Turn it off.
We are all being
fucked by the Network.
Find out who really runs it.
Record, report them.
Get their names.
You just met one
of them. Dan Killian.
You remember that face.
Don't watch Free-Vee.
Watch who pays for it.
Turn it off.
Turn it...
Great speech.
Too bad I'm the
only one who saw it.
We've been on an ad
break since you said
nothing you did on the
show made you a hero.
You think it was worth it?
You think your little
rant makes you a martyr?
We're going live again in 30.
And this time,
you'll play your part,
because if not, I'm
gonna run this instead.
I told you I was gonna
burn this building down
and everyone in it!
That was fast.
Work with me, Richards.
Don't throw your life away.
Don't make me fly that jet
into the Network Building.
They'll blow you out of the sky.
Are they dead or alive, Dan?
- Who?
- My family!
Who cares? If I told you they were
alive, would you even believe me?
We are live in five...
four... three... two... one.
Okay, have it your way.
I told you, I was gonna
burn this building down
and everyone in it!
I will see you in hell
and laugh in your face!
Altitude alert.
Ben, are you insane?
There's 5,000 innocent
people in this building!
Remote pilot engaged.
Look at what you've done.
You happy?
I told you I was gonna fuck you up.
Yeah.
Warning. Collision alert.
Remain calm, everyone.
The NCG will blow
him out of the sky!
Missile inbound.
Okay, true believers.
Let's wind that back.
Ben Richards! Legend.
The Network wants you to
think that on day 18 of his run,
after taking out all five Hunters,
the longest-surviving
contestant since season one
committed suicide by
surface-to-air missile.
The Apostle calls bullshit.
First of all, they cut to ads
six minutes earlier than usual
and ran them for twice as long.
They must've needed the
time to write this fake-ass shit.
I will see you in hell
and laugh in your face!
And then, they swapped the crowd.
Where'd purple-shirt guy come from?
Season five, episode
13 to be exact.
That's how dumb the
Network thinks we are.
Their vile distortions meant
none of us knew the truth
about what happened on that jet!
Until a revolutionary riot
girl found the jet's black box
on the roof of her Co-Op.
Her uncle hacked the audio, duped,
distributed and put it on blast.
Turn it off.
And goddamn it, did we ever.
The Network wasn't
about to give us the gospel,
so we learned how
to give it to each other.
Ben lit the fuse and The Truth
exploded like a nuclear blast
before the Network
even knew it existed.
Don't watch Free-Vee.
Watch who pays for it.
But questions remain
about that fateful night.
Keep going, kid!
Did the Hunters really
assassinate Ben's family?
Did Killian sell him just the right
lie for a bloodbath season finale?
And the big one on everyone's mind:
Did Ben survive?
The Apostle's research reveals
that one of the Flying-V Mark 2
state-of-the-art safety features
was a crew escape pod
just about the size of
this so-called debris.
Did Ben cheat death one last time?
Stop filming me!
The Network won't say.
But one thing's for sure.
Richards lives! Richards lives!
He's still here, you shit-eaters!
Attention, shoppers.
Our store will be
closing in 30 minutes.
Please make your final selections
and proceed to the front registers.
And the belly.
Thank you for
shopping with us today.
Yeah.
And what else do we need?
Oh, my God. These are adorable.
Oh, no, sorry, those aren't mine.
That guy outside bought
them for you, Mrs. Richards.
Groceries, too.
That's...
not my name.
Richards lives!
Richards lives! Richards lives!
Goddamn, Richards!
- You are indeed a tough act to follow.
- Thirty seconds!
- Where do you think you're going?
- You don't hear that?
I'd say that's some valuable
audience feedback, Dan.
No. You get back out
there and you do your job!
- How about you do my job?
- Hey.
Been crushing the ratings for
20 years. I own that audience.
You don't think I
can turn this around?
You're the one who wanted to make
him a star, Dan. Mission accomplished.
It's his show now.
You think you can just walk?
Sweeties, please.
Take another look at my contract.
Page 42, paragraph 6.
There's a special clause
in the smallest of print that reads
"Fuck you!"
- Ten seconds!
- Ten seconds, Dan.
Coco! Come on, let's go.
You know what? Fuck
that! This is my house.
I set the rules. Max the
theme, drown them out.
Sir, are you sure this is...?
Play the theme, right now.
Fuck you, Dan!
Season seven, let's go!
Burn it down!
Kill him!
Mr. Killian! No,
Mr. Killian, this way!
Fuck!
Richards lives! Turn it off!
In five...
- four...
- No.
Three...
No.
Two...
one.
And action.
♪ Keep on running ♪
♪ Keep on hiding ♪
♪ One fine day I gotta be the one ♪
♪ To make you understand ♪
♪ Oh, yes, I gotta be your man ♪
♪ Keep on running ♪
♪ Running from my arms ♪
♪ One fine day I gotta be the one ♪
♪ To make you understand ♪
♪ Oh, baby, I gotta be your man ♪
♪ Everybody's talking about me ♪
♪ It makes me feel so bad ♪
♪ Everyone is laughing at me ♪
♪ It makes me feel so sad ♪
♪ So keep on running ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ Keep on running ♪
♪ Keep on hiding ♪
♪ One fine day I'm
gonna be the one ♪
♪ To make you understand ♪
♪ I gotta be your man ♪
♪ Everybody's talking about me ♪
♪ It makes me feel so bad ♪
♪ Everyone is laughing at me ♪
♪ It makes me feel so sad ♪
♪ So keep on running, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Running from my arms ♪
♪ One fine day I'm
gonna be the one ♪
♪ To make you understand ♪
♪ Whoa, Lord, I gotta be your man ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Keep on, keep on
Keep on, keep on running ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Running from my arms ♪
♪ Yeah, baby ♪
♪ I gotta be your man ♪
♪ Look out, look out, baby, yeah ♪
English - SDH