♪
Ugh, you came at a bad time
But you just crossed the line
You wanna get wild?
Okay, I'll show you wild
Better come right, better luck tryin'
Gettin' to our level
'Cause you might die, never the time
Tryna start a battle
Bleeding isn't in my blood
Ppyeosokbuteo dallaseo
Beating you is what I do- do- do, yeah
Body on body
I'm naughty, not even sorry
And when you pull up, I'll pull up
A little late to the party (Na-na-na-na)
Locked and loaded, I was born for this
There ain't no point in avoiding it
Annoyed? A bit
Bureul bichwo da bikyeo, ne apgireul ppaetgyeo
Knocking you out like a lullaby
Hear that sound ringing in your mind
Better sit down for the show
'Cause I'm gonna show you
How it's done- done- done
(Hey) Huntrix don't miss
(Hey) Huntrix don't quit
How it's done- done- done
Run, run, we run the town
Whole world playin' our sound
Turnin' up, it's going down
Huntrix show this, how it's done- done- done
♪
Yeah
Something about when you come for the crown
That's so humbling, huh?
Gapjagi wae geurae? meonjeo geondeuryeo, wae?
Ijeya pogihae, what?
Nothing to us
Run up, you're done up, we come up
From sunup to sundown, so come out to play
Won either way, we're one in a million
We killin', we bring it, you want it? Okay
Heels, nails, blade, mascara
Fit check for my napalm era
Need to beat my face, make it cute and savage
Mirror, mirror on my phone, who's the baddest?
(Us, hello?)
Knocking you out like a lullaby
Hear that sound ringing in your mind
Better sit down for the show
'Cause I'm gonna show you
(I'm gonna show you, I'm gonna show you)
How it's done- done- done
I don't talk, but I bite, full of venom
Spittin' facts, you know that's
How it's done- done- done
Okay, like, I know I ramble
But when shootin' my words, I go Rambo
Took blood, sweat, and tears, to look natural
That's how it's done- done- done
Hear our voice unwavering
'Til our song defeats the night
Makin' fear afraid to breathe
'Til the dark meets the light
(How it's done- done- done)
Run, run, we run the town
Whole world playin' our sound
Turnin' up, it's going down
Huntrix, show this how it's done- done- done
We hunt you down- down- down
We got you now- now- now
We show you how- how- how
Huntrix, don't miss, how it's done- done- done
♪
I was a ghost, I was alone
Eoduwojin abgilsog-e (Aah)
Given the throne I didn't know
How to believe
I was the queen that I'm meant to be
I lived two lives, tried to play both sides
But I couldn't find my own place
Called a problem child 'cause I got too wild
But now that's how I'm getting paid
(Kkeut-eobs-psi on stage)
I'm done hidin', now I'm shinin'
Like I'm born to be
We're dreamin' hard, we came so far
Now I believe
We're goin' up- up- up, it's our moment
You know together we're glowing
Gonna be, gonna bе golden
Ooh, up- up- up with our voices
Yeong-wonhi kkaеjil su eobsneun
Gonna be, gonna be golden
Ooh, I'm done hidin', now I'm shinin'
Like I'm born to be
Oh, our time, no fear, no lies
That's who we're born to be
♪
Waited so long to break these walls down
To wake up and feel like me
Put these patterns all in the past now
And finally live like the girl they all see
No more hiding, I'll be shining
Like I'm born to be
'Cause we are hunters, voices strong
And I know I believe
We're goin' up- up- up-, it's our moment
You know together we're glowing
Gonna be, gonna be golden
Ooh, up- up- up with our voices
Yeong-wonhi kkaejil su eobsneun
Gonna be, gonna be golden
Ooh, I'm done hidin', now I'm shinin'
Like I'm born to b-
♪
I'm done hidin', now I'm shinin'
Like I'm born to b-
♪
No more hiding, I'll be shining
Like I'm born to be
'Cause we are hunters, voices strong
And I know I belie-
♪
Hey hey
Hey
Don’t want you, need you
Yeah, I need you to fill me up
Masigo maysyeo bwa do
Seonge chaji ana
Got a feeling that, oh yeah (Yeah)
You could be everything that
That I need, taste so sweet
Every sip makes me want more, yeah
Lookin like snacks ‘cause you got it like that
Take a big bite, want another bite, yeah
Neoui modeungeol nan
Wonhae- wonhae- wonhae
Neomalgon modu
Peonhae- peonhae- peonhae
When you’re in my arms
I hold you so tight (So tight)
Can’t let go no, no, not tonight
Jigeum dangjang nal bwa shigan eobtjana
Neon naegeoya imi algo itjana
‘Cause I need you to need me
I’m empty, you feed me
So, refreshing
My little soda pop
You’re all I can think of
Every drop I drink up
You’re my soda pop
My little soda pop
Cool me down you’re so hot
Pour me up I won’t stop
You’re my soda pop
My little soda pop
♪
Uh, make me wanna flip the top
Han mogume you hit the spot
Every little drip and drop
Fizz and pop, ah
Soreum doda it’s gettin’ hot
Yes, I’m sippin’ when it’s drippin’ now
It's done? I need a second round
And pour a lot and don’t you stop
‘Til my soda pop fizzles out
Kkum soke geuryeowatdeon neo
Nan jeoldae notchil su eopseo
Neol wonhae kkok
I waited so long for a taste of soda
So, the wait is over, baby
Come and fill me up
Just can’t get enough
You’re all I can think of
Every drop I drink up
You’re my soda pop
My little soda pop
Cool me down you’re so hot
Pour me up I won’t stop
You’re my soda pop
My little soda pop
Ooh ooh
You’re my soda pop
Gotta drink every drop
♪
My little soda pop
So sweet, so easy on the eyes
But hideous on the inside
Whole life spreading lies, but you can’t hide
Baby, nice try
I’m ’bout to switch up these vibes
I finally opened my eyes
It’s time to kick you straight back into the night
♪
I’ma gear up
And take you down (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
It’s a takedown (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
It’s a takedown, I’ma take you out
You break down like, “What?”
And it ain’t gonna stop
♪
I’ma gear up
And take you down (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
It's a takedown (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
I'ma take it down (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
(Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
♪
Time to put you in your place
'Cause you're rotten within
When your patterns start to show
It makes the hatred wanna grow outta my-
♪
It’s a takedown, I’ma take you out
You break down like, “What?”
And it ain’t gonna stop
Jeongsin-eul nohgo neoljib balgo
Galleul segeonwa
You’ll be begging and crying, all of you dying
Never miss my shot
I don’t think you’re ready for the takedown
A demon with no feelings don't deserve to live
It's so obvious
I'ma gear up-
♪
(You can try but you can’t hide)
It’s a takedown, I’ma take you out
And I ain’t gonna stop
♪
I tried to hide but something broke
I tried to sing, couldn't hit the notes
The words kept catching in my throat
I tried to smile, I was suffocating though
But here with you, I can finally breathe
You say you're no good
But you're good for me
I've been hoping to change
Now I know we can change
But I won't if you're not by my side
Why does it feel right every time I let you in?
Why does it feel like I can tell you anything?
All the secrets that keep me in chains, and
All the damage that might make me dangerous
You got a dark side
Guess you're not the only one
What if we both tried
Fighting what we're running from?
We can't fix it if we never face it
What if we find a way to escape it?
We could be free- free
We can't fix it if we never face it
Let the past be the past 'til it's weightless
Ooh, time goes by, and I lose perspective
Yeah, hope only hurts, so I just forget it
But you're breaking through all the dark in me
When I thought that nobody could
And you're waking up all these parts of me
That I thought were buried for good
Between imposter and this monster
I been lost inside my head
Ain't no choice when all these voices
Keep me pointing towards no end
It's just easy when I'm with you
No one sees me the way you do
I don't trust it, but I want to
I keep coming back to
Why does it feel right every time I let you in?
Why does it feel like I can tell you anything?
We can't fix it if we never face it
What if we find a way to escape it?
We could be free- free
We can't fix it if we never face it
Let the past be the past 'til it's weightless
Ooh, so take my hand, it's open (Free, free)
What if we heal what's broken? (Free, free)
I tried to hide but something broke
I couldn't sing, but you give me hope
We can't fix it if we never face it
Let the past be the past 'til it's weightless
♪
I was a ghost, I was alone
Eoduwojin abgilsog-e (Aah)
Given the throne I didn't know
How to believe
I was the queen that I'm meant to be
I lived two lives, tried to play both sides
But I couldn't find my own place
Called a problem child 'cause I got too wild
But now that's how I'm getting paid
(Kkeut-eobs-psi on stage)
I'm done hidin', now I'm shinin'
Like I'm born to be
We're dreamin' hard, we came so far
Now I believe
We're goin' up- up- up, it's our moment
You know together we're glowing
Gonna be, gonna bе golden
Ooh, up- up- up with our voices
Yeong-wonhi kkaеjil su eobsneun
Gonna be, gonna be golden
Ooh, I'm done hidin', now I'm shinin'
Like I'm born to be
Oh, our time, no fears, no lies
That's who we're born to be
You know we're gonna be, gonna be golden
We're gonna be, gonna be
Born to be, born to be glowin'
Balg-ge bichnaneun uli
You know that it's our time, no fears, no lies
That's who we're born to be
♪
(Takedown, takedown)
(Takedown- down- down- down)
(I don't think you're ready for the takedown)
(Break you into pieces in a world of pain)
('Cause you're all the same)
(Yeah, it's a takedown- takedown)
It's a takedown
So sweet, so easy on the eyes
But hideous on the inside
Whole life spreading lies, but you can’t hide
Baby, nice try
I’m ’bout to switch up these vibes
I finally opened my eyes
It’s time to kick you straight back into the night
‘Cause I see your real face and it’s ugly as sin
Time to put you in your place
’Cause you’re rotten within
When your patterns start to show
It makes the hatred wanna grow outta my veins
I don’t think you’re ready for the takedown
Breaking into pieces in the world of pain
’Cause you’re all the same
Yeah, it’s a takedown
A demon with no feelings don’t deserve to live
It’s so obvious
I’ma gear up
And take you down (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
(Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
♪
(I'll be your idol)
Keeping you in check, keeping you obsessed
Play me on repeat, kkeuteobsi in your head
Anytime it hurts, play another verse
I can be your sanctuary
Know I'm the only one right now
I will love you more when it all burns down
More than power, more than gold
Yeah, you gave me your heart
Now I'm here for your soul
I'm thе only one who'll love your sins
Feel the way my voicе
Gets underneath your skin
Listen 'cause I'm preachin' to the choir
Can I get the mic' a little higher?
Gimme your desire
I can be the star you rely on (You rely on)
Nae hwanghorui chwihae you can't look away
Don't you know I'm here to save you
Now we runnin' wild
Yeah, I'm all you need, I'ma be your idol
Uh, bichineun fame, gyesog oechyeo
I'm your idol
Thank you for the pain
'Cause it got me going viral
Uh, yeah, natji anhneun fever
Makin' you a believer
Naleul wae neon jonjaehaneun idol?
Living in your mind now
Too late 'cause you're mine now
I will make you free
When you're all part of me
(Listen 'cause I'm) preaching to the choir
(Now) Can I get the mic a little higher?
Gimme your desire
Watch me set your world on fire
Nae hwanghorui chwihae you can't look away
No one is coming to save you
Now we runnin' wild
You're down on your knees, I'ma be your idol
♪
Nothing but the truth now
Nothing but the proof of what I am
The worst of what I came from
Patterns I'm ashamed of
Things that even I don't understand
I tried to fix it, I tried to fight it
My head was twisted, my heart divided
My lies all collided
I don't know why I didn't trust you
To be on my side
I broke into a million pieces
And I can't go back
But now I'm seeing all the beauty
In the broken glass
The scars are part of me
Darkness and harmony
My voice without the lies
This is what it sounds like
Why did I cover up
The colors stuck inside my head?
I should've let the jagged edges
Meet the light instead
Show me what's underneath
I'll find your harmony
The song we couldn't write
This is what it sounds like
♪
We're shattering the silence
We're rising, defiant
Shouting in the quiet, "You're not alone"
We listened to the demons
We let them get between us
But none of us are out here on our own
So we were cowards, so we were liars
So we're not heroes, we're still survivors
The dreamers, the fighters
No lying, I'm tired
But dive in the fire
And I'll be right here by your side
♪
We broke into a million pieces
And we can't go back
But now we're seeing all the beauty
In the broken glass
The scars are part of me
Darkness and harmony
My voice without the lies
This is what it sounds like
Why did we cover up the colors
Stuck inside our head?
Get up and let the jagged edges
Meet the light instead
Show me what's underneath
I'll find your harmony
Fearless and undefined
This is what it sounds like
♪
(This is what it sounds like)
(Hey, hey)
(Hey)
(This is what it, this is what it)
This is what it sounds like
We broke into a million pieces
And we can't go back
But now I'm seeing all the beauty
In the broken glass
The scars are part of me
Darkness and harmony
My voice without the lies
This is what it sounds like
Why did we cover up the colors
Stuck inside our head?
Get up and let the jagged edges
Meet the light instead
Show me what's underneath
I'll find your harmony
Fearless and undefined
This is what it sounds like
My voice without the lies
Fearless and undefined
This is what it sounds like
Truth after all this time
Our voices all combined
When darkness meets the light
This is what it sounds like
♪
(Takedown, takedown)
(Takedown- down- down- down)
Huntrix girls to the world
It's a takedown
So sweet, so easy on the eyes
But hideous on the inside
Whole life spreading lies, but you can’t hide
Baby, nice try
I’m ’bout to switch up these vibes
I finally opened my eyes
It’s time to kick you straight back into the night
‘Cause I see your real face and it’s ugly as sin
Time to put you in your place
’Cause you’re rotten within
When your patterns start to show
It makes the hatred wanna grow outta my veins
I don’t think you’re ready for the takedown
Breaking into pieces in the world of pain
’Cause you’re all the same
Yeah, it’s a takedown
A demon with no feelings don’t deserve to live
It’s so obvious
I’ma gear up
And take you down (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
It's a takedown (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
I'ma take it down (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
Take it down
It’s a takedown, I’ma take you out
You break down like, “What?”
And it ain’t gonna stop
Jeongsin-eul nohgo neoljib balgo
Galleul segeonwa
You’ll be begging and crying, all of you dying
Never miss my shot
When your patterns start to show
It makes the hatred wanna grow outta my veins
I don’t think you’re ready for the takedown
Dangdanghage eodum ape dagaseo
Da muneotteuryeo
Yeah, it’s a takedown
A demon with no feelings don’t deserve to live
It’s so obvious
I’ma gear up
And take you down (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
It's a takedown (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
I'ma take it down (Watch me do it, yeah)
Oh, you're the master of illusion
Nareul sogiryeo hajima
Look at all the masses that you're foolin'
But they'll turn on you soon, so how?
How can you sleep or live with yourself?
A broken soul trapped in a nastiest shell
Yeonghoneomneun ni moksumeul geuneureo
And watch you die-ie-ie
(You can try but you can't hide)
It’s a takedown, I’ma take you out
You break down like, “What?”
And it ain’t gonna stop
I'ma cut you up, you'll lose control
Then rip out your heart
You’ll be begging and crying, all of you dying
I’ma gear up
And take you down (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
It's a takedown (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
I'ma take it down (Ooh-oh da-da-da down)
It's a takedown (Watch be do it, yeah)
Take it down
♪