Huh? What are you doing here?
Why aren't you in your own room?
I'm practicing my swimming.
No, I meant diving.
Okay, you keep doing that, Ja-in.
'Cause there's a swimming pool outside.
Mom, let's go swimming.
- Come on, Mom.
- Why do you always want to go swimming?
And I told you not to wear those at home.
They'll make your face ugly.
Outside, not here.
There's a real swimming pool.
Come on, let's go.
Just skip work today. Please?
Get up. You need to go to kindergarten.
Just one more dive.
Dive with me, Mom, please?
You do it. Mom will count.
Count to 30.
All right. One,
two,
three,
four,
five,
six,
seven…
Shin Ja-in. You can't breathe
while you're diving.
I didn't. I was holding my breath
the whole time.
Keep counting. Hurry.
Eight,
nine…
What was that?
Shin Ja-in, you need to take your meds
after breakfast. Don't forget.
Mom might not remember.
Mom. You know that thing you use for work?
Can I draw on it?
Why do you keep drawing on that?
You have lots of sketchbooks.
'Cause if I draw in my sketchbook,
you don't look at it.
What do you mean? Of course I do.
It's on the bed. Go get it.
- Mom!
- Yeah.
The password thing isn't working.
Not again...
Ja-in!
- What will you do about the rain?
- What can I do?
I'll have to take the day off.
Is it raining over there as well?
Yeah, it's pouring down.
- Ah, check the freezer.
- Grandma! Miss you!
- Ja-in, move.
- I left some beef.
- Come over!
- Ja-in...
Use that and the miyeok I left you
to make soup.
I didn't even know it was there.
Miyeokguk sounds good.
Add some water
when you stir-fry the miyeok.
Stop eating junk
and eat some proper meals, okay?
You might be fine now,
but you'll feel it when you're older.
Mom.
I get it. I'm making breakfast.
I'll bring you side dishes
and soup ingredients next week.
Don't skip meals, okay?
You eat so poorly. I should move in…
Mom, okay.
I'm getting another call.
Talk to you later.
All right. Ah, wait. An-na...
Shin Ja-in. Did you leave the tap on
in the bathroom?
No, I didn't go to the bathroom. Why?
- Never mind.
- Mom, look at what I just drew.
What is it?
Mom and me.
Ja-in.
If you're going to draw Mom,
can't you make me look pretty?
How?
Look, here's red, and here's green.
Don't just use black... Ah, that's cold.
Mom, this place really is a swimming pool!
- This is the management office.
- Pool!
- Ja-in, shush.
Due to record-breaking rainfall,
floodwaters have reached
the second floor of buildings 101 to 107
and the third floor
of buildings 108 to 110.
- Residents affected…
- Swim, Mom!
- We can swim at home!
- Ja-in, just a second.
- Why not?
- …Evacuate to the upper floors.
You said you'd play with...
Shin Ja-in! I told you to be quiet!
Elevators are out of service
and cannot be used to evacuate.
You said we'd go swimming!
- Once again…
- Why won't you do as you're told?
- Due to record-breaking rainfall…
- And I told you not to wear this at home!
Stay right here
or you're not getting these back!
…and the third floor
of buildings 108 to 110.
Residents affected…
Hello?
Is this Dr. Gu An-na
from Emotion Engine Dev Team 3?
I'm Son Hee-jo from Security Team 1.
- Is your unit flooded?
- Yes.
I'm almost at the apartment
to pick you up.
- Me?
- The third floor will flood soon.
Evacuate upward as soon as you can.
If you're packing, just leave it.
Don't be scared.
Climb the stairs with Ja-in. I'll find...
Hello?
SHIN JA-IN (JULY, WEEK 2)
Ja-in!
We need to leave now. Come out!
Ja-in, let's go!
We need to go now.
Ja-in, Mom's sorry.
I was just overwhelmed earlier.
Mom's not mad.
Should Mom give you a piggyback?
Hurry up, honey!
Gyu-na, don't cry. We have to hurry.
- Hi.
Excuse me, can we get past?
You can't carry all that
and look after the kids!
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Why can't we go up?
Sorry?
I don't know.
Something's blocking the way up there.
I heard someone collapsed.
Excuse me. Can I get through?
Lord, have mercy on us. Deliver us from…
Hurry!
Honey, be careful! You'll fall over.
PRESENT DAY, SEOUL
Ja-in, are you scared?
I thought it was just water,
but I don't think
it's water I can swim in.
Do you want to sing with Mom as we go up?
Since we were going to play together
today regardless.
All day long.
"Regardless"?
What does "regardless" mean?
"Regardless" means...
Mom, look!
- Help!
- Somebody help!
Please!
Help!
Along the Milky Way in the blue sky
A little white boat drifting by
With a single laurel tree
There sits one tiny hare
No mast upon the boat
No paddle to keep it afloat
Yet still it drifts on
Huh?
Ja-in.
Stay here, okay?
Where are you going?
I'm not going anywhere.
Just taking a quick look.
We're from 407.
Could we please use your bathroom?
- My children need to go. Please let us in!
- Anyone home?
We just need some water
to mix baby formula!
Make way, please.
If you need the bathroom
or some water, please come in.
- Thank you.
- Yes, come in.
- Slowly, please.
- Dr. Gu An-na!
- Yes, this way.
Are you here, Dr. Gu?
Dr. Gu An-na!
Here!
I'm here!
Ja-in, let's go.
Ja-in.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Shin Ja-in!
An-na, are you okay?
- Ja-in!
- Pass me the kid!
He's not breathing.
Ja-in.
Mom!
You must've been so scared.
It's okay.
Thank you so much.
I'm Son Hee-jo. We spoke earlier.
I just need to film this.
July 7th, 7:55 a.m.
I've confirmed the survival
of Lead Researcher Gu and Shin Ja-in.
We're moving out now.
It's done. Let's go.
Come on.
- Mom!
- I'll carry him.
Let me carry him.
- Will you be okay on the stairs?
- I'll be fine.
Here, get on.
Ja-in, are you okay? Done crying?
I thought you left me
and went into that apartment.
Where would I go without you?
Then so much water came in,
and I was scared, and I thought
about what happened ages ago.
Mom, you know.
Back when our car fell in the water, Dad...
Ja-in.
Shall we sing like we did earlier?
No.
I'm not in the mood for singing right now.
All right. Get some rest, then.
We're going to the rooftop.
The company chopper's on its way.
- Is it your first time in a helicopter?
- I noticed the water's salty.
This isn't normal rain, is it?
Three hours ago,
an asteroid hit Antarctica.
All the melted ice is coming north
along with the seawater.
Half of Japan is underwater,
and at this rate,
this 30-story building isn't far behind.
An asteroid collision?
How could they not see this coming?
They did. They just kept quiet
because it couldn't be prevented.
The human race as we know it
will end today.
Wait, hold on.
Are all human beings going to die?
You thought your workplace was
just an AI development lab, didn't you?
Nope.
They say it's your job
to create the new human race.
What? How can I...
There are only two people in the world
who worked on the Emotion Engine
that's used for AI.
Our first choice went missing
early this morning.
That's right, your boss,
Chief Researcher Im Hyeon-mo.
She was swept away
with the child she was raising.
We've concluded that she's dead.
You're number two.
When you get to the temporary shelter,
you'll receive your mission.
Just a second. Wait...
Walk while you talk.
I don't really know that much.
The Emotion Engine we made
was actually just for testing.
If Chief Im isn't there, I can't...
Should I cancel the helicopter?
The other teams are done
with their research.
Human-like bodies,
intelligent, able to reproduce.
All that's left is the Emotion Engine.
Do you understand?
It's all up to you now.
Mom.
Yeah?
I have to poo-poo.
Hold on.
Did you poop?
No. I'm holding it,
but I can't do it anymore.
This wasn't in the plan.
Can he hold it or not?
We don't have much time.
Ja-in, Mom didn't bring
any spare pants for you.
You know what I mean, right?
You have to hold it.
I thought you didn't have pants.
Ja-in, not yet, okay?
Ja-in.
Not yet.
Hold it. Wait.
Yes, it's me.
Fifteenth floor. Fine so far.
The kid needed the bathroom.
Why would I tell her that?
She's cooperating without complaint.
Yes, we'll leave now.
The kid?
He finishes up by himself.
You two should put those on.
Not like they belong to anyone.
So this Emotion Engine,
it contains human feelings?
Human emotions?
Yes.
So, what, it's just like a human?
I don't get it. Why human emotions?
Aren't there better options?
It's the new human race.
Shouldn't it have something new?
What's wrong with human emotions?
When we get up there, it won't be easy
getting on the helicopter.
People will rush at us.
They'll beg and fight to be let on.
They'll push aside their own families
in order to live.
The funny thing is,
you'll be just the same,
pushing past them to get on.
And that's not wrong.
That's just how human emotions work.
That thing you have,
can it make regular calls?
And call me right away
if something happens.
Why did I tell you the third floor
was fine when you were house hunting?
Don't say that.
I'm glad you've evacuated safely, Mom.
Be careful, okay?
An-na. This place is starting to flood.
Listen to me.
Mom and Dad don't matter to you now.
Only Ja-in matters.
- You need to remember that.
- Mom.
What do you mean?
Nothing's going to happen.
The rain will stop soon.
Bring me new side dishes next week.
An-na.
Thank you for everything.
I…
I love you so much.
I know.
Mom.
Me too.
Are you done?
How heartwarming.
You and your mother.
So loving.
That's how human emotions work.
Not that you seem to care.
Yes, well,
I don't even have anyone to call.
Let's go. The water's already reached
the tenth floor.
Get out, now!
Ja-in!
Let's go.
This way.
Put these on.
It's not a big deal.
Climb up and pass the kid to me.
Mom, the fire's really hot.
It's all right, Ja-in. We're going up now.
Hold on tight to Mom, okay?
- Lift him straight up.
- Ja-in.
Ja-in, you go up first
and stay with this man, okay?
- No, I don't want to!
- Mom will be there in a second.
- You go first.
- Mom!
- I don't want to!
- It's just for a moment.
- Mom, no!
- Stay still!
- Ja-in!
- Mom!
Mom!
Mom, no!
An-na!
- An-na, are you all right?
- Mom!
- I'm okay!
- It's okay!
Mom's not going anywhere, Ja-in.
- It's okay. I'll be right there.
- Don't go, Mom!
Wait for me, okay?
Mom…
Hello?
Is there anyone there?
Yes, please open the door.
What's your name?
Lee Ji-su.
Ji-su, I'm going to open this for you.
I'll be right back.
Just wait a second, okay?
Fuck, so much goddamn rain.
Damn, what's this watch worth?
C'mon! We gotta loot the building
before the rain stops.
Fuck, no one will know if we kill someone.
Ji-su!
I'm here, Ji-su!
Open this! Ji-su!
An-na, where are you?
- An-na!
- I'm here.
Where's Ja-in?
Hurry.
Ja-in! It's me. Mom's here.
Does it hurt?
You have his meds, right? Where are they?
I lost them.
Mom, it hurts so much.
Shit. Damn it.
Mom.
Ja-in.
- Just hold on.
- Where are you going?
- To get medicine.
- Don't be ridiculous.
We'll deal with it
after we get on the helicopter. An-na!
You can just revert the kid
to how he was this morning.
To be blunt, you have his data.
You can just recreate him.
We need to go!
He's dying!
Mom.
Ja-in, just hold on, okay?
- Who are you?
- I'm sorry. Excuse me…
Ja-in, hold on.
- I'm sorry. I'm just so desperate.
- What are you looking for?
Ja-in.
Wake up, Ja-in.
Let's drink this, okay? Here.
- I'll hold him.
- Don't touch him!
Here, Ja-in.
Ja-in, open your eyes. Please?
You've got to drink this
to dive with Mom and play with Mom.
Come on, drink.
Ja-in.
Come on.
You want to give Ja-in up?
Is it because of your husband's accident?
Strictly speaking,
I met Ja-in because of our work.
I don't think I'm cut out to be a mother.
Who is cut out to be a mother?
The center has acknowledged
that the Emotion Engine is complete.
We don't have to raise
the kids ourselves anymore.
In a few months' time,
the center will retrieve Ja-in.
And my Yu-jin.
Maybe we should never have created them.
When will they take him?
Mom.
Ja-in.
Mom's here.
I peed. I'm sorry.
Well done.
It's warm, so it's nice.
You okay now?
Yeah. Mom, hug me.
You know, today I fell in the water
and got sick,
but I'm happy because I get to spend
the whole day with you.
I thought it was a temporary lull,
but now the sun's out.
Use this water to wash the rag.
The tap won't work.
Is it over, then?
Yeah. And after all that hassle.
Is Ja-in all right?
Early this morning, the Head of Security
told me about the reassignment.
That I was to fetch you.
There's a temporary shelter
at the stopover point.
We're getting off there,
and you're going
to the final destination alone.
Ja-in can't go. He'll be retrieved.
I didn't mention this earlier, did I?
You thought
I wouldn't come if I knew?
I thought you would, actually.
I'm not that interested
in the new human race.
I came here to see what you'd do
with Ja-in in the end.
It would make sense for you to leave him.
Why did you want to see that?
That's what my so-called mother did
when I was Ja-in's age.
She was crying harder than me
when she said she'd come back,
but she never did.
Kids never forget that kind of thing.
So I thought watching you leave alone
might make me feel slightly better.
"Ah, I'm not the only one
who was abandoned."
"There are others like her."
"That's just what humans are like."
That's what I wanted to be sure of
on the day the world ends.
Some people take comfort in such things.
Damn it.
Let's go.
Ja-in.
- Let's go.
- Mom!
Mom!
I'm sorry. Take care.
Say, "Ah."
- Are you all right?
- Mom!
- Come on.
- I'll carry him.
- Mom!
Mom.
Let's go.
Please, we need help!
What do I do now?
Hey, it's okay.
Help us. Please!
What are you doing? We have to go!
I'm sorry.
Mom, why is that lady sick?
Well,
she's not sick.
She's having a baby.
Were you like that?
Did you hurt as well?
Ja-in.
Mom's a little tired.
Can you come down for a second?
Nuh-uh.
Mom's tired, Ja-in. Come down.
One more flight. Come on.
Let's go.
- What are you doing? We're almost there!
- Why do I have to leave him?
Why can't I just take him with me?
Listen. It's not...
You said I have to go alone. How?
How can I leave him behind?
Mom.
Ja-in.
I'm sorry. Mom's not mad.
Just calm down and think about it.
I found it strange as well.
With Chief Im and her kid dead,
Ja-in's the only one left.
He's crucial
if the center wants to get anything done.
There must be some mistake.
I'm certain.
"July 7th, 8:27 a.m."
"The Darwin Center informs Lead Gu An-na
of the following instructions
prior to her rescue."
"One. The Darwin Center,
an unofficial research institute
under the UN,
will exert every effort
to prevent human extinction
following this disaster."
"Two. Dr. Gu has been appointed
as one of
the 49 special operations researchers."
"She will report immediately
to the temporary research lab
to complete the Emotion Engine."
"Three. Dr. Gu will cooperate fully
with all measures necessary
to fulfill the two objectives above."
That concludes the procedure.
Handing over the appointee.
Good work.
Dr. Gu, effective immediately,
we are taking back the center's property,
the data of Newman-77.
What is this?
Get those off him now!
You said he could come with me.
Tell them to let him go!
You want to know something?
Chief Im didn't drown.
She fled with her kid.
Said she'd rather die today
than abandon her daughter.
You, on the other hand…
I heard you tried to give him up.
Be honest.
You knew this was going to happen.
This is just how human emotions work.
Let's not make this harder.
Say your goodbyes.
Extract it. We're short on time.
Wait.
Are you all insane?
Don't touch him!
I said don't touch him!
I'm going to kill you!
I'll kill every one of you!
Please.
Wait, please.
Please stop.
Please let him live.
Don't kill him.
I'll make the Emotion Engine, I promise.
Please don't do this.
Dr. Gu.
You achieved good results with Ja-in.
That's why we require him
to build another Emotion Engine.
Isn't that what you said yourself?
Please.
Please, I'm begging you. Please.
Or
Just until the temporary shelter.
Let him come with me
until the temporary shelter.
Please.
Did you really think
there'd be a temporary shelter?
Dr. Gu.
The rest of us
will all die here.
You're the only one leaving.
Ja-in.
Your personal items, please.
Security reasons.
Experimental subject data retrieved.
Proceeding to the launch site.
Dr. Gu, this is Lee Hwi-so,
the director of Isabela Lab.
Since you just joined us,
let me repeat the mission briefing.
Within 15 minutes, tens of thousands
of meteorite fragments will fall on Earth.
Most life on Earth
will become extinct as a result.
Thus, to prevent human extinction,
the Darwin Center
launched seven rockets
from sites around the world this morning.
We are now the last survivors of mankind.
One moment.
Humankind must now evolve on its own
to enable its survival
in the aftermath of the Great Flood,
using our knowledge and technology.
Our goal is
a minimum viable human population,
and our team's task is
the creation of "mother and child."
At our destination, Isabela Lab,
we are able to produce
physical human bodies,
but you are the only one,
Dr. Gu, who can replicate human emotions
by completing the Emotion Engine.
Let me tell you
about your mission, Dr. Gu.
Since the child is complete…
You now want me to create the mother?
Do you have a plan?
I'll set the experimental subject
as the mother of a child,
and I'll make the child disappear.
While searching for the child,
the subject will face many obstacles.
If she fails,
she'll go back to the start and try again.
If, after countless repetitions,
she finds the child...
What if she doesn't?
That will mean the extinction of humanity.
Dr. Gu?
This is Beagle 6.
Debris of the asteroids hit our engine.
Likely leaking oxidizer.
Can you report
the status from your visual?
Mom, wake up. Our home is a swimming pool!
Ja-in.
What's happening?
Why is our place like this?
The water came in when you were sleeping.
It kept coming and coming!
Hello?
Is this Dr. Gu An-na
from Emotion Engine Dev Team 3?
Yes. Who is this?
Son Hee-jo from Security Team 1.
I'll be brief since it's an emergency.
How flooded is your home?
- The water's...
- Mom!
Dr. Gu, listen.
You need to evacuate immediately.
- Mom, I had a dream, and I drew it.
- I'm almost there.
- Wanna see, regardless?
- The third floor will flood soon.
Evacuate upward.
- Chief Im was our first choice.
- I sent it to your phone. Look!
She just passed away.
- No time to pack. Leave now.
- I sent it to your phone, Mom.
- Look at my drawing!
- Ja-in, Mom's on the phone!
Dr. Gu? Are you unable to talk right now?
No, it's okay. Go on.
Evacuate upward as soon as possible,
and make sure you bring Ja-in with you.
In a few months' time,
the center will retrieve Ja-in.
And my Yu-jin.
They're our most important assets.
Just raise him until then.
When will they take him?
Hello? Dr. Gu, are you there?
The center is retrieving Ja-in today.
Make sure you...
Shin Ja-in, get up. Come on.
You won't even look at my drawing,
and you won't do anything I want to do...
Shin Ja-in. Look at me.
You need to listen to Mom today.
No drawing or swimming. Not today.
- What about diving?
- No diving either.
Today you have to stay close to Mom.
Don't follow any strangers
that tell you to go with them.
If you're a good boy today,
Mom will go swimming and diving
with you next time. Understand?
Answer me.
You're lying.
What?
Why am I always six years old?
I was six yesterday,
and the day before yesterday,
and the day before that! Why?
What are you talking about?
Come on. Piggyback.
Shush! Stop crying!
- Hi.
- Be quiet!
Excuse me.
Mom said not to cry!
Everyone, did you see?
It happened just as I said.
This is all the will of God.
We must offer up a sacrifice
to be forgiven of our sins!
- Amen!
Hurry up! I said move!
What are you doing? Hurry up!
Get a move on!
Let's go!
Dr. Gu An-na!
Are you here, Dr. Gu An-na?
Ja-in, climb up.
Ja-in!
Shin Ja-in!
Ja-in.
Ja-in!
Are you all right?
God, you scared me.
We spoke on the phone.
I'm Son Hee-jo from Security Team 1.
I just need to film this.
July 7th, 7:55 a.m.
Lead Researcher Gu confirmed alive.
Newman-77 unaccounted for.
Hey, this way.
The helicopter will land on the rooftop.
My son fell in the water.
Wait!
He didn't.
Here.
I took a photo. It seemed off.
I saw a kid going up alone
just after spotting you from over there.
That's him, right?
Ja-in!
Shin Ja-in!
What are you thinking?
You think someone took him?
I told you. I saw him go up by himself.
My son would never just leave me.
Ja-in!
Shin Ja-in!
An-na.
There's no time for this. We have to go.
- Let me go.
- For God's sake.
I told you. We'll find him
and bring him to the rooftop!
Where is he?
Give me that.
I won't say it twice.
Where is my son?
An-na, we'll all die at this rate.
Let's get up there first, okay?
What did you do with him?
What do you mean?
I've never even met the kid!
If we took him,
why would I show you a photo?
We want to find him too, and quickly.
Take my hand.
I said take it!
I thought you wanted them to take him!
Why're you acting like this?
Don't you dare lay a finger on him.
- I'll kill you.
- What?
An-na!
Mom! Don't go!
Mom!
- Mom! Let go of me!
- An-na!
Damn it.
Don't move! I'll come get you!
Is someone in there?
Yes, I'm here.
Wait, is your name Ji-su?
Yes. How did you know?
Never mind, Ji-su.
Hold on, okay?
I'll open this for you.
You don't have to.
These older guys tried earlier
and they couldn't.
No, Ji-su. I'll open it.
Just hold on.
Yes, I'm here.
Ji-su, just hold on.
I'll be right back.
I promise I'll get you out. Just hold on!
Fuck, what the…
It can't be helped.
Let's put these on and return them later.
Everyone must've gone up to the rooftop.
Your grandpa will be there too.
Don't worry.
Huh?
But how did you know
that I was on my way to my grandpa's?
Ji-su.
I have to go look for my son. I lost him.
Be careful.
Ji-su.
I don't even know what I'm saying,
but I'm going to die
soon after I leave this apartment.
If you happen to see a six-year-old boy
about this tall called Shin Ja-in,
could you tell him
that his mom is looking for him?
I heard something when I was trapped.
Some people,
they were asking a kid some questions.
First they asked him where his mom was,
then, "Where do you live?"
and, "Do you know the door code?"
And then? Ji-su, can you remember more?
What kind of people
do you think they were?
I heard them
dragging something on the floor.
Thank you, Ji-su.
I have to go. Take care.
Damn it.
Damn!
Fuck!
Damn it.
Hey, use this.
Hey, that's enough. Let's go.
No, let go.
Fuck, I'm so pissed.
Why'd you freaking stay in here
and make us into robbers?
And why leave the fucking door open?
Why give us hope, you know?
Who are you?
What is it?
Sir!
Sir, are you all right?
Who're you, barging in
on other people's business?
Just move along.
What the fuck's going on?
My son.
What did you do to him?
Let's just go.
An-na!
Did you find the kid?
I'm here! Hurry!
- These guys...
- Lock the door!
- Damn it!
- Shit.
Goddammit.
Freaking hell.
Fuck.
Come here!
You okay?
An-na!
Die already, damn it!
What the hell?
Get a grip, you little shit.
Hey, get up.
Come here!
Damn it!
My arm!
You saw what happened to your friend.
You won't float with a broken arm.
No, it's just that the kid was on his own.
We were just talking to him for fun.
He said he lived on the third floor,
so we let him go.
I don't know where he went. I swear.
Yeah, I believe you.
Some rough kids have shown up
and started looting empty homes.
From the looks of it,
the kid really did vanish on his own.
Any ideas? Someplace he might have gone?
I don't know.
He doesn't do this kind of thing.
- Why would he?
- Goodness.
You were ready to kill me earlier,
but you don't even know why your kid left.
Ja-in, open your eyes. Please?
You've got to drink this
to dive with Mom and play with Mom.
Come on, drink.
Ja-in. Come on.
Ji-su.
I have to go. Take care.
Here. This…
Ma'am.
How did you know about this?
Ji-su, come with me. You can't stay here.
I'm okay now.
I want to stay
with my grandma and grandpa.
This place will be flooded soon.
Come with me.
But, lady,
you wouldn't leave without Ja-in either.
I'm going to stay here.
I'll get Gu An-na there. Don't worry.
They can find the kid right away
once they get here?
Right.
Also,
that temporary shelter.
Where's it located exactly?
Yeah.
I have to go. All right, see you soon.
An-na.
Other members of my team
will soon arrive by boat.
They're good at finding people.
They'll comb the whole building,
so we can head straight up.
It's past time for his medicine.
I have to find him first.
An-na!
What difference does it make
if we find him first, huh?
My team will find him and bring him up!
Tell me, then.
Why would a kid who never leaves his mom
just disappear? There must be a reason!
Be honest. Didn't you say
you weren't sure you could raise him?
An-na.
You keep changing your mind.
Get a grip of yourself.
You know as well as I do
that this is your last day with him.
That's why.
That's why I want to find him. Please.
I've failed to find him every time.
There can't be many units with open doors.
Help me, just this once.
I'll check odd floors, you check even.
You take those stairs. I'll go this way.
Do me this one favor.
Why's she always asking for favors?
We've only just met.
Or have we met before?
I don't know!
We haven't seen a kid like that.
I swear...
Mom. You know that thing you use for work?
Can I draw on it?
Why do you keep drawing on that?
You have lots of sketchbooks.
'Cause if I draw in my sketchbook
you don't look at it.
What do you mean? Of course I do.
Let me.
Along the Milky Way in the blue sky
A little white boat drifting by
With a single laurel tree
There sits one tiny hare
No mast upon the boat
No paddle to keep it afloat
Eun-su!
The water's lukewarm. I hope it's okay.
Our baby's so beautiful.
Yeah, Eun-su.
Recently, I kept dreaming about a tsunami.
It must have been a lucky dream.
Mom, I had a dream, and I drew it.
Wanna see, regardless?
I sent it to your phone, Mom.
Look!
- Look at my drawing!
- Ja-in, Mom's on the phone!
PHOTOS
An-na!
I found him. Hurry!
Why am I always six years old?
I was six yesterday,
and the day before yesterday,
and the day before that! Why?
How long am I going to be six?
Ja-in.
We'll wake you up
on the rooftop once we find Ja-in,
so you can say your goodbyes.
Let's not make this harder.
You…
Won't get on the helicopter.
You died on the rooftop.
Don't you remember?
We've met before.
What?
An-na, what did you just say...
We will take care of this. Please leave.
Move aside. Hey, you over there. Stop.
Please board the helicopter.
Boss's orders.
Hey!
An-na.
An-na...
Shoot!
Shoot, now!
Good job, An-na.
This might hurt a little…
No, actually it hurts a lot.
But bear with it.
Look at me. You with me?
What did you say earlier?
That we've met before?
So…
How many times has this happened?
After I left Ja-in the first time,
he's disappeared every time since.
Thousands of times.
We've had this talk before.
And I think he knew everything
from the beginning.
So that's why he disappeared.
Didn't want his mom to abandon him again.
For a while, I didn't know
this apartment was a trap,
but even after I knew, I still came.
Because from here on, I need your help.
When Ja-in is upset or sulking,
he hides in a closet.
The only unit left with its door open
is on the 30th floor.
He's got to be in there.
The problem is...
Our security team.
Yeah.
I remember now.
The security team is trying to stop me
from finding Ja-in.
Just like how they took him away
in reality.
No matter what I tried,
I couldn't find him.
The security team's all over the building.
Same plan as last time.
No.
Follow me.
Maybe
none of this is any use now.
Even if I manage to find him,
what if he doesn't want to see me?
Target spotted on the 30th floor.
All units, move in.
Why?
You reckon he thinks
his mom abandoned him?
If he's disappeared thousands of times,
it's not because he hates his mom.
He's waiting for you to find him.
His mom abandoned him,
but he doesn't hate her.
He's waiting for you somewhere,
desperately wanting to be found.
That's how I felt.
Go. Just go!
I want to see it.
What you do in the end.
That was why I came here, you know.
A long time ago,
you know how Mom abandoned you?
But Mom kept forgetting. I didn't know.
I didn't know about your drawings…
And I didn't know you were here.
Goodbye, Ja-in.
Mom's sorry…
For abandoning you again.
But
I think I'm going to forget again.
No.
You didn't abandon me, Mom.
You told me to wait.
What?
Back then. Ages ago.
You promised you'd come back.
You said, "Wait for me."
You whispered it.
Ja-in.
See the closet behind Mom?
When you open your eyes,
make sure you hide in there.
Okay? Mom will come find you, I promise.
Wait for me, okay?
Dr. Gu, are you all right?
Let it be me.
The experimental subject.
Send me in with Ja-in.
He'll be waiting for me.
I've informed the other teams of our plan.
As you requested,
both Ja-in's memories and yours
will be extracted
and transmitted to Isabela Lab.
Experimentation will commence
based on the memories transmitted.
If, one day, the experiment is successful,
the new human race will return to Earth.
Ja-in, do you want to swim
over there with Mom?
You start first.
Ja-in, go!
Mom will follow you.
I liked your idea at the briefing earlier.
Creating emotions through experience.
FIVE YEARS AGO
The problem is, it takes too long.
Let's think of another way.
What if we create the baby first?
A real child,
with its own thoughts and emotions.
We could do it in five years.
Ja-in, what's wrong?
Is it your diaper?
Ouch, it's hot!
"Ocean."
"Ocean," Ja-in. Can you say it?
Say it after Mom. "Ocean."
"Ocean."
Hm? Let's try a different one.
Mm! So yummy!
You want to take it off?
Say, "Ah." Kimchi!
You want kimchi?
Here we go. All done, Ja-in.
- All done...
- Mom…
Ja-in.
What did you just say?
Mommy.
- Mommy?
- Mommy.
Mommy.
Hello.
So you're Ja-in.
Whoa!
Ja-in.
Ja-in!
Shall we dive together?
I'll count to 30.
THE GREAT FLOOD
Mom.
Mom, wake up!
Mom. Wake up!
Mom, let's dive. Please?
Do it together, like yesterday.
You do it.
I'll count to 30 for you.
Set, go!
One,
two,
three,
four,
five,
six,
seven,
eight,
nine,
Subtitle translation by: Elizabeth Yoo