[Schreier] Hi, everybody. I’m Jake
Schreier, director of Thunderbolts*.
I’m gonna try to lead us through here
and throw credit to as many people as I can
while we’re watching this.
And, also,
as a snapshot in time,
this is the day the movie comes
out, and I’ve been on a press tour,
and I’m a little tired, so...
I never have much enthusiasm,
energy, but I might have even less.
Anyway, this title sequence
was created by Imaginary Forces.
We talked about
really wanting to do
something that honored
the traditional Marvel flip
that announced that this movie
was gonna be a little bit different.
And they did a great job with that,
of kind of bringing the Void into it,
which we’ll see later.
And here we find Florence,
without whom none of
this movie would work.
Um, what an incredible actress.
Obviously, this stunt
got talked a lot about.
This was something, when
Lee Sung Jin came in, uh,
and did multiple drafts
of the script,
we talked about wanting
to build our own version
of a kind of Bond
or Mission: Impossible opening.
But for our movie, that felt
like more of an emotional stunt,
so it was this idea of finding
a young woman in a place of...
where you might imagine
it was a suicide,
but then actually,
it’s disaffection.
And it was like, "Oh, can we go
to the tallest building in the world?"
And, you know, I said to Florence
in the beginning of this shoot,
"How are you with heights?"
And she was, like, "I love
heights. What are we doing?"
Um... And she just
took this on,
’cause Disney health and safety said no at
least three times, and the whole shoot...
This was one of the... the last
sequence we did in the film, this roof.
Uh, she just
would not let it go.
And just the amount of planning
that went into getting up on that roof
and her embracing actually
stepping off on that descender rig,
I’ve never really seen
anything like it.
We were up there,
every time there’s lightning,
you have to come off of
the roof for half an hour.
Uh, I also want to mention Katie,
the best BASE jumper in the world,
who did the wide shot of that.
Um, that’s Florence doing
her own stunt right there.
Man, there’s too many things
to say with this movie as we go.
This shot, again,
it was this idea of, like,
"Is there a kind of different way we can
approach an opening action sequence?"
You know, our own sort of...
I mean, you know, we can’t
approach the Oldboy hallway fight,
but this is our own version.
This is Sarah, um,
Florence’s wonderful
stunt double, doing this,
and this idea of,
like, could we use it
as a way to thematically put
shadows into the movie early?
Again, if we’re gonna be a bit
of a different sort of action movie,
or an emotional kind
of action movie,
is there a way to establish that
up front and let you know that?
So, Joanna Calo, who... another
one of our wonderful writers,
this is her work here.
[chuckles] Talking to the guard.
She wanted a taped guard
that wasn’t listening to Florence.
Um...
Well, whatever.
You’re useless to me...
[Schreier] Yeah, I just love
Florence’s sort of...
her ability to play that humor and that
disaffection just so kind of quietly. Um...
And, then, yeah,
this was another Sonny add,
the idea of doing a kind of
whole opening monologue
that really delivered to a guard that
you have tied up and a guinea pig.
I think initially, perhaps, it was a
chicken, in one of the early drafts,
and then, yeah,
landed on guinea pig.
But it helps you show, again, even
in her sort of disaffection and loss,
that, like,
she is a caring person.
There are things, especially
this adorable animal,
that she cares about.
Also, if you look closely at that
maze that the guinea pig is in,
Grace Yun, our wonderful
production designer,
you actually find
Yelena’s Void rooms in there.
It’s a little Easter egg,
if you look closely.
Did Valentina send you?
This research is property
of OXE Group.
- You’re gonna tell me I don’t understand.
- You don’t understand.
[Schreier] This is Eric Lange,
an incredible actor
who I’ve worked with
on numerous TV shows,
who was nice enough to come down
to Atlanta and work with us on this.
Um...
You know,
it’s a part probably...
You know, he’s bigger
than this part,
but at the same time,
I just felt, like,
it’s the first person that you see
Florence interacting with in the movie,
so to have someone
of his abilities,
and, you know, he was nice enough
to come down and do a day for us
when he was on another show,
it just was a huge lift
for the film.
Oh, God.
[Schreier] So, yeah,
this was an interesting one,
where we’re trying to do a version of
a kind of disaffected action sequence,
which was tricky ’cause,
you know, it’s a big movie
and you want to have fun
action in it, but at the same time,
we need to sell
this idea of a character
kind of on the edge of caring
about any of this.
And a little bit of a meta
commentary on these films, um,
where, you know, because
she’s disaffected with her job,
she’s going through all the
things that happen all the time,
but at the same time, obviously, that’s
a bit of a wink to how guys, you know...
grunts can never
aim well enough.
And you get to have
a bit of that commentary,
because of her perspective
on her life.
[sighs]
Oh, damn.
I needed that face.
[Schreier] So, this was actually
shot on the exact same day
that we did
the step off the building.
We did a company move
and then, in a oner,
blew up a whole floor
of this building.
Adam is a wonderful special
effects guy in Malaysia. Um...
And, again, the thing I should say
about that, and the opening shot,
is it’s the kind of thing you can only
do if you have an actress like Florence,
where you know that she’s
going to be totally in character,
and when you only get one
take at it, and it is all in one shot,
you have every bit of confidence
that she’s gonna pull it off,
and you always do with her.
And here we have
the wonderful Sebastian Stan,
uh, uncomfortable as he is
as a congressman. Um...
You know, we had to figure out
what is a new path to take Bucky on,
and it was something I
talked to Sebastian a lot about,
and he had a lot of input in.
This idea that, you know,
obviously, in so many of these films,
a lot of his arc has been resolved
in terms of where he overlaps
with what our main characters
are going through.
So is there a new arc
and a new sort of want,
a need or frustration
that we can take him on?
And this idea that he’s trying
to figure out how to help
in a more kind of
conventional way,
and that, obviously through the film,
is gonna become frustrated with that.
The great Wendell Pierce, who I’d spend
every day thanking for coming and doing this.
I’ve just been
such a fan of his for so long.
And then we meet
Julia and Geraldine.
And, uh, obviously, for me to
get to work with a legend like Julia,
someone who I’ve admired for
this long, it was so, so wonderful,
and also just the fact that
she’s such a lovely person
and so committed and
just trying to make it better.
And her notes throughout were the
kind of notes that writers usually give.
She’s so focused on story and
how to make things clearer and better.
It was just an absolute
pleasure to work with her.
- ...of OXE Group?
- Yes.
Although, I have fully divested
in OXE since taking office.
[Schreier] This scene has
been in the movie
in every iteration of drafts
from Eric Pearson’s initial script.
It’s just taken on many forms,
and, you know, the story
kind of shifts over time,
but it always felt like a nice way to kind
of establish the conflict of this movie,
which is always gonna seem,
at first,
potentially smaller than you’re
used to in a big, superhero film,
where it is a little more
ground-bound in a political context.
Um, but we always liked this
idea that we could make a movie
where it wasn’t
from the beginning,
you know, the traditional
evil villain world stakes,
and that there is no
necessary conventional villain.
I mean, you could look at
our main characters as villains
in the right context, in
that, from Val’s perspective,
she’s just sort of frustrated at
having to kind of back-channel
in order to have power,
and this scene is supposed to
kind of establish that,
that she’s under investigation,
under threat,
and therefore needs to get rid
of our main characters.
But, God, would she want
just her own,
uh, you know,
Golden Guardian of Good
that she could stand behind
and just be in control of everything.
That would make things
a lot easier for her.
And there is also, again,
this running meta commentary
that we try to establish here
about this idea that the Avengers
are not in this world anymore,
and that obviously the way
that sets on Bucky
and sets for the audience
is feeling like
we are a ways away
from those films at this point,
and there is this kind of gap left
in the world that people can feel.
- ...this investigation?
- Oh, of course not.
[chuckles]
Shit. We gotta get
all of this outta here...
[Schreier] This is all, uh, a real
set. None of that is extension.
It’s a very large building in Atlanta,
convention center that we shot at.
And that was really something we tried
with Grace Yun, our production designer,
to always find places that...
either that we build all of
or that we find a location that
we can dress and really try--
even if it means,
if we did this onstage,
maybe we could make it
an even bigger warehouse,
but then it would all be in post, and
just that feeling that starts to come in
when everything behind their
heads is real and has real texture, um,
felt like we would get an
overall lift for that in the movie,
and I thought Grace
did such a nice job,
if you actually went to that
place, of what it looked like
to make it feel big and
like it could belong to OXE.
Uh... [chuckles]
Still remember the day
of filming David on blue screen
to put him into
this old footage.
It was fun looking through all
of this old footage to go through.
This obviously... this is another scene
that Sonny really brought to the script,
where, you know, instead of
traditionally opening a movie like this
with a big action scene
to establish the Red Guardian,
it couldn’t be more opposite.
And I also pushed, even though we
probably could’ve built this onstage,
but it’s only one day
that we shot in here,
and to go out on location and
whatever that odd constraint
of being in a small apartment--
You know,
this was shot in Atlanta--
would bring in
this strange feeling of reality
and feeling oddly small
and a little bit sad,
which is where we’re supposed
to find these characters.
And I just thought Sonny did
such a beautiful job here,
and then Joanna pushed it
even further, of, you know,
this idea that they’ve missed
each other over these years.
There-- There’s a loss
that they’re not processing,
and they’re kind
of talking past each other.
That was something that
really came up in rehearsal
that Joanna put in so nicely
of, you know,
Yelena was always kind
of talking in this scene
about not really having a
purpose or a reason to live,
and Alexei is not in a place
to receive that.
Thinks she’s just
talking about work.
Can’t understand why she
wouldn’t want to pursue the glory
that he misses so much.
And it’s such a lovely bit
of acting between these two
of kind of talking past each
other and not being able to connect
in the way that they eventually
will need to in the film, and it really...
You know, I don’t think
we filmed this scene
until maybe five weeks
into production.
And it was at night.
It was raining.
We had to do it in one night, which is
not so hard, but it is more like a TV pace,
where it’s
a four-and-a-half-page scene
that goes a lot
of different places.
And I... I just remember
what a lift it gave us,
even though it is in such a small
place and feels kind of almost dingy.
But to see, you know, really the theme of
what our movie is about established here
with these two great actors
who are really bringing it
and play so well
off each other...
You know,
sometimes on these action--
I think the biggest learning curve for
me making a movie like this was that
the proportion of the shoot is not
equal to the proportion of what you watch.
I love directing action, but you
spend so long on the action sequences
that, you come to
a scene like this,
and it only makes up one day
of your, you know, 72-day shoot.
But in the movie,
it’s such a huge part
of establishing
what the movie is about.
You know, and for Florence right
here, look at this moment where,
what is the point
of any of this,
to kind of allude to
the purposelessness of life,
but not in a way
that feels overwrought.
And that actually
could be missed by Alexei.
I mean, that takes
such deft acting.
And, again, for David here to
not overly lean into the humor of it.
I mean, Red Guardian is
absolutely very funny,
and David is amazing at that,
but he never goes too far
in that direction
so that he can pull back
in the moments like this,
where you really feel his loss and what he’s
missing out on and the things that he misses.
We always talked about Alexei as
sort of doing it for the wrong reasons,
that he was the one that
was gonna assemble this team
’cause he believed
in the idea of teams.
But he’s invested in this sort
of meta idea of superheroes
and forming a team
and to be aware of this.
He can say things like, "Scrappy
antiheroes," like he does later.
But, of course,
what he really needs to learn
is that you’re supposed to
be doing it for the sake of it,
not for the glory,
as he later says.
Um... [chuckles]
This is a small personal note.
These soccer uniforms are based,
uh, on my soccer team growing up,
which is what I pitched as
the basis for Thunderbolts*.
We were called the Colossal
Cleats. I named the team.
We lost every game.
I was the goalie.
Uh... All of that is true.
And Sanja Hays
did an incredible job
of recreating those, uh, reversible
mesh jerseys from my childhood.
It was strange to see.
Reporting for duty.
What’s my next assignment?
Thank you, Ms. Belova.
I was starting to worry.
After this though, I--
[Schreier] This is
an interesting phone call
in that we always weren’t sure
if it was gonna be okay
that our two kind of, you know,
our antagonist and our protagonist
never really meet in person
in the movie.
There used to be versions
where they did, and then it felt like
by getting them together, it was
almost gonna cause too many problems,
where, if Val was able
to search her out,
she would know that, uh, she
wasn’t really in the right place
to do what she needed to do,
and also that Yelena would be too smart
to know what Val was gonna do to her,
so the phone call made sense
as a separation
and also a way to just propel
us into the action with that cut
and use this more
as a kind of montage voice-over
to establish the rules
of the world.
This, uh... A lot of this is CG,
but this is a real helicopter shot
that Jake Morrison, our visual
effects supervisor, did out in Utah.
And then this whole plaza,
this is real, that entire facade.
This whole plaza, the rocks,
Grace built all of this out in Atlanta,
and then, you know, anything
beyond that is extension.
But all of this, they shot
this entirely in-camera,
except, I think, at the very, very edges
there might be some trees painted out.
You’ll have full access.
[Schreier] Probably my favorite
shot in the film coming up right here.
This was one I really
just wanted for the trailer.
I wasn’t even sure we’d use it.
But we actually ended up...
You know, it’s funny.
These little pieces
of her going down to the vault,
these got shot over the course
of the entire shoot,
’cause we didn’t have time
to do it as its own scene,
and the sets were getting built in
different pieces. But I really wanted...
I actually didn’t think we
would end up using all of them,
but there was something nice
about, even though it’s-it’s small,
on a smaller scale
of getting to see each piece
of where eventually our characters
were gonna have to get themselves out of,
and if you don’t show every piece of
that, then you feel disconnected from it.
But you now,
just subconsciously,
have seen every
single one of the places
that we’re later gonna revisit when
they’re stuck down there as a team.
Um, this vault also exists
as an entirely built set.
Those side corridors
aren’t real,
but that entire corridor that she
walks down into this giant vault...
Grace built this
incredible set where, again,
it just means that in this whole
fight, everything behind their heads,
all the texture
that they’re interacting with,
everything that they’re
inside of, that’s all real.
And, again, it means that
it’s a slightly...
Hilariously, given how big it
is, it’s probably a smaller set
than you would ordinarily see
in one of these movies,
’cause usually you would use background
extension to make a larger space,
but then it also wouldn’t have
that same texture of reality,
and that was something that we
tried to prioritize as much as we could.
Okay, so here begins the fight. This
was one of, you know, Eric Pearson’s...
This was in the very first
draft of the script that I read,
this idea of a fight where
everyone is sent to kill each other.
And I thought that was such a great flip
on what you expect maybe this movie to be,
um, where it’s just a team of antiheroes
sent to do bad jobs for the government.
But it became, of course, a very,
very complicated sequence to design
with Heidi Moneymaker, our
wonderful stunt coordinator, uh,
trying to establish the idea that each
of them is going after a different one
was something that took
a lot of stuntvis, they call it,
and in the end, Andrew
Palermo, my DP, and I went in
and sort of shot our own
iPhone version of this fight,
so that each of the shots were
what we were gonna shoot on the day.
And had that all edited,
and we would reedit it
and add pieces and
make it clearer and clearer.
And then on this movie,
this wonderful thing about it
was that we had Harry Yoon
and Angela Catanzaro, our editors,
on set with us
cutting as we went.
So as soon as we would shoot the
shot, we’d go throw it into the edit,
and we’d basically be
cutting on top of the sequence
that we had edited before
as stunt reference.
And then we could see, oh, that works,
but actually we need one more piece here.
I mean, even lines like
this of, "There you are,"
which seems a little silly
for a character to say,
to remind the audience that
that’s Yelena’s target.
All of the little pieces
of it, you know,
I think it was our first
two weeks of shooting.
It felt a little bit
like being under water.
It was a tough sequence
to start out in,
just ’cause, again, these line
pulls and the stunt stuff take so long
that it felt like, okay, when are we
gonna get to the more emotional stuff?
But, also, as we put it together,
it was a great kind of reference
for how this movie was gonna
work and to establish the tone.
And, also, felt a little bit,
in this weird way,
like, we, as a movie, we’re doing
what the characters were doing,
which was, we were starting
in this very contained vault,
and eventually, we’re gonna
work our way out of it,
eventually to Utah,
towards the end of the shoot,
and then Malaysia
at the very end.
So this is where we started
the whole thing.
There’s Bob, just a little hint of
Bob. I don’t know how many...
Maybe on your third viewing,
you’d catch that.
Maybe on the first...
Um, but, again, yeah,
even those shots, okay.
So there’s Ghost, that’s
my target, I have to throw it.
This is, um... Federico D’Alessandro,
one of our main board artists,
who did some of the biggest
sequences in this movie.
He and his wife, Coral,
she edits the animatics.
It’s almost like
watching animated movies.
And yeah, that knife catch
was in one of his early boards,
and we just felt like
we had to pull that off.
And a lot of discussions of the little
camera movements necessary to make that work.
Okay, so, yeah, that’s...
that’s a big moment.
I’ve been asked about this
a lot obviously.
We felt,
coming out of the strike,
when we were, uh, redeveloping the
script and spending more months in it,
we really felt like the movie
was a little bit bloodless.
Um, and in order to establish this
amount of tension that we wanted for it,
it felt like, as sad as it was to
not get to work with Olga more,
that there was a value
in doing an unexpected thing
and having one of our
characters kill another one,
because that’s what
they were all sent there to do.
And to really establish that
as a possibility in this world,
we thought it was worth it
and that it could hang over
the rest of the movie.
And, also,
as far as where to do it,
that if we did it later, the
emotion of that, while powerful,
would step on the Yelena
and Bob relationship,
which was crucial to the movie.
And speaking of Bob, I just
talked over his introduction,
but obviously he will become more
and more important as we go in here.
We now find, uh, Bucky
the spy working the room.
And this benefit,
you know, this is fun,
where, you know, again,
we’re referencing this history.
Given where the movie is gonna end up
and what they’re gonna be announced as,
we felt like it was important to
weave in as much as we could,
these kind of tinges
of Marvel’s own history.
What’s fun about working in a place
like this is that they have those things.
So Grace built that whole "A,"
the Stark "A" in the background,
but a lot of the items that
you see around in this room
come from the actual
Marvel vault.
You know, they’ve lovingly protected
and curated all of these things,
and we could pull them out for a
scene like this to reference that history
of, uh, of the last time the
Avengers had to save New York.
You’re scared because your
investigation of my office came up clean.
Squeaky clean.
Mm-hmm.
[Schreier] I love Wendell
so much in this scene.
There was more to this scene
that is all very funny
and that we would have liked to
keep in, but we really felt like, um,
as we went through
the edits and screenings,
that we needed
to get out of that vault.
Um, you know, obviously we love a lot
of the things that happened down there,
but spending too long
in this section of the movie
and being too contained
within this benefit,
so there was a lot of kind of
editing that went into this section
to streamline things,
even at the expense sometimes
of really good moments.
Um, just to keep the
overall pace moving forward
and not spend too long away
from your perspective characters.
But I do love Sebastian
and Geraldine in this scene,
especially her, uh,
her business card line.
That was something that the
two of them came up with together
that feels like
a really fun kind of...
Again, just trying to establish
Bucky as this fish out of water
trying to do things
a different way,
but it’s not exactly working
as well as he would like it to,
and we need to
kind of feel that frustration,
and then that’ll buy us
the lift of him coming in
on the motorcycle
later in the film.
You say you know
who I am.
So you know my story
and you know I didn’t have
a choice who I worked for.
But you do.
[Schreier]
And Geraldine kind of has
this perspective character
for, you know,
she says later, "I was in high
school when the Avengers came."
You know, establishing her as this
kind of moral perspective on the film
of someone just trying to work in a
job and not trying to do anything evil,
but having a boss that is, you
know, perhaps beyond complicated.
And to navigate those ideas, I
think, is an interesting way in,
especially for younger people
watching the film.
I’m-I’m Bob.
I told you. I’m, uh...
[Schreier] Okay, here’s Lewis
doing his Bob thing.
We know that happens in another
major franchise from a few years ago.
When I first met with Lewis
about doing this part,
he asked, "Does he have to be
named Bob? ’Cause I have done that."
And I was like, "Well, it’s pretty
important to what we’ve done,"
so it was very nice of him
to get past that
and embrace the role in other ways,
and, boy, are we lucky that he did.
This was one of the great joys, you know,
just when we first started rehearsals,
it’s just with this core four that
we spend so long with in the vault.
You know, just how quickly the
chemistry seemed to be there.
And I think Hannah does such amazing
work here as the glue for this group,
and keeping the rhythm and the
pacing up and tying them together.
And then Wyatt, you know, is someone who
I worked with on a show called Lodge 49,
and we’ve been friends
for a long time.
So I knew that there was
this other side of Wyatt
that was deeply affable
and charismatic.
And, I mean, John Walker, obviously,
we’re meant to have some fun with him here,
but knowing that he had that,
even if, you know,
it hadn’t kind of leaned
in that direction, you know,
his work in the MCU
before that,
it felt exciting knowing that
we could get there with him.
And Joanna did such a great job
in these scenes,
establishing this kind of
dynamic between the girls and him,
and this idea of a guy who just refuses
to believe that he’s been thrown away
and left to die, where
they’re more able to process it.
And, again, we’re not, you
know, leaning into that too hard
other than to give him
somewhere to go.
If it’s about, you know, eventually
him having to be honest with himself
about what he’s done and
what’s happened to his family
that’s starting it
in this dishonest place,
you know, it’s not about lying to them
as much as it is about lying to himself.
That-That felt like a really
fun arc to take him on.
I’m not leaving here without
completing my mission.
Valentina gave me a clean slate
guarantee, and I’m not screwing that up.
[Schreier]
And Lewis is so good here.
We have such little
narrative real estate,
that you have to come to
care about this guy very quickly
before we go to the other sides
of the character.
And, you know, he and I did a
lot of work in rehearsal and in prep
and kind of going through the
script, really every weekend,
and we would go line by line
and talk about this idea of Bob
and The Sentry and the Void,
which even in this early phase,
like, which side of the character
each of those lines leans into
and kind of mapping that out
so that later when we get there,
it would be... it would feel
like it had been established.
That’s the sound barrier.
[breathes heavily]
[Schreier] Yeah, again, all
of this... this whole structure,
Eric Pearson had set up so it
really remains from that original draft
of them all being
locked in there
and where it goes
with the fireball.
That they’d be trapped
in a vault,
sent to kill each other
and trapped,
needing to work together
to get out.
And everything that we
talked about in that early phase
was about, you know,
people thrown together
who could not trust each other,
but were going to need to
in order to get out of this.
Holy shit, Bucky.
The assistant, she’s ductile.
Ductile?
Yeah.
[Schreier]
Love Sebastian in this scene.
He’s so excited about his spy work,
and... [chuckles] ...Wendell just...
Again, just this idea of having
characters that can be in this world
where it doesn’t feel like
we’re breaking the fourth wall
or stepping so far
outside of it,
but the character themself
can comment on this idea
of how Bucky has
approached things in the past
and how that’s not the world
that he’s living in now,
and when you have Wendell Pierce
doing it, then... then it really lands.
...then let the system
do its job.
The system that goes on
recess every day at 4:00 p.m.?
We are in a good spot,
I assure you.
My team is putting together a
juicy packet for the next hearing.
[Schreier] I think Joanna
added this "juicy" stuff.
And when Wendell says "juicy" and then we
do it again later, it really... [chuckles]
I think there are
a couple takes
where he said "juicy" twice
just to really lean into it,
but I think we landed on a good,
solid one. Felt like the right place.
...has been completely
sealed off. All right, then.
[Schreier] And, again, yeah,
this idea of, you know,
an assistant who wants
to prove herself to her boss,
but at the same time, is uncertain
about the path that they’re going down,
and Julia just having
no patience for that.
Oh, my God.
[Yelena]
Hey. Job or not...
[Schreier] And this... Okay,
sure, it’s pretty dismissive.
But it feels like, again, this is
honest to who these characters are
at the beginning of our film
where it is just a job,
and this is what they do.
And, you know, Florence
found it very important,
even though her character didn’t
know Antonia directly so well,
but was aware of her story.
You know, wanting to have some
sense of protectiveness over that idea
that’s still honoring
that she’s a character
who is in a dark place
and doing these things.
You don’t know that for sure.
Could be for anything.
Could be for when
they come to pick me up.
[Schreier chuckles]
Again, yeah, this is more
of that dynamic
that Joanna established
between the three that I find so fun.
Okay, it’s an incinerator.
Oh, boy. That is no way to go.
Well, how would you
like to die today, Bob?
- Okay, ghost lady.
- Ava.
Sure. Whatever. Don’t care. We
need to get you through the walls...
[Schreier]
I remember this line.
Look, in these movies, you’re
gonna have to do some exposition.
What?
"They built it just for her.
It’s gotta have
an independent power source."
I remember Wyatt and Florence
trying to pass this line
back and forth to each other
’cause it was hard to say.
Uh... I think Wyatt was like,
"Maybe you could say that,"
and Florence was like, "Nah, I
think you’ve got it. I think you’re good."
And Wyatt did very well
with that in the end.
[breathing heavily]
[Schreier] Again, just trying to
seed the sort of origins of Bob here,
you know, that they don’t pay
quite enough attention to
’cause they’re distracted
with other things.
Move!
[Schreier] But, yeah,
this was sort of the last...
I think the last thing
we filmed in this vault area.
Uh... Getting them out and that
search during the countdown.
And this was such an
important moment in the shoot,
’cause as they go to the door here,
they’re waiting for the countdown.
I remember I went up to Florence,
and, of course, we hadn’t shot it yet,
and I said,
"Just in this moment,
while you’re waiting to see
if the door will open or not,
just think about being on that
building from the beginning of the film
and how you feel, if there’s
anything that you would do
in connecting with that sense
of kind of loss or hopelessness,"
and she thought that was
so interesting, and she did...
I mean, we did the next take,
and it was beautiful.
She did this thing she does
here of closing her eyes,
taking a deep breath,
and perhaps there’s
a form of acceptance,
and then of course
the door opens and she’s out.
But then that became this memetic
idea for the rest of the movie,
so she does that four times, the
deep breath and open her eyes--
at the beginning,
then when she steps
into the Void
and then at
the very end of the film.
But that wasn’t written in
as exactly what would happen.
It was a thing that
she did in this moment
based on that idea
that we then took
and translated
to the rest of the film.
I think this is one of Grace’s
most beautiful sets. Um...
When we talked about doing
the surrealism of the Void,
we really wanted to
try to find a way to...
in sort of a Gondry or Spike
Jonze style, to do it in-camera.
So you can see here that if
you actually pay any attention,
that those are just walls in the
background from the beginning,
but because you’re so focused
on the characters, you don’t.
Those lights in the background
of the red room in the distance,
that’s just painted
on to the wall,
and those are lights behind
the scrim, like, built into the wall.
But you’re so in the moment
that you don’t quite process at first
that this is in fact a sort of
shame room, as we talk about.
And, yeah, I mean, Grace... All of
these are real trees painted black.
There’s black sort of soot
underneath the snow.
And the way Andrew lit it,
I mean, everyone just looks
so beautiful in this scene.
I feel like it’s the first time
our movie really gets to tell you
there’s gonna be more to this,
you know, than what you expected.
This is a different...
a different sort of story,
and there’s something going on
underneath the surface there
and connecting these two
characters, Bob and Yelena.
’Cause, also, we’ll see this
echo, this idea of, "You okay?"
"Yeah, I’m fine," but, of course, the
way he says it, he does not seem fine.
And we’ll revisit that idea
at the very end of the film.
Hey. Didn’t think
you’d come back. Thanks.
I had to. Someone cut
the power to the elevator.
[Schreier]
This is a shot I got in DC.
I wanted to
really go down there.
We had a crew of about four,
getting a few of those exteriors.
Um... And then this scene,
this is back in Atlanta,
but something Andrew was
really committed to in this film
was really trying to never use
green screen or LED,
so this is out on location
in Atlanta at night, in a limo,
I think this is, like,
2:00 in the morning.
And poor Julia and Geraldine, they’d
had a long day of shooting the, um,
the OXE loading-dock scene
before this and a couple other things,
and then had to do this
at the end of the night.
And, I think, really only had
about three takes,
maybe four,
before we got shut down.
And, yeah,
pulled it off beautifully.
But, again, I just think it’s so
nice to have that real texture
of what’s out the windows.
Um... And as the camera
pans around,
like, we’re augmenting
those things a little bit
and putting DC
into the background.
But to start from a place
where the shot has real texture
and then all this in-camera,
I just think that approach really
helped the movie out in so many ways,
and it took such hard work from so many
people on our crew to make that happen.
It’s also the kind of thing
you can only do
when you have actors like this
that you can trust.
Even though we’re gonna
get fewer takes,
they’re gonna nail this stuff
and pull it off.
This is a Sonny idea.
The whole idea of having Alexei
as a limo driver was Sonny’s idea.
And this kind of very
Ocean’s overheard thing here.
Uh, you know, it’s on the edge of
reality, but the lift of how we’ve seen him
and bring him back
into the movie felt worth it.
Less talking to yourself,
more talking to us.
[Schreier] And, again, this is this
very limited narrative real estate
to establish
those different corners of Bob,
that there is this kind of darker, more
inward side that you see for a moment,
but, you know, still very eager to
please when he presents to other people.
He’s really not trying to be a bother,
but there being an inner darkness
and then within that same scene,
also needing to show a little bit more
of the hubristic side that comes out
when Walker is being such a dick to him.
- Choke hold? Nerve pinch?
- No.
I think he’s just a civilian.
If he’s a civilian, he knows too
much. If he’s an agent, he sucks.
Either way, I say we
throw him back into the fire.
[Schreier] This is so good
on Wyatt’s part.
It’s hard sometimes,
’cause sometimes actors
won’t want to play, uh,
"assholes," as Bob calls him here,
but I think Wyatt and I have that trust
and knew where the character was going
and was really willing
to embrace this stuff,
knowing that there would be a
redemptive arc for Walker in the film.
And he plays it
with such subtlety here
where it’s not just
a cartoon asshole.
And here, just a little
glimmer, just a glint in the eyes,
we see, okay, there’s something
a little bit more going on with Bob,
and there is a bit of that hubris
where he’s not afraid of this,
and he’s not just
docile and depressed.
And we’re-- again, we’re trying to
get each of those sides of the character
into the film
with as little room as we have.
This scene, of course,
is crucially important
for establishing that idea of Bob,
but also his connection to Yelena,
and really this idea of them connecting
over this thing that they both feel.
And it’s very hard, um...
You know, it’s a scene
Sonny wrote multiple times,
and then Joanna, I think,
wrote the final version
of how we got this there,
and it was a lot of rehearsal
with Florence and Lewis
to see if we could...
Again, it’s so quick
to get to this idea of feeling,
you know, borderline suicidal
or feeling this idea of the Void,
but we need it.
We need it to happen here
so that she’ll feel
that connection for later.
And so we’ll get these hints of what
eventually allows her to step into the Void.
And this concept of, you know,
that the movie hinges on, of,
"Are we all alone?
Or are we not?"
And, you know, as simple
as an idea as that sounds,
that’s gonna become
the crux of the ending,
and we have to
establish it here.
This was shot at hour
12 of a Friday, I think.
The week that Florence
had come back
from the Oscars on Monday
for Oppenheimer.
We were all so tired
and running out of time.
And I don’t think I knew
until we got into the edit
for sure whether we had it,
but for them to do that, you
know, in just, I think, three takes...
Uh, actually, maybe really two takes
with a close-up on his side was all we had.
And maybe three or four
on her side.
And then getting into the edit,
just really carefully
peeling apart the layers,
and it was there,
you know, that connection,
and it’s so important
to what the film becomes.
Look, we’re all alone.
All of us.
[Schreier] Yeah, so there it
is, that thesis of the movie.
That’s how she views things.
That’s what she’s sort of
come to accept or believes,
and that’s something
that he accepts as well
and why he’s willing
to trust her
is he finds someone
that connects over that,
so they’re kind of connecting over
the idea of an absence of connection.
But, eventually, they’re
gonna have to confront that.
[reading indistinctly]
[Schreier] Okay, so the arm.
This little piece of this, this...
I think we got an additional of showing why
he had to put the arm in the dishwasher.
Um... But, yeah, the arm in the
dishwasher was an Eric Pearson beat
from very, very early on
in the script,
from a totally
different structure,
but, uh, just such a funny
thing to think about for Bucky,
and, I think for our movie,
felt right,
that, you know, we’re trying
to honor, you know,
and live up to a lot of these
great Marvel movies,
but definitely taking a slightly
more irreverent approach,
and it felt like such a
funny beat to get in there.
- ...network.
- [Mel] Mm-hmm.
[Schreier] And, again, here you
have this meta between, you know...
uh, between Bucky
and Mel about, you know,
and Geraldine has talked
about this,
she was in high school
when Avengers came out,
and that’s what she says
in this scene.
And the sense of distance
from that time and how it feels
and how things feel murkier.
You know, Sebastian has
this great line, you know,
"I think we could be
the people that are coming."
You know, that...
You don’t necessarily...
He’s appealing to this idea that
you don’t necessarily imagine
that’s going to be you, but
sometimes in the right circumstance,
that’s who it has to be,
and that’s what Mel
is really grappling with here.
You must really
not know my boss.
We can protect you.
[Schreier] But also, it’s
important for Bucky’s character
to find himself
in this position of saying,
"I don’t do that anymore. I’m
trying to do things in a different way."
And, you know,
Mel really pokes at that.
"Is that coming from
the freshman congressman
who can’t get a bill passed
or the Winter Soldier?"
So really trying to
build up all of this,
even if it feels
like a slow burn for Bucky,
is to buy you that moment where
he comes back on that bike later,
and it feels so triumphant
because he felt the frustration
of trying to do it
a different way.
Okay, so the elevator shaft.
This was one of the earliest
sequences that we talked about
when I was pitching
on the film.
There was
an elevator shaft sequence
that they got up
in a very different way.
And something I talked about
in that first pitch
is that we really wanted in this movie
to feel like these are action scenes
that maybe they could accomplish
if they could work together well,
but they can’t,
so it doesn’t happen,
and needing to
really rely on each other
and trust each other,
or they’re gonna die.
So, I think Brian Chapek,
our executive producer,
had this idea
in that early pitch
about what if
they’re just back-to-back?
And they really, like... They
would fall without each other.
And it’s just... [chuckles]
It’s so funny to think about,
and I think we used
to refer to it as the, uh,
least dynamic action sequence
in Marvel history,
that they’re just crawling up
this thing together.
But it also
gives us a way, you know...
Obviously you want to spend time
building connections with characters,
understanding backstories,
having them share things,
but in this way, you get to do that
as part of, again, a action scene,
used liberally, perhaps,
because, uh, it’s not very active,
but, uh, it is at least part of
an action of where they’re going
where you’re not just pausing
to talk and expose things.
Like, it’s all happening as part of
the trajectory and the journey up.
And, again, this is where we start
to feel we’ve seen all of these things.
We’ve seen her go down
that elevator shaft.
We know each piece of the journey
that they’re gonna have to take up.
That we-- You know, she said "a mile
down" when we look up here at the end.
Maybe we didn’t realize quite exactly
how far that was gonna be for them.
And this, again, is filmed
predominantly practically.
Any of these close-ups. We
built two 64-foot elevator shafts.
The lighting is all real.
Obviously, it’s set extension
when we look at something like that,
but even the foreground
of those shots is real
and an in-camera set
that Grace built, uh,
just so that everything is based
on, uh, real textures and real sets.
Oh, God.
[Mel gasps]
[Schreier]
I love this Joanna line.
"Please don’t gasp at work."
I don’t know where
she came up with that,
but I love it so much.
Um, if you wanna look under
the hood, this is actually...
Later, you’ll see
a helicopter in this film,
and I know it’s a Marvel movie
and we have a lot of resources,
but there are always
budgets to adhere to
and coming out of the strikes,
we had to trim here and there,
so part of the way we did that was
this interior of Val’s special airplane
is actually also just the helicopter
set that we reconfigured for this.
Maybe, uh... Maybe I shouldn’t tell
you guys that, but it’s still filmmaking.
At any level, at some point, you
have to find ways to be creative
and, uh--
and use what you’ve got.
Um... And this, you know, yes,
there’s a lot of exposition here,
but this scene we leaned on a
lot to kind of establish Val’s plan
because it is a sort of unusual
thing for a movie like this
where it’s not that she starts
with a dastardly plan.
She had a plan. It failed.
She’s getting rid of the evidence,
and then, all of a sudden,
when it seems like it might work,
she’s gonna pivot
in the middle of the movie
to try and go on a different
path, and that’s unusual,
but, I thought, interesting
for a character like Val
who’s complicated and gray and
not necessarily your typical villain.
Then the other three
immediately fall.
Shit.
[Bob] Sorry. Yeah,
I guess I didn’t...
I didn’t really think
this far ahead.
Genius plan, Bobby.
Always making things worse.
[Schreier]
"Always making things worse."
Maybe on your sixth viewing,
you notice he says that,
and that connects
to his ending.
I don’t know. I wanted to
leave it in because I liked it.
Uh, so coming up,
this cucumber idea.
This is a Eric Pearson
original,
and there’s a funny story
to this ’cause it’s, uh...
His girlfriend Ashley would
always say "cucumber,"
and then we were
at the premiere,
and I said, "We got
your cucumber thing in there."
She looked at me like she didn’t
understand what I was talking about.
And then I talked to Eric
who said, apparently,
she genuinely believed that
everyone in the Western world
said "cucumber"
to avoid a sneeze
and didn’t realize
it was only her.
She asked her mom,
and her mom didn’t know
what she was talking about,
so, uh...
And then this was a really
great Joanna add here at the end,
to have the, uh, the sneeze
punctuate this action sequence.
[sneezes]
You selfish prick.
[Schreier] So, again, finding
ourselves in these sets that,
you know,
even if it seems small,
just seeing Yelena walk
through this in the beginning,
and now we’re back here again
really trying to understand the space
and understand this world
that we’re grounded in.
And then again it’s this idea
because Bob just came near death
and is angry at Walker, that
puts him into this Void space
where it’s not just anytime you
touch Bob, you go into a Void,
but it’s when he’s at his
darkest, and you connect to that.
Um, and this is another one where
we probably could’ve built the set.
We filmed this on location.
Um, if you want
a very small Easter egg,
that little silver mug on the shelves
over there is a mug from Lodge 49
for the 11 to 15 Lodge fans that
are watching this for me and Wyatt.
Um...
But yeah, just that thought...
You know, this was such a nice...
You know, Sonny had written
a kind of domestic scene,
and Joanna took it further
of just this very small idea
of not watching the kid, uh, because
you’re lost in your own shame.
You know, and this way of
kind of addressing Walker’s past
and this terrible thing
that he’s done,
but not in the expected way
of going back to that moment
or something more active,
but in this sort of...
the way that it reverberates
within his life
and, you know, what he’s gonna
end up losing because of that.
And that was actually Wyatt’s
addition, um, to have Walker have a kid.
’Cause, at first, it was just about
losing that relationship with Olivia,
but he felt like people would
care and invest more deeply,
and I thought that was
a really great add on his part.
And also the first time you kind of see
inside the humanity of that character,
which we’re eventually
gonna connect with much more.
So now we’ve finally connected
all of those spaces back to the front.
Um, again, this whole plaza
was built for real.
It’s obviously extended in CG,
um, but always trying
to combine those elements.
Um, Framestore did a great job
building this whole sequence
folding that CG
in a very integrated way.
...I might just surrender,
probably.
Okay, fine.
Every man for himself.
[Schreier] Uh, this is one of
the more fun conversations
in the film.
Well, let’s see.
[Schreier chuckles] Wyatt
just leans into this so great,
the "Back-to-back-to-back.
Go Bears."
But, of course,
this is our way of getting
the Thunderbolts name
into this movie.
Um, and, again,
that soccer team of mine that--
that never won a game.
Um, but it-it does establish
this nice idea of, you know,
Yelena trying to
push this past away,
but eventually Alexei will
allude to that and show how,
even within that context, that was
a way in which she cared for others.
And this, of course,
is us trying to plant
that sign-twirling
meth chicken... [chuckles]
...if we can get that into the movie
so that you’ll remember it later.
Uh, but, again,
just this idea of a team
that is the last team you would want
to try to break out of anything with.
Um, exceptionally ragtag.
- It will only work if you wait.
- Terrible plan.
[Schreier] This is very small
here, but, uh, "What about me?"
Um, we’re really trying to
establish this idea, again,
of Bob as this d--
You know, duality
between hubris and despair,
but, uh, this is
the sweet version of him.
He wants to help, but it’s
not just that he wants to help
’cause he’s a sweet guy. It’s--
Bob wants to matter.
He wants to mean something.
He wants to be something.
That’s gonna feed, even if it’s
very subtle when you see it there,
that’s gonna feed later
into this idea of The Sentry.
Uh, very, very kind of Chris
Bauer to come and do this for us.
He’s another actor that
I’ve loved for a long time.
Obviously, I love The Wire,
uh, with both him and Wendell.
Um, and Kevin said to us,
you know, I think when we
first had Holt in the script...
He was a little bit more just
a military guy, and he said,
"I always love in,
you know, in Die Hard,
the FBI guys,
there’s a thing with them.
Can you give it anything?"
And Sonny-- It’s a
very Sonny line, this, uh,
"I spend a lot of time
planning for lethal..."
Just, you know, even amidst
all of this tension,
that there’s just a guy
frustrated at the bureaucracy
and the way he would
like to do his job
versus the way
Val is telling him to do it.
George Cottle, uh, Chris
Nolan’s longtime stunt coordinator,
uh, worked on
Spider-Man as well,
was our second unit director
on this along with Paul Hughen,
whose, uh, second unit DP
filmed all of those, uh, laser shots
which are so cool.
Um, and if you want me to
really pull... just... [chuckles]
...remove some of
the magic to this world,
so all of these hallways,
everything inside this building,
that’s the same, uh, kinda... same
hallway set, every one of these.
Grace did a great job
putting these machines into it
and putting things on the back
walls to make it feel different.
But, again, I know it seems hard
to believe on a movie like this,
but you do have to make budget concessions
and find places to tighten your belt
so that you can do some of the other
crazy things like own a whole road in Utah
or be on the top of the second
tallest building in the world in Malaysia.
So it is funny to go through all the
Marvel films and see the hallways.
Y-You always end up in a
hallway somewhere or another.
Um, but this scene which Joanna
wrote is another lovely example.
We have, again, this very
little narrative real estate
to establish
these two characters,
and their connection is
gonna be the crux of the film.
And also this neat little idea
in here where, you know,
Yelena could’ve heard what he’s
talking about and really connected,
but she’s in her own world
and not paying attention
or how she just kind of doesn’t
pick up on what Bob is saying
even though he’s talking
about establishing that past
and the memory loss and the highs
and the lows and what he’s been through.
But still, if we get any hint of
connection between the two of them here,
it’s gonna pay dividends
down the road in this film.
Give me that. Follow me.
I hate to say it, but I think
Walter was right on this one.
[Schreier] I love Lewis’s
little hop there
and then the way
he bounces out of frame.
Small things.
Turn on the lights, Yelena.
[Schreier] Again, same hallway.
[chuckles]
Same sets. And, uh, very hard.
You know, Andrew did
such a beautiful job here.
It’s a tough situation to give
a DP when the lights are off,
but you have to see things and
how you approach lighting that.
Um, Andrew had such a great rapport
with, uh, Chuck and Rafi Sánchez,
uh, our key grip
and our gaffer on this film.
And Andrew and Rafi
really building that together
and did a great job in
a very difficult circumstance.
- Where is he?
- He’s gone.
[Schreier] If I’m allowed to
say this on a commentary track,
I would say, you know, I’m proud
of a lot of the work in this film.
I’m so proud of
everyone else who made it.
Uh, this is not a sequence
that I am the proudest of.
Um, sometimes, you know,
you’re focusing on things,
and I think it ends up working.
I like the concept of it.
This idea of a sequence in which the
action is that Yelena has to protect Bob
while also taking out
a set of guards,
but we just didn’t end up with
quite the amount of time to focus on it
that I was hoping to.
And I think in the end,
like, once the effects are in,
and you add all the smoke,
like, it works out.
And the concept sells,
which is much more important
as to whether
it’s breathtaking or not,
but I think if we’re really
getting into it,
this is a place where I feel like
if I had to do it again, I think...
[swallows] ...maybe we could--
could’ve done it a little better, but...
Sliding into
director brain there.
But I-I think what’s nice
is that throughout post
and with some of the additions
that Base FX added to it
as well as when you have that smoke
in there and the effects on top, it sells.
Also, it’s a lot of ADR lines
to carry you through it.
And then when you
get to this, it’s funny
’cause it’s just such a small
scene in a dingy hallway,
but that kind of brother-sister-
yelling-at-each-other feeling.
The... [inhales deeply]
How-- How frayed this team--
Uh, if it-- if it even is that-- uh, is.
Like, it’s what you’re really
trying to get towards.
...what she was supposed to,
maybe we’ll all get out of here alive.
[Schreier] Another shot that
George got for us. Great overhead.
And, again, this is,
you know, a moment
that maybe isn’t really narratively
important, and we did consider cutting,
but I just thought that since they don’t
confront Val until so late in the movie,
that it was important
to see these characters
who thought that they
were destined for better things
have one moment like a brush
past the person who did this to them
and unable to really, in this
context, do anything about it.
But just to sit
in that moment and feel it.
You never know
with these things.
Pace is important, but I
just felt like that was a beat
that we wanted to keep in the
edit that I tried to keep in till the end.
Get in.
[Schreier] This was a tough
four nights shooting this.
I think it was raining
half the time,
which maybe sometimes you can
see in the background, but, uh... Yeah.
Andrew and Jason Tamez,
our wonderful line producer,
Jeff Okabayashi, our AD, really
pulled me through on this sequence
’cause I started with saying,
"It’s raining. We can’t do it."
And they were like, "We shoot.
If we can shoot, we shoot."
Uh, and over the course
of those four nights,
got all of this
predominantly in-camera.
We’re just extending the skies
and the background.
We didn’t end up adding
anything to this sequence.
There were never any pickups
for it. Like, it all worked in the edit.
And, again, that’s credit to Harry
being there on set for this sequence.
And Angela just cutting
the stuff in as we went,
making sure that it worked,
checking in about what else we needed
so that by the time we got
through those four nights,
we had every piece
of this sequence.
No
[Schreier]
That’s a very funny Joanna add.
Again, Walker’s sort of
self-confidence
and sometimes lack of skills in
the areas that he thinks he’s great at.
Um, but, again,
having planted this earlier
about Bob’s desire to help,
you know, we’re gonna see that
come into play here
where he really wants to be of
use, he wants to be important.
And there’s
a good side to that.
He’s doing
a very selfless thing here.
But also we’ll see
later in the film,
there’s a desire to matter
that, you know,
in the wrong context, if appealed
to, can lead to dangerous things.
And, again, at night.
Middle of the night. Raining.
But, you know, when you’re
on Florence, even if it’s two takes
in a truck that’s making too
much noise and smells like gas,
the emotion on her face,
you know, it sells so much.
- What the hell are you doing?
- This has gone far--
[Schreier] When I first talked
to Julia about the film, she said,
"I wanna punch someone. I wanna
beat someone up in the movie."
Uh, so we got that
in there for her.
I knew there was someplace
we could put it.
Come on. Let’s go.
[Schreier] And, again, seems a
little cold, but that is why he did it,
and in their circumstances, if
he’s dead, as they assume he is,
it’s time to go.
And this is, I think, Andrew’s
favorite shot in the film.
One of my favorites of knowing
Bob was gonna step up into this.
Uh, and really that moment where
you finally... We’ve teased it, you know,
that this guy that you think is the
least valuable member of the team
might actually be the most powerful
and exactly what Val needs for her plan.
And his sort of anger
at being discarded.
Like, seeing these other sides
of him come out
amidst this action sequence,
seeing that he can fly.
You know, it’s--
it’s kind of in our--
in our world,
an origin story for The Sentry.
So it’s always teasing these little
bits of powers and flying up into the sky.
This is another, I’ll just
say it-- I’ll let you in on--
I think Framestore did a
beautiful job on this sequence,
but, uh, in general, I would not
advise putting yourself in a position
where you have no
motivated lighting whatsoever
except the moon
and a full night sky.
Um... See, even when
you have just those lights
that you can see down below,
those shots work better,
but it’s very tough when you’re
putting yourself in a position like this.
Jake Morrison calls it AB, where
it’s just your character against,
uh, you know... We didn’t do blue
screen. We did gray screen for this,
but just against a background
that’s being replaced,
and it’s something that I think we did a
great job of avoiding so much in this movie.
Like that whole wall
behind them there,
that entire building,
40 foot high, that’s real.
Their heads being against that allows you
to do sky extension, and it looks right.
Or having that motivated
lighting on the ground.
That shot is actually real,
out in Utah, of the truck,
but in just a couple
of these shots,
we put ourselves in a situation
where we are reliant on CG.
This looks better
’cause of the lights,
and it looks great,
this explosion.
So, it’s-it’s nothing on...
You know, I think sometimes
visual effects companies
get judged on how things look,
and it has-- it has much more to do
with the concept and execution of
how you gathered those elements
’cause in the right position, Framestore
did incredible work on this sequence,
and it’s more on me to--
to concept things in a way that puts
us in the best chance, uh, to succeed.
This is now out
entirely in Utah.
I mean, the amount of cabling and
lights that Rafi and Andrew had to bring in
for that shot and this whole
sequence was enormous.
And, you know, it’s subtle.
Like, could you do it
on a gray screen
back in Atlanta
and comp this in?
You could,
but we just felt like
this was where we wanted
to put our resources.
We wanted to really have
this film feel like it was out there
as much as possible.
And whether you notice it
or not,
in every moment where you could’ve
gotten away with something else,
over the course of time,
I think that that texture
really gets into the work.
[Ava]
"Golden Guardian of Good."
[Schreier] This was something,
you know, obviously
we love those--
that initial run
of Paul Jenkins and Jae Lee
of The Sentry,
and Kevin was always pushing us
to see if there was a way to get some
of those meta ideas that are
in that comic into the movie.
It’s hard to do. We can’t do the
strange erasing everyone’s memory thing,
or put Sentry
throughout history.
I mean, that would be
an amazing story,
but for obvious reasons,
different things have owned
that corner of the MCU.
But even that, th--
a lot of that stuff
came from our own concept art
for designing The Sentry.
And the idea that they would be
looking at those as marketing materials
that Val would have
for The Sentry
became our way
of getting into that
kind of sense of the meta
in The Sentry creation.
This scene is also just very
important for tying their fates together
and, again, paying off
as they talk about it here,
what happened to Antonia and the
idea that that could be any of them,
and that’s likely where they’re
headed if they don’t find a bond
or a way out of this life.
And then I think Wyatt does
such beautiful work here
of, uh-- of covering, you know,
the story that he’s been telling them
and telling himself.
But you can see underneath,
uh, for a moment,
you know,
he sort of forgets himself
and admits to
how he really feels.
Uh, and we’ll see that
paid off later.
...just keep working
at it every day.
[Schreier] But, yeah, Sonny always felt
we need some kind of campfire scene.
We need a pause here
at the end of all that action
just to bind these characters
together and start building those ties.
And then this... [chuckles]
I think Joanna wrote
the Dr. Phil thing,
and then this whole run here,
this was just Wyatt
and, uh, his true understanding
of Dr. Phil
and whether he’s on air
or not anymore.
I love let-- just letting this
trail off. That’s just for me.
But it does get laughs
in the theater.
Well, it isn’t great.
[Schreier]
This was a tough shot to get.
This is actually
on this mountain in Utah
and so hard to get
the technocrane out there.
And for Grace and her team to
build at least a version of that crater.
That’s a real helicopter.
Uh-- I mean, that,
what you see is CG
laid over an actual helicopter
and an actual box that it’s
tethered to on the ground,
and we did a real airlift
to get this in here.
But, again, you don’t have to,
but, uh, we’re trying to really
kind of put a stake in the ground
that, you know, we were making
this Marvel movie differently.
And really out there. God,
the vistas are just so beautiful.
I mean, Grace really fought
to get us out to Utah
’cause of the rock textures
and the tonality.
The sort of cyan in the shadows
and the more beige textures
as opposed to the reds
in New Mexico which, again,
seems like a... a funny thing to be able
to consider, but if you have the resources,
putting it towards that and really
being out in this incredible vista
at magic hour
with a real helicopter.
This airlift is entirely
in-camera except for, you know...
They don’t make OXE-designed
helicopters, so we’re laying over that,
but the entire rest
of the shot is real.
And this too.
Just another great vista,
and having them actually in
this environment, this texture.
And you really feel like,
you know,
we’ve been, you know, hemmed
in so much with the movie,
and in this, you know,
intentionally contained space
that it’s nice for the movie to
feel like it’s opening up here.
All right, Walker, we get it.
You were in the military.
Five or ten clicks to the
bird. Da-da-da-da-da!
[Schreier] And then this very
funny... This, again, part of the limo.
The Sonny addition of... [chuckles]
...Yelena’s dad showing up
and exactly how you would feel
if you were... [chuckles]
...you know, just with
your friends leaving soccer,
and your dad showed up
in his ridiculous car,
and how embarrassed you’d be,
but to do that in the middle
of an action movie
is a very funny thing
to tie together.
And of course, David just...
[inhales deeply] ...leans into it so hard
and, you know, never shies away
from that and brings every bit of it.
But I love also that you’re
doing that kind of comedy
but with
these beautiful vistas,
and you really feel the texture
of just actually being out there
and shooting that wide shot and
having all of these mesas in the distance.
You know, it’s this weird
intersection of our movie
where it is a very
kind of silly humor sometimes
that is married with visuals that
treat it a little bit more seriously,
and if that works for you, then that is
this kind of tone that we’re going after.
I got this shot myself.
[chuckles]
I was on the tripod,
found this spot down the road.
This is this road that we owned
for this whole sequence.
Uh, and I actually went back
and reshot it ’cause it turned out...
You know,
we waited for magic hour,
and, uh, you actually want those
mesas to be a bit more front lit
so you get the shadows
to show up a little more.
It gives more shape
to the mesas.
I felt like, "Oh, we came all the way
out here and got the timing wrong."
So went back out and got it
one more time before we left Utah.
Um, I have a picture of me and just a
silly little set of baby stick tripod legs,
uh, and a little crew out there
getting the shot, which was fun.
And this whole sequence, I mean, this
was something Andrew really pushed for,
was, again, this is out on the
road in a hundred-degree heat.
The AC in this car
is breaking down.
We had, I think, three red limos.
Or two. I can’t remember now.
They all broke.
Everything broke.
Uh, but they’re in there and, you
know, a lot of the sound we didn’t replace.
I love the sound of kind of
the rig on the...
the shading rig
on top of the car
and the way it rattled
and the noises in this car.
It meant, you know... It means
the actors get fewer takes,
but when you have actors
like this, like David, you know,
we had a long run of road,
and we would stop, give notes
and then keep going
down the road.
But once you turned around, it
took so long to turn this thing around
and to put on
the new camera mounts
that you really had to
get it in that run.
They had four takes each
for each of these setups.
Uh, but, yeah, Andrew was
just committed to this idea
that it’ll just look better
if it’s out there.
It’s hard to do LED
or green screen
for a car this big
and have it feel real.
And, again,
just the texture for the actors
and the way they’re talking and
speaking over that environment.
Just trying to put our resources
into really going out there and doing it.
It was crazy.
I was yelling at the ref.
[Schreier]
Great improv by David here.
Uh... "A girl who pooped."
And this-- this whole...
The Shane and Dmitri
was a Sonny addition.
And the Shane, "He didn’t
have that kind of money,"
that’s a great Sonny add.
What about this Bob you
mentioned? What’s the plan?
[Schreier]
There is also this moment
that I sort of skipped over
in there that’s very important,
where, again, you have such
little real estate where Alexei says,
"The light inside...
Whatever it is..."
Or, "Whatever they are, the
light inside you is brighter."
So we have to establish
in her performance,
and it’s so subtle
on Florence’s part,
that she gives Walker
a little bit of credence.
And, again, there’s nothing to be so
happy about at this point in the movie,
but just that there’s
a little bit of lightness
in the performance
for him to pick up on,
so that you can establish that and
go into that kind of extreme close-up
where you can see that,
where she’s trying to process
that he sees that in her even if she
doesn’t want to admit it about herself.
Those are the kind of things we
talked about in building this scene
as well as all of the comedy.
- Do you understand? You don’t understand.
- I do. You don’t.
[Schreier] I love that read
from David. It’s so childish.
...is going to use the power
of this Sentry Project...
Yes... to take
over and kill us all.
[Schreier] And then here
our action sequence begins.
So we-- we were out there for,
I think, two weeks in Utah.
Um, this sequence, maybe, I think
we shot in seven days, I wanna say.
We didn’t really
have a second unit,
but George was out there
with the splinter unit
down the road
with a camera car.
And at some point, after we
got kind of the actors’ parts of it,
it was just both of us
just shooting action shots,
and he would text me what
he was getting on an iPhone,
and we’d make notes, and
just building this piece by piece.
Again, we had this boarded out. Vinny Dellay,
one of our, uh, great storyboard artists,
we worked on this a lot, uh,
before we went out there,
and it was in the edit.
Uh, and Harry was in a... You
know, there’s no tent out there,
but we were in a kind of camera van
that we had the editing rig built into.
And just each shot,
just cutting it in
over the course
of seven shooting days.
Just building this piece by
piece along with the boards
and, you know,
seeing that it worked.
You know, figuring out what we
needed to add in, but it really...
It’s fun watching back and knowing that
you were there for each of these pieces.
You know, it was-- it was all-- it
was all of us just making this happen.
Okay, not really appropriate.
[Schreier] That, uh-- The pony
thing was a Jon Watts joke suggestion.
He was nice enough
to lend us that one.
Uh, I think-- I think the song
"Pony," I think, was my pick.
It was gonna be that or
Exile, uh, "Kiss You All Over."
Even that shot, we shot for--
I mean the bottle is CG,
but, you know,
tracking in its trajectory,
we threw a real bottle
out of there
that obviously didn’t stay up
as long as that.
But really, you know,
the bullet hits and some things
in the sequence are added,
but almost every single thing
you see in frame is practical.
The dust, you know,
being along these Humvees.
You know... [stammers]
...Jake Morrison, again,
it was that-- that precept
of everything in-camera,
and if it does not-- if nothing
else, it’s incredible reference
so that the CG
has direct reference
of what that thing’s supposed
to look like out there.
But there’s very few shots
with any real major CG in this.
Sometimes it’s the--
the firing or the gun turrets.
Those will get added,
but there’s a ref--
You know, we’re shooting
with a real one on location.
It’s Florence right out of
the window. No rigging.
And that explosion is real.
That flip.
I mean... [chuckles] ...it
was tough getting those flips.
We didn’t have
any backup Humvees.
Again, that was part of being
a little bit more frugal.
So I think that, if I’m not wrong, was
Shane Habberstad’s, uh, Humvee,
and he had to get it of into that
dirt and make sure those tires caught
so that he’d get a proper flip.
And I think this one
is Noon Orsatti.
Incredible stuntman.
Longtime stuntman.
Uh, that one flipped
a little bit easier,
not that it’s easy
to be in that thing.
And then here comes Bucky.
And, again, that’s real dust
blowing across the road.
You know, everything out there,
you’re just in this incredible playground
where it’s really hard, it’s
really hot, but, you know...
I think what was nice about it
is the "hard" goes on screen,
and everything that was difficult about
it is also what makes it breathtaking
and shooting it in full IMAX.
Uh, Joe, what-- Maybe the best,
uh, motorcycle stunt rider in the world
doing all of these. That wide
shot looks like it’s CG. It’s not.
That’s just how fast
he was going on that bike.
Uh, and, yeah, I think this ending
piece was a George suggestion
about using the winch
and shooting that off.
And this, I think,
maybe right here, the flip,
I mean,
that’s not sky replacement.
Uh, it really looked like this
when this-- this Humvee flipped.
It was the last thing we shot out
on that road and got it with a drone.
Uh, all of this
stuff in-camera.
Um, and just to be out there
getting stuff like that
and, you know, being on the edge
of whether you can get it or not,
it’s just such a great feeling.
Oh, sh--
[Schreier] Another one
of my little DC pickups.
We didn’t bring balls and charts
for this, so, uh, I had to bring...
I got, uh, Christmas ornaments...
[chuckles] ...for lighting reference.
And then this was, uh...
This was... This did come
in additional with Wendell,
and we just felt like we
needed to sort of keep the stakes
and the pressure up on Val
in the movie,
and it’s another chance
for Wendell to say, "Juicy,"
so that’s always worth it.
Um, and this is,
you know, again,
when you talk about AB
with effects, you know...
Sure, they’re against gray.
They’re not up on this roof.
But they’re outside, something
Jake Morrison always insisted on,
and we have that real helicopter
behind their heads for enough of it,
so at least you have the
foreground and the mid-ground
if not the background
that gets added,
and even just that little element
helps it sit in much better.
Or choices like this where, you
know, as opposed to building a set,
you know, that’s an actual abandoned
floor in Atlanta with a real city outside
that isn’t New York, but the value of it
being real and then adding some things
out the windows as opposed
to creating it all with a set
and green screen out the windows
is worth it for that sense of texture.
I would love
for this to be my bedroom.
I’ve told Grace this
multiple times.
I love this design of hers. I would
sleep here, in this recovery room.
I would be Bob.
This scene was in many,
many drafts of the script,
and, ultimately, Joanna,
you know, really brought
this really interesting
dynamic to the scene
that I thought was so interesting
of the way that someone like Val
can play upon the sort of
insecurities and desires
of a character like Bob,
who really does just wanna
matter and wants to be important
and wants to
do the right thing,
but, you know, that can
very easily get confused
with the sense of, you know, validation,
or importance, or feeling left out,
and, you know, this idea that that
can really lead you down the wrong path
if you meet up with the wrong
people or if you’re in the wrong hands.
And you know, we see
a little bit of that in Alexei,
and all of them are grappling
with their own versions of that.
But of course,
Bob is so powerful
that you’re really
playing with fire here,
which is what Mel
keeps suggesting to Val,
and Val, of course, thinks that
she always can gain the upper hand,
but she-- she’s not exactly aware
of what she’s dealing with in Bob.
And, you know, just watching
the way they play off of each other
and the way that, kind of,
Val massages him into this.
And I was there
with Joanna on set.
She was there this day,
and I was at the monitor,
and she’s like,
"You’re doing such a good job."
I was like, "Are you...
Are you Valling me right now?"
"Is that what’s happening?"
I said.
And I could see it. She had
written it and she was doing it to me
at the same time.
And so, that was fun to watch.
But yeah, again,
just such subtlety in Lewis
of needing to now portray
some of that darkness in there
along with the desire of this--
you know, seeing this belt,
which is a symbol of meaning
something, of being important,
of being what other people
couldn’t see.
Because Yelena truly
has come to care for him,
even in this limited time,
but it’s in this way that Val
will later describe as pity,
you know, as opposed to
someone seeing him, you know...
Yelena says, "Stay behind me.
I have it. I’ll take care of you."
And Val is coming to him and saying, "You
could be something much more than that."
We actually-- This was part of a--
an additional photography, uh, piece,
where I initially thought because we
were talking about, uh, Bob’s backstory
that you would expect
to go into his past,
and we had a preview
of his addict scene
that Val went into.
In testing, it was nice,
’cause people did understand
the concept of the Void, but they
got very frustrated at that sequence
and said, "Why isn’t it Val’s?
It’s always someone else’s."
And so we got to add
this, uh, really nice scene
that Joanna wrote, you know.
And, I mean it’s just a
testament... I mean, these are...
Uh, Chiara, who plays the
little girl, these are great actors,
’cause a scene like this being dropped
in the melodrama like this is so delicate.
And you have some leeway in a
comic book movie to do that, I think,
to have these
kind of heightened backstories.
I mean, who’s to say?
We had a lot of discussion.
I mean,
Valentina Allegra de Fontaine.
Is that Italian? Is that French?
You know, we went with Italian.
Um, and it gives you
a little bit of that distance.
Um, and, you know,
tries to show you a window
into how Val has become
what she’s become,
which is this idea that, you
know, if it’s a story about isolation
and, you know,
the damage that that can cause,
you know, if Val is just
sort of someone like them,
but who never found anyone
else to lift her out of that place,
she has hardened
into what she has become.
But she’s starting
from a similar place,
that there is
a point of connection
even between your antagonist
and your protagonists,
that they all share.
All right, let’s get the
press here in the morning.
It’s time to show everyone
what I’ve been working on.
Val, you put a serum into
someone like Steve Rogers...
[Schreier] I do think we added
a number of things.
We came back to this scene
’cause it was where we
really needed to establish
that concept of,
you know, that you’re
playing with fire here.
And, you know, that--
Yeah, that Bob and The Sentry,
and it’s about an
internal conflict that he has
that is exacerbated
by the serum
and turned into world stakes and, you
know, superhero levels by the serum.
That-That concept that it
starts with what’s inside of you,
which I think a lot of people
watching will understand implicitly
from watching
a lot of these movies,
but that we maybe needed to
define for more of the audience.
This was a beautiful gas
station in Green River, Utah,
and this is not a set
on the inside,
even though we probably
could’ve done it that way.
But everything that’s outside
those windows were really there.
Uh, and Grace did such a great
job of dressing this, uh, for this scene,
and this scene
was a very complicated one.
And this is towards the end
of our shoot.
It’s one of the last things we
shot with our principals in Utah.
And it needs to do
such heavy lifting
to kinda have all of your characters
get together by the end of it
when they start
on opposite places.
And I thought
what Joanna did...
You know, there are
these little deft turns
in the way that they’re trying
to convince Bucky about Bob,
you know, that they
believe that there’s a threat,
but they themselves
do not see themselves as worthy
of going after it and are
just trying to escape it.
But he doesn’t even believe in
the thing that they’re telling him.
And using this kind of humor of the
repetition of "Bob" to establish that
is such a neat way to get you,
’cause it has to do so much
in such a compressed amount
of time to keep the story moving,
and it was so impressive
how she did that.
I know it’s been hard since
Olivia left you and took your kid,
but still, this is on you.
[Schreier] And this is such a
nice moment of acting between...
between Wyatt
and Florence here.
And we didn’t want to lean
into the music for it.
Just this recognition,
on her part,
that he, of course, is
struggling with the same thing
that she has struggled with,
in his own way,
and that all of that bravado
and bluster is really masking
feeling very similar
to the way that she feels,
and, you know, the way they
share that with just such tiny looks.
When you have actors like this,
you can... you can accomplish a lot,
but, you know, we’re so...
They’re the magic that
makes any of this stuff work,
and I was lucky to have some of
the very best in every single role.
I mean, Project Sentry is not
just a failure. It’s dangerous.
[Schreier]
And, yeah, that’s our movie.
To do that and have that really
nicely observed character moment
and then the kind of near
silliness of this "Bob" repetition.
And, again, if it doesn’t
work for you, I understand.
You know, it’s an--
It’s an interesting tonal
set of things to hold,
but, uh, yeah,
that’s our movie.
[Mel] The press are set
to come tomorrow morning.
Someone has to do something.
Shit. Okay, I have to go.
But come now, please.
Bring anyone.
Everyone you can.
[Schreier] I love this, uh, "How
many times?" from David here.
Bob.
- Bob.
- How many times?
[Schreier] But sometimes,
it gets--
The first "Bob"
gets a big enough laugh,
then you don’t get to hear it,
but you at home,
uh, with just your friends, will
get to-- will get to hear that one.
And then, yeah, this big shift
where Bucky has to take this turn
and bring these folks
along with him,
and needing to establish there’s enough
time pressure that that makes sense.
And then Sebastian
really worked very hard
and essentially
wrote this speech himself
to make it honest
to the way that Bucky speaks
and kind of appealing to the sense of,
you know, shared past and emptiness.
And this really becomes Bucky’s
role in our movie, is he has--
You know, he’s gone through that
therapy in Falcon and Winter Soldier.
He has processed the things,
you know, that they haven’t yet,
and he knows where it leads
if you don’t,
and just that idea of
you have the wrong people,
but no, actually,
you are the right people,
if you can overcome it.
So you can either
do something about it now,
or live with it forever.
[Schreier] I haven’t
mentioned Son Lux yet,
but this beautiful theme,
you know, to their score,
with kind of a hint
of the Thunderbolts* theme
and uniting these characters,
but just played very gently
in the background
where we’re not
leaning into it too much.
And you get room for how
subtle they’re being in that,
and then, of course, uh,
Alexei is not a subtle man.
Yes!
Yeah!
[Schreier] This is a scene that used
to be much longer and was very fun.
Then again, there are a lot of
these parts of the movie where...
There’s very, very few scenes that
were cut whole cloth from the film.
The movie that you’re watching,
you know, is essentially...
Those are the scenes
that we shot,
but we definitely pared
things down for time and pace.
And this used to be a longer
exploration of this kind of idea
about youthful idealism and the way
that power actually functions in the world.
And just for overall time
and needing to spend a little bit
more time with Bob learning his powers,
we did trim this down, but I still
love, uh, what Joanna wrote here
about a bad guy and a worse guy
and nothing else,
and that really is Val’s ethos,
which is not that
she aspires to be a bad guy,
but she just believes that
she sees the truth in the world,
which is that it’s all just a set of
grays and people aspiring for power,
and if that’s
how the world works,
then you wanna be the one
with the most power,
and that’s something that Mel
just hasn’t come to terms with yet.
This was another place
where we wanted to have fun
with the meta of Sentry.
Um, all of those things that
you see in the background there,
um, those are the actual... [chuckles]
...costume pieces and, uh, concepts
for the development
of The Sentry costume,
and it felt like what Val
was doing in our movie
is the same thing Marvel does
so well, which is build superheroes,
and you would need to make
a costume for one,
so we thought it would be fun
to kind of wink at that
by having
the actual development.
Those are-- Russell Bobbitt,
our wonderful prop master,
longtime Marvel prop master,
those are his 3D printers to the side
that he uses to make all of
these props and to form them,
and we tried to just kind of
lean into that connection point
between what the movie was doing
and what Val was doing as a character.
And then really lean into,
again, you know,
there’s still an innocence to
this, of Lewis is not turning evil.
It’s that Bob is having someone
appeal to his importance
in a way that no one else has
maybe ever in his life.
And you see the kind of
excitement of what that could mean
to someone like that
and this idea of the hint in
his eyes at that Sentry side.
I was in this helicopter.
I got that shot. It’s morning.
This was also
a very funny Easter egg of...
That’s a C.C. Rentals truck
that we painted.
When I was in film school, there
was one rental service in New York
that would rent you a truck
to film students
who consistently ding it and
scratch it as much as possible, um...
And when we needed a vehicle
for them to come in on,
I just thought
it would be funny
cause that is who would rent to
them on short notice in New York.
This whole scene, I think this is two
takes of improv in the back of that truck.
And at this point in the shoot,
they had just figured out these
characters so well and their dynamic,
you could just let them go and
you would get great things like that.
You know,
about Walker’s insecurity
and maybe a little hat tip to how
he felt about his, uh, his helmet
in Falcon and Winter Soldier.
But just, yeah,
the interplay felt so nice.
This is actually out on a set.
Th-That was onstage, and this
is, again, never any green screen.
This is out on our 45th Street
set, with a camera mount.
Again,
just two takes of improv.
Sorry. Joanna wrote
a lot of these lines,
but just letting
these two guys go
with each other
to establish this.
...I drive. [chuckles]
I don’t get tired.
No, I mean metaphorically.
I don’t actually want to drive.
[Yelena] Are we there yet?
- Almost!
[inhales, exhales deeply]
Okay. Mr. Soldier,
what is secret plan, huh?
The plan?
[Alexei] Yeah.
[Schreier] Okay,
so this whole set, I mean,
is one of the craziest sets
I’ve ever seen built.
Grace built an entire recreation
of 45th Street in New York,
three stories up,
with this lobby inside.
Some of the background of
the lobby is extended by ILM,
but it all connects,
it all exists.
The overpasses are real.
I mean, I’ve really
never seen anything like it,
and then Chuck built this incredible
rig with silks over the top of that street,
so that you could play it as this
consistently cloudy day the whole time,
and then ILM did a beautiful
job extending that set.
But again, when 60 to 70% of what
you’re looking at is entirely in-camera,
when you extend things
in the background,
you’re giving everyone a much,
much better chance of success.
And it was just such a, you
know... You’re in this weird position
where shooting on location
wouldn’t make any sense,
’cause Avengers Tower
doesn’t exist in New York,
so you’d be adding that, so it
makes sense to have the control,
especially given all the action
that we’re gonna do there.
But then to have
this level of detail,
Michael Hersey,
longtime art director,
who we worked with on Beef, supervised
this over months of building that thing.
And then we just tried to set
as much as we could there
to make it pay off for how
much effort went into it.
How crazy is it to think
of all the monumental fights...
[Schreier] It was really fun when
we got to this part of the shoot.
I think we’d been making this
movie that felt very different
um, and almost felt like
it wasn’t a Marvel movie,
and then I remember getting
to this scene and this sequence
and being in our
remodeled Avengers Tower,
and it felt like, "Okay, no,
it is a Marvel movie."
I mean, this is a villain
face-off with a team of heroes.
Just in our context, with a
little bit of dryness underneath,
but knowing that the movie was
gonna exist in both of those worlds,
that it was gonna
feel different,
but also in the end,
hopefully, if it works,
aspire to live up to the legacy
of the great movies
that this studio has made.
And there was a comfort
being in this scene
and feeling
the familiarity of that.
It’s tropey for sure,
but done in our own style,
and that was always the hope
was to kind of get
to have the fun of those tropes
and what these movies can be
and then also undercut it
a little bit
and hopefully have
all of those things
live in harmony together.
And it was also just fun to get
them together with Julia finally
and have that
interplay with her.
She was so great
with the team in this.
The Santa line, uh,
which was Joanna’s add,
and the way
Alexei plays this, uh...
or the way David plays this
is just so fun.
What?
- Where’s Mel?
- Mel?
Oh, Mel. Yeah.
Uh, Mel is having
a little loyalty issue.
But I’m just so grateful...
[Schreier] And then, we finally
get to our big Sentry reveal,
which, you know, again,
it’s so many different places
that this character needs to go
in so little time,
and leaning into this idea
that it’s not necessarily
the most comfortable fit.
And, you know, I think what’s so
great about having Lewis is that
he has the stature
and he can physically embody
this Golden Guardian of Good,
and at the same time,
bring a level of insecurity
underneath that.
And, God, yeah,
Florence’s face there.
I mean, obviously the most
important part about this scene
is this idea that, you know, if
you’re with Yelena on this journey
and you believe that nothing
really matters at the beginning,
and then you meet this guy
who’s going through a similar thing,
and you form some sense
of connection with him,
and then you feel like you’ve lost
him, but you’re there to rescue him,
to see him
in this other context,
you know, this is what drives her
to the rest of where the story is going
and her true low point,
which is to find
that person that she met
lost to her,
and you know, this sort of
fight for his soul and his purpose
between her and Val
that they’ll play out here.
The fact that she loses it is really
what drives the rest of the story.
Oh, no.
No, I’m not gonna hurt people.
[Schreier] And meanwhile, of
course, we get to hear Val’s plan
and that she does want to be
in charge of everything,
you know, with this, uh-- you know,
the idea that in this world of the MCU,
you can’t really have that without
one of these heroes at your side,
especially in this case, the
most powerful one of all, um...
And I love the way Alexei sort of
engages in that meta, you know.
Thinks the name is cool and is
impressed at the same time as he wishes...
I think all of them,
at some point, wished
that they were standing
in that position.
And now, to see this guy who they,
you know, not dismissed, I mean,
in Walker’s case, perhaps,
in a pretty negative way,
but just not imagining
that this is what he could be.
But to see him
standing opposite in this role
has personal resonance
for each of them
and thinking about
what they didn’t become.
Please, don’t do this.
[Schreier] And, again,
these lines are very delicate
with Lewis, you know,
to make clear
that he doesn’t
want to hurt them,
that if it feels like
a quick turn for the audience,
we understand
where it’s coming from,
and he really just does
wanna be important,
but it’s not that he bears them
any necessary ill will.
But, again, yeah,
that close-up is where
Yelena really realizes
that he’s lost,
and to see
that sinking feeling,
I mean, it’s just so great on
her part in just a little close-up.
Thunderbolts?
[Schreier] And then here we go!
We finally get to see him work.
But the idea here
in this sequence was also
that he hasn’t
trained very much,
so it’s not only establishing
for the audience--
for the Thunderbolts,
what his powers are,
but also for himself to see,
"Oh, I can stop bullets,"
and become more comfortable
as the sequence goes on.
You know, and obviously,
Sentry’s power set is limitless,
so if the sequence went on
further, if he had more people to fight,
we could go even further,
but it felt like we could contain it
to a level that still
fit within our movie,
where obviously we’re stepping
outside of the fully practical thing now.
There’s more CG in this.
But we’ve been
yearning for that.
We wanna see.
This is where it becomes more
of a superhero movie,
if we’ve been
something different.
You wanna see
what The Sentry can do
that we thought
still balanced with...
This is shot with a lot
of our first unit as a oner,
with a motion control rig
and a TechnoDolly.
And then there’s CG
in between, obviously,
’cause he’s doing things
that humans can’t do,
but it is real performance
amidst all of that.
And still feels, within that
context, like our movie,
but expanding into that more kind
of traditional superhero territory.
This is also a shot
with a lot of design from Rico,
our board artist
who I mentioned before,
who does such great stuff
with action like this.
And you land again, just
continuing to lock in on Yelena
and how she feels
about losing Bob,
and then playing into this very
kind of, you know, Bucky’s moment,
where in a normal movie
you might expect...
You know, we want this
to be Bucky’s moment.
We want him to succeed here,
but really, you know, it’s interesting.
Unlike normal fights
in normal movies,
these are kind of
overall scene arcs
where they have all wins
downstairs with the guards
and then all losses in this
sequence to bring them to a low point.
They get nothing in on Sentry.
And that’s when
you really feel it.
It’s pretty rough
having your arm
tossed towards you
after being knocked
unconscious with it.
[Valentina] I’m so glad you were able
to catch a glimpse before your, uh...
retirement.
[Schreier] This is gonna
sound very silly,
but there is a children’s book called
Cookie Monster and The Cookie Tree,
um, which involves a witch
and a magic cookie tree
that she puts a spell on so that it won’t
share any cookies with Cookie Monster,
but then it won’t share
any cookies with her
’cause it only gives cookies
to people who share.
That was her spell, and she’s
sort of hoisted by her own petard.
And I would think about that a lot
when thinking about Val in this moment.
I think I even gave
Julia that book.
And she laughed and said,
"You’re very strange, you know that?"
And she’s not wrong.
Okay.
Hannah told me
this is an actual moment
where she forgot to give
Sebastian his arm back
and then had to remember it.
And we kept that in,
which was fun.
In this scene,
which Joanna wrote,
I just thought
it’s an interesting one
where I was worried about
having Yelena go this far.
I was worried that the audience would
lose touch with her if she was this harsh.
I mean, it’s obviously
the point of the scene
is to bring your characters
to a low point
and have your protagonists,
you know--
because she feels
those bonds broken--
tear apart the team.
But how far she went,
I think I, you know--
my mistake was cautious
in how far we would let her go, and
everyone else really spoke up for...
Joanna spoke up for, and the actors
spoke up for the idea that it was...
Not only was it okay
to go there,
but it was important
to go to this place.
And it really added
so much to this scene.
[scoffs] See?
Slow down. Um-nichka.
Alexei,
I am not your um-nichka.
I haven’t heard from you
or seen you in a year.
[Schreier] And here we start
to delve more into that thing
that’ll become the crux of the next
scene, of how they’re processing...
Again, you may just know it
in this movie as Yelena’s sister,
but obviously,
if you’ve seen these films,
you know, hinting at
this sense of loss
after Natasha is gone
and how they’re processing it.
Yelena!
[Schreier] Meanwhile,
back in the tower,
not going so great.
And, again, it’s a tricky
balance, you know.
I mean, when you have
Julia Louis-Dreyfus,
you want to
lean into this humor,
but I felt like we never
pushed it too far
to come at the expense of the
stakes that are starting to emerge.
But again, Lewis has
such little real estate here
to play this more
sort of, you know, manic side
of the duality
of this sense of hubris
and the way it’s frustrating
to feel limited in that.
And this is the side
Val didn’t get to see
before she put him
into this position,
because she’s so rushed and
trying to get out of her circumstances.
But, you know, again, Lewis is
doing so much here with so little time
to show that it’s not just
a sort of traditional
villain drunk on power, but
someone who wanted to matter
but is also uncomfortable
with that position,
and again, we were always
trying to get at this idea,
based on a friend of mine,
of the hubristic side
actually bringing about
the self-destructive side
and that sense of despair.
And this was something that we really
drilled in on in this moment of the scene,
to show that hubris
but in an unstable sort of way,
which I thought
he did so beautifully.
[grunts]
You were gonna turn on me...
[Schreier] And this idea of feeling
like everyone always abandons him,
which is something that’s true,
or doesn’t see him this way,
or is willing to
cast him aside,
which has been true
his whole life,
which he now sees in her,
which brings about this darker side,
so that when he is
killed by Mel,
we then transfer him to that
Void side of The Sentry character.
And this is sort of completing
Mel’s arc of deciding,
"Okay, between the two, I
would rather not be on the outside.
Even if there are
compromises to it,
I would rather
be closer to power."
I want a raise.
[Valentina] Okay, fine.
Get cleanup on the body.
And tell Holt it’s finally time
to go lethal on these losers.
[Schreier] This took a
lot of development here
of how to turn Sentry dark,
you know,
and how to kind of do a version of
creating this character of the Void.
This is ILM’s work of kind of
drawing the shadows to him
to establish
the beginning of that.
And adding that eye flip.
[Alexei] Yelena!
[Schreier]
And this is probably...
well, one of my favorite scenes
in the movie for sure.
This is another scene
that Sonny really wrote,
paired with that scene in Alexei’s
apartment from the beginning.
And, you know, really
trying to push this movie
to a different corner
than you might expect
for a young woman who’s
really going through something.
Uh...
And I think this was always
one of my favorite scenes
from the moment I read it.
I don’t think we shot it
till about eight weeks in,
and I think we had
half a day for it, um...
But you just were so excited, knowing
how good David and Florence are together
and were gonna be.
And I remember
there actually...
Yeah, there was
a lightning storm that day.
We had to wait on stuff.
There was this tension
of just wanting
to see this scene happen.
And I think after
the first take on her,
David turned to me
and he was like,
"I mean, that’s it.
I don’t know that
you’re gonna get
any better than that."
And we did more takes,
of course,
but they were just so ready
to perform this, um,
and I don’t know,
there are just times when,
you know,
I care a lot about camerawork,
but in a scene like this,
sometimes you wanna just be
as simple as you possibly can.
And it’s just two lens sizes,
you know, one at a time,
so you’re on the eyeline on each
of them, and you just let them go.
There’s a wide shot
to lead you into it,
but there’s no
fancy camerawork.
We’re not pushing in.
The last thing you wanna do
is get in the way
of performances like that.
There are times
to do fancy things
and there are times
to just let it go.
My first...
[Schreier] And it’s
interesting, you edit this movie,
and you watch this stuff
over and over.
I remember the first time
I saw this in the assembly,
and, you know, I choked up a little
bit just ’cause of that performance.
And it’s hard to remember that
that’s a thing that’s out there for you
as you edit it
over and over again.
When you see it with an
audience again for the first time,
you can feel it in the room.
Maybe not for everyone,
but certainly for me, I think,
just, again, as someone
who appreciates great acting.
You know, to be able
to be in this movie
and with the scale and scope of
everything that’s going on around you,
but to get to this place that
feels so small and relatable
and how much she commits to it.
I mean, you don’t really...
This is the thing
about making these movies.
You’re on so much stuff,
and you’re doing all the action
and all these things,
but the movie only works if this
thing that you get in half a day
with two setups,
with two actors, if it sings.
And, you know, the...
I mean, she’s actual magic.
I mean, if you ever get a chance
to work with her, you should take it.
And David, you know,
to do that performance,
to be as big and as funny
as Alexei can be
but bring it in the way
that he does in this scene,
I mean, I’m just so in awe
of both of them.
This scene actually used to, and I
think you see it in some of the posters--
used to end in a hug,
and the hug was beautiful.
I loved that moment.
But we actually felt like she
was arcing a little bit too soon,
like we were letting her learn too
clearly the message in the movie too early,
and we needed to leave room
for it to go,
so we cut around that
and had him look up here
and moved around the hug
before she can entirely process
what she’s learned here.
Little Easter egg, some posters for bands
I’ve done music videos for on the wall:
Haim, and Francis and the
Lights, that I was in for a bit,
and Cashmere Cat.
I think also that perfume ad
on the bus station behind it
we made Watts Perfume,
in Jon’s honor.
And now the movie gets a little
bit bigger and we get the scope.
And this is... Obviously,
there’s a lot of CG going on here.
ILM did such beautiful work
building New York City
and also just the design
of what the Void looks like,
which, you know,
Kevin encouraged us to make...
He asked if there was any photographic,
in-camera way we could do it,
which there wasn’t really,
but embracing that concept,
just trying to make it
as simple as it could be,
where we did shoot Lewis
and then it is sort of...
You know, it’s not
an overall mask on him,
but it is kind of
these adjustable, like...
just allowing a little bit
of light in certain parts
and turning the rest into
a nearly 2D silhouette.
And then the eyes
are not animated.
I mean, those come from
his actual eye movements,
and it really doesn’t work
if they stay on the whole time.
It starts to feel a little bit
like Terminator,
like they come from
the specular highlights,
you know, in his eye light
that they animated.
And then, of course,
these shadows...
Grace brought in
a ton of references for these,
a lot of, like,
the way burns spread.
We went to that.
And, again, just trying to figure
out, like, what’s something simpler?
You know, when you work
on effects... This is not simple.
This is incredible
CGI work from ILM.
There’s no other way
to do this.
But when it comes
to the shadows, you know,
we would get wedges--
and some of that
shadow development
happened with Framestore
and Rising Sun Pictures as well--
of, "Here’s six ways we could
do it. Here’s the simplest."
And we would often say,
"Actually, start from the simplest,
and then do a wedge of six
ways even simpler than that."
You know, that we really
didn’t want this to feel like CG,
even if we were using some of the
best CG companies in the world to do it.
We wanted it to have
a bit of a different texture.
This sequence... You know
what I think is funny about this
is Kevin actually asked,
"Do we have to do another
crane falling? We do that so much."
I mean, he kept pushing me
more than I even expected
to try to do things differently,
and I stood up for that one.
I wanted the crane falling. I felt like
the trailers were gonna need that scope,
and really
this entire sequence...
You know, Alexei references it
in the beginning, you know,
saving civilians
in the streets, you know,
it’s this kind of
time-honored thing.
And even if there is a little bit of, you
know, near hokeyness to some of it,
you know, especially
when they’re lifting the slab,
it all exists because
this is a thing they can solve,
and then there’s going to be
a problem that they can’t,
so I used to talk about how all of
this money and all of this shooting time
and all of the CG
was really only going into it
for that one moment of
the little girl getting voided,
which we’re gonna come to
in a moment
and is maybe my favorite moment
to watch in the theater of this film.
But, again, so much more of this than you
would think was in-camera, like this slab.
Dan Sudick and his special effects
team built an actual cement slab
that was on a hoist
that we filmed for this.
This shot is in-camera,
everything that they’re lifting up.
That is an actual, gigantically
heavy slab that they’re lifting.
And, sure, okay,
what is Ghost really gonna do?
What is Yelena gonna do?
They’re not super soldiers.
But we just struggled to come up
with an image that would work as well
for establishing them finally
coming together as a team
in that very classic hero way
before we undercut that.
This came from Phil Langone
boards for this sequence,
and we were never
able to beat it.
So that’s an actual fall.
All that dust is real.
We put a little too much dust
on the thing,
and then we went with it
as a transition.
[crowd applauding]
[Schreier] And this moment was
very important, as Kevin pointed out--
Yeah, Alexei soaking it up,
what he wanted--
of Val processing her idea for what
she’s gonna do at the end of the film.
[child] Mom?
[Schreier] And here we
go. Here’s our little girl.
So edging on cheese, saving the
most classic little girl in the street,
which is all, again, this entire
sequence is just building up
to get this moment to land, which it
didn’t in our earliest test screenings.
We didn’t get the gasp
that we now get in theaters,
which I think really had to
fine-tune the music with Son Lux,
of building up to
this borderline cheesy moment
before it’s undercut
and then we finally start to...
Maybe it’s also just getting
all the VFX finished
and buying into that sequence.
But now you get to see more of
that shadow spread that ILM built.
You know, and there’s a lot of
nice texture in those shadows.
It is a very simple effect
with no flash.
It’s a one-and-a-half frame animation
from being upright to becoming a shadow,
and anything more than that, you
started to feel the CG creep into it,
so it really took
some confidence to feel...
It feels a little exposed
to do such a simple...
It’s almost just a cut
to them being gone.
But, you know,
it just felt like
a different way
to approach this.
And it’s nice to see how
effective that is in theaters.
And this is one of my
favorite moments in the film.
You know, really Yelena processing
that, and maybe that little feeling inside,
that is she drawn
to that same thing
she was drawn to
in the beginning?
Is this it for her?
You know, is she not along for this
ride given what she’s gone through?
But also she’s had
that experience with Alexei,
and, of course,
really what’s happening is
she understands maybe
even a little bit of guilt
for having expressed this idea
to Bob of "We’re all alone" to him
that he’s now processing and knowing
that she needs to take a leap of faith,
and again, that same memetic,
eyes closed, breath in and step.
And we matched that frame.
I mean, it’s not exact,
but we actually had to shoot
on a different side
of the building in Malaysia
to match the angle that she’s
stepping into the shadow here,
so it’s meant to truly mirror that
image of her stepping off the building
at the beginning of the film.
And now we’re back in
one of my favorite sets.
[Anya] Yelena!
[Schreier] And this is where we really
come to understand the idea of the Void
and these loops, ’cause we
haven’t looped these things before,
and I think
we kept adding to that,
I felt like, in the edit,
as we were cutting it on set.
You would need
to do three of these
to really understand
the looping nature of this.
Something Kevin thought was
very important, which was nice,
is that she’s calling out to Bob
so there’s an urgency to this,
like she’s in here to find him
but then is also almost unable to
look away from her prior shame.
And again, that wall’s just been
there the whole time, and this is a very...
You know, again,
sometimes you feel exposed
and you’re, like,
everyone’s just gonna notice,
but I think most people don’t
until this moment
when she hits it
and you see the loop extend,
which then draws her back in,
attempting to stop this from happening.
But of course,
the sort of rule of the Void,
you know, that we learned
through the course of making this
is that you cannot
interfere with it.
That only through some sort of acceptance
and distance can you get out of this loop.
As she tries to fight it,
it makes it even worse,
and the Void fights back
against her.
This is the "sentient tree" that
Sonny added, we used to call it.
Looked a little silly on set, but
Florence really sold that thing,
and then the little additions
in post made it work.
[speaking Russian]
[Schreier]
These kids are so good.
Uh...
Alexa plays Anya,
and of course, Violet McGraw who played
a young Yelena Belova in Black Widow
is back to play
Young Yelena here,
and they both did
just such a great job.
Bob?
[Schreier] These scenes, that
scene of Yelena’s childhood
and having a friend killed,
that was a Sonny addition
as well as this scene,
and going through
to the bathroom in the attic,
all the details
of that sequence
were something he really
brought to the movie
in such a beautiful way.
He really felt it was important
that this not just be about trauma
but focusing more on a sense of
shame and one’s own culpability
for the darkness
that one finds oneself in.
And I thought that was
such an interesting distinction,
so that you see each of that
in these scenes, you know,
that it’s not just
a terrible memory
but one’s own culpability
within it.
Florence is just so good here
playing both sides of herself, you know.
And this is in a very recent
dark place she felt.
Incredible VFX work here.
You know, we didn’t do
motion control for any of this,
but just filmed
Florence with the double
and filmed both sides of it,
got it as close as we could,
and then used face replacement
and compositing
to bring those
two shots together.
And then, again, it’s just an
editing transition of the loop.
And this is where I think you
really start to feel the weight
of there being no way out
of here if you try to disturb it.
This scene was a later add
and a Kevin idea
about wanting to find...
to track our heroes on their journey
into this Void after her and showing...
It’s nice to see some of--
despite the last time
we saw them together--
Ava’s faith in Yelena’s
decision to go in
and the idea that
that would be worth following.
And of course,
Alexei in his sadness,
is grateful for any idea that
he might be able to find her.
And here we find where
she just says, "Enough,"
and it’s a simple thing,
but it just means she’s
not gonna fight it anymore,
and in not fighting it,
that brings her closer to Bob.
This was actually all built...
So that wall with that mirror,
we built onto the attic set.
This is all in-camera. There’s
no compositing in those mirrors.
And these sets are built
just for that shot.
Obviously here, we’re in
the normal bathroom set.
But as we begin
this transition...
You know, after she says,
"What we talked about in the vault,"
this is all in-camera,
where the lights go down here
and we pan her through.
And it’s just two joined sets
that brings her into the attic
and to the center of the Void
because he’s allowed her in.
And then, of course, we establish
now that’s not there anymore.
But, again, just very, very
simple editing tricks for this.
It felt like, in a funny way, by
doing smaller, simpler things,
that was the way to take things in a
newer, different direction for Marvel
and honor that instruction
from Kevin to make it different.
And then, you know, when you
have an actress like Florence,
when you can establish, uh,
with humor, what this is,
these interconnected
shame rooms,
but even amidst
all this darkness,
that always gets a laugh
in the theater.
Some beautiful sound work
here too from Paul Hsu.
Skywalker did the sound for this
movie and did an incredible job.
Paul is someone I’ve known
since my first movie, Robot & Frank,
where, you know, we tried to
design the sound of the Void.
And we tried a lot of things and this idea
of voices poking in from the other rooms,
which was too much
of a cacophony,
but it ended up
this very simple thing he built
where building this infinity
reverb tail on the lines of the Void,
processing that
and then doing a detune on that
and mixing that in so there’s this
constant spooky, detuned reverb wash
that is built on the lines
that are being said above it.
So yeah, this was a beautiful
scene that Sonny wrote.
Then what’s happening
down below,
Joanna wrote beautifully,
this sense of...
You know, there’s so much
to establish in this moment
of Bob trying to be the hero,
which his dad alludes to,
and protect his mother.
But then the heartbreak
comes from his mother saying,
"In doing that,
you only made it worse."
And in such a few
amount of lines
to establish both sides
of that duality
of Bob’s desire for heroism
and his sense that, in fact,
that aspiration is what
brought about the worst thing,
to have all of those things
in such a tiny scene
to establish The Sentry side
and the Void side,
I thought that was such
beautiful writing on her part.
And this scene...
We filmed this, I think,
in the third week of filming,
and I was so excited to have
these two actors and do this scene
and have it build
to this conversation.
But it’s one of those things
where I think all of us
would say if we were asked,
I don’t know that any of us felt for
sure that we had it when we left set,
and it was only really
when we got in the edit
where I was able
to find those moments,
and it’s like,
"Oh, no, it was there."
But it’s a risky thing
to build a movie like this
up to a conversation
with no movement in an attic.
And just her
sense of confidence
and how nuanced and small
her performance is,
and just that moment of Lewis
being unable to hold her gaze.
And then this idea
that things are shaking
because he’s beginning
to be won over
and that he thinks
he might leave,
that’s when the Void begins to
fight him, that it begins to wake up.
And the other side of himself is
gonna fight them to not let them out.
And so much of this
was done practically.
There’s a bunch of excellent CG
in here from Framestore, but this...
I’m one shot early, but this
footstool that flies at them,
these were all Pyrocell pieces
that Dan Sudick and his team built
that are actually
flying at them
and look like they have weight.
This is an actual
guy in the wall...
Just trying to really honor
that kind of handmade sense
of how some of these
more horror ideas were done.
And the papers that are
flying around are real,
but then, yeah, we do have
some added CG pieces,
but again, that idea that if
you get enough of it in-camera,
you’re putting yourself
in such a position of success.
I mean, even the way
this curtain strangles them,
that almost is
an in-camera edit,
you know, that we add
a little bit of CG to.
Again, you’re just dependent
on these incredible actors
being able to sell that a magic
evil curtain is strangling them.
But when it’s these actors and
when they built up to that moment,
you go with it, you buy it.
And then we get our...
[chuckles]
Maybe the strangest
triumphant save
in one of these movies
where you’re...
breaking furniture
and ripping apart a pillow.
But, you know, within the
context of what we’ve established,
we were always a little... wondering
if people would go with this.
But then when you get
to Bucky’s line and he says,
"It’s okay. I have a great
past so I’m totally fine,"
that’s one of the biggest
laughs that we get in the movie,
and you would only get that
laugh if people were with you
on that journey of understanding
what it means to go through this Void.
And believe me, in another
version of this movie,
I would’ve loved to see
inside all of their Void rooms.
And there were different drafts of
the script where we tried to do that.
But in the end, it felt like going
through Bob’s was the most important
as far as how to
get out of here.
Okay, okay. Just h-how
do we get out of here?
I mean, as far as I know,
it’s just endless rooms.
[Schreier] From this point on, this was
really something that Joanna pushed for,
which was the idea
of getting back to a big bad
and finding the worst room and
finding the Void at the heart of this thing
and needing to confront him.
And then this is about
establishing the external stakes
if they don’t solve this.
And, you know, I thought, at first we
had kind of ominous music over this,
but in the end it felt more
spooky to just let it play.
That’s actually my old commercial
production company office
in New York, Park Pictures.
They were nice enough
to let us shoot there
when I did all the New York
aerials and exteriors.
Um, and then we find ourselves
back in the Void
and back in this very kind of
Spike Jonze, Gondry escape, uh,
through Bob’s rooms.
And here we have...
this was added later.
This is the meth chicken room,
which is definitely on the edge.
Probably the only time
you’re gonna see "meth chicken"
on a strip board
or a schedule board at Marvel.
But I just felt... Both for the
dynamics of them falling through...
And it felt like in the
Pixar version of this movie,
you would have a bit of humor
before you got to the lowest point,
even if it’s a very
dark form of humor,
and it’s atypical to say... [chuckles]
..."I was on meth," in a Marvel movie.
Or to have Bucky Barnes save
the day by punching a chicken,
but it felt like we really wanted to push
the concept to its furthest extensions
before we got
to the lowest point.
So hopefully,
you go with us on that one.
Love that shot.
Great shot by Andrew.
And it’s nice
where you actually have...
I mean, obviously the Void, that’s
an effect to make him a silhouette,
but by putting him against the
backlight, it doesn’t feel as incongruous,
like it feels like it fits
with how the photography actually
would be for a moment like that,
so that’s a really nice...
You know, between Framestore,
who did this sequence,
and Andrew and Rafi and Chuck
and all the lighting,
that’s a nice way to watch
those two things dovetail.
[Bob] Felt like a miracle.
[Schreier] And here Bob
finally defines, you know,
this idea of what would the worst
room for someone like Bob be,
and it’s not actually, in some ways,
the trauma of his childhood, but more...
you know, is there something
more heartbreaking
about it being the place
where he tried to be a hero,
where he tried to become
something bigger than himself
and, in his own estimation...
You know, he says it here,
"The most shameful thing of all
was thinking you could be
anything more than nothing."
And for the way that Bob feels
about himself in this moment,
this is the biggest shame,
is to imagine that
he could be anything better.
And that feels
like the lowest feeling.
No.
[Schreier] It’s quite a thing when you
ask a bunch of the greatest actors on Earth
to be locked up against a wall
by furniture.
Requires a lot of faith on their
part and a lot of faith on our part
to know that Framestore was
gonna come through eventually,
and even though we had practical
versions of these things on set, for sure,
obviously they’ve augmented
them to make them look better.
And then just to watch Lewis, you
know, have to play both of these parts,
have to learn both sides
of this fight
and still appeal to this sense
of him trying to protect people
and, you know, have his
darker side laugh at himself
for wanting to do that.
[laughs]
Robert, the hero.
[Schreier] That’s a real
glass explosion that we did.
And then there’s candy glass
on their faces.
I’m stronger than you.
[Schreier] And this idea
that you’re expecting to
want to fight the Void
and beat him,
but that, in fact,
this is what the Void wants.
He’s goading Bob
into doing this.
And, again, Lewis learning both sides
of this fight and having to perform it,
switch costumes,
do it for each of these shots,
and do both sides of it
before he becomes a silhouette
’cause even as a silhouette, even
though sometimes this is Alec or Ben,
his wonderful stunt doubles,
you really want Lewis, even in
silhouette form, embodying that character.
And so we really did it both ways
as much as we possibly could.
And then here’s the idea of the
movie: "We will always be alone."
And then this was something we
added later, after principal photography,
this idea of the room expanding
and physically carrying
our protagonists away from him
and establishing
that sense of isolation.
That first shot
is actually done in-camera,
where we just had Lewis on a piece
of Lexan attached to a camera car
and pulled him back.
So even though there’s a lot of
wonderful CG in this sequence,
a lot of it is practical
and in-camera.
Again, always trying
to find that balance.
And then, again, this
is this thing you root for,
as you see a near smile
on Walker’s face.
You’re used to rooting that
you should beat up the bad guy.
You should beat the big bad, but in
our movie, there is no winning that way.
You know, there’s no version
of this that ever could’ve ended
in just a punch solving it,
and you see that, in fact,
in trying to fight himself
and destroy
that side of himself,
he’s becoming the darkness
that he’s trying to avoid
and that our characters and
everyone watching needs to learn
that there is no kind of
physical solution to this.
Bob, stop!
This is what he wants!
[Schreier] And, of course,
in a superhero movie,
maybe that feels
like an odd resolution,
you know,
or it feels too small.
We added this sequence of
Yelena so that there was, you know,
for our protagonist who’s
been inactive on the sidelines,
a very active role in solving
this in a sort of action context
in which she needs to
get to him to save him
and thus save the world,
which will be plunged
into darkness
if she doesn’t succeed.
That’s actually
Heidi Moneymaker.
So to have Scarlett’s
longtime stunt double
and now stunt coordinator
performing that
felt like a real... something
really coming full circle.
I’m here.
It will always be just us.
[Schreier] Okay, yes, if you
want to be frustrated with us
’cause it ends in a hug,
I mean, we always said
it’s not truly a hug.
They’re trying to
pull him back from himself,
but, of course,
that’s how it functions.
And this idea of her answering,
"You’re not alone,"
this idea that she’s expressed to him
in the beginning now being answered.
Okay, it’s a hug, but how
else were you gonna solve this?
And it’s a hug that we try
to frame in an action context.
You know, as much as it can,
we’ve tried to externalize
these very internal ideas
of the Void and also just...
I mean, Son Lux’s score
in this moment, I think,
with these actors
and with those ideas,
we did everything we could to
have you come along that ride with us.
And, you know, it was always
gonna end in some version of that.
And I feel like where Lewis
got to, I’m just so proud of him
and amazed by Florence
and all of them
for executing such a resonant
version of that moment.
It was very fun
being in this helicopter.
That’s all I’ll say.
That’s a treat.
This was something
we also talked a lot about,
about the ending
and how it would resolve,
and there’s a reason in the comics
why Sentry always loses his memory,
’cause you can’t really have someone
as powerful like that in the world.
Um, and in this case...
Yes. Don’t worry.
We’re not gonna kill a
little girl. She comes back.
That was one of the earliest shadow
tests we did, uh, was rejoining that shadow
as a means
of getting us out of this
without having to do tons of shots of
people waking up around New York.
But we played around with
a lot of different versions of...
You know, there were times
when Bob did remember
but had learned this lesson that he
can’t be The Sentry without the Void,
so he can’t be on the team,
but then he would
have to walk away
’cause they have to
go confront Val,
and that just felt sad.
So the memory loss
felt like the best way
that we could kind of
keep them together
but still be true to the story of
Sentry that we were telling, um,
and kind of reserve that payoff
for later, but also find this way...
You know, we had tried a version
where he didn’t remember anything at all,
and then that felt like you
hadn’t really, you know...
People didn’t feel like it had honored
the journey that they had gone on enough,
so we landed on this version
where he remembers who they are,
but he doesn’t remember the most
recent events of what’s happened
and his episode.
Okay. Come on.
[Schreier] And in this very
simple way, it’s like, "Yep.
We stick together from now on,"
and not in a kind of cheesy
way, but just, you gotta...
you don’t want someone
like Bob out there.
You gotta keep that connection
alive. You gotta keep him with you.
And then this was in the very
first draft of the script that I read,
that everything that we did, whatever
changed, it always ended here
with Val, you know, kind of...
This very classic thing that
Kevin and Marvel are so good at
about, you know, this kind of
flip and reveal that we go into.
Um, and knowing that this whole movie
was building up to this announcement,
you know, it needs to work as
a fun twist for the audience,
but also
on a character level where...
You know, it’s interesting,
you’re not... if you’re doing that,
then you’re not traditionally
beating your bad guy.
You’re not killing Val.
You’re not arresting her.
But that line of, "We own you
now," becomes very important.
We had to send all the
extras away on set this day
when she said that, just to make
sure no one heard about it first.
[crowd cheering, applauding]
[chuckles] Love that shot
of Lewis clapping.
The most powerful one unaware
that he’s even on the team.
[cheering, applauding continue]
And what I love is that
even amidst all of that,
and, you know, this fun sort of
positioning for where the story will go,
there is a character moment
that we need to complete here,
and we need to push back into that
close-up that we start the movie with.
And, again, it just came from a moment
that Florence did instinctively on set
that we then built into
the rest of the movie,
of that same eyes closed, breath
in, look up, but now with a smile.
Uh, this is once again Imaginary
Forces. Um, this sequence...
We felt like when we showed the movie,
you know, we maybe expected at first
that people would cheer on this
New Avengers thing a little more,
and people needed
a moment with it,
and so we wanted to kind of
acknowledge the way the real world works
and how snarky
everything is at first
and how people might not be
so certain about this partnership,
so this was this fun sequence
that Imaginary Forces did
such a great job of painting,
of kind of starting
in that skepticism--
I love the
New York Post headline--
um, and then bringing you around
by the end of it to some sense that,
hey, maybe this could work out,
maybe you could buy into this.
I’ll just say, I love all these
people who made this movie.
Everyone worked so hard,
so incredibly hard
um, and cared about it
and took it seriously.
I mean Florence,
I can’t say any more.
I mean, like I said,
actual magic.
Sebastian, to have him as
part of this. Wyatt, who’s a friend.
Olga, who was such a good sport
to show up for this.
Lewis, who, I mean, I think really,
you know, is the find of this movie.
Geraldine, who did such a
great job. Chris for showing up.
Wendell.
I’ve been a fan forever.
David, one of the most
committed actors you’ll ever meet.
And Hannah,
really the glue of that group.
Julia, who’s a legend that I just
feel lucky that I got to work with.
I just, you know,
as a director,
if you can ever
get a cast like that,
it just makes the whole job
incredibly easy.
And then, yeah,
there’s our flip.
[chuckles]
Like I said,
this is release day,
so it’s almost hard
to speak on this until
we see how that plays
out in the world,
but I think that’s a fun one to try and
an example of how open, you know,
everyone at Marvel was to
try new ideas on this project.
And this was a fun one
we did during additional...
We didn’t shoot any of our post credit
scenes during principal photography.
We sort of wanted to see where
the whole thing was gonna go
and what we would need,
but, again,
it felt like paying off
that kind of meta idea
of the Wheaties box
and Alexei’s investment in it,
but then undercutting it a bit,
uh, felt right for
where we ended our story.
And then because it’s Alexei, and
we start with Muzak in a supermarket,
you get into kind of...
You know, he’s the kind of guy
who would love to have
a classic post credits song.
And so we get to
give that to him
and therefore give it
to our viewers.
[♪ "Nothing’s Gonna
Stop Us Now"plays]
I’ll just say that, you know,
I’m struck when I sit in a theater.
Um... And I look at this credit
sequence, and it’s a long one.
You know, I’ve sat through
credits before.
I like to kind of
let a movie sink in, you know,
but going through this experience,
I know all of these people.
Um, and I know what they did
and how much...
You know, I could talk for an hour
about each of their contributions,
and it’s just one name on the list
that’s scrolling by that you won’t notice,
whether it’s, uh, Onnalee and
Michael, our incredible mixers,
or Alex Levy,
our music editor, who...
so instrumental in creating
this score with Son Lux.
You know, the stunts on
this movie were incredible.
Every single one
of those people worked so hard.
You know, Michael Huggins, who
was our... who did the rigging, and...
I mean, if you’re Florence Pugh
and you’re stepping off the roof
of the second tallest
story building in the world,
you have to have a lot of faith
in that rigging.
Um, I could single out
any one of them,
and I think I’m just struck
by how many people it takes,
working so hard
and caring so much,
uh, just to make a good movie.
It’s just hard
to make a good movie,
and, you know, I guess, if you
got this far, hopefully you feel like
this one was all right.
Um, and I am just so grateful
to all of those people
and for all of the work
that they put in,
and, really, when I look back
on this process...
something that Grace and I
would talk about, she would say,
"You know, we’re going to grad
school. We’re gonna learn so much."
And I think, you know, it’s wonderful
to put a movie out in the world,
and it’s wonderful
to have it connect with people,
but also what I mainly look back
on is the experience of making it
and how much I learned and how much
you have to lean on this incredible team.
Um...
And I’ll never forget that.
So, um, thank you guys
for watching.
Um...
Obviously, uh... Oh, yeah, I
gotta call out Samara Handelsman,
my assistant, who had
to put up with so, so much.
[chuckles]
Um, what else can I say here?
’Cause I do wanna get
to the VFX houses
and explain kind of more
specifically what they did, but, uh...
Sean, who drove me every day.
Not an easy job.
Definitely going through it.
Our wonderful second unit.
Um, really, there were days
where I would start there
and then come over
to first unit,
and it was always great
working with those guys.
Getting out to Utah, obviously.
I feel like that’s when the
movie really opened up for me,
just feeling like
we were out there.
And Malaysia. You know, they don’t
have the entire crew in Malaysia listed,
but it really was
a wonderful crew.
Adam in special effects, particularly
for blowing up that building,
one take to do it.
Did such a great job.
New York. We actually
did shoot in DC as well,
but it was such a small shoot I
don’t think they have it listed here.
Believe it or not,
as long as these credits are,
there are even more people
that work on these movies.
All the wonderful people
at Marvel.
And of course it was great to see
Paul Jenkins at the, uh, premiere for this
and just talk a little bit about
his view of Robert Reynolds
and the way we treated him.
And I think he was very happy,
which was nice.
Everyone in marketing, they did
such a great job with this movie
and really embracing
doing something different.
Okay,
our visual effects houses.
Third Floor
for all of the previs.
Digital Domain
and their previs department,
we worked on earlier,
as well as Framestore.
It’s really such an
important part of the process.
OPSIS did a lot of work
for us in that area as well.
Then ILM... Really, the whole
New York street sequence
and all of the voiding and the
crane falling, all of the heavy lifting.
And Chad and everyone over
there did just such an amazing job.
Framestore, uh, did
the vault exterior environment,
Bob’s flight, all of the stuff in
Bob’s attic and that ending lab fight,
which, really, I mean, we were
finishing right to the very end,
and the movie
doesn’t work without it.
They just did
such an incredible job.
Digital Domain, that was a lot
of the early vault sequence,
a lot of that fighting,
Ghost phasing,
uh, just every part
of that fight they worked on,
and that stuff came in great.
Rising Sun, a lot of the face
replacement stuff in the film.
Base, really, just a company
that saved us on Beef as well
and just a workhorse on this.
A lot of the Bucky arms and Void
shadow growth, things like that.
Raynault did the airplane.
Val’s drop-off, the crater design.
Some of the penthouse stuff.
And then a lot of fill-in work
by these other houses.
I mean, it just takes
so many people doing so much.
Imaginary Forces, who worked so
incredibly hard on that opening Marvel logo
and our ending
credits sequence,
um, which really is such
a narrative lift for the film.
Tom Poole did such a great job
of coloring this movie with Andrew.
Looks beautiful.
Uh, yeah.
Again, at every line, there are
people working so incredibly hard
to make what you see here.
Doc, who also helped record
this, uh, commentary track.
And Son Lux again.
What an incredible job
they did.
And it was so fun
to go out to Abbey Road,
be in that room
and record this score.
I wasn’t there the whole time, but just
to see it for a few days was amazing.
And special thanks
to the Merdeka,
Jon Watts, who helped me out
so much on this film,
and my friend Francis.
Atlanta Metro Studios. Green
River, Utah. Filmed all over.
Malaysia.
A lot of these places
you see here,
a lot of this is, you know,
where the effects are finished,
not necessarily where we shot.
And I’m just...
I’m killing time here
’cause we do have
one more scene to talk about.
Okay, so this scene got filmed maybe
a month before the movie came out.
Out in London,
on the set of Avengers,
and really it is also meant to be really,
like, a hand-off of these characters
into the world going forward
and trying to bring back that sense
of connection between these movies
and bringing in
the Fantastic Four.
Um, you know, for our movie,
what we always talked about is that
because of the way the movie ends
on the street and has an immediacy to it
and Bob’s just lost his memory,
you can’t really get into, you know,
the future of Bob in that moment,
and so for us,
on a narrative level,
what was really important
about this scene
is knowing that, you know,
Bob is with them, but had sort of
processed the lesson of the movie,
which is that, you know,
you can’t be The Sentry
without the other side
coming underneath,
and, you know, the real task
is to learn how to just be Bob.
And, of course, I expect, you know,
the tension between those things
to play out in the future,
though I have no insight into that.
I don’t know anything.
And then, of course,
if you have David Harbour,
you gotta use him.
He carries it all.
He’s dumb, litigious man,
but I am smart.
I am smart man.
I have smart solve.
Avengerz.
Avengerz. With a "Z,"
there is no copyright.
- No.
- [Alexei] So soft too.
[Schreier] But, yeah, it just,
you know, it looks different,
and we talked about
embracing that.
You know, it sounds different.
It has the music that feels...
You know, it’s Avengers music,
not our music.
And really seeing this team
kind of step into a new light
and, you know,
see how that feels.
And for you, Bob, in the corner
hiding, pretending to read the book.
[Schreier] And this is, yeah.
You just get to see
that Bob is there with them,
and for our movie, you know, if
this has any narrative import on it,
that was the most important
thing for us about this scene.
- Get a satellite image.
- And fire up--
And fire...
I was gonna say that.
[Schreier] And, yeah, just a
really interesting day to be out there
when they were filming this,
and they were filming
some stuff for Fantastic Four
on an adjoining stage in London,
and just seeing that whole...
You know, something Lou was
always excited about for Marvel
was the idea of, you know, having a lot
where all these things were getting made
and getting to go around and feeling
the connectedness between them,
and it really felt like
I was there on that day
where, in theory, we were finishing
our movie and starting another,
and another Marvel movie was being
made, you know, at a stage next door.
And it was just a really,
really nice day.
[Alexei] Extradimensional?
What does that mean?
[Walker] It’s a...
It’s a cool ship.
[Schreier] And there we go. It is very
fun to watch people applaud for this.
And there we go. The New Avengers,
not the Thunderbolts*. And Bob.
Thank you guys so much for
watching, and sorry it was just me,
but we got through it.