[fire crackling faintly]
IN ASSOCIATION WITH
ÁNIMA & CHATRONE
WARNER BROS. ANIMATION
PRESENTS
[intense percussive
ceremonial music playing]
[singer humming, vocalizing]
AZTEC BATMAN: CLASH OF EMPIRES
[singer chanting in gravelly voice]
BASED ON DC CHARACTERS
[music fades out]
[panting]
Father?
Papa? Tahtli!
[footsteps thudding]
[ominous music playing]
[gasps]
[snorts]
[yelling]
- [shrieks]
- [snorts]
[yells]
[bat shrieks]
- [bull growls]
- [bat screeches]
[gasps]
[shrieking]
No!
[panting]
[man] Another vision?
A nightmare, I'd say.
Must have been that old huitlacoche I ate.
Ah, I've never known you
to eat old huitlacoche, my son.
Especially so many times in a row.
It's nothing, Papa. Just the corn.
Don't you ever ignore your dreams, Yohu,
no matter where they come from.
Now, then, if it was nothing,
then let us be thankful for that.
Tlacatlé, totecoé Tzinacan.
[serene woodwind music playing]
[grunts] Tlaca...
[yawns]
You will give our Bat God
the respect that he is due.
Even your mother
would not have blamed him.
Her death was not his fault.
But he also didn't lift a finger
to save her.
Even when we prayed
with the utmost respect.
She's watching over you. You know that.
Yes, Pa. I know.
Your mother's got her eye on you
right next to Tzinacan.
Now don't forget, son,
your training isn't a game,
so before you join the village...
[grumbles]
Ah, it's always so unnerving
when our Young Shadow vanishes like that.
[lively traditional music
playing in distance]
GULF OF MEXICO COAST
[music continues nearby]
[chattering]
[chuckles softly]
[chuckles]
Hey! Yohu!
[gasps]
[music stops]
[fighters grunting]
Let's begin with the overhead strike.
Shields!
They are your best defense.
Now show me your side-kick.
Yohu! And hold. Don't move a muscle.
The position of your arm
needs to be higher.
Or your strike will completely lack power.
All right. Let's continue.
I know how difficult it was for you
after the death of your mother,
but now that you're grown up,
it's time you get serious
about your future.
Don't scold me, please.
When you take my place,
it'll be your duty
to always be ready for battle
and, when your people need you,
to serve them as best you can.
Remember, fear can kill you
or inspire you to action.
It's your call.
You're... You...
- [foreboding music playing]
- What are those?
[woman] Look! Mountains carried by clouds!
[man] No. Those are monsters
from the depths.
[music turns ominous, militaristic]
They look like they're gods.
Listen carefully to what they say, Yohu,
but pay closer attention to how they act.
That's how you can tell
if they're gods or not.
[Spanish guitar cadence plays,
then music fades out]
Mm.
I salute you, blessed people.
I am Captain Hernán Cortés.
I've come to your lands
in the name of Almighty God
and the Holy Roman Emperor,
His Majesty Charles I,
the king of Castilla.
I am Chief Toltecatzin,
first son of Oquitzin.
May I ask the reason you come?
I am exploring the New World.
You found a new world?
The vast green landscape
stretching out before us,
it's called the New World
since we only just discovered it.
Many suns have already passed
since our people first knew these lands.
[tense music playing]
We seem to find ourselves low on supplies.
[tense music spikes]
Would you be willing to make a trade?
No.
No?
Our village has plenty that we can share.
Join us. You shall be our honored guests.
[laughs] That is excellent.
What a splendid idea.
[villagers murmuring]
[grunts]
My lord, I don't trust
these pale strangers one iota.
They act as if this village
now belongs to them.
I understand your frustration,
old warrior.
Tonight I'll consult
the judgment of the gods.
We shall let them decide.
[woman] Want another? We have plenty.
Diego sent us here to get gold,
not to fill our bellies.
- [cup shatters]
- And he'll get it, once we discover...
Your fabled city swimming in gold?
Gold is what makes Diego
and the authorities happy.
My plans with God
are far more grand than such riches.
[foreboding music builds, then fades out]
I would like to thank you all
for this warm welcome.
Allow me to show you
some of the wonders of my world.
Inventions, ideas,
from some of our brightest minds.
- Behold!
- [crowd gasping]
- [gasps]
- And this is Toledo,
the most glorious city in Castilla,
the land where I come from.
I've heard your capital is beautiful.
- Tenochtitlán?
- "Tenochtitlán."
Oh, thank you.
- I want to say it right when I get there.
- [chuckles]
And finally, this is an arquebus,
or, as some Mexicas already know it...
[all yell]
[all gasp]
...the thunder of the gods!
- Time for bed, Young Shadow.
- But it's still light out, Tahtli.
Your father is right.
Enough talk for today.
Until tomorrow, Chief Toltecatzin.
Rest well, Young Yohualli.
[foreboding music playing]
And their armor looks so shiny,
almost like the skin of a fish,
and yet it seems also like it's as hard
as a turtle shell.
And their writings possess magic.
One even showed how to fly like a bird.
Is it possible? To fly?
[serene music playing]
Again you're asking for advice
from Tzinacan?
I pray for guidance and for answers.
I believe that they do look like gods.
They're not gods.
But if it's Tezcatlipoca who advises them,
then they might be as devious
as they are powerful.
In that case,
then wouldn't that make them gods?
Do you remember Acatzin?
The one who watches
over our house in the city?
I think so, yeah.
- Do you think that Cortés...?
- Enough with Cortés. [sighs]
Please, if something bad happens to me,
go find Acatzin, and he will help.
Yes, Pa.
[eerie flute music playing]
[music turns dramatic]
- [crowd murmuring faintly]
- [horse whinnies]
Pa?
[uneasy music playing]
[thunder rumbling]
[woman] What was that? Thunder?
- [child] I'm scared, Mama.
- Huh?
- [thunder crashes]
- [ominous music spikes]
[gasps]
- What is it, Father?
- For now, nothing. Keep quiet, though.
Chief Toltecatzin, we are grateful
for your generous hospitality.
It was nothing.
What might be nothing to some people
can be everything to others.
That's why my men and I
require a little bit more from you.
The location of Tenochtitlán.
Impossible. We have strict rules
in place that forbid this.
Rules are rules. Hmm.
Ah. How about this idea?
What if you joined our expedition
and showed us?
Even better, Yohu could be my herald
and announce my arrival to the Sun King.
- Yes.
- That's out of the question.
Father, please. I can do it.
The boy is more than old enough
to make his own decisions,
don't you think?
Captain Cortés speaks the truth.
I'm a grown man.
That's what you said.
Listen close, son.
If anything happens,
you run and go straight to Acatzin.
Take your mother as well.
She'll protect you.
[villagers gasps]
[man] Do you see his hair?
How it shines like the sun?
Is he a god, Mama?
Tonatiuh.
[gasps]
- Tonatiuh.
- Tonatiuh is here.
I will personally request for an audience
on your behalf with Moctezuma.
Meanwhile, you shall wait in our village
as our guests of honor.
Ah, it's best to arrive unannounced.
Besides, everybody loves surprises.
Well, that all depends on the surprise.
So you still don't trust me, hmm?
You have nothing to fear.
We're Christians. We are here to help you.
- [whinnies]
- [man] The gods!
- [woman] The gods have arrived!
- Back, or I'll kill you.
[ominous music playing]
This is help in your world? No!
None of you strangers are gods!
You're nothing but liars and murderers!
[thunder crashes]
As long as I draw breath,
you'll never see Tenochtitlán.
[laughs] Fine.
Thank you for such wise counsel.
- [ominous music spikes]
- [gasps]
[Yohu breathing shakily]
[all gasp, then grunt]
[thunder crashes]
Slaughter them all!
[all yelling]
[villagers screaming]
[somber music playing]
[sobs]
Tahtli!
Papa!
Pa. I'm sorry.
- [music turns ominous]
- That decides it.
You're coming with me now.
[yelps]
Filthy wretch!
[yells]
[music turns intense]
[bat shrieking]
[music fades out]
[Poison Ivy in echoey voice]
It courses through your veins.
It runs through your body.
Mama?
[Yohu groans]
- [Poison Ivy] Through all of our bodies.
- [yells]
[Poison Ivy] You must fight...
or die.
Fight...
and die.
Your life...
it must be in balance.
[yells]
Our world...
must also be in balance.
- [shrieks]
- [yells]
[pants]
- [vines rustling]
- Huh?
[grunts]
[ethereal music playing]
No, he isn't ready yet.
Give him a test, you say?
Hmm. Perhaps.
Excuse me.
Is this Mictlán?
No. You aren't dead.
Not yet.
Then what is...? Please, I have to leave.
Which way is the path...
[ethereal music swells]
...to...?
What is that?
What you witnessed will come true.
But not all of what you saw
has come to pass yet.
There's time.
Nothing you're saying makes any sense.
- What is this place?
- It's the beginning for you...
and the end.
- It wouldn't be wise to say any more.
- You crazy witch.
[grunting]
[music turns eerie]
[water dripping]
Huh?
[grunting]
- [eerie music spikes]
- [yells]
It's you.
You, who let my mother die.
Did you see what they did to my father?
To my village?
How is this a balance of justice?
You have done nothing!
That's because you're a lie!
[whimpers]
[stone creaking]
[yells]
Help me! Get them off! Get them off!
What is this?
[yells]
[panting]
Huh?
[mystical music playing]
[steady percussive music playing]
[groaning softly]
- [music stops]
- [panting]
I can give you a little food,
but I told you, you cannot sleep here.
Yohualli?
Are you all right? Where's your father?
[sobs] Acatzin!
- [melancholy music playing]
- [sobbing]
Oh, my dear Yohu.
MOCTEZUMA'S PALACE
You're not alone, Yohu.
I've been at your side
since the day you were born.
You're saying you were robbed
by a Jaguar God?
That's absurd.
Try telling that to my guards
with the scars on their faces.
It slashed them all with its flying claws.
This isn't the first time
it's stolen from us either.
[solemn music playing]
This humble servant comes
before Your Eminence
to present his new lord, Yohualli Coatl,
son of Chief Toltecatzin
from the Smoking Village.
Is this the young man
who saw the teúles and their leader?
Yes, I am the one, high priest,
that saw them.
You may speak,
Little Lord of the Forest.
Huey Tlatoani Moctezuma II is listening.
Their leader, he calls himself
Captain Hernán Cortés.
He came into our village with soldiers.
- My father, he shared food with them...
- What else happened?
Cortés wanted to know
how to find Tenochtitlán.
Hmm? Hmm.
[Yohu] My father refused.
Cortés murdered him,
then slew my whole village.
But not you? You must run fast, then.
Cortés seems to behave
the same way gods act towards men.
Sometimes he will be kind.
Other times, cruel.
What's your take on this,
High Priest Yoka?
Are they men or are they gods?
Gods, Your Eminence.
And we should invite them here
to prevent them from getting angry.
- No!
- Silence, you little...
Go ahead, young one.
Cortés is not a god.
But he is a powerful and cruel man.
He must be stopped
before he sets foot in this city.
This boy from the provinces
is but a simple warrior.
What gift was he endowed
to know who is or isn't a god?
Please, my lord,
I beg you to heed my words.
We shall test their capabilities.
Although, if they were gods,
they'd get here on their own.
[growls]
He has no idea how dangerous Cortés is.
I believe you,
but Yoka is the city's high priest.
He speaks directly to the gods.
He knows them.
The gods don't need to use weapons
when they come to take your head.
- What are you talking about, Yohualli?
- Cortés murdered my father.
He spoke of my right to seek revenge.
At your age, no one expects you
to take such rash action.
Avenging my tahtli isn't rash action.
- It's my debt.
- No, it's not.
You don't understand.
I wouldn't listen. I wasn't ready to.
I let fear take control.
I vow never to make that mistake again.
I want you to train me
to become the greatest warrior
that the world has ever known.
I'm to going to stop Cortés
and his soldiers.
Your wish is my command, my lord.
[foreboding music playing]
[Yoka] Damn that Yohu!
The prophecies are certain!
[grunts angrily] Insolent forest whelp!
Tlacatlé, totecoé Huitzilopochtli!
[Huitzilopochtli] Is that doubt I sense?
No, I would never. I'd never doubt you.
But what of the king?
Are you saying you doubt yourself, Yoka?
Make him see.
- [Yohu grunting]
- [weapons thumping]
[winces]
And again.
[grim music playing]
[grunts, then pants]
And again.
[yells]
[music turns ominous]
[screams]
[grim music playing]
[pants] Hmm.
[grim music continues]
ALLIANCE WITH TLAXCALTECAS
CHOLULA MASSACRE
[all grunting, yelling]
[music turns solemn]
[solemn music continues]
[birds screaming]
- The teúles are at our door.
- Just as I predicted.
Nothing will hinder them,
for they are gods,
and they deserve our welcome.
And you, Yohualli Coatl?
What do you think?
Will it be impossible to stop them?
Give me the order, great king.
My warriors and I are more than ready
to test them in combat.
- [warriors yelling in unison]
- [man] Death to the pale invaders!
We'll push them back into the sea!
He's insane, Your Majesty.
It's a fool's errand
to wage war against the gods.
Huey tlatoani,
these intruders are not gods.
I swear upon the blood of my parents.
I have much to think over.
In any case, I expect you to be prepared,
regardless of my decision.
CORTÉS ARRIVES IN TENOCHTITLÁN
Look. A silver metropolis.
It's even bigger than Toledo.
[laughs] What did I say, Pedro?
That we'd soon find
their hidden metropolis.
And finally, we are here!
[laughs menacingly]
There must be a mountain of gold
and riches within.
But we won't know until we're inside.
Let us make for the city gates.
[foreboding music playing]
I salute you, O blessed people.
I am Captain Hernán Cortés.
[music fades out]
I'm here in the name of God
and King Charles I of Castilla.
I humbly ask permission to enter
so I may share the many wonders
of my world with you.
[eerie music playing]
Persuade the king
that he must open the gates to the teúles.
Yohualli Coatl clouded his judgment
with foolhardy counsel.
Tloque Nahuaque,
Yohualli Ehecatl, Ipalnemohuani!
He refuses to listen.
If it's what I desire, he will listen.
[laughs coldly]
You are my voice on earth, son. Go.
Huey tlatoani, I beg you,
please welcome the teúles into the city.
[tense music playing]
The time is nigh. Rise, gentlemen!
Time to claim what's ours!
[soldiers shout]
- [soldier 1] Show no mercy.
- [soldier 2] Kill every last one.
Tell us, war leader,
what are your orders?
Allow them inside.
[conch trumpeting]
[ominous music playing]
[gasps]
We're entering into the lion's den.
Everything will be all right.
How do you know this?
Did the Lord tell you?
Yes.
Every morning, I hear from him on high.
"Hernán, it is all in your hands."
[music quiets, turns suspenseful]
Hmm.
[both gasp]
Yoka, why are they not satisfied
by our many sacrifices and offerings?
[Yoka] They look like teúles.
Perhaps they wish us
to present them with different gifts.
Is it you?
- Are you...? Are you Moctezuma?
- Yes.
I am Moctezuma.
Welcome to our city, my lord.
Take your rightful throne.
I've watched over it
for you all this time.
My predecessors Itzcoatl,
Moctezuma I and Axayácatl
all proclaimed that one day
you'd come for what's yours.
And today is the day.
Welcome, at long last,
to your destined land.
[crowd gasps]
I'm Hernán Cortés,
first emissary of God
and the Holy Roman Emperor,
King Charles I.
- You think they're Gods?
- The king will know.
I've come all this way
to show you the many wonders...
He touched the king!
[crowd murmuring]
- It's forbidden to touch him!
- The gods would never do such a thing!
Uh, would you like, O great king,
for us to speak in a place
that's a bit more...?
- See that, child?
- Citlālim popōca!
The teúles used their godlike powers
to cause citlālim popōca
to appear in the sky!
- [man 1] In the sky!
- [man 2] It's a sign.
- What is it, Hernán?
- Be on your guard.
No! Not the end!
How could you have missed this?
Was it because...
Because I delayed in welcoming Cortés?
Or because I allowed him in?
Why does the end approach us? Yoka!
Great and powerful king, I...
I don't know.
[solemn woodwind music playing]
[Acatzin] Tzinacan, protect this city.
Help our people survive
this great calamity...
Are you going somewhere? At this hour?
Cortés won't sit on his hands
and do nothing.
He'll explore the streets.
But you won't be able
to fight him at night.
Not without the protection of the Sun God.
Fortunately, my family
worships a night god.
Tzinacan owes me.
Blasphemy.
Cortés is a royal guest.
He's been offered hospitality by the king.
To touch him now
would merit a sentence of death.
This is why you trained me.
To avenge my father.
So if you won't help, then leave.
I release you from my service.
[pensive music playing]
My lord, in the spirit
of my continuing to assist you,
what say you to the idea
of wearing a costume?
[suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
It's not gold, but it shines.
[laughs]
Please excuse my friend.
His manners are rather brash.
Please, consider it my gift to you.
I guess those rumors about the teúles
and gold turned out to be true.
But did you know
it's the sun's excrement?
[Cortés] How dare you?!
- Huh?
- [yells]
I'll gut you slowly,
like you're some pathetic little cur.
Wait! I want to see what he's capable of.
Your arrogance will be your death.
You took the words right out of my mouth.
[grunting, growling]
- [yells]
- You murdered my father!
I can't seem to recall
exactly who he was,
but when you see him again,
give him my regards.
[growls]
- [snarls]
- [screams]
Hand me the arbalest!
[whimpers]
[seethes]
- [soldier 1] Did you hear that?
- [soldier 2] Yes. Over here.
Let's go.
This isn't over.
Are you coming or not?
Wow! Did you feel that?
Yes. That was a really good fight.
[in monotone]
"Yes. That was a really good fight."
[in normal voice] Come on, get excited.
You could at least be a little thankful
you're still breathing.
Tlazocamati.
[sighs]
Thank you. I'm very grateful.
You were brave.
- You're pretending to be a Jaguar Goddess?
- Same as you.
Except I invoke the powerful,
untamed spirit of the jaguar.
Ah. I saw.
I'm intrigued.
What were you thinking
when you ran at them
like a chicken without its head?
That Cortés was weaker.
I was mistaken.
But I will find a way to defeat him,
no matter what it costs me.
Sounds suicidal.
I guess it's good
we have opposing missions, then.
Perhaps.
But at least mine's a mission of honor,
unlike certain people that...
- Steal? That's what you were gonna say?
- I didn't mean...
Next time, I'll just let them chop you up
for their soup like a tuna.
Hmm.
AXAYÁCATL'S PALACE
- I can close your wound, my captain.
- [Cortés] Find that bat and that cat.
But your infection will only worsen.
[Cortés] Drown them in the lake.
Then draw and quarter them.
Did you hear me, Pedro?
Mm-hm. Don't be upset,
but the men and I were talking,
and we think that back in Toledo
you'll find the best doctors in the world,
who can heal your...
Uh, your scratch.
I see.
You all wish to return home,
then, don't you?
[all gasp]
Perhaps, then, you need reminding
that there's still a mission to complete.
[sinister music playing]
That's why I commanded
all our ships be set ablaze.
[all gasp]
Now that you've all been made aware,
who wants stay here with me?
Anyone else can swim
all the way back to Cuba.
And then she used this whip
to balance herself and...
It's just... she's so resourceful.
- Tlacatlé, totecoé Tzinacan!
- Huh?
- I'll make an offering.
- But she's not an actual goddess.
It's not for her.
It's for Tzinacan. [inhales]
Oh. All right.
- For sending her to save you.
- No. No one sent her to save me.
She stopped you from getting killed.
Of course she was sent
by him to save you.
Listen, the more important point here
is that, even with all of your training,
I can't defeat the teúles
and their weapons.
What's your next move, then?
I need to learn how their inventions work
and use that knowledge
to gain the upper hand.
But how will you even get close?
They're not going to invite you in
to study them.
- I'll be careful?
- Hmm. Too risky.
If only there was somebody
that you know
who was stealthy
and who had sticky fingers.
Perhaps they'd be able to help you.
Ahh.
[suspenseful music playing]
[chuckles softly]
[energetic music playing]
[music slows]
[gasps]
[gasps, then giggles]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
Huh?
[suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
Didn't take long for you to miss me.
[grunts]
[yells] Stop! I'm not your enemy.
My mission's to take back what we've lost.
But you wouldn't understand,
since you're one of them.
I just want to talk.
- Then talk.
- Sorry for following you.
But I needed to know what you did
with the things you steal.
- And now that you know?
- You saved me.
I want to do the same thing for you.
But please, you have to stop stealing
from our people.
At least don't do it while Cortés
is trying to take everything from us.
And if I don't? You'll kill me?
No. But in these times,
someone else could.
Don't throw your life away
when you have so much to live for.
What do you care for the life
of another dishonorable thief?
A path of dishonor that aims
towards good deserves admiration.
Now, please. I could really use your help.
Must have been hard
realizing you needed me, wasn't it?
Looks like you were right.
By night, the guards patrol this place
in a pattern.
And if you want to get in
without having to fight them,
repeat the magic words.
I'm sorry for being rude to you.
I shall forever be in your debt,
great jaguar,
for teaching me the ways of the night.
Uh-huh. Very well.
Next time, try your best not to sound
like a chicken with its head cut off.
[stealthy music playing]
[ominous music spikes]
[yells, then grunts]
Pretty clever idea
to disarm the enemy from afar,
- don't you think?
- Mm.
Well, that's odd.
There's still a while
before the Atlcahualo festival.
These trees weren't for the festival.
Cortés is behind this.
- What's he doing with them?
- Nothing good.
[mysterious music playing]
Ah. Is this the place?
Yes. It was here.
- [gasps]
- This is the forgotten temple of Tzinacan.
I thought it was a myth, though.
[gasps]
So you said
that when you were wounded,
you ran all the way from your village
to a temple you had no idea existed,
one that your father had discovered
in his earlier years?
I got lucky.
Luck's has absolutely nothing
to do with this.
The Bat God guided you
that day to its lair.
Tlacatlé, totecoé Tzinacan!
No! Stop it, Acatzin!
That day, Tzinacan left us all to die.
But, my lord, what about
the forest goddess that helped you?
She was nothing but a hallucination.
It was the fever, exhaustion, who knows?
You're so stubborn.
Blindness are those who refuse to see.
Stubborn and maddening are those
who see a stone god altar
and think it's listening to them.
You're the Bat God's chosen one, my lord.
You've been given a sacred mission.
And whether you accept it or not,
it's the truth.
If you really believe in the gods,
then let's test you.
Stand there and don't move a single finger
until night falls.
Yes, my lord. It'll be a great honor.
I'll be as still as a chinicuil worm
as it hides in the dirt
from a hungry bird.
Ah. Huh?
No! Get them off me! Get them off me!
See, guess it's not such a sacred mission
after all, is it?
[determined music playing]
[determined music continues]
[music fades out]
[gasps]
[ethereal music playing]
You do exist. Forgive me for doubting.
You're not the first nor the last
to have doubted.
Ask your questions.
Tell me how to defeat Cortés.
How to get the teúles out of the city.
Without him, you don't exist.
Without him, you cannot win.
Is it better to earn his trust
or kill him?
What's Cortés doing with all those trees?
When empires clash,
some will rise,
others fall.
A great metamorphosis will take place,
and the gods shall anoint
their chosen emissaries,
whether they know it or not.
Balance depends on them.
Not by way of vengeance
but through sacrifice.
For all must move in eternal momentum.
I don't understand you!
Stop speaking in riddles for once!
[in booming voice]
Respect the will of the gods!
[gasps, then pants]
Was it a vision?
[sighs] Just go back to sleep.
Oftentimes the gods use dreams
as a way to speak to the chosen ones.
That's how they offer guidance
during times of great adversity.
Then someone should tell them
to be a little less confusing.
Well, some gods speak to you plainly,
while there are others
who will act quiet or more evasive.
Some visit to tell you the truth,
while others seek to deceive
and torment you, such as Tezcatlipoca.
You must be extremely careful
with that god.
[sighs] Try and get some sleep.
Tomorrow's gonna be a long day.
[man] Our people believe
that they have powers,
but they don't think they are gods.
The white rock discovered
upon their arrival is proof
that they are correct,
contrary to all that Yoka has said.
Tell him he must feed them.
That he is wrong about the teúles.
They are hungry.
Oh, good, my lord.
Huitzilopochtli, he assures me
our visitors are not some sort
of cosmic test we must overcome.
On the contrary,
we must satisfy their hunger.
Your answer is always
more and more sacrifices.
You disappoint me, Yoka.
Now I am certain
that for us to achieve peace,
every member of this kingdom
will have to right their wrongs,
including you!
[Yoka yells in fear]
No! Not this! No!
- I beg you, my lord, no!
- You are hereby banished, Yoka.
Go to the mountain
and contemplate the ruin
that your choices have brought upon us.
But I am your most faithful!
I am the gods' messenger!
Please, I don't deserve this!
[dramatic music playing]
[yells]
[whinnying]
Huh?
To arms! It's the Bat Warrior!
[horses whinny]
[both gasp]
Dealing with this infernal bat is starting
to become quite the endless headache.
For now, there's a more urgent matter
we must attend to.
Ah, yes.
It seems the glorious governor
of the island of Cuba
is ordering me to return,
like some useless mongrel!
What's his messenger been up to?
Watching everything
so he may report you.
Send him inside.
Did you reconsider?
Will you obey Diego Velázquez de Cuéllar,
officer of King Charles
and governor of Cuba?
Or would you prefer I call the army
to haul you back in chains?
[menacing music playing]
Ah, of course I shall comply
with this order.
Tell me, how would you care to join us
on a secret mission?
What do you say, hmm?
Very well.
I couldn't ask for more.
What else do you require, my lord?
Fear.
[pensive music playing]
[music turns dramatic]
[music fades out]
Thank you for agreeing to make
the offerings before we begin our trials.
Yes.
It's the right thing to do.
Do you remember how to say it?
Tlacatlé,
totecoé Tzinacan.
Oh, thank the gods.
I thought that I had failed you, my lord.
- I, who am just but a humble...
- Acatzin...
other than my father,
you are without a doubt
the best man I've ever known.
I feel like Tzinacan would smile
if he saw me leap into the fray.
Don't you think?
[Acatzin] I'm grateful
you finally accepted your destiny.
Break your backs
if that's what will get it up there.
- Pull!
- [soldiers grunting]
Excellent work, gentlemen. Take a break.
[groans]
Nature calls.
[gasps]
[dramatic music playing]
On your feet, you vermin!
We're under attack!
Quick! Put it out!
[soldiers shouting]
[dramatic music swells]
[panting] Bravo. I see that you've made
a few improvements.
You took the words right out of my mouth.
[growls]
[gasps]
[clears throat] Was this mission
supposed to show me your abilities?
Too few of you understand
what Almighty God has given me.
The opportunity to finally sit
on a throne.
A throne? Just the one in a Cuban jail
where you shall face judgment.
He has also told me
my hands control the power of destiny.
Hmm. Fate can be cruel.
By the Lord and his saints, you're...
You're a monster!
- [sword pierces flesh]
- [gurgling]
Goddamn you!
It was the Bat!
He was the one
who murdered Diego's messenger.
I shall see you're avenged, my friend.
Leave him there. Let's return to the city.
[chuckles] You'll need
some new armor first, captain.
Some new armor.
[chuckles coldly]
And a new strategy.
[grim music playing]
[Cortés] It's outrageous!
To be waylaid like this
on an excursion through the forest.
My men and I, we come in peace.
But I answer to King Charles,
and he is not nearly as merciful
as my God is.
But why not inform me
you all were leaving the city?
And why were you in the forest at night?
That's not what's important here.
We were attacked.
[sighs]
For this reason, I humbly request
the Sun King accompany us
to avoid any future attacks.
[Moctezuma] I will go with you
as compensation for your losses, sir.
Please, if you would accept,
I wish for you and your men
to be my guests of honor
at our Tóxcatl festival.
Your Highness is too generous.
I'd like to do my part
to avoid future misunderstandings
and to promote a better understanding
between both of our peoples.
I'd be very eager to hear your proposal.
Huey tlatoani, I volunteer in your stead
to be companion
to the esteemed Captain Cortés.
I'll answer his questions
and learn with him,
and from him.
Very well. Our war leader
shall accompany you henceforth.
[crowd murmuring, praying]
I gave my life to the king!
To our people!
How am I repaid?
With humiliation and disgrace.
Show Moctezuma his mistake.
He must see just how immaculate you are.
That your faith is pure and undeniable.
Yes. My faith.
With all of its power,
it will drive away Cortés
and that citlālim popōca.
Precisely.
Such zealous ingenuity
is why you are my chosen one.
[drumming & chatter in distance]
Do you also believe that the citlāl-pōca
up in the sky predicts misfortune?
[chuckles]
I think its appearance,
alongside your arrival,
is not a good sign.
We also used to believe that the comet,
the name we call it,
was the portent of a bad omen.
TLATELOLCO'S MARKET
But today we know
it's simply a floating ball of gas
revolving around our world
in the cosmos,
just like the sun and the moon.
Are you saying you believe
the sun revolves around this world?
It's been proven.
You don't think so as well?
No.
Our people have known for many suns now
that this world
isn't the center of anything.
Well, if you know so much...
[laughs] then why didn't you all
discover us before we discovered you?
Your people already have your own magic,
your own world.
What exactly do you want from us?
Oh, it doesn't matter how much you have,
because you can always
have something more.
Isn't it important
how you go about getting it?
Does your god approve the slaughter
of women and children?
In this world, our souls shall be tested.
The more difficult
the test we face becomes,
the more pure we shall be as a result.
That is not...
That's not an answer.
The sad reality
is that sometimes a leader will be forced
to make some decisions that are difficult.
But what if those decisions they make
are wrong?
When that happens,
I'll make sure you're the first to know.
Come here, my love! I want a hug!
Give me a big hug!
How I've missed you, my son.
Oh, it's been far too long.
I'm so happy
that you've finally come back home.
Yoka, come. Come. Come in.
Come in. Come in.
Why so serious?
You've always smiled
since you were little.
The work of the gods
is a serious matter, Mother.
You saw citlālim popōca?
It appeared the same day as Cortés
and all of his soldiers.
[sniffs]
And if we fail in our duty
to feed the gods,
it shall spell doom for our people.
[tense music playing]
Now I must ask you, Mother...
to put your trust in me.
Are you certain?
Moctezuma also agrees with you?
You're sure this is the right thing?
Yes.
[ominous music spikes]
Then we place our faith
in your hands, Yoka.
Without any risk,
there would be no reward.
This festival shall be the perfect moment.
You will be in charge.
The plan hinges on you.
So don't screw it up.
If we were to call
upon the Tlaxcaltecas,
then we wouldn't need
to divide our forces like this.
And why would you share with someone,
when you might easily have it
all for yourself, Pedro?
This way, we kill two birds
with one stone.
Am I interrupting?
No. Perfect timing.
We received some stupendous news just now,
and we're planning a surprise
for your people.
You do all enjoy surprises, hmm?
Well, that all depends on the surprise.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Hmm. Right.
Pardon me. I must go get ready.
Tonight things shall take
quite a radical turn.
Citlālim popōca's still there.
Cortés is still armed.
He taunts you at every turn.
Oh, he isn't taunting me,
for it's been I
that's taunted you since the start.
What are you saying, Huitzilopochtli?
[in demonic voice]
I am not Huitzilopochtli.
[laughing maniacally]
Tezcatlipoca?
Wretched deceiver!
But don't worry,
for you're still my chosen one.
Providing ways of testing people like you
is why I exist in the first place.
But what have I done to be punished so?
You were always far too eager
to dismiss the idea of your own sacrifice,
because you are nothing.
You're no one.
It must all be a dream.
It's only a nightmare.
Only a nightmare. Yes, yes.
Oh, and, you know,
your mother really had a point.
You should smile more, Yoka.
[sobbing]
How can I earn your forgiveness? [sobbing]
What? Mother? Is that you?
Tell me.
Ohh.
[sinister music playing]
Yes, I will, Mother.
I will make sure I enjoy life.
And smile. I promise.
I promise.
[laughing maniacally]
[suspenseful music playing]
You're mine.
[growling]
[whinnies]
[growls]
TÓXCATL'S FESTIVAL
[music stops]
[suspenseful music playing]
Do you want blood? I shall give you blood.
- Calm down, Pedro.
- [grunts]
I knew it was you in there, Yohualli.
I could sense you.
I saw it in the way
that you forged metal.
But I couldn't be certain.
That is, until I heard you quote the words
of your father.
Good. Now you won't be surprised
when I end your terror.
You are truly one hell of a warrior.
Too bad you aren't back in the city
to defend Moctezuma.
[laughs]
He could use the help
of someone of your talents
when we pay him a visit tonight.
No.
[ominous music playing]
[laughs] Yes. Did you think
this circus we put on here
was about you?
My friend, despite our history,
you are nothing but my dessert.
[growls]
You wretched bastard.
The captain's not going to like this.
MASSACRE IN THE GREAT TEMPLE
They started it. Now clean that filth up.
[ominous music playing]
[gasps]
Well... there you are, Your Highness.
You wanted a festival of blood.
Well, there you have it.
Hold him there.
And kill the others.
[gasps] What have I done?
No!
- [growls]
- [soldier] Kill him!
The Bat Demon has finally come!
Keep shooting!
Fire!
Seal those damn doors already.
"Without him, you don't exist."
She meant Tzinacan, not Cortés.
Acatzin, you and my tahtli
have been right all along.
Cortés is the bull.
And the Bat God is who protects me.
How could I not see it sooner?
I'm such an idiot.
[conch trumpeting in distance]
The horn of the king. He's summoning us.
Maybe he escaped.
I don't think that's the king.
I can only hope that we're not too late.
Did my father leave any gold?
[crowd murmuring]
[crowd clamoring angrily]
[gasps]
How dare they lay hands on the king?
[crowd gasps]
The life of your beloved king
depends on how well
you all behave yourselves.
Your own warriors will be in charge
of making sure you vermin comply.
[laughs] What I want is gold.
Not one piece or two.
You see, I want all of it.
All of the gold there is.
I want it now!
Yes.
This is exactly what I desire.
[chuckling coldly] Yes.
[crowd clamoring angrily]
For the love of Moctezuma!
No, stay back.
We don't want to have to hurt you.
[Cortés] Yes. [laughing maniacally]
More.
More!
I want it all!
[crowd clamoring angrily]
Why didn't you do it? Vengeance was yours.
It was within your grasp.
Because what happens here depends
on something far greater than me.
Cortés must stand and face our justice,
not my vengeance.
What's your plan, then?
Our warriors won't be able to fight.
Not while the king is being held prisoner.
That's why I have to free him.
Huh. How easy.
[solemn music playing]
- [Catwoman] Nice shrine.
- [gasps]
Better make that last prayer count.
- I'll go get the weapons ready.
- Bring all of them.
- You came here to help me?
- No.
- Just to say farewell.
- Farewell?
And that's all?
Don't get me wrong,
you're quite interesting.
But not enough to risk death.
Not when so many people
still depend on me.
I understand. I have to go and get ready.
I'm sure what you're planning to do
is probably insane.
But that doesn't mean it can't be
something pure and selfless either.
To catch a glimpse of that is rare.
I wanted to see it and wish you the best.
Thank you.
- [suspenseful music playing]
- [blades pierce flesh & guards grunt]
- [spear clangs]
- [gasps]
[gasps]
I beg you, Tzinacan,
spare me from your vengeance.
Pardon this bastard disgrace
of an emperor.
I thought I saw a god
where there was nothing but death.
[sobbing] Now I don't know what to do.
Cortés and his soldiers are not gods.
They're evil men who must be stopped.
Summon your warriors.
Tell them to rise and fight back.
Yes, O powerful Tzinacan.
[knife slits flesh]
Your sacrifice won't be for naught,
nor will your armor.
[laughing maniacally]
Move it! Hurry up!
[Cortés] What did I tell you, Pedro?
[Pedro] You told me that we would be rich
and that, after all the bribes
had been made,
we would all live like kings.
[seethes] If I see one more feather...
No more useless bird feathers!
Or I'll hang your king next to all those
who've dared provoke my anger!
[conch trumpeting]
Captain, we have to get out of here
right now.
[conch trumpeting]
Ahuaque tepehuaque, I have a message!
One that I heard directly!
It's from Tzinacan himself!
[crowd jeering]
Listen! Listen to me, I beg you!
I know I've failed you,
that I've made mistakes,
but the Bat God has visited me...
[groaning]
[laughing coldly]
It seems you've lost the trust
of your people, my lord.
Fear not.
There's one way
you may still help the cause.
[Moctezuma groaning]
And that's with your death.
[Yoka laughing maniacally]
Your fear is the reason
your empire dies with you.
- [laughing maniacally]
- [Yoka laughing maniacally]
[all gasp]
The teúles have slain Moctezuma.
[laughing maniacally]
Huey tlatoani has been murdered.
Now our plans have been ruined, you fools!
'Tis nothing our swords cannot remedy,
my captain.
To the palace. Until more troops arrive.
[all shouting]
[groans]
Just 50 meters more.
This is war, gentlemen. Give them hell!
Ocelotl!
At your service, great Tzinacan.
The horn. Summon all of our warriors. Now.
[horn blowing eerily]
O great and powerful Bat God,
grant me a weapon
that may vanquish the pale invaders.
Tzinacan, here are the weapons.
Never again.
Not one shall set foot in these halls!
They shall not take this sacred throne!
[all yelling in unison]
Attack!
[all shouting]
[dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
- [both whimper]
- [growls]
[Yoha growls]
[Yoha] Cortés!
- I am going to end you.
- Let's finish this.
[Ocelotl yells]
Get the cannon ready! Load it and fire!
Fire!
[warriors yelling]
It is inevitable, Yohualli.
There always must be a loser.
Fire!
[all gasp]
[soldiers yelling]
[Yoha] You were saying?
Yes.
I was saying... [laughs coldly]
...that God Almighty himself
always safeguards my victory.
Now let's see if your gods
move a single finger for you!
- [sword pierces flesh]
- [groaning]
[rumbling in distance]
In case you were wondering
what all of that wood we cut down was for.
[laughs coldly]
All that remains
is to leave it up to fate.
Damn you!
[gasps]
[warrior] For Huitzilopochtli!
Fire!
On all I hold sacred,
I will destroy this city.
I am your new god now!
[groaning]
I knew you'd come back.
[chuckles] Oh, really? I didn't.
My lord, you're wounded!
It's just a scratch.
- Did you do as I asked?
- I placed it at the top of the temple.
[Catwoman] All you have to do
is jump off this wall?
- I mean, you're joking me, right?
- No.
I followed what
all of their writings said.
It'll work. I've got to try. [grunts]
Are you sure
you'll be able to pull this off?
A little blood
has never stopped me before.
[Catwoman gasps]
[Yoha theme playing]
Here, for good luck.
I knew it! He is the chosen one!
[warrior] Tzinacan is here!
The Bat God has come
to fight alongside us!
[soldier] They've invoked
an infernal winged demon!
Impossible.
[warriors cheering]
[music turns intense]
[grunting]
Come on. I know we can pull through.
[yells]
[gasps]
[all cheering]
[snarling]
Gunners, load. And fire!
Don't stop shooting, soldiers of God!
Slaughter them all!
Tlacatlé, totecoé Tzinacan.
I know I should've been a better servant,
but please permit me
to see my mission through,
and I'll submit to your power
and take the path to Mictlán.
Fire!
No!
Axcan kema, tehuatl, nehuatl!
- What?
- [growls]
[growls]
Now is our moment!
Let's break their skulls!
[all yelling]
For Tenochtitlán!
[snarls]
[all gasp]
[breathing raggedly]
I will make you bow to me!
I'd rather die!
Those wounds look dire.
You won't last much longer.
I've got long enough
to bring you to justice.
[dramatic music playing]
Huh?
[soldiers screaming]
No, no!
No!
[Yoha groaning]
[woman 1] Citlālim popōca's gone!
- [man 1] The ill omen has ended!
- [woman 2] The gods have granted us mercy!
[man 2] We have been blessed
by the blood of the dead!
[all cheering]
[Cortés] Am I not your chosen one?
[sobbing]
Why have you forsaken me, Lord?
Why did I fail?
This can't be it.
Captain, perhaps we could improve
our strategy to take the city?
Send a message to Xicotencatl,
the leader of the Tlaxcaltecas.
Tell him that he and I must speak.
[Yoka] And repeat
the same stupid mistakes,
captain?
[laughs coldly]
I will...
make the throne yours.
[laughing maniacally]
- [poignant music playing]
- [crowd crying]
Look at you.
[sobbing]
Such a fool.
Look at what you've done.
A wise man told me once...
"Fear can kill you
or inspire you to action."
I'm glad I was there to save you.
You shouldn't have sacrificed
yourself like that.
Fate leaves me with no regrets.
Well...
maybe there's one thing I'll regret.
- [sobs softly]
- [sobbing] My boy.
[serene music playing]
Now rest in peace, Yohualli Coatl.
Young Shadow of Chief Toltecatzin.
Tzinacan's chosen one
and sacred Bat Protector.
Rest in peace.
Sleep until Quetzalcoatl...
our creator,
decides that he needs you back
in this world.
- [Catwoman] Do you think this is over?
- No.
I fear there's far more evil to come.
[ominous percussive music playing
& man chanting in gravelly voice]
[dramatic Nahuatl rock music playing]
[song ends]
[solemn organ music playing]
[music fades out]
[wheezing]
[ominous percussive music playing]
[music turns energetic]
[suspenseful percussive music playing]