Once upon a time, long, long ago...
Come on!
one unlucky sailor
fell under an ancient wicked curse.
And thusly, he became known
as the dreaded Flying Dutchman.
Legend has it,
the only way to lift his curse
is through the pure heart
of an innocent.
Henceforth, the Flying Dutchman
is doomed to wander the seas
in search of this magical soul.
A precious youth
with an innocent mind.
Will he find this soul?
Does such a soul even exist?
Who lives
in a pineapple under the sea?
Meow. Meow. Meow.
Good morning!
This is Rocket Fuel Randy on BKNI 101,
and I got the jet fuel
to get you rocking.
Are you ready to get the day started?
Chicka-chickahh
I'm ready.
Wah! Wah! Ooh!
Big things are happening today.
Today's the day! I just know it.
Things feel different.
My whole life is about to change.
Meow.
I know I said that yesterday, Gary.
- Meow.
- And the day before.
- And a bunch of days before that.
But today is different.
Big things in store.
Well, what's it say, Gary?
- Meow.
- What? That can't be.
- Gary, what's it really say?
- Meow-ow.
- Gary!
- Meow.
- Whoo!
Do you know what this means?
- Meow.
- For the last time,
we are not rehoming you.
No, this means
- I'm exactly 36 clams high!
- Meow.
I know it doesn't seem like much,
Gary,
but that half a clam I grew
changes everything.
- Meow.
- That's right, Gary-licious.
Everyone's gonna look at me
in a brand new way.
Big guy
Big, big guy
Because now... I'm a big guy.
SpongeBob Big Guy Pants okay
Big things 'bout to happen today
I woke up feeling a brand new way
Big guy!
SpongeBob Big Guy Pants okay
Tight fit, square hips
Doing a dance in my big guy pants
Big guy.
SpongeBob Big Guy Pants okay
Ain't a jellyfish, but I'm the catch
Feel like that fish
so I'm puffing my chest
Big guy.
Well, catch you later, Gare Bear.
I'm off to do some important stuff
that only big guys like me
are allowed to do.
Uh...
Whew. We're gonna need
a bigger doorway.
Meow.
Morning, Squidward!
Want to hear my big news?
Oh, sure.
Let me go mark some time
on my calendar.
Hmph!
Great! Let me know when!
Good morning, Patrick!
Good morning!
Who are you?
Patrick, it's me!
Grandma? You're upside down!
No, Patrick, it's me, SpongeBob.
You can't be SpongeBob.
He's far more diminutive.
- He's what?
- Of reduced stature.
- Come again?
- Vertically challenged.
- Say what now?
- He's shorter.
Patrick, I can't believe all I do
is grow half a barnacle overnight,
and now I'm 36 clams tall,
and you don't even recognize
your best friend!
Did you say you're 36 clams tall?
Yes!
You're a big guy now!
This guy's a big guy!
- So big!
- Really big!
- Big! Big! Big!
- Guy! Guy! Guy!
Look out, everyone. Really big.
Really guy.
Hey, Sandy,
notice anything different about me?
Howdy, SpongeBob.
Did you get a new pair of shoes?
Ouch!
Hi, Plankton!
Watch where you're going,
you big dummy!
Aw. Thanks for noticing.
Wait, no! Ow!
Patrick, I've never felt
so respected before.
Get used to it, buddy.
And do you know what the best part
of being a big guy is?
- What is it, Patrick?
- No, I'm asking.
It means I finally get to do
what every little guy dreams of doing
when they grow up.
You don't mean...
That's right.
Ride the big guy roller coaster
at Captain Booty Beard's Fun Park!
- Whoo-hoo!
This calls for an extra-special
bubble blow.
To Captain Booty Beard's!
Whoo-hoo!
- Gimme a "big!"
- Big!
- Gimme a "guy!"
- Guy!
- What does that spell?
- 36 clams high!
Don't waste my time, squirt.
Next!
Ugh, you again.
Congratulations.
- Patrick?
- It's official.
Don't make me call security.
Whoo-hoo! Yay!
Patrick?
Wait a minute!
Huh?
What's the matter?
I thought you were a big guy.
I am! I mean... I am.
I just, uh, promised
someone else that I'd ride with them,
that's all.
Oh, yeah? Who?
The guy who--
Um, I--
Mr. Krabs!
Oh. That makes sense.
- Phew.
- Let's go get him!
Sorry!
Coming through!
Heads up, Mr. Krabs!
It's time to ride the Shipwreck!
Whoo-hoo!
What are ya talking about, Patrick?
The roller coaster!
Get your head in the game.
Remember that big
terrifying roller coaster?
- Nope.
- We had a deal to ride it together.
- So I couldn't ride it
if you were too busy
to ride it with me. Hmm?
Wha--
Hoo-whoo-whoo-whoo!
Shipwreck!
Hmm.
Oh, right!
Our old roller coaster deal.
- Of course, yeah.
- Phew!
But, uh, we can't go today, lad.
Things are too busy around here.
Oh. Hear that, Patrick? Mr.--
Ow!
Shipwreck!
Thanks for covering for me, Mr. Krabs.
I don't know why I got so scared
when I saw that roller coaster.
I thought I was big enough.
Just 'cause you're taller
don't mean you're a big guy.
It doesn't?
Big guys are rough and tumble.
They don't blow bubbles.
Hmm. I guess not.
Being scared of roller coasters
ain't nothing to be ashamed of.
Glad you understand.
You must've been scared
of roller coasters, too,
- when you were my age.
- Well, I wouldn't really--
You were probably hiding-under-the-bed
kind of scared, weren't you?
Well, I, uh--
Maybe even cwyin'-fo'-Mama
kind of scared.
I wasn't crying for Mama!
Poopy-pee-pee-in-my-pantsy
kind of scared.
Am I right?
Get it straight, SpongeBob!
My pants were clean!
'Cause nothing ever scared me...
and nothing ever will!
But didn't you say being scared
wasn't anything to be ashamed of?
It ain't! For you.
But I'm different.
I wasn't blowing bubbles at your age.
I was risking me life
on the high seas!
I ate danger for breakfast!
Peril for lunch!
And adventure for dinner!
- Wha-what? -what? Really?
- That's right!
I was in command of me own vessel,
and sailed many a dangerous mile.
Tell me about your greatest adventure.
What if I told you I sailed
with the Flying Dutchman himself?
The Flying Dutchman?
The most pants-wettingly
scariest ghost
to ever roam the high seas?
Oh, my lucky brick.
Aye!
Like many a young sailor before me,
I longed for adventure.
And that's when
the Dutchman's hornpipe appeared.
I summoned
the cursed pirate,
and journeyed with him
to the deepest part of the sea.
A nightmare realm
called the Underworld.
It was filled
with ghostly pirates,
haunted hurricanes,
terrifying monsters!
Roar!
Whoa!
I faced 'em all
with steel in me backbone
and a cutlass in me claw!
Hyah!
Hoo-waa!
It was the greatest adventure
of me life!
Wow!
You're almost like
a real swashbuckler!
Almost? I am a real swashbuckler!
How do you think I earned this baby?
What is that?
It's a Swashbuckler Certificate.
It means I proved my bravery,
courageousness, daring, panache,
guts, grit,
moxie,
and intestinal fortitude.
Well, that's it!
I'd be a big guy if I could earn
my Swashbuckler Certificate.
And you could teach me!
Teach you? To be a swashbuckler?
I don't mean to laugh
in your face, but...
You're too scared
to even ride a roller coaster!
I can do it.
I want to be a brave swashbuckler
like you.
I'm ready.
SpongeBob, you're just
a bubble-blowing baby boy
who's not ready.
- But... But... But--
- Butts are for toilets!
Speaking of which,
the heads need swabbing, so git!
And no more talk
about being a swashbuckler.
Aww.
You're not ready...
not ready... not ready...
not ready... not ready!
Bravery. Courage.
I got to learn this stuff if I'm gonna
prove myself to Mr. Krabs.
You got this, SpongeBob.
Uh-oh.
Now what else did he say I needed?
- Daring.
- Oh, right. Daring.
- Guts.
- Definitely need those.
Panache.
Moxie. Intestinal fortitude.
- Okay, okay! Slow down!
- You spelled "fortitude" wrong.
It's F-O-R-T-l-T-U-D-E.
Mr. Krabs's certificate!
- Why do you have this?
- I always read in the bathroom.
I know I can do this.
I just need a chance to prove it!
Prove it...
Well, that's weird.
Oh, shrimp! The certificate!
Mr. Krabs won't like that.
- Oh, we got to get it, right?
- Uh, I'm not going in there.
Yeah, you'd have to be pretty brave
to go in there.
Hey, wait a minute!
- Patrick, this is it!
- It is?
Destiny is squeezing my buns.
Do you feel it?
Yeah!
This vent is just what I need
to start earning my
Swashbuckler Certificate.
You mean the one we lost?
Oh, yes, that one,
but also the one I'm gonna earn.
We lost two of them down there?
The hero's journey
starts with one squish.
Right behind you.
I'll catch up.
Ooh. Side adventure.
- Hmm. Left or right?
- Hmm.
Left! Definitely left!
Ow!
This must lead to the basement.
This must go deeper than the basement.
Wha--
Where am I?
Wow!
This must be Mr. Krabs's
swashbuckler sanctum.
Whoa, look at that.
And that.
And that! And that! And that!
Hi.
- Argh!
- Ahoy!
So, who's a bubble-blowing
baby boy now, huh?
Whoa!
Oh, who am I kidding?
I'll never be a swashbuckler.
Hmm?
Mysterious Glow...
Part Two.
Whoa.
This must be the hornpipe
Mr. Krabs took
from the Flying Dutchman!
"If a swashbuckler ye want to be,
"blow this horn and ye shall see."
Patrick,
I'm feeling destiny again.
Still nothing.
But don't let me slow you down.
Huh? That sounds like... Oh, no!
Huh?
SpongeBob! Get out of there!
Have fun.
Land ho!
Uh, you dropped your lucky brick.
I don't have a lucky brick.
On your feet,
ya sea-drinkin' polliwog!
You're in the company
of the Flying Dutchman!
Hmm.
Who blew my hornpipe?
Uh... I did.
Hmm.
SpongeBob, I'm comin'!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Weird place for a painting.
Move it, Squidward!
Hurry! Hurry!
Ah, let me take a look at ya.
Spit-shine shoes. Long socks.
Short pants.
Empty middle-distant stare.
Tell me, laddie, can ya blow a bubble?
Why...
you're the very swab
I've been lookin' for!
Really?
You look the kind of strappin' young
bubble-blowin' fella who wants...
nay, needs a chance
to prove his mettle.
He was just saying that
in the bathroom!
Quiet! You don't matter.
Very good.
That's why I blew the horn,
Mr. Dutchman, sir.
I need to prove I'm a big guy
by earning my
Swashbuckler Certificate.
Well, I'm here to offer you
a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
to prove your worth in the Underworld.
Just like Mr. Krabs!
Aw. But he doesn't think
I'm ready for that kind of thing.
Well, maybe he's right.
You might not be ready for...
swashbucklin'!
Swashbuckling?
Swashbucklin'.
Swashbuckling!
Ah!
Huh?
Whoa!
I'm ready!
Then it's a deal.
The Dutchman's deal.
Stupid passcode.
Four... fifteen... eight.
Permission to come aboard, sir!
Granted, shipmate!
- Me, too?
- Only if ya put on some pants.
I guess.
Pupil scan?
- Ooh!
- Whee!
Welcome aboard!
Blast these long eyes.
Come on.
Right this way to your quarters.
I'm gonna be a swashbuckler. Yeah!
What do ya think, Captain?
Pure heart, innocent mind,
desperate to be a big guy.
He's perfect.
Ahoy, Krabs!
Long time no see!
Please, don't take SpongeBob!
You'll never see him again.
He's the key to unlocking my curse.
SpongeBob!
Cinch up your trousers, me hearties.
A trip to the Underworld
is not for the faint of heart.
Oh, Squidward, what are we gonna do?
Sorry, I don't speak "do."
All me blusterin' and braggin',
fillin' that boy's head
with adventure!
I drove him right into
the tender mercies of that monster,
the Flying Dutchman.
Look, Eugene,
you can't blame yourself.
Mr. Krabs.
- Say what?
- Call me Mr. Krabs.
Okay.
- Look, "Mr. Krabs"...
- There ya go.
- You know what? It is your fault.
- You're right, Squidward.
- Which is why we got to go save him!
- Hold it.
You don't think
I'm actually participating
in this fool's errand, do you?
I know you are.
Because if you don't, I'll demote you
to fry cook. Permanently!
But the grease inflames my acne!
So, just the two of us
against the Dutchman, huh?
There's three in this crew,
Mr. Squidward.
- Meow.
- Why was I worried?
Nice to see
me old gear still fits, eh?
Squawk!
What the-- Huh?
Hmm. Not bad.
And to get us there in style,
say hello to our noble vessel,
The Patty Blaster!
Hey, we might actually be safe
on this adventure, driving a...
Winnebago.
We can't lose in a "Win" -nebago,
Mr. Squidward.
Hilarious.
Squawk! Hilarious!
Do you even know
how to find SpongeBob?
Aye, Squidward, but it won't be easy.
The Dutchman's taken SpongeBob
to the deepest,
most dangerous part of the sea.
A realm of dark magic
called the Underworld.
Under where?
Underwear.
Well, how do we get there?
First we've got to find
the magical portal.
Then navigate the Slime River
through unimaginable terrors.
And if we survive,
this is where we find SpongeBob.
Meow!
Challenge Cove?
That's where the Dutchman
can use SpongeBob to break his curse!
And if we don't get down there in time
to stop him,
our favorite fry cook
is doomed!
Now saddle up!
We got no time to waste!
Full disclosure,
that's farther than I thought
we'd get.
Pop the clutch, Gary!
Whoo-hoo!
Welcome to the Underworld!
Huh?
Maybe I'm not ready for this place.
Ah, yes, the Underworld
can be terrifying to most.
But not to a brave big guy
like yourself.
You think I'm brave?
Aye, you laugh at danger!
I mean...
You can do better than that.
I can't hear you.
Don't worry, Patrick.
We laugh at danger!
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
Incoming!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo!
- Ooh!
- Wow!
Uh... Huh?
You were right, Dutchman.
I'm not afraid of the Underworld!
Glad to hear it, lad.
I'm not afraid, either!
Who cares?
SpongeBob, I want you to think of me
as your swashbuckling guru,
and your friend.
Aw.
Look! More danger!
Here, kitty, kitty.
Nyah-ah!
Captain, this lubber
is a complete barnacle brain.
Are you sure he's the one?
True, he don't have physical prowess
or pirating ability,
but the boy's got
the very thing we need...
Staggering stupidity.
He won't figure out the truth
until it's way too late,
when we finally break my curse!
Break your curse!
My curse!
Your curse!
What are we laughing about?
Oh, uh, nothin', lad.
Accordin' to the map,
the gates to the Underworld lie
in the most horrible place imaginable.
Bikini Bottom High.
- Aye, dangerous waters.
- Ew.
- Nice ride.
- Losers.
See what I mean?
Hey!
Yeah!
- Whoa! Whoa!
- Ahh!
- Whoa!
Right! Take a right!
Hmph!
Is that Squidward Tentacles?
Coach Tuna?
You still owe me laps.
Incoming fire!
- Ah!
- Squawk!
Hah.
Huh?
Hey!
Ow!
Meow! Meow! Meow!
Huh?
We're close.
I can smell it.
Me, too.
Are you Davy?
No, man, I'm Phil. Davy's over there.
Thar she blows!
Davy Jones' locker.
The entrance to the Underworld.
If you're
gonna be a swashbuckler,
you got to dress the part.
Now step out, lad.
Let's get a look at ya.
Are you sure this is
a swashbuckler outfit?
Absolutely! Standard issue.
Really? Wh-- Whoa!
That safety suit
should keep him alive long enough
to break my curse.
Your curse.
Come on, Barb... read the room.
Hold it!
No! No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no!
This is all wrong!
Let's find something else.
Wait! Mind your business!
Fashion show! This feels much better.
I don't think that's quite right, lad.
I agree, Dutchie.
It's missing one thing.
Achoo!
Pink guy's drivin' me nuts!
He's distracting the fool.
Their friendship is a problem.
That's why we work
so well together, Barb.
We've never been friends.
Exactly! I-- Wait, what?
Yeah, we'll have to take care
of that one.
Land ho!
Whoa!
Whoa
We've arrived at Challenge Cove.
The place where you'll finally
become a swashbuckler.
Whoo-hoo!
Meow.
Are you sure about this?
Don't worry, Mr. Squidward.
I've got everything under control.
These creatures
look friendly enough, huh?
That was the scariest thing
I ever saw!
Till I saw that.
- Huh?
Meow.
Here's an idea. We go home
and you hire a new fry cook!
What do you think, Gary?
SpongeBob's first Krusty Krab ID card.
Look at him. So... yellow.
That answers that.
Is that where we have to go?
Aye!
To succeed, you must reach that X.
And then I'll get my certificate!
Right after you make it up
to the next X.
And then up to that one.
And up to the next one.
And then up again. And up there.
How high do I have to go?
To the top, lad!
If you make it there
and blow that hornpipe,
oh, you'll become a swashbuckler.
Mr. Krabs will be so proud!
- If I can do it.
- No, it'll be easy!
We'll get through
these challenges together.
Starting with, uh, oh...
intestinal fortitude.
To begin,
we'll walk that path until we--
Not so fast!
You said we have to walk this path.
But this is clearly a road.
- You're right, Patrick. It is a road.
- I know.
Tartar sauce!
Now what are we gonna do?
I know.
What difference does it make?
You say "road," I say "path."
I say "potato," you say "po-tah-to!"
No, I don't. I say "string cheese."
Ooh.
- String cheese.
- A road of string cheese.
- String Cheese Road!
- String Cheese... Expressway!
String Cheese... Castle!
I can't take it!
Barb, no!
Killing him might tip him off.
What do you say we go beat
these challenges, road or no road?
Wait!
Watch out for the Skeleton Guardians!
- Huh?
- What?
Watch out for the-- what? -oof--
Watch out for the what?
- oof?
Not sure what that means.
Plus, it's hard to hear with all the
"cck-oo-cck-oo-cck-oo" sounds.
Well, whatever it is,
I'm sure it's not that important.
Patrick, I think these are the guys
who are gonna...
fortify our intestines!
Yay!
Barb, we got to reach that nitwit
before he gets killed!
Desperately trying, sir!
What do you think, path or road?
Can someone
hand me my eyebrows?
Swordplay, huh?
I think my skills will satisfy.
Dodge! Parry! Thrust! Plié.
Patrick!
What if Mr. Krabs was right
and I am just
a bubble-blowing baby boy?
That wouldn't be good.
Oh, Patrick, what are we gonna do?
Yer askin'
the wrong question, lad!
Mr. Krabs?
If ya want to get out of this pickle,
you're gonna have to start actin'
like a rough-and-tumble swashbuckler.
Well, how do I do that?
Ya start by askin' the right question.
It's not,
"What are we gonna do?"
It's, "What would I do?"
What would I do?
Huh? No. No, no. Me!
What would me do?
Not you. Me! Mr. Krabs!
What would I do?
Oh! That makes way more sense.
So, how does it-- Does this end or--
Wake up!
Patrick,
maybe if we act like Mr. Krabs,
we can make our way through this.
Why didn't I think of that?
Because you're not a Swashbuckler
Certificate recipient in the making!
Barb! Do ya spy the barnacle?
Sorry, sir. I don't-- Wait.
- Hey, look at me!
- Huh?
Argh.
I'm no bubble blower.
I'm a rough-and-tumble swashbuckler.
Rough and tumble as the day is long.
They don't come
as rough and tumble as me.
Rough and tumble, tumble and--
Huh.
Look at me!
Rumble and tumble!
SpongeBob? These look like...
...our intestines.
And they're fortified!
This means
I passed the first challenge!
Whoo-hoo!
- Look at mine wiggle.
- Huh?
Look at them. Wiggle, wobble!
Peekaboo!
Hairdo-do!
What are those idiots doing?
What is happening?
I don't know
how he did it, Barb.
That fool must really be the one.
I think you're right, sir. Look.
Yes?
Whoa!
Yes!
Huh?
- SpongeBob?
- Uh-oh.
You know what that means, Mr. Krabs.
I'm in deep shrimp.
SpongeBob!
Hold on, lad!
Whoo-hoo!
Onto challenge number two!
Shello?
Bad news, sir. Krabs is following us.
What? No, no, no!
If he catches up, he'll tell SpongeBob
the truth and ruin everything.
Oh, Barb,
it's been so long and I'm so close.
I wouldn't worry about Krabs, sir.
He ain't gonna last long
in the Underworld.
Huh? Where is that music comin' from?
Mmm. Not bad.
Huh?
Greetings, travelers.
Come play with us.
Come play?
Cover your ears, Squidward.
Those are Sirens, temptin' us
into a smooth jazz trap.
Later, losers.
Squidward. We got to save SpongeBob.
There's no time for a solo!
There's always time for a solo.
Meow.
Well, music lovers,
what do you think? Ack!
Help me!
Ooh, now we got to save that
good-for-nothin'
easy-listenin' layabout.
Help me!
Whoa! Put me down!
There's got to be somethin' in here
that'll help Squidward.
Hmm.
Whoa!
- Huh?
- Better hurry up!
Or instead of being a big guy,
I'll be a dead guy.
Whoa!
Bandages, no. Antiseptic, no.
Flare gun, no. Breath mints, no.
Huh? Whoa-hoo! Agh!
Help!
- Squawk!
- Oh, no, you don't!
Uh-oh.
No more wastin' time, Squidward.
We might already be too late!
You know, I think we cracked the code
to these challenges.
All I got to do is keep acting
like Mr. Krabs,
and I'll be swashbuckling in no time.
To Mr. Krabs.
- Big guys!
Oh, what are they doin' now?
Uh, eh... You can
celebrate later, lad!
Let's head to the next challenge!
SpongeBob?
Whee!
His pink friend
is slowing us down.
Oh, just give me five minutes
with him, sir.
I'll explain
how we do things around here!
Okay, chill out, Barb.
I have a better idea.
SpongeBob.
Swashbucklers don't spend their time
seahorsin' around.
Really?
What's the swashbuckling stance
on giggling?
Not good!
What about butt wiggling?
Maybe you don't want this
bad enough, SpongeBob.
That's not true.
I want to be a big guy
more than anything.
Well, uh, if you want
to be someone big,
you're gonna have to leave
some of your small ways behind. Hmm?
Oh. Hmm.
Okay. No more seahorsing around.
Smart lad!
Now, let's get you
to challenge number two!
Ow!
Welcome to the Underworld
for what promises
to be an exciting contest.
We're just moments away
from challenge number two.
Tell me, Barb,
will it be even more difficult
than the last challenge?
Uh, yes.
There's, uh, no telling
what's lurking along
that path to the platform.
It could be a charging Bull Clam.
Or a terrifying JellyHook.
Hope it's not my
third-grade math teacher.
She scares the heck out of me!
- Know what I'm saying?
- You're on my foot.
Let's meet our challenger!
Standing at a full 36 clams high
and hailing all the way
from Bikini Bottom,
my best friend,
SpongeBerb SquareShorts.
This bubble blower
has got a lot to prove
if he ever wants to show the world
he's a swashbuckler.
Challenge number two won't be easy.
But I believe in you, big guy.
Now, go get 'em.
Big guy.
Big guy. Big guy. Big guy. Big guy.
Big guy. Big guy. Big guy.
Yikes!
Yeow!
Okay, SquarePants, you can do this.
What would I do?
Hmm.
- Huh?
Whoa!
Whee!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, my God! Yeah!
Yeah, baby!
Whoo-hoo!
Ooh, your lucky brick.
- Huh?
- Ooh!
Huh?
Whoo!
Hmm.
Whee!
Huh?
En garde!
Huh-ho!
Hyah!
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
We interrupt this movie
for an important message
from Paramount Studios.
This picture's gone completely
off the rails!
The only thing that can save it
is some serious star power.
Get Sandy Cheeks
in this movie, pronto!
Howdy-do, SpongeBob!
Huh.
That's not what I meant!
Who is it?
Hey, what--
Get out of here! Get out!
Huh?
- Whoo-hoo!
- Yeah!
Boy, if only Mr. Krabs
could see me now.
He'd finally see
what I've been seein' all along,
a swashbuckler in the makin'.
- Really?
- Really.
But remember,
if you want to become a true big guy,
you have to stay focused.
Got it. Focused.
Bubble break!
You had me at "bubble."
Let's do a triple-dog
backslash wand-grabber.
With a banana-slap twist-blister!
Hmm?
- Huh?
- Yeah, um...
sounds fun, Patrick,
but maybe we shouldn't
do this anymore.
What?
Well, it's just-- You know, it--
I have this other thing I'm doing.
You mean,
you don't want to blow bubbles
with me?
I really want to, but...
- That's okay.
- It's just that I should...
No, it's fine.
- Pat.
- I'm not crying!
It's just raining on my face!
Ah, don't worry about your friend.
You can make it up to him
once you're a swashbuckler.
Well, I guess.
Good lad.
Just keep your eyes on the prize.
Come on. Almost there.
You're pushing this tub way too hard.
We can't stop
until we reach SpongeBob!
Can't stop. Won't stop.
No stop!
We stopped.
Oh, I'm so sorry, me boy.
Why didn't I just show ya how to be
a swashbuckler when ya asked?
You never told me how much you cared.
Well, I couldn't. Emotions that
are emotional are hard for me!
Well, it doesn't matter now.
- What?
- You're stuck, so I'm doomed.
Goodbye!
Quick! We got to fix this camper!
We got to fix it!
Oh, sure.
Let's go pop into an
auto parts store and get what we need.
- Meow.
- Huh?
Good eye, Gary!
Does this seem a little convenient?
Nonsense.
These big-box stores are everywhere!
Meow.
Spare tire, exhaust pipe,
tire iron, and oil.
Oil, oil, where's the oil?
Just ask somebody.
Hello! We need some oil over here!
Hello?
Hello!
Where is everybody?
- Hello?
- That might be our cue to go.
- Meow-ow.
- Huh. There's someone's shoe.
And there's the other one.
What kind of big-box store is this?
Run!
I see the exit!
Meow-ow.
What's the plan, Mr. Krabs?
Meow.
Meow-ow.
It looks hungry.
And it's getting closer!
Meow.
Say the word.
Anytime now.
Sooner the better!
Really?
Meow.
Huh?
Hey, I found the oil!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Bye-bye, Krabby.
Huh?
Whoa...
Barb?
What do you do when your best friend
doesn't want to blow bubbles anymore?
Uh...
Well, I, uh...
- Yeah, I, uh...
- Thanks. Makes a lot of sense.
This is it, lad.
The last challenge.
Finish this
and you'll become a swashbuckler!
Let's do it.
Ready, Dutch?
Bang it.
Ta-da!
Daring, bravery,
courageousness,
panache, guts, grit, moxie...
...and intestinal fortitude!
You did 'em all!
I knew you were special, lad.
Whoa!
Look at that!
Inside those doors,
you'll stand at the altar,
blow the hornpipe,
and a swashbuckler you'll become.
And once I get my certificate,
Mr. Krabs will finally see
that I'm a big guy.
Then I can do what every little guy
dreams of doing when he grows up,
ride that big guy roller coaster.
Yes, roller coa-- Uh, wait.
You mean your dream is
to ride a roller coaster?
Well, of course. We all have dreams.
What's yours?
What?
Well, uh...
I dream of a wonderful world
above the waves,
where the sun shines in your face
and the wind blows through your hair.
What's this magical place called?
Santa Monica!
Look at me,
chatterin' like a cabin boy.
- Let's get goin'!
- Stop right there!
Good thing this bird is allergic
to shellfish!
Mr. Krabs?
Ooh! Tartar sauce!
Are you okay, boy-o?
Did ya get hurt at all?
Any bumps? Bruises? Scratches?
I'm so glad we found you!
- Who's "we"?
- Me, Squidward and Gary.
We're here to rescue ya! From him!
Whoa! Well, now hold on, Krabs!
Oh, I'm not in any danger.
The Flying Dutchman's been helping me
become a swashbuckler.
- Just like you.
- Oh.
Well, ya see, I, uh...
You want to tell him, or should I?
Tell me what?
It's about me past, lad.
I embellished a few o' the...
tsk, uh, finer details.
I did spend me youth at sea,
but I wasn't the captain.
Wait a minute.
You were a fry cook?
Aye. And like you,
I dreamed of bein' a swashbuckler.
But nobody believed in me.
They said I was a--
Bubble-blowin' baby boy!
I was so ashamed.
And that's when something
called out to me.
It was the Dutchman's hornpipe.
Huh?
The dirty deceiver promised
to make me a swashbuckler,
and lured me to the Underworld.
But I froze when I saw
that terrifyin' place.
The Underworld shivered me timbers
and I ran home, tail between me legs.
I had many adventures at sea, boy,
but I never did become a swashbuckler.
But, what about
the Swashbuckler Certificate?
Well, about that...
I've been battling
the horrors of the Underworld
for a Kids' Menu?
I thought it looked familiar.
I'm sorry I lied, lad.
I just couldn't bear
for you to know I was a coward.
But I'm tellin' you the truth now.
The Dutchman is trickin' ya!
No, he's not. He's just helping me
become a swashbuckler.
I thought you'd be proud of me.
Instead, you're treating me
like I'm still just a bubble blower.
That's right.
Krabs has never believed in you.
Come with me and blow that hornpipe.
Show him you're a real swashbuckler.
The biggest of the big guys.
I'm ready.
No, SpongeBob!
Wait!
Hurry, lad. On the pedestal.
SpongeBob! Don't do it!
You'll see, Mr. Krabs.
I'm gonna be a big guy.
No! No, no, no!
Come on now!
Hurry.
SpongeBob!
Meow, meow, meow, meow!
- No!
- Too late, Krabby!
I'll save ya, lad!
Gotcha!
No, no, no, no, no!
Whoa!
Ooh!
Swashbuckler shine!
It's not swashbuckler shine.
Yeah, no. It ain't.
Huh?
No!
Squawk.
My curse is lifted!
- What?
- I tricked you.
Oh, you're such a big guy,
ready to be a swashbuckler!
It's all been a big lie,
and you fell for it.
Huh?
Oh, no.
Hang on to your square derriere.
Guess who's cursed now?
Meow.
All hail the new FlyingBob DutchPants!
What?
Oh, Mr. Krabs,
you were right about him.
Mr. Krabs!
Ugh!
It looks like you got
a little Dutchman on you, too.
It's a double Dutchman, sir.
You tricked me.
Well, you wanted to be
a big guy swashbuckler, didn't you?
So what are you complainin' about?
You should be thankin' me.
No. Please, Mr. Dutchman, sir.
I changed my mind.
I don't want to be
a swashbuckler anymore.
Oh, don't fret, sailor.
All you need to do
is find someone to trick
into trading places with you.
It only took me...
Let's see, uh...
500 years!
Oh!
Now I finally get to go home.
Yep, we got to run.
Huh?
Whoa!
Wait. Aren't you taking me?
Why would I do that?
I don't need you anymore.
What have I done?
It's not your fault, lad.
It was my lyin' that led ya here.
And now we're cursed
to be ghosts forever.
Forever?
Forever.
Forever, forever?
Forever, forever.
Forever, forever, forever, forever,
forever, forever, forever, forever?
forever, forever.
Forever.
- One more.
- Forever!
Ghost captain's log,
Tuesday, the 4,732nd,
in the month of Forever,
in the year of Eternity.
I had it all. Good job, great friends.
I should've stayed a bubble blower.
You'll always be
a bubble blower to me.
I'm sorry, Patrick.
I can't believe what a jerk I was.
Can you ever forgive me?
Oh, there's got to be
something we can do.
I'm afraid there's nothin' we can do.
You made a deal with the Dutchman.
It's hopeless.
Oh, no!
Barb?
We're not lettin'
that son of a perch win yet.
I've read the "Dutchman's Deal,"
and I know what's in the fine print.
"Pursuant to the provisions outlined
"in the official Pirate Curse
Rule Book of 1586,
"it is hereby stipulated that
"the recipient of
an officially designated curse
"is afforded the chance to rectify
and nullify all banes
"and burdens through demolition,
"if done so within the morrow,
and so on and so forth, et cetera."
Of course!
Break the horn before sunset
and you'll reverse the curse!
How'd you understand that?
I don't know.
Oh, but the Pirate Formerly Known as
the Flying Dutchman
took it to the surface.
The surface? I can get us there!
Remember, you can only go to
the surface this one time.
When the sun sets,
the curse is permanent.
I told you! I don't know!
Woo-woo! Gee.
Bye, everybody!
Hopefully not forever!
Bye, SpongeBob!
You know, for a doofus, you've got
a pretty good head on your shoulders.
What? Where?
Get it off! Get it off! Get it off!
Come on.
I'll give you guys a ride home.
Remember, boy-o,
break the hornpipe
and reverse the curse.
Right. Break the pipe,
reverse the curse.
- Break the pipe.
- Reverse that curse.
Reverse that curse.
- Break it. Break it.
- Reverse it. Reverse it.
Break,
breaky-breaky-break-break.
B-B-B-B-Break that curse!
- Whoa!
- Whoo-hoo!
We made it!
Oh, but it's so big up here.
The Dutchman could be anywhere.
Well, we better find him quick.
There's no tellin' what trouble
that cutthroat pirate will cause.
I'm here, surface world.
And I am ready...
...to partay!
Let's go!
Come on!
Whoo-hoo!
Hey!
Yoink!
Santa Monica.
Paradise!
- Break that pipe.
- Reverse that curse.
Huh?
Come on, pull.
- You?
- Quick, grab the hornpipe!
Huh?
No! What are you doin' here?
I served my time as Dutchman
and I'm not goin' back!
You will if we break that hornpipe.
Well, then I'll just have to take it
to the one place you'll never go.
Oh, no.
A roller coaster?
Why did it have
to be a roller coaster?
Come on, SpongeBob,
we got to stop him!
Hey! There he is!
- Dude! No cuts.
- Oh, right. Sorry.
Hmph.
Arr!
- Arr!
Thirty minutes later.
Arr!
Next.
See ya at sunset!
After those pasty white legs!
Whoa!
- He's gettin' away!
- Jump!
- Yeah!
Made it!
Oh, no.
I'm on a roller coaster!
Roller coaster!
Huh?
Oh, ya got to be kiddin' me.
Well, hold on, SpongeBob ScaredyPants.
I got to get off this thing!
No, SpongeBob! What you got to do
is stay on this thing,
and get that hornpipe.
How am I gonna do that?
Ya start by askin' the right question.
What would you do?
No, not me! That's... Look.
You. SpongeBob. What would you do?
Huh? How's that gonna help?
You said it yourself.
I'm not a big guy.
I'm just a bubble blower.
Well, I was wrong
about bubble blowers, okay?
They got more panache, guts, grit,
moxie and intestinal fortitude
than any swashbuckler I ever met.
SpongeBob,
big guys aren't rough and tumble.
They're... smart.
And loving, and brave, and playful,
and just fun to be around!
Are you talkin' about me, Mr. Krabs?
Of course I am!
And you're the only one
who can break our curse.
So ask yourself, what would you do?
Well, I'd blow a bubble.
Then get blowin',
ya bubble-blowin' big baby guy!
That sun's about to set.
Nyah, nyah!
Hmm.
Oh, yeah. Whoa!
Hold on, lad!
Don't look down, bubble boy!
I'm coming for you.
Persistent little barnacle.
Give me that!
Bleaaghh!
Weiner, ten o'clock!
Arr!
Huh?
- Huh?
- I gotcha, lad!
Nice catch, Mister K!
Now let's go get that hornpipe.
Whoa-whoa-whoa... yow!
Miss me?
I came here to do two things,
kick butt and blow bubbles.
Looks like I'm all out of butt.
Huh?
Hey,
what are ya doin'?
Cut it out!
Get back!
Seriously?
Blowin' a bubble
was your big plan, baby boy?
Huh?
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Huh?
Oh, the poor boy! He's lost his mind!
I'm fine, Mr. Krabs.
It just tickles my belly.
- Ain't ya scared?
- No, it's really fun!
Huh?
It doesn't even matter.
Once the sun sets, I win!
Mr. Krabs, look!
It's your bubble!
Hmm.
Hey, Dutchman.
What happens again when the sun sets?
I win.
I win!
Huh? My hornpipe!
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
Whoo-hoo!
No!
What?
Fish sticks!
Avast, Barb!
Uh, no hard feelin's
about leavin' ya behind.
What say we pick up
where we left off?
Well, not exactly where we left off.
Outdone by a bubble blower!
For proving his silliness,
good nature, gaiety,
merriment, sense of humor,
high spirits
and bubble-blowing ability,
it is my great honor to present
SpongeBob SquarePants
with the official Big Guy Certificate.
Uh, is this where I order?
Wow. It's...
It's beautiful.
And to honor our beloved fry cook,
all Krabby Patties are full price!
- Hey, wait a second.
- Huh?
Thank you, Mr. Krabs.
But I have to say,
I couldn't have done it
without my best,
bubble-blowing buddy
in the whole wide world...
- Congratulations.
- ... Patrick.
Your name is Patrick, too?
I think he means you.
This award is half yours.
Yay!
Here's your half. I win!
Meow.
I'd also like to thank
someone very special to me.
My boss, my mentor, and most of all,
my friend, Mr. Krabs.
Oh, SpongeBob.
This calls
for an extra-special bubble blow!
- Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo.
- Ack-ack-ack-ack-ack-ack!
- Aw!
- Huh?
Bikini Bottom Bubble Hug!
Is this really necessary?
Meow.
You're right, Gary.
It does feel like something's missing.
I can't believe they forgot me!
Those lousy, stinking bunch of...
Who do you think you are?
Mr. Big Stuff!
Grah
Stop playing with 'em, Riot
Big Guy, Big Guy
Big, Big Guy, Big Guy
SpongeBob, Big Guy, pants okay
Big Guy, Big Guy
Big, Big Guy, Big Guy, grah
SpongeBob, Big Guy, pants okay
Move to wake up, I'm feeling my best
I bend over, I do my little stretch
Ain't a jellyfish, but I'm the catch
Feel like that fish
so I'm puffing my chest
I blow bubbles so big like Mrs. Puff
I be locked in like
no, this isn't luck
Eating fancy like, no, this isn't chum
Who my bestie, like everything fun
Big Guy, Big Guy
Big, Big Guy, Big Guy
SpongeBob, Big Guy, pants okay
Big Guy, Big Guy
Big, Big Guy, Big Guy
SpongeBob, Big Guy, pants okay
Big things 'bout to happen today
I woke up feeling a brand-new way
Facing the world in a brand-new way
SpongeBob, Big Guy, pants okay
Tight fit, square hips
Doing a dance in my Big Guy pants
The baddest, the top of the list I am
And all my pearls
they came fresh out of clam
Big Guy, Big Guy
Big, Big Guy, Big Guy
SpongeBob, Big Guy, pants okay
Big Guy, Big Guy
Big, Big Guy, Big Guy
SpongeBob, Big Guy, pants okay
Move to wake up, I'm feeling my best
Big things 'bout to happen today
I bend over, I do my little stretch
I woke up feeling a brand-new way
Ain't a jellyfish, but I'm the catch
Facing the world in a brand-new way
Feel like that fish
so I'm puffing my chest
SpongeBob, Big Guy, pants okay
Big Guy, Big Guy
Big, Big Guy, Big Guy
SpongeBob, Big Guy, pants okay
Big Guy, Big Guy
Big, Big Guy, Big Guy
SpongeBob, Big Guy, pants okay