[water trickling]
[seagulls squawking]
[waves crashing]
["Nanä" by Polo & Pan plays]
[woman] On vacation,
you can be anyone you want.
You can do anything you want.
You can spend an entire day at the beach.
Nothing but the warm sun on your face
and clear skies above.
[chuckles]
Or being on vacation
transports you
into another version of yourself.
Because on vacation, you strike up
conversations with fellow travelers.
…his parents' place.
[laughter]
["Nanä" continues]
[snickers]
You're more outgoing, more confident.
[whispers] Sorry.
No, you know what it is?
On vacation, you're free.
Free to nourish your soul.
Free to follow your heart.
And maybe you'll get swept off your feet
by a handsome stranger.
["Nanä" continues]
Uh...
Or maybe you just get
some much-needed alone time.
Because being alone on vacation is great.
There's no commitments.
No expectations.
Anything could happen.
You're free, remember?
Free to slip in that fancy shower.
- [slips]
- [thuds]
Free to lie dead for days
because you put
the "do not disturb" sign up.
Your corpse gradually decomposing
until a cleaning lady
comments on the putrid...
[woman 2] Poppy.
["Nanä" stops]
Swapna.
Did I just read the words
"gradually decomposing" on your screen?
No.
Well… yeah.
But I was just, um…
I was just trying something new.
And this isn't done, like, at all.
It's just, um…
It's all a part of my… process.
- Your process is quite disturbing.
- [Poppy] Fair.
But, I mean, don't you ever
find travel a little
lonely?
Poppy… [chuckles impatiently]
…need I remind you
that you take vacations for a living.
People would kill for this job.
In fact, five years ago, in there,
you told me you would kill for this job.
- I know.
- So then write like it!
Make me burn with jealousy
for your young, cool,
carefree, jet-setting life.
And if I don't at least consider
leaving my husband and children
after reading your article,
then you are not doing it right, okay?
[Poppy] Mm-hm.
Okay.
[Swapna sighs]
[pleasant ethereal music plays]
[ethereal music becomes upbeat]
[Poppy] Yes,
I am back in America safe and sound.
[woman] Poppy!
We had no idea you were back.
I'm sorry I didn't call.
I know.
How are the plants?
How are my plants? [Sighs]
Mom, it's a massacre.
There should be tribunals
about what I've done to houseplants.
Do you have any recipes that use
one shriveled lime, hot sauce,
mustard, and no other ingredients?
What? No.
- Oh.
- [phone beeps]
Tell me, how was the trip?
[phone beeps]
Uh, hey, I gotta go.
Yeah, I gotta go. I love you.
[phone clicks]
Hey, David, what's going on?
What's going on?
Well, I'm getting married in Barcelona.
Yeah, I heard that. Congratulations.
Yeah, why haven't you RSVP'd?
I sent you an invite, like, months ago.
[whispers] Shit.
Um, yeah, I'm so sorry.
I, um... Well, I was in Prague.
And then Kyoto, and, um…
I gotta get back in the whole…
The mail situation because, you know...
But it's fine because I found it.
Wow.
Ooh, pretty!
Shit, it's this weekend?
I'm sorry, David. I don't think I can go.
You have more airline points than God.
Just book it.
No, it's not about that.
I'm supposed to be in Santorini
for this hotel opening.
Boo!
Also, I don't really think Sarah and Alex
would want me to be there.
Wait, he didn't tell you? They broke up.
- Uh…
- I knew things were weird.
I didn't think they were that weird.
Me neither.
You were best friends.
You'll figure it out.
We've got an open bar.
- Who is that?
- It's Poppy.
- Hi, Poppy!
- Nam says hi.
Hi, Nam.
[David] Poppy, please,
you're good at a wedding.
You make my family fun somehow, okay?
I need you here. Whatever happened
between you and Alex, get over it.
Okay? And get your ass to Barcelona.
- [inhales sharply] I don't… David, it's…
- [line disconnects]
Hello? David?
David?
[phone clicks]
[sighs]
[serene music plays]
[snickers]
[music turns energetic]
[Poppy] Alex?
Hi!
Hey, hey!
I'm Poppy. And you're Alex, duh.
Whoa, do you go to Boston College?
I'm just messing with you.
I love the school spirit.
Go… Eagles? Is it the Eagles?
I swear to God, I go here too.
Thank you so much again for the ride.
You're much better than the bus.
Also, I cannot believe there's
another person here from Linfield, Ohio,
and we have never met before.
I know you went to West Linfield
and I went to East Linfield,
but still, crazy.
I mean, two ships
passing in the night, right?
Thank God Bonnie suggested we carpool.
You're an hour late.
Didn't you say 8:00-ish?
Well, it's 9:00.
And I wouldn't say "ish."
Sorry, that's my bad.
I had to get breakfast.
I get weird if I don't eat.
[Alex] Uh…
What are you doing?
You blocked my whole
field of vision, so you know...
- Ooh! Gnarly! Are you okay?
- Yeah.
That was a good one.
It's funny because I thought
you were firing me from our road trip.
No, I just really wanna get on the road.
It's a long drive.
I'd like to get ahead of the traffic.
Dude, I'm sure we'll be fine.
- [cars honking]
- [train horn blasting]
[Alex sighs impatiently]
So tell me everything.
Like, just from the top.
Were you born in Linfield?
Natural? C-section?
[Alex sighs]
Okay, I know you're mad at me,
but when you taste this breakfast burrito,
you'll agree it was worth it.
- I got you one too.
- I'm good. I don't wanna make a mess.
No, seriously, I can hold it here,
and then you can take a bite.
I'm good. Really.
All right. Your loss, honestly.
It's the best...
I have an idea.
Maybe we just don't talk for a little bit.
[Poppy crinkles foil]
- [Alex sighs]
- [Poppy chews loudly]
[Poppy] Mm!
It needs hot sauce.
Can you just not...
This Tapatío really takes it over the top.
Oh!
That is spicy!
[Poppy chuckles]
Might've overdid it.
This will take the edge off.
- I'm sorry, can you be careful with that?
- Dude, I got it.
[vehicle in front moves forward]
[Poppy keeps chewing loudly]
[Poppy] Mm…
[brakes squeal]
[Alex] Oh!
Shit.
[Alex sighs]
If you could be anywhere in the world now,
where would you go?
- Right now?
- Mm-hm.
Linfield, Ohio.
We're gonna be four hours late.
You know what they say.
Four hours late to Linfield
is four hours well spent.
What? Who says that?
- What's wrong with Linfield?
- Um…
Everything.
- Linfield was a great place to grow up.
- Ooh, hard disagree.
My turn. I'd be in Paris.
Having, oh, like, a little cortado.
And a cigarette at a café.
- You smoke?
- No.
Paris me would smoke.
Okay, your turn. And don't say Linfield.
Back in Boston, I guess.
That is so boring. Japan's my number two.
Okay.
Canada.
So just to recap,
your top three destinations are
where we are going, where we just left,
and the more polite version of the US?
Hm.
- You wanna, like, play some music?
- Yeah! Oh.
Wait, I'd be honored.
- Jesus. Oh, sorry. I got it.
- Just be careful with that. Great.
["Forever Your Girl" by Paula Abdul plays]
[mouths] ♪ Hey, baby ♪
[sings] ♪ You got to remember ♪
♪ I'm forever your girl ♪
[mumbles] ♪ Baby, forever ♪
♪ And ever and ever ♪
[speaks] ♪ You know I am… ♪
You hate this song.
How is it possible you hate this song?
It's just the saxophone.
What do you have against saxophone?
Name a single song that has been improved
by the appearance of a saxophone. One.
I can name literally hundreds.
- Right.
- And that's just the Kenny G catalog.
- You've gotta be kidding.
- What else do you hate?
- Come on.
- Flip-flops.
- Flip-flops?!
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Christmas music.
- What?
- Reality TV.
- [scoffs]
- Holding hands.
I literally love all of those.
Yeah. I bet you love everything.
Yeah.
No, it's not true. I hate running.
[laughs]
What?
I love running.
Well, let's face it, Alex.
You and I are not meant to be together.
Um…
I have a girlfriend, so…
That's so cool.
♪ He promised the world… ♪
Doesn't mean we can't enjoy a little…
- Casual sax.
- [turns up volume]
["Forever Your Girl" fades out]
I'm gonna get a coffee.
Do you want anything?
- I'm good.
- Okay.
What are you doing?
Isn't it great?
It's a well.
It's a friggin' wishing well
next to a gas station
in the middle of nowhere.
You gonna make a wish?
I don't have any money.
[Alex scoffs]
[Alex sucks his teeth]
[soft ethereal music plays]
Thanks.
[coin dings]
[Poppy chuckles]
Okay, your turn.
- That was my only coin.
- What? Why didn't you tell me?
- I took your wish.
- It's fine. Come on.
- You wanna know what I wished for?
- Doesn't work like that.
Come on.
- [Poppy] But I really wanna tell you.
- [Alex] Nope.
What?
- Did you lock the car?
- Yeah.
I didn't want anyone to steal it.
I thought you had the keys!
- Oh my God!
- I…
- Oh… no.
- [sighs]
[Alex blows raspberry]
Maybe Triple-A isn't here yet because
they locked their keys in their truck.
And who would they call?
Quadruple-A?
[Alex sighs]
Hi.
Two of your finest rooms, please.
Cheapest.
Oh, you're in luck.
We got two rooms available.
Room 106 and, uh…
Hold up.
Hey, Phil, what's the status
of the big stain in 108?
- We'll just take 106.
Yeah.
No, Dad, you don't need to drive
five hours to Pennsylvania to pick me up.
Yeah, I can't wait to see you.
[Poppy] Yes. Alex is a male Alex.
I'm 95% sure he's not a murderer.
Actually…
Hey, Alex's girlfriend, is he a murderer?
- She's just kidding. Ignore her.
- He dodged the question.
I'll sleep on the floor. I promise.
He's a Virgo, so probably not.
- [Alex] I'll see you tomorrow. Bye.
- Okay. Love you. Bye.
Wait, so your girlfriend's from Linfield?
Yeah.
High school sweethearts?
[Alex] Mm-hm.
Good for you.
Yeah, you know, we like the same things.
Our families are close. It's nice.
Hey, if Mom likes her, she's a keeper.
My mom never met Sarah.
She died when I was little.
[sighs, whispers] Shit.
Can't even imagine.
That must've been really hard.
My brother and I were pretty young.
It was worse for my dad.
Took him a long time
before he was, you know…
Normal.
My grandma helped a lot.
- Sure you don't wanna sleep head to toe?
- No, I'm fine.
Okay.
[Alex sighs]
So what is it with you and Linfield?
[Poppy chuckles]
Um… [sighs]
We moved there when I was 11.
And I was just so lonely.
I was always on the outside of everything.
And finally, I got invited to this party.
Right before high school.
Played Seven Minutes in Heaven.
Brian Kelvey kissed me.
Horrible experience.
[snickers]
The next day at school,
everyone was laughing at me.
It turns out…
He told everyone that I blew him.
[sad music plays]
Over the next three years,
I was Porny Poppy.
That's awful.
Screw those guys.
That's the problem with small towns.
Once people decide who you are, that's it.
Hm.
That's why I wanna travel.
You can actually be who you wanna be
instead of who they say you are.
You know, for what it's worth,
if I'd have known you,
I wouldn't have called you that.
You know, I think I believe you.
And thanks.
For what?
For being the first person
who I've told that story to
who didn't ask whether I did it.
Good night, Poppy.
Good night, Alex.
["That's How I Got to Memphis"
by Tom T. Hall plays]
I can't believe you went
on a freaking run this morning.
I thought you ditched me.
I was this close to hitchhiking
with some me thy trucker.
[Alex] Oh, a me thy one.
That's smart. Fast drivers.
[Poppy laughs]
Nevertheless, I am happy
that I didn't scare you off.
You're terrifying for many reasons,
but you're four feet tall.
- You don't scare me.
- Hey!
I'm small, but fierce.
- You're a tiny fighter.
- [gasps]
Wait.
I like that.
[both laugh]
Okay, so considering the last 24 hours,
where does Alex Nilsen stand on travel?
Love or hate?
I mean,
I've never really traveled anywhere.
But, this morning,
I saw this beautiful sunrise
over this place I've never been before.
[contemplative music plays]
And I wouldn't have if everything
had gone according to plan, so
love.
I'm thinking love.
Okay.
So should we detour
this road trip to Canada right now?
I know it's at the top of your list.
Let's try being friends first.
Fair.
Friends do not shake hands.
Nice.
[Poppy giggles]
[instructor] Is that the best you can do?
- ["Ani Kuni" by Polo & Pan plays]
- Get those booties in the air!
Keep it up! Keep it up!
I can't go to the wedding.
Right?
Right.
That'd be crazy.
Insane.
And also, I have Santorini,
so I don't even need to make up an excuse.
- 'Cause I already have an excuse.
- Yup.
And back down.
Oh, thank God.
But maybe the universe
is giving me a sign.
No, it's not.
- This is you in a rut trying to go back...
- What?
This is you in a rut
trying to go back in time
to fix a friendship
that blew up in your face!
[Poppy] That's harsh.
["Ani Kuni" continues]
- You're getting me in trouble.
- What are we, ten?
No one can hear us.
Everyone can hear you.
- Back up. Take it to the max.
- [mouths] Oh…
[instructor] Now!
Don't feel like talking now, do we?
[woman 1] Seriously? Like…
- [panting] Screw this.
- I know, right?
Like, it's torture and it's expensive,
but I'll be back Monday.
What are you doing?
- I'm gonna call Alex.
- Now?
Mm-hm. Post-workout adrenaline.
If I wait, I'm gonna chicken out.
Okay, so I'm just gonna tell him
that I'm not going.
- So he doesn't think it's because of him.
- Yeah, totally.
- [line rings]
- It's ringing.
Wait, how'd you do the foot thingy?
- Wiggle and pull.
- I'm wiggling and pulling.
- Can you help me?
- Just wiggle…
[ringtone plays]
Hello?
- Help me. I'm wiggling.
- [woman 2] Wiggle harder!
[Poppy] I'm pulling, dude.
[Alex] Hello?
- Poppy?
- [woman 2 whispers] What?
Sorry, who's this?
You called me.
[whispers] Speaker.
Yes, I did. I did.
Is this about my brother's wedding?
[clears throat] Yeah.
Uh, yeah. So here's the thing.
The issue is I have a work thing
this weekend, so…
Okay.
Yeah, okay, well,
that's probably for the best.
[mouths] For the best?
I just mean David's super stressed
about the seating arrangements, so it's…
So where is R&R sending you this time?
[whispers] Santorini.
[slowly] Santorini.
- Poppy…
- Barcelona.
[woman 2 gasps]
- What?
- God, give me that!
Yeah, it's so funny.
It's such a… It's a crazy coincidence.
R&R is doing this whole feature
on Barcelona.
- Oh, really?
- And I can attend the wedding.
- [mutes phone]
- Okay. Wow. Cool.
- What are you doing?
- What? I don't know!
- It just came out! I don't know!
Tell him you're actually
going to Santorini...
Are you still there?
- Yeah, but...
- Shut up. Sh... sh... sh.
- [unmutes phone]
- Looking forward to catching up, buddy.
[whispers] Buddy?
Okay, well, I'll…
I'll see you soon.
Bye.
[hangs up]
Wow. Deep down in my heart,
I knew that was gonna happen.
[peppy music plays]
Where is this wedding anyway?
Please say somewhere nice.
Barcelona.
Fine, then I will expect an article
about destination weddings in Barcelona
in my inbox when you get back.
Thank you.
[Swapna] Mm.
- I know lately I've been...
- Bad at your job?
- Yeah.
But I think that this might…
help with that.
Well, good.
Because I miss my favorite writer.
Now go away.
[softly] Okay.
["Hang with Me" by Robyn plays]
♪ Will you tell me once again ♪
♪ How we're gonna be just friends? ♪
[Poppy sings]
♪ If you're for real and not pretend ♪
♪ I guess you can hang with me ♪
♪ When my patience's wearing thin ♪
♪ And I'm ready to give in ♪
♪ Will you pick me up again? ♪
♪ Then I guess you can hang with me… ♪
Ah!
[sings] ♪ And if you do me right ♪
♪ Then I'mma do right by you ♪
♪ And if you keep it tight ♪
♪ Then I'm gonna confide in you ♪
- [song ends]
- [scatting] ♪ If you hang with… ♪
Hi.
- Hi.
- [Poppy] Alex.
I was not expecting to see you… yet.
Uh, yeah, I just landed.
You were singing pretty loud.
Yeah, my bag came out first, and that…
- Never happens.
- [Alex] Huh.
Cool.
Uh…
Long time no see.
It's been a couple of years.
Well…
Oh, you're offering me a handshake.
I just didn't know what was…
Uh…
You know, appropriate.
[sighs] This is really weird.
It's very hard for me not to hug you.
Because I come
from a very hug-forward family.
I know.
[doorbell rings]
Hey. You must be Mr. Wright. I'm...
Alex! Come here.
Ah, come here.
- [mom] Honey?
- [Poppy] Hm?
- [knocking]
- Alex is here. Can I come in?
If I said no, would that stop you?
What?
- Ta-da!
- Ah!
What the hell is that? Are those condoms?
I can demo on a banana if you need.
No, Mom. Don't need.
Sweetie, I just want you kids
to be safe, that's all.
How many times do I have to tell you?
We are not…
Alex and I are just friends. That's it.
No. No, don't shake the condom box
to make a point, please.
Please stop.
Mom, you're gonna kill me.
Mother! Okay, Wanda!
Didn't you say Alex
broke up with his girlfriend?
Yes, she broke up with him,
which is why we're going camping,
so he can take his mind off of it.
Alex is not my type and I am not his,
so we don't need condoms.
And we definitely don't need 500
because we're not an army.
They're lambskin.
Oh my God.
I have to tell you,
he seems really nervous down there.
You don't get nervous
going on a trip with a friend.
Trust me. I know. I have experience.
Mom, he's nervous about flying
because he's never flown before.
[breathes deeply]
Boy, you are as nervous as a cat
in a room full of rocking chairs.
I think I know what's going on here.
[breathes deeply, sighs]
Is this your first time?
Poppy told you?
She didn't have to.
It's written all over your face.
This is a big deal what you two are doing.
Thank you. That's what I said,
and Poppy laughed at me.
Ah…
- That's not nice.
- Right?
She says people do it all the time.
Well, that is true, but it doesn't
make the first time any easier.
Exactly, and I keep reading
about the science of it
to try and calm my nerves.
But the more I read,
the more I realize what can go wrong.
Like what?
Like sometimes…
It just goes down.
For no reason at all. Mechanical failure.
Yeah, well, sure.
That can happen sometimes.
But you're a young guy, so the chances
of that happening to you are slim.
As you get older, then it increases
and that could be a problem.
But you're a young guy.
You can't let it affect your confidence.
It's not confidence. I don't wanna die.
Why would you die?
Do you have a heart problem?
What do you think we're talking about?
Sex. What do you think
we're talking about?
Oh, no.
No, sir. That's not what I'm...
No, we don't do that, Poppy and me.
- Why would you think that?
- Hey, Alex.
Do you have room in your carry-on
for that box of condoms
for all the sex that we're gonna have?
[Wanda] Poppy, you're embarrassing him.
Listen, I'm a very nervous flyer too,
but I got some beta blockers
from my friend Rita
who goes to Mexico for her veneers.
Everything's cheaper there.
Anyway, all you gotta do
is take two of these at takeoff.
[breathes deeply] Drugs and condoms.
Our work is done here.
- [Wanda] Mm-hm.
- [Dad] Mm-hm.
[alert chimes]
[Poppy] Alex.
Hey. Alex.
Alex! Wake up. Come on.
Okay. I swear he's not dead.
He's just on drugs.
No, I mean, not those kinds of drugs.
Just… my mom gave them to him.
They're from Mexico.
["It All Feels Right" by Washed Out plays]
Alex!
["It All Feels Right" continues]
[Alex] "Squamish is known as the outdoor
recreation capital of Canada."
"To best enjoy your trip,
we suggest the following itinerary."
"Brave the crowds of Shannon Falls,
climb the Chief to get the best views,
and end your trip with an enlightening
visit to the Lil'wat Cultural Centre."
The book tell us when to use the bathroom,
or do they leave that to us?
What's wrong with an itinerary?
That's what everyone is gonna be doing.
Then we'll all have the same trip
and all take the same pictures.
I say we just wing it.
Wing it?
See where the wind takes us.
["It All Feels Right" continues]
Oh, uh…
[Poppy grumbles]
What's in here?
You're fine.
Woo, ooh… [laughs]
[both laughing]
There's a window.
If you stand like that all night,
this is fine for me.
You don't even need the poles.
- ♪ It all feels right… ♪
- [Poppy yelps] You!
♪ Close my eyes… ♪
[Poppy chuckles]
I told you.
[Poppy laughs]
That's a good fire.
- This is a good fire.
- Good job.
♪ The feeling when it all works out ♪
[Poppy pants]
["It All Feels Right" fades out]
- [crowds bustling]
- [live music plays in the distance]
See?
No, see, I told you.
- What did I say? [Gasps]
- It's pretty cool.
Oh, that's pretty.
- Hi.
- Ooh, now we're talking.
- Oh, yeah.
The perfect travel souvenir.
A giant chain-saw sculpture
that fits right in your carry-on.
[gasps] He speaks to me.
"Bring me home."
Poppy, think about this for,
like, two seconds.
He's enormous.
How are we gonna get him home?
Alex…
When art speaks to you,
you find a way to make it work.
Fine. But I am not carrying him.
[Alex grunts]
[both panting]
We have to hurry,
or we'll miss our water taxi.
- You say that like it's my fault.
- [boat engine rumbles]
[driver speaks indistinctly]
Believe it or not,
I actually used to work in finance,
and I just gave that lifestyle away.
I said, "Screw it," you know?
I wanna get in touch with myself…
- Can you hear what he's saying?
- Huh?
- No.
Then why are you smiling and nodding?
I do not care what he's saying right now.
I mean, look at him. He's hot.
If I said that about a girl,
you'd say I was being creepy.
I know. It's an unfair double standard.
Unbelievable. You wanna jump his bones.
Maybe.
Right there, a girl got killed by a bear.
Don't worry, you're safe.
She wants to jump your bones!
Stop!
What?
- She wants to jump your bones!
- Shut up!
I can't hear anything up here.
It's so loud. Hold on.
I said, she wants to bang you!
- Oh.
- He was just kidding.
Well, that sucks for me. [Laughs]
That sucks.
You guys seem like you're fun.
My friends and I,
we're posted up at this amazing spot.
It's by McNab Creek.
Pure, untouched nature.
Only accessible by a boat.
But, lucky for you,
you know a guy with a boat.
[Alex] As lovely as that sounds,
all our stuff
is back at the camp, so it's…
No worries. We got an extra tent.
["Genesis" by Grimes plays]
- [driver] You smell that?
- Yeah.
It's so good.
Ow. Shit.
- My pants are falling down.
- This is incredible.
Yeah, I'm sure I'm gonna fit right in.
[driver] Hey, guys!
- Meet my new friends. They're from…
- [crowd] Hey!
- Ohio.
- Boston.
- Ohio, Boston. Cool. Never been there.
- Hey.
Hi.
I'm Daisy.
Oh, hi. I'm Poppy.
- Oh, another flower. Crazy.
- Whoa, that's crazy.
Wait, so are you guys like a thing?
- We're just friends.
Platonic travel companions.
- Cool.
Do you wanna put your stuff down?
You can take Chip's tent over there.
- Will Chip mind?
- [driver] No.
He got arrested.
Lucky us.
- Mi casa, tu casa. Come on.
- [Poppy] Okay!
- Yeah. You're awesome.
- [Poppy] Su casa.
- [driver] Su casa, whatever, same thing.
- [Alex] Okay.
Be right there.
["Genesis" continues]
[driver] Poppy, that's gonna cost you.
- [Poppy] Oh, how much?
- [driver] Not too much.
- Well, you put it on my tab.
- [driver] Okay.
- Oh, thank you.
- Okay.
Well… here we are.
Where exactly is "here"?
Where are we?
We are where the wind has taken us, Alex.
See how Daisy was making eyes at you?
I think she's just on drugs.
Oh, you sweet, sweet man.
Those are not mutually exclusive.
- Yeah, I don't know.
- Alex. You're on vacation.
On vacation, people do stupid shit
with people that you never
have to see again.
I don't do stupid shit.
Yeah, well…
Maybe Vacation Alex does.
[Poppy snickers]
[Alex snickers]
[rhythmic electronic music plays]
Don't you just love nature?
It's just so peaceful, you know?
It's so... [coughs]
Peaceful.
Yeah.
[quietly] You okay?
What's so funny?
[whispers] You okay?
Yeah.
Okay, guys,
who wants to go skinny-dipping?
Alex does.
Oh, no, Alex does not.
[Daisy] Yes, he does.
["Esperar Pra Ver" by Evinha plays]
- Do you wanna go, or…?
- [Poppy] Mm-mm…
- Do you wanna see my tent?
- Yeah.
[driver] It's this way.
[Alex scoffs]
[Daisy] Come on, Ohio.
All right, I'm coming.
All right, let's do it. [Laughs nervously]
[cheering, whooping]
["Esperar Pra Ver" continues]
Oh, wow, you're all getting naked,
and so far from the water.
You're not getting shy on me now, are you?
Huh…
I'll see you in there.
Yeah.
Okay.
Vacation Alex.
Come on!
I'm coming!
Vacation Alex. Vacation Alex.
Vacation Alex.
Vacation Alex!
Come on!
["Esperar Pra Ver" fades out]
[Poppy] Come on.
- [driver gasps]
- [Poppy] Mm…
Jesus.
- That is an intense tattoo.
- No.
This is Memento Mori.
It's Latin for "remember you must die."
Because we're gonna die.
You are gonna die.
[quietly] Cool. Cool.
[driver] Yeah.
["Esperar Pra Ver" continues]
[Daisy] Hey.
Oh, hey.
[Daisy laughs, pants]
[man] Let's go cliff diving!
This will blow your mind.
Okay.
Wait up. I'm coming.
Oh, shit.
[mysterious music plays]
Whoa. [Pants]
[Alex] Poppy?
The tents all look the same.
- Poppy?
- [man] Shh!
Sorry. Sorry.
Are you… [kisses] Are you… Are you okay?
- [Poppy] Mm-hm.
- You seem a little off.
- Sorry.
- What?
- Oh, no.
- No, you can tell me.
I just can't stop thinking about death.
Right. Okay.
- Would it help if I put a shirt back on?
- Yeah!
Maybe that'll get you out of your head
and into your body.
[Poppy and the driver keep chatting]
[whispers] Poppy?
Poppy?
I think I heard your friend.
[Alex] Poppy?
Yeah, I think he needs my help.
I don't know.
I think he's gonna be all right.
He's with Daisy. He's good.
Poppy!
What if I don't go, and he dies?
I mean, it might just be his time.
[Poppy gasps]
No, I'm kidding.
No, but you should help him.
He doesn't sound good at all.
- Yeah, okay.
- Yeah.
[whispers] Alex. Alex.
[yelps] Why are you naked?!
[whispers] My clothes are out at sea.
What?
[louder] My clothes are out at sea.
Okay. What do you want me to do?
I need clothes!
Now.
Okay. Okay.
Just anything. Anything.
- [Alex grunts]
- Sorry!
[Alex] What even is this?
[Poppy] It's a romper. It's like overalls.
- What are you looking at?
- Full moon, man. [Giggles]
[panting]
You're ripped?
What?
No, shut up.
Who would've thought?
Vacation Alex wears women's clothes.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
What is that? What is that?
What... Ew!
Disgusting. Go away. Go in the tent.
- I don't know which one is our tent.
- I don't know.
[Alex] Hey, Poppy.
[Poppy] Yeah?
I'm sorry I ruined your night with Buck.
You didn't ruin anything.
I couldn't stop thinking about
my grandpa's open-casket funeral.
What?
It's a long story.
I'll tell you about it later.
- You are my weirdest friend.
- [Poppy chuckles]
And don't you forget it.
[gentle music plays]
Would we still be friends
if we didn't go to the same college?
You mean like…
After we graduate?
I mean like…
Hypothetically.
If I didn't go back next semester,
and I used my tuition
to get a terrible apartment in New York
and intern at a magazine
and work on my blog.
That's a very specific hypothetical.
Would I ever see you again?
How about this?
Every summer,
wherever we are,
whatever we're doing,
whoever we're with…
We meet somewhere in the world for a trip.
Deal.
[both chuckle]
[both laughing]
[plane engine roars]
[Poppy] How was your flight?
[Alex] Yeah, it was good.
I just slept most of the time.
Smart.
Do you maybe wanna share a taxi?
I rented a car.
Oh, cool.
Do you want a ride?
["I Don't Know What I Can Save You From"
by Kings of Convenience plays]
♪ You called me after midnight ♪
♪ Must have been three years
Since we last spoke ♪
♪ I slowly tried to bring back ♪
♪ The image of your face
From the memories so old… ♪
It's hotter than I thought
it was gonna be.
Yeah. Linfield too.
It's the hottest summer
we've had in years, apparently.
[Alex exhales]
[sighs] Oh man, Alex. This is bleak.
How did we become people
who talk about the weather?
Does this mean
that we're officially grown-ups?
[both chuckle]
I'm actually in the middle of redoing
the HVAC system in my house.
Wait, you own a house?
It's, uh, it's Grandma Betty's, actually.
She left it to me.
Is Betty gone?
You know, she was old.
It was peaceful.
You can just leave it.
No, seriously, you don't need
to bring my bags in.
- Just go do wedding stuff.
- [Alex] It's fine.
[Alex grunts]
Wow.
It's like a sauna in here.
It says it's 32 degrees. Is that bad?
That's like 90 degrees.
Right. Bad.
Okay, well, maybe I'll open some windows.
[control beeps]
Or not.
I'm leaving a very negative review
upon checkout.
[Alex] I think this thing is broken.
No, it says the AC does work.
"You must lower it one degree at a time
and let it rest in between."
- What does that mean?
- I don't know, I'm just reading the paper.
Okay.
[rapid beeping]
One degree at a time.
[quick beeps, long beep]
Oh, wait, maybe that did something.
No.
Hey, you don't need to stick around.
This is gonna take a while, so…
This is ridiculous. I'm just gonna fix it.
Well, I'm going on the record to say
I did not ask you to do this for me.
Well, if you die of heat stroke,
the seating arrangement's gonna be
messed up, and David will be furious.
Of course. Well, at least it's a dry heat.
For my hair's sake.
- [Poppy chuckles]
- Oh, yeah, right.
The famous Poppy poof.
Yeah.
New Orleans is still talking about it.
[jazz music plays]
[man singing] ♪ I feel like funkin' it up
Feel like funkin' it up  ♪
♪ I feel like funkin' it up
Feel like funkin' it up… ♪
Okay, Napa was fun last year,
but this is next level.
Julian gave me a list of restaurants
we have to go to.
Look at you with the itinerary.
How very un-Poppy.
No, it is not an itinerary.
We can do them in any order that we like.
He had a po'boy
that made him believe in God.
Well, dating a chef
has its perks, I guess.
[Poppy] Hm.
- I'm happy he was okay with you coming.
- Summer trips are non-negotiable.
Cheers to that.
See, I am so happy that Grad-School Alex
didn't kill off Vacation Alex.
Are you kidding me?
Vacation Alex is alive and well.
Thank you.
[jazz music continues in background]
- [jazz music continues]
- [laughing]
Good.
Oh, cheers! [Laughs]
Mm… Mm!
Oh my God.
[Alex] Yup. That is so good.
Maybe we should have done
the beignets and coffee
before the Hurricanes.
- No, I think we did it perfectly.
- Okay.
[jazz music ends]
[server] Beignets on the house
for the lovebirds. Enjoy your honeymoon.
[wife] Thank you! [Laughs]
[Poppy clears her throat]
No. No. [Chuckles]
Hey.
Hey, what a coincidence!
We just got hitched too!
- So sweet.
- Congratulations, you two.
["Hello Hello Hello (Polo & Pan Remix)"
by Remi Wolf plays]
♪ Answers in the room… ♪
Drinks and chips are on us, y'all.
Enjoy your honeymoon.
- Oh my God! Thank you!
- Thank you so much.
♪ Hello? How's my little lady
In the New York snow?  ♪
♪ Yeah, he says
"I love you, I love you loads"  ♪
♪ We got a certified gambler
Messin' with me  ♪
[Poppy gasps]
♪ So why she be callin'…?  ♪
We just got married!
♪ Hello, hello, hello  ♪
♪ How's my little lady
Playin' rock and roll?  ♪
♪ Or maybe these days
You like pop and soul  ♪
♪ He's a certified gambler
Messin' with me  ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey!  ♪
- [mellow background music plays]
- What can I get y'all?
- Gin and tonic, please.
- No, sir.
We will have two Sazeracs
because staying on theme matters.
Right. Theme matters.
- Yeah.
- Are those our fellow newlyweds?
Oh my God. Of course.
Wait, sweetie. Look who it is.
Oh, yeah. It's our beignet buddies.
I hardly recognized you
in that cute little wig.
I'm Stacy Pagano. This is Bob.
Gladys Vivant.
And this is my husband… Keith.
So how did he propose?
Uh, Keith took me to Paris.
He said that it was a work trip.
Cheeky monkey.
Uh, and then he got down on one knee,
and the rest is a blur.
Work in Paris. What do you do, Keith?
[clears throat] I, uh…
I work in government.
You don't have to be shy, baby.
We can trust them.
He's CIA.
Wow. What's that like?
Oh, it's… a lot of coups.
- You know, assassinations.
- [sets down drinks]
Just boring stuff, really.
But the benefits are great.
Goodness.
Is it dangerous?
Well, it's nothing compared
to Gladys's work on the oil rigs.
[Poppy chokes]
- [Poppy coughs]
- Wow. You two are something else.
How'd you meet?
That's a long story. We...
Well, I was on vacation, right?
And Keith was undercover
as a professional dancer.
Yeah, this guy, he's got moves.
You know, in fact, you should've seen
our first dance at our wedding.
Keith choreographed the entire thing.
Oh, I would love to see that.
Do you have a video?
- No, sorry.
- No, but I'll do you one better.
Barkeep, can I borrow
your auxiliary cord, please?
Gladys, nobody wants to see that.
- Oh, yes. We absolutely do.
- Oh, yeah. Yes.
- We want a show.
- [Stacy laughs]
Well, it sounds like they wanna see it.
[background music stops]
[Poppy exhales]
Let's give the people what they want.
["Forever Your Girl" plays on speakers]
♪ You got to remember ♪
[mouths] ♪ I'm forever your girl ♪
♪ Baby, forever ♪
[mouths] ♪ And ever and ever ♪
- ♪ You know I am… ♪
- [mouths] No.
You gonna keep
that beautiful woman waiting?
Yes! Get over here!
- ♪ Baby, pick your head up ♪
- ♪ Head up ♪
♪ Come on and look me in the face ♪
[Poppy singing] ♪ Face ♪
♪ 'Cause I can tell that something… ♪
Oh, come on, Vacation Alex.
Is that the best you got?
♪ Why are you down? ♪
♪ Is it the rumor… ♪
Okay.
You asked for this.
♪ That another boy
Wants to take your place? ♪
♪ I hear he's after your heart… ♪
[gasps, yelps] Okay!
Oh, oh!
♪ Baby, don't you know that I love you? ♪
♪ And I'd never put nobody above you ♪
♪ He could promise the moon ♪
♪ And the stars above ♪
♪ Even if he promised me the world ♪
[Poppy yelps]
♪ Just remember I'm forever your girl ♪
♪ He could promise the world ♪
♪ You got to remember
I'm forever your girl ♪
♪ I'm forever your girl ♪
♪ Baby, just remember
I'm forever your girl ♪
♪ He could promise the world ♪
♪ Hey, baby ♪
♪ You got to remember
I'm forever your girl ♪
- ♪ Yeah, remember ♪
- ♪ I'm forever your girl ♪
♪ I'll be loving you ♪
♪ I'll be loving you still ♪
- ♪ I'm forever your girl ♪
- ♪ Hey, baby ♪
[song fades out]
[Poppy gasps]
Whoo!
[gentle guitar music plays]
[both panting]
I love it when you get weird.
I'm only weird when I'm with you.
Oh my God.
[Poppy sighs]
[gentle guitar music continues]
- [Poppy] So many alcohol.
- [Alex laughs]
[Alex] I think too many alcohol.
So, what do you think of him?
Julian. Be honest.
We didn't really spend much time together
when I came to New York.
But he seems cool, I guess.
Yeah, but he's all like,
"I love you. You're the one."
Like, what does that even mean?
How would you know?
There's, like, a billion people
in the world.
What, has he met them all?
No, I think I'm being love-bombed.
Am I broken?
You're not broken. You're just selective.
- Yeah, but love comes so easy to you.
- What?
Yeah, you and Sarah
are all natural and perfect.
Poppy. We're not even together.
We just break up all the time.
[blows raspberry] Yeah,
but you always come back together.
Like magnets.
I'm like the other side of the magnet.
The closer I get to a guy,
the more I wanna push him away.
That was so good. Did I come up with that?
I think that you will be drawn
to the right person at the right time.
And maybe that's Julian or...
Nah! Phhht!
I don't think
that we're right for each other.
Can I really be honest?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Julian kind of sucks.
- He does!
- Yeah.
He does. He sucks.
He calls me "Al," and he's 30 years old,
and he waxes his armpits.
- Hey, I told you that in confidence.
- [Alex chuckles]
I'm gonna die alone, Alex.
Hey…
How about we die alone together?
Okay.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
- Oh, shit. You okay?
- No.
You okay?
Oh my God. Is there a bone sticking out?
No, but I think you might've sprained it.
Oh, good.
Can you just roll me down the street?
That would be great.
No. Here's what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna pick you up,
and I'm gonna carry you back to the hotel
on the condition
that you don't call me Seabiscuit
and you don't scream
"faster, faster, faster" in my ear, okay?
[laughing] How did you know
that I'd really wanna do that?
Because I know you.
[gentle piano music plays]
Okay. Come on.
- You ready?
- Yes.
- Whoa! Oh!
- Uh! [Sighs]
Thank you.
[Poppy giggles]
[Alex grumbles]
- I'm the king of the world!
- That is not better than "Seabiscuit."
- Here we go!
- No! No, no, no!
- God!
- [Julian] Poppy.
[Poppy] Julian?
Hey, man.
Surprise.
What?
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
I got someone to cover my shifts.
You surprised?
Yes. Very. Very.
Am I interrupting something?
- No, she sprained her...
- I sprained my ankle.
- [Julian] Oh.
- Hence the carrying.
That was purely medicinal,
not recreational.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
I've been texting you.
Oh my God, I'm sorry.
My phone died several bars ago.
- I'm gonna get some ice.
- No, we're good.
I can take it from here.
Okay, she's all yours.
I know.
Good night, Al.
Good night.
- Hey.
- You are sneaky.
- [Julian] This wig.
- [Poppy] Do you like it?
- [Julian] It's so good.
- [Poppy] It's good, right?
[Julian] It's so good.
- [Alex opens door]
- Wow.
[Alex] Shit! Shit! Shit!
- What? What?
- [Alex] Shit! Shit!
- My back! Oh, shit.
- What? Alex?
- Oh, shit. My back. A spasm.
- Okay.
Are you…? Can I…?
- Don't touch me. Don't touch me.
- Okay.
- Sorry. Thank you.
[groans]
I have no idea what I'm looking for.
Do you need a splint? This a splint thing?
What's a splint?
- No, I just need to breathe.
- Okay.
- Can I help you get down off the chair?
- No. No. Yes. Yes. No, I... Yes.
Okay. Okay.
- Careful. [Grunts in pain]
- Then you have to step down.
- Do you wanna sit down?
- Yeah.
- And… touchdown.
- [groans]
- Sorry.
- Thank you. Sorry.
What happened?
- I leaned funny.
- You leaned funny?
Shit, am I getting old?
Temporally challenged.
- [chuckles] Ow!
- Maybe there's an ice pack in the freezer.
[Alex pants]
[Alex whimpers]
- Good?
- Yeah.
Uh… [sighs]
I'm sorry I made you miss
groomsman wine tasting.
You did not make me.
In fact, you pretty clearly
told me you didn't need my help.
My own ego got me here.
Hey, you said it.
Here.
Hey, I know that we haven't talked a lot
in the last couple of years…
But you should've told me about Betty.
I know.
And Sarah.
[Alex] Mm…
Can we maybe talk about this
when I'm in a little less pain?
- Yeah.
[serene music plays]
Okay, um…
I think I can drive. I should go.
No, you cannot drive.
And you don't need to flee.
I won't make you keep talking.
You promise?
I promise.
[Alex exhales]
You stay here tonight. Take the bed.
I'll sleep on the couch.
- I don't know if...
- I won't take no for an answer.
Thank you.
Hey, I'm just returning
the favor for Norway.
One of my favorite trips.
Mine too.
[serene music continues]
[Alex] Oh, hey.
Hey, sorry I missed your call.
I was just going through security.
[Poppy] Alex…
I know my flight's not for three hours,
but I just finished this thesis defense,
and I have never
been more excited for a vacation.
Alex, don't hate me.
I just woke up with the craziest fever,
and I have never felt so sick
in my entire life.
Oh, no.
Please don't make me feel worse
than I already do.
No, it's…
It's fine.
Really. It's fine. It's just, uh…
This is the only week that I had.
But we can go to Norway next summer.
No! Alex, R&R is footing the entire bill.
It's already all paid for.
Go.
I'm not going without you.
Why? If you don't wanna go alone,
you can invite somebody.
Invite Sarah.
[Alex sighs] That's over.
Yeah, but that's what you always say
and then shock no one
when you end up back together.
I know, but…
It feels different this time.
That's another reason
why I was so excited about Norway.
Oh, shit.
I'm so sorry, Alex.
Don't be. Really. Uh…
Just feel better.
Just get on that plane, Alex.
[chuckles]
Okay.
Bye.
[sighs]
[knock at door]
Mm…
Oh, Poppy.
I think I'm dreaming.
You're not dreaming,
but you are burning up.
Mm, but you're in Norway.
Obviously not.
Okay, let's get you back in bed.
See if we can get rid of this fever.
But how are you supposed...
You're gonna be late for your flight.
I already missed my flight two hours ago.
Come on.
But you're supposed to be in Norway.
What's the point of being in Norway
if you're not there?
I was gonna take you
to a freaking hotel made of ice.
[Alex chuckles]
Well, how about later on
we can stick our heads in the freezer
and pretend we're there, okay?
- No.
- Come on.
Lay down.
Okay.
[pleasant music plays]
[Alex chuckles]
Mm, I'm gonna get you sick.
I have the whole week off anyway.
Do your worst.
I do not deserve you.
I know.
[snickers]
Chicken noodle soup?
[quietly] Chicken noodle soup.
[sighs]
[pleasant music continues]
[exhales]
Mm…
[sighs]
[dishes clatter]
You went running?
You madman.
Are you ignoring me?
Oh. [Chuckles]
Alex.
Hello. Alex!
Wow. Alex. Hello? Alex!
- [Alex shouts]
- Sorry! [Laughs]
Shit, sorry. You scared me.
- Those are very noise-canceling.
- Oh, yeah. [Pants]
- Morning.
- Good morning.
How'd you sleep?
Oh, it was very cozy.
I felt like I was being cremated.
Yeah, me too.
You went running? What about your back?
Oh, no, it's good. It loosens me up.
That's what you think,
but I've never run once,
and my back is great.
I'm sorry, you've never run once?
I almost failed PE.
On principle.
[Alex scoffs]
Here. Made coffee.
Well, thank you.
Listen, I don't know
what your plans are today, but…
You wanna come
to the rehearsal dinner tonight?
Oh. Uh…
I mean, am I invited?
Isn't it kind of just for family
and the wedding party?
Yeah, but…
I mean, you're basically family, Poppy.
And I think David
would really like it if you came.
Okay.
["August" by Taylor Swift plays]
♪ Salt air ♪
♪ And the rust on your door ♪
♪ I never needed anything more ♪
♪ Whispers ♪
♪ Of, "Are you sure?" ♪
♪ "Never have I ever before" ♪
♪ But I can see us lost in the memory ♪
♪ August slipped away
Into a moment in time ♪
♪ 'Cause it was never mine ♪
♪ And I can see us twisted in bedsheets ♪
♪ August slipped away
Like a bottle of wine… ♪
- Hi.
- Hey.
Since when are you so fashionably on time?
Since when are you
so fashionably fashionable?
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
- Is that Miss Poppy Wright?
- [Poppy gasps]
Bring it in, Mr. Nilsen. Oh my gosh!
I missed you!
Hey, congratulations.
Oh, thank you.
How come I never see you in Linfield?
Oh, uh, because she wouldn't
be caught dead there, Dad.
Oh, your son is a liar and a coward.
I love Linfield.
In fact, I think that we should get
matching Linfield tattoos. You in, Ed?
- [David] What's going on over here?
- David!
Oh my God!
Your dad and I are getting
matching tramp stamps.
- Alex is still undecided.
- This is why I wanted you here.
You look, like… amazing.
Wait, now you have to meet…
Nam, hi!
Finally!
No, you're right. [Laughs] You're right.
Alex would never.
He'd never go skinny-dipping.
- But Vacation Alex…
- [Nam] Mm?
[David] Okay, just to be clear,
the wedding tomorrow
is not clothing optional.
Please, please respect this.
Okay, let's not say things
we can't take back.
Thank you.
I don't think I've ever met
this Vacation Alex.
Ooh, you're missing out. He's fun.
You know, one time
I caught him trying on my romper.
- [Nam gasps]
- Okay, that is very out of context.
Do you want me to give some context?
[Nam] Photos or it didn't happen.
I'm so glad you got out
of your work thing.
You can go to Greece anytime.
- ["August" continues in background]
- [inaudible dialogue]
[thunder rumbles in the distance]
Thanks for walking me home.
[Poppy chuckles]
[Alex snickers]
Yeah, well, I guess I'll see you tomorrow.
Why did you come here?
What do you mean?
What I mean is, you told me that R&R
was sending you to Barcelona anyway.
But that wasn't true, was it?
I miss my best friend.
I missed you too.
[gentle music plays]
I just wish that…
We could go back
to the way things were before Tuscany.
I don't think that's possible.
I'll see you tomorrow.
[mumbles]
[sighs]
["L-O-V-E (Italian Version)"
by Nat King Cole plays]
Wow.
- This is…
- [Sarah gasps]
…huge.
Wow.
[door opens]
Hi!
- There she is.
- [Poppy] You made it!
- Yes!
- Uh, Poppy, this is Sarah.
- Sarah, this is Poppy.
- Hi.
- [Sarah] Hello. Hi.
- Hey.
- Oh my gosh, this is...
- Oh! So weird.
- I feel like I already know you.
- [Sarah] Yeah, same.
I can't believe I finally
get to meet the famous Poppy.
This place is stunning.
- Thank you so much for letting us come.
- Oh, no.
Thank R&R.
I have done nothing to deserve this.
- Hi! Hey.
- [man] Benvenuto.
This is Trey.
- Hi, Trey.
- Hey, Trey.
I've heard great things.
He's being nice.
I've done nothing but complain about you.
Come on. Come see.
It's actually pretty amazing inside.
- Stop!
- ["L-O-V-E" ends]
- [Poppy] Cheers!
- [Sarah] Cheers!
- [Alex] Mm.
- [Poppy] Mm-hm.
That's good.
It's a gorgeous spread.
There's eight different types of cheeses.
- Oh. Nice.
- Oh, wow. Cool.
So if you try them all,
we'll do a ranking.
Ranking?
- I went a little overboard.
- [Alex] No.
I'm just so excited
that we're all here together,
and I think that, you know,
we've taken way too long to do this.
It's gonna be jarring with you here.
Who is Alex gonna be texting nonstop?
Is that wine okay? I have a Chablis.
It's the one in Napa you liked.
Ooh, that was good.
Oh, uh, no, this is great.
Okay.
[jazzy piano music plays]
I was a professional surfer
for a bunch of years.
Then my photos
started getting published a lot.
[Poppy] Mm…
Started freelancing for R&R.
Now I get to travel the world
with my girlfriend.
Have someone else foot the bill.
That's not bad.
God, I never heard of jobs like this.
I wanna sue my high school
guidance counselor.
No, you have a great job too.
You work with your family, right?
Yeah, I don't wanna bore you.
It's not as cool as you guys.
I think me and Poppy would crawl out
of our skin if we were stuck in one place.
Mortgage. Mailbox.
You don't have a mailbox?
We have wanderlust.
- That's why we're good together.
- Oh.
We're nomads, mate.
Aren't we?
[Poppy] Mm-hm. Mm…
Okay.
I'm gonna clear the table now.
- I'm being a great hostess.
- [Trey] Mm.
Living like that would drive me crazy.
What?
You love seeing new places.
Yeah.
But I like coming home from them too.
That's what makes
these trips special, right?
You get to come home.
What's wrong with home?
I couldn't agree more.
Would you pass me that?
[chill pop plays in background]
Your mate Alex,
he's a bit of a wet lettuce, isn't he?
I'm joking. Come on.
- Are you all right?
- I think I need to get out.
Hey, you just got in.
I don't feel good.
I think I'm gonna call it a night.
Okay.
Uh…
[sighs]
[tapping keyboard]
[quietly] Shit. Shit.
They are not gonna last.
[Sarah] What do you mean?
They're nomads.
- [both laugh]
- [phone buzzes]
[phone buzzes]
Let me guess.
Yeah, she's fully freaking out.
[phone buzzes]
Jeez.
I should probably go check on her, right?
Yeah, that's fine. Of course.
Go check on your friend.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna go to bed.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Okay. I love you.
- Kiss. Love you.
- Okay.
- Bye.
[door opens]
- [whispers] I'm sorry.
- Hey, it's okay.
- I'm sorry.
- What is it? What's wrong?
I think I'm pregnant.
That is so bad.
I don't know what to do.
Well, why isn't Trey here?
I didn't tell him.
Oh.
Oh…
We should get you a test.
[phone app chimes]
It's negative.
[gentle music plays]
Hey. Hey.
That's a… that's a good thing, right?
No, I'm relieved. I'm just…
Scared.
Yeah. It's okay.
It's okay.
Hey, breathe, okay?
Just breathe.
I'm here.
For you. I'm here, okay?
I'll always be here.
[Poppy sniffs]
[whispers] Wait.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Whoa…
I'm sorry.
What was that?
I didn't mean it.
No, I'm just confused, and I'm…
All turned around.
But I didn't mean it.
I…
What am I to you?
You're my friend.
[Alex sighs]
My best friend.
[Alex exhales]
I don't wanna ruin that.
I'm sorry.
No.
It's fine.
[door opens]
[Poppy] Mm…
[Trey] Woohoo!
Get out here!
What?
[Trey] Come on out here!
Get your ass out here!
- All right.
- [Trey] This is crazy!
[laughs] Hold it.
Babe, you gotta see this.
Come on!
- What?
- Look!
Jeez.
I said yes!
[Trey] This is crazy.
He asked me at the most
beautiful spot on our walk.
He's such a romantic.
Oh my God! Oh my God!
Congratulations, you guys! What?
Thank you! I'm so happy!
- Thanks. Thank you.
- [Trey] Hold on.
You nipped out this morning
and bought a ring?
No, no, I've had it for a while.
Just… waiting for the right moment.
Well, come on, girl. Let me see that ring.
Come on.
Oh my God! [Giggles]
[pensive music plays]
[pensive music continues]
[pensive music fades out]
I'm happy for you.
I am.
Thank you.
Yeah, it was… it was time.
What's the plan? What are you gonna do?
We're gonna stay in Linfield.
[Poppy scoffs]
What?
What about your PhD?
What about teaching in Europe?
Or New York?
- You always said that was your dream.
- Yeah.
- So what are you gonna do in Linfield?
- I'm gonna teach at the high school.
Sarah's gonna take over
her dad's real estate business.
What does that have to do
with what you want?
Well…
What I want is a stable,
loving relationship.
And sometimes that takes sacrifice.
It's called compromise.
- Alex, I think it's called settling.
- Uh… [scoffs]
Yeah.
You would think that
because you live in a fantasy land, Poppy.
Always running away to new places.
New friends.
New connections.
But Sarah and I,
we're building something together.
Something real.
That sounds like what Sarah wants.
That's what I want.
I think this is our last trip together.
[sad music plays]
[thunder rumbles]
Hmmm…
[purse crashes]
[thunder continues]
[control beeps]
[beeping]
[scoffs]
[door opens]
[Poppy grumbles]
I don't wanna go back
to how things were before Tuscany.
It doesn't work for me.
It's too hot in here.
I can't have this conversation.
Like, I can't even breathe in here.
I need…
Air.
Did you hear me?
I heard you.
[scoffs]
Why did you and Sarah break up?
[sighs]
- A lot of reasons.
- That's such bullshit.
The last time I saw you,
you just got engaged,
and then you ghosted me for two years.
And then you broke off the engagement.
- Now you can't say three words about it.
- What do you want me to tell you?
I want you to tell me it's not my fault.
Tell me I'm not the reason
you're not married right now.
Tell me that… it's not because of me.
Of course it's because of you.
Right.
What are you doing?
Poppy.
- Poppy, what are you doing?
- I need air!
[Alex] Poppy.
Poppy.
I messed up, okay?
Whatever we are, whatever this is,
I asked too much of you.
Friends shouldn't ask
that much of each other.
I don't wanna be
your fucking friend, Poppy.
I want you.
But you, you don't know what you want.
You never have.
I want you too.
- You don't mean that.
- Don't tell me what I mean.
Why do you think I'm here?
Because I love you.
Since when?
Probably always.
[serene music plays]
[serene music turns energetic]
[serene music continues]
You skipped your run.
I didn't wanna leave.
I never wanna leave.
So…
What is on the itinerary today?
[Alex] Mm…
I'm thinking we wing it.
[Poppy] Hm…
["When I Get My Hands on You"
by The New Basement Tapes plays]
Can you clip my dress?
[Alex] Uh…
No.
♪ When I set my eyes on you ♪
♪ Gonna keep you out of town at night ♪
- [Alex breathes deeply]
- [Poppy groans]
♪ When I set my eyes on you ♪
♪ Not gonna be out of my sight ♪
♪ Now you know ♪
♪ Everywhere on Earth you go ♪
♪ You're gonna have me as your man ♪
["When I Get My Hands on You" continues]
[song ends]
[officiant] Do you, Nam and David,
take each other
to be your wedded husbands?
- You bet I do.
- I definitely do. Yes.
[officiant] And now,
by the power vested in me,
I pronounce you duly married.
You may kiss your husband.
[cheers and applause]
["Stumblin' In" by Cyril plays]
♪ Our love is alive ♪
♪ And so we begin ♪
♪ Foolishly layin' our hearts ♪
♪ On the table ♪
♪ Stumblin' in ♪
♪ Our love is a flame ♪
♪ Burnin' within ♪
♪ Now and then ♪
♪ Firelight will catch us stumblin' in ♪
♪ Wherever you go… ♪
That's a heck of a girl.
♪ Whatever you do… ♪
[Alex] Yeah.
♪ You know these reckless thoughts
Of mine are following you ♪
["Stumblin' In" ends]
["X's" by Cigarettes After Sex
playing softly]
So…
[Poppy] So…
[exhales] What's next?
After this?
[Poppy] Hm…
I think
some sweet…
Air-conditioned lovemaking.
[Alex] Mm.
Yeah.
[Poppy] Mm-hm.
But after that?
- [Poppy giggles]
- [Alex chuckles]
Could you see a life in Linfield?
- [Poppy laughs]
- Or in New York?
- [Poppy] Uh… Um…
- What?
Do we have to talk about this right now?
I mean, you are jumping on a flight in,
what, like six hours, so…
Yeah, but… [clears throat]
…I'll call you when I get to New York.
I know.
But we're both here right now, so…
We could just
get on the same page about timelines.
[Poppy] Shh…
Don't ruin this moment with an itinerary.
Hey, I'm kidding.
N... I just... Let's just…
Enjoy tonight.
Talk about all the real-life stuff later.
This is real life.
Unless this is just
another vacation for you.
No, no. Wait, okay.
Alex, just…
Give me a minute, you know?
This just happened.
Well, I'm sorry
if I need a little time to just…
Just think things through.
How is it possible
you still don't know what you want?
[Poppy scoffs]
You will always run away.
Yeah, well, it's better
than being stuck in Linfield waiting.
For what?
No, I don't know. What?
I was waiting for you.
[Alex sighs]
This isn't gonna work.
Not now, not in another ten years.
Not as long as you're you and I'm me.
- It's…
- Wait, Alex.
I love you.
[whispers] I love you too.
But, uh
love has never been our problem.
[music crescendoes]
[music fades out]
[Sarah] Poppy Wright?
Oh my God.
- Sarah. Hi.
- [Sarah] Hey.
Wow, when did this happen?
Uh, about a year ago. [Chuckles]
Listen, I'd love to stay and catch up,
but I'm late for my pre-flight.
- But it was great to see you.
- [Poppy] Yeah.
Hey, wait, Sarah.
I was really careless with everything.
My friendship with Alex…
Wasn't fair to you.
I'm sorry.
You know, I spent a long time
blaming you for our problems.
I thought that if you just went away,
they'd all get solved. [Chuckles]
And then you did, and somehow
that was even worse for my relationship.
But, honestly, you did me a favor.
I thought I knew what I wanted from life.
Turns out, I had no idea.
Bye, Poppy.
[sad music plays]
[sad music continues]
[quietly] This isn't working…
Is it?
[pleasant guitar music plays]
[Swapna] "I need to stop."
"I need to stay in one place for a while."
"Most people need
a vacation from their life."
"And that was never my problem."
"I need the life part."
[pleasant music continues]
[sighs deeply]
This is the best thing
you've written all year.
I can't believe
this is a resignation letter.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's fine. [Sighs] Don't worry.
I'm not gonna beg you to stay.
Too many people want this job.
It wouldn't be fair.
And also, obviously, I don't want you here
if you don't want to be here.
I know.
I'm not saying this as your boss.
I'm saying this as your…
Fan.
Please keep writing.
Even if it's not here.
Especially if it's not here.
I think this could be something.
Like, where does the girl
who's gone everywhere go now?
If you could be anywhere in the world
right now, where would you go?
[pleasant music continues]
[inhales] Have you ever been
to Linfield, Ohio?
[Swapna] God, no.
Why? Am I missing something? [Laughs]
Not really.
But I think I am.
[pleasant music continues]
[pleasant music fades out]
- [rings doorbell]
- [hopeful music plays]
[Poppy keeps knocking]
[Poppy] Alex?
Wait, Alex!
Alex! Wait, hey!
Alex!
[pants]
Oh, I hate running.
Alex!
[panting]
[moaning, panting]
[panting slows]
[hopeful music turns triumphant]
[Poppy pants harder]
Alex!
Alex! No, Alex!
Oh my God.
[Poppy's panting slows]
- Poppy?
- I… Just a second.
[Poppy catches breath]
What are you doing here?
[Poppy breathes deeply]
[car honks repeatedly]
Can you tell me over here?
[pleasant music plays]
[breathes slowly]
I always felt like…
If I stayed in one place too long…
Everyone would see that I'm too much.
Even you.
So one week a year with you…
It was safe.
It's all that I thought that I could have.
But I love you.
I'm always gonna love you.
So there's not one thing in my whole life
that I wouldn't give up…
To build something new with you.
Because…
When I'm sad or sick…
You're all I want.
And when I'm happy,
you make me so much happier.
And I know I have
a lot of things I gotta figure out,
but if there's one thing that I know,
it's that wherever you are in the world,
that's where I belong.
You're not a vacation to me, Alex.
You're home.
And I think that I'm that for you too.
[pleasant music fades out]
You can…
You can talk now.
[hopeful music plays]
[whispers] Please talk now.
[triumphant music plays]
So what do we do now?
As long as I'm with you, I don't care.
[triumphant music fades out]
[serene music plays]
[Poppy] When people think of home,
they think of the place where they live,
or maybe the place they grew up.
Uh, Kenny G, no. Be nice to your brother.
[whimpers]
Those places never felt like home to me.
Wait.
Do you teach at Sarah Lawrence?
Come on. You got me this.
You can't make fun of me.
I love the school spirit.
What's the mascot again?
Is it the fighting… Sarah Lawrences?
- It is the Griffins.
- [Poppy] Hm.
- Now can you get me the butter, please?
- [Poppy giggles]
[Poppy] I spent most of my life
looking for somewhere I belonged.
And believe me, I searched everywhere.
But it's a thin line
between searching and running away.
[gasps] Hey, beau.
So after all my searching,
this is what I've learned.
Hi, Kenny G.
[Poppy] Home is where
you can be entirely yourself.
[serene music continues]
In fact, home doesn't have
to be a place at all.
It doesn't matter where you go
or what you do.
When you're with the person
who loves you for you…
You're always home.
Even on vacation.
["Higher Ground"
by ODESZA feat. Naomi Wild plays]
♪ I'm waiting here ♪
♪ I need you now ♪
♪ Gravity can't hold us down ♪
♪ So just take me there ♪
♪ So won't you love me better? ♪
♪ I'm waiting here ♪
♪ I need you now ♪
♪ Gravity can't hold us down ♪
♪ So just take me there ♪
♪ To higher ground ♪
♪ Save me ♪
♪ I'm holdin' onto you ♪
♪ My soul is fadin' ♪
♪ I'm fallin' into blue ♪
♪ Why don't you save me? ♪
♪ My blood is running cold ♪
♪ So lift me up
And get me to higher ground ♪
♪ If I ♪
♪ If I, if I ♪
♪ Would you give me shelter? ♪
♪ I need you now ♪
♪ If you lead, I'll follow ♪
♪ Follow ♪
♪ I'm reaching out ♪
♪ So won't you love me better? ♪
♪ I'm waiting here ♪
♪ I need you now ♪ [echoes]
♪ Gravity can't hold us down ♪
♪ So just take me there ♪
♪ To higher ground ♪
♪ Save me ♪
♪ I'm holdin' onto you ♪
♪ My soul is fadin' ♪
♪ I'm fallin' into blue ♪
♪ Why don't you save me? ♪
♪ My blood is running cold ♪
♪ So lift me up
And get me to higher ground ♪
♪ If I ♪
♪ If I, if I ♪
["Higher Ground" fades out]
[pleasant music plays]
[pleasant music fades out]
[hopeful music plays]
[hopeful music fades out]