[waves crashing]
[radio static crackles]
[radio announcer] Heads up.
Hawaiian Electric gonna be--
[Hawaiian music plays briefly]
[radio announcer 2] Holoholo Ka'a Traffic.
[cycling through stations]
[radio announcer 3] Happy
Chinese New Year.
[♪ Keauhou sings "Hanohano Hai'ku"]
- [station changes]
- [radio announcer 4] Hard Rock 102.9.
- [♪ Guns N' Roses sing "Paradise City"]
- [radio DJ] Aloha.
It's Big T Velvet here,
live from Waikiki Beach,
getting us started
with another uninterrupted block
of the throwbacks that you love.
A hui hou.
♪ Take me down to the Paradise City ♪
♪ where the grass is green
and the girls are pretty ♪
- ♪ Take me home ♪
- ♪ Oh, won't you please take me home? ♪
♪ Just a urchin livin' under the street,
I'm a hard case that's tough to beat ♪
♪ I'm your charity case,
so buy me somethin' to eat ♪
♪ I'll pay you at another time ♪
♪ Take it to the end of the line ♪
♪ Take me down to the Paradise City ♪
♪ where the grass is green
and the girls are pretty ♪
♪ Oh, won't you please take me home? ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
- [bangs, tires squealing]
♪ Take me down to the Paradise City ♪
♪ where the grass is green
and the girls are pretty ♪
- ♪ Take me home...
- [fireworks whistling, popping]
[song fades]
[lively chatter]
[rhythmic drumming]
[indistinct chatter]
[tense, dramatic music playing]
[lively, indistinct chatter continues]
[fireworks whistling, popping]
[busy chatter]
[speaking Chinese]
[sighs]
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Steal my jacket!
Steal my jacket! [continues in Chinese]
[electronic music plays briefly
over speakers]
[panting]
[bell jingles]
- [tires squeal]
- [engine idling]
[over van stereo] ♪ Take me down
to the Paradise City ♪
♪ where the grass is green
and the girls are pretty ♪
♪ Oh, won't you please take me home? ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ Take me down...
- [engine revving]
[song fades in distance]
[tires squealing]
[tense music playing]
[intriguing, percussive music playing]
[muffled grunting]
[James] What the hell was that?
If that's the best you can do,
you might as well go out
and ring that fucking bell right now.
Or I'll ring it for you.
We go again in 30 seconds.
Get your asses back in the pool.
[cadets] Sir, yes, sir!
Commander Hale.
- Come on! Back in the pool!
- [hands clapping]
Commander Hale, you have a phone call.
If it's not my wife,
tell 'em to call back.
It's the police, sir.
[bluesy, melancholy music playing]
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
So it was a hit-and-run?
You can get a copy of the police report
and the death certificate by tomorrow.
Sorry for your loss.
- Thanks.
- Mm.
[♪ Souls of Mischief sing "Home Game"]
♪ It's home game, baby,
and we wearin' that black ♪
♪ I got two pits smokin'
in the yard out back ♪
♪ I just brewed up a fresh batch,
them hos waiting to get cracked ♪
♪ Special blend,
ain't no way to get that ♪
♪ Yet we still sippin', bong bubbling
'cause it's full of that green Gremlin ♪
♪ I'm trying to skewer up some veggies,
but my fingertips keep slippin' ♪
♪ Call up the missus for assistance ♪
♪ She came with a bevy of bad bitches...
[Leila chuckling] Wow.
- Cooking dinner.
- Yes, ma'am.
You trying to get in my pants?
- Why, hell yeah.
- [laughing]
Big dog got to eat.
[growling playfully]
- Is it working?
- [kids laughing]
- We'll see after dinner.
- Hey.
What'd I say about running in the house?
Sorry, Dad.
Yes, sir.
Before I forget, Lani has
a dentist appointment tomorrow.
So can you get Kai from soccer?
I can.
How was your day?
It was good.
You know, the usual.
Water competency drills
with the new cadets.
I really don't know how many
are gonna make it, though.
You'll get 'em there. You always do.
Yeah, hope so.
Also, Walter finally managed
to get himself killed.
Hit-and-run.
Had to go down to the morgue,
I.D. the body.
Wait. Your father died?
Traffic down there is out of control,
with all that roadwork.
Took me an extra 45 minutes to get home.
Babe, I'm so sorry.
Do you want to talk about it?
- [grill sizzling]
- Not really.
Well, did you at least call your brother
in Oklahoma?
Jonny doesn't take my calls.
So leave a message.
Damn it.
The tank's empty.
He needs to know his father died.
Well...
knowing Jonny, it's a safe bet
he's got bigger problems.
- [sighs]
- [♪ ZZ Top sing "Tush"]
Fuck.
- [motorcycle engine revving]
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I been up, I been down ♪
♪ Take my word, my way around...
Oh, what the fuck?
Hey! Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa. Hey, baby!
♪ I said, Lord, take me downtown ♪
♪ I'm just looking for some tush...
Valentina. Baby, what are you doing?
Hey. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Hi. I'm home.
- [song fades]
Uh, you're packing because...
Whoa. Why is everything in the car?
Where are you going?
What the hell's going on?
Valentina, please talk to me.
Now he wants to talk. [laughs]
- We talk all the time.
- No, no. I talk.
And talk and talk and talk and talk,
but you don't hear me.
Ooh. So weird.
[sighs]
I'm a grown-up, Jonny.
I manage a bank.
And... you're dicking around.
I am a police officer who just had
a really shitty day at work.
I'm sorry that I'm late, but I'm still
the same guy that you fell in love with.
- You know, I haven't changed.
- Yeah, and you never will change.
Oh, fuck.
This is that, uh... this is that
boundaries shit, right?
Uh, I'm sorry.
Valentina, please look at me.
I am sorry.
I hear you, and I'm listening.
Um, what do you want to talk about?
Okay.
I am leaving...
you.
No!
Do you even know what today is?
Wednesday.
[sighs]
It's my birthday.
- No.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm so sorry, xuxu.
- [Valentina groans]
- Don't "xuxu" me!
- [banging on trunk]
- [car rattling]
- I don't need a man who's sorry.
I need a man who is here.
Even when you're here, you're not here.
Valentina.
Mi amor...
mi mucho te quiero.
Mucho.
Te quiero mucho.
[snickering]
Like, big, big-time.
- Okay, Jonny. [speaks Portuguese]
- Will you forgive me, please?
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry. I'll make it up--
Nenê.
[smooching]
Nenê, ne--
[groans]
Today's Friday, by the way.
And I don't speak Spanish,
'cause I'm from Brazil.
I speak Portuguese.
Seu idiota.
- Ah, they're just so similar.
- [car door closes]
- I mean, Portuguese is basically...
- [engine starts]
- drunken Spanish.
- [engine revving]
Baby!
Xuxuzinho!
Ah, come on.
Oh...
Goddamn it.
Not again.
I'm so fucking horny. Shit.
[♪ Air Supply sing
"Making Love Out of Nothing at All"]
♪ I know just how to whisper ♪
♪ And I know just how to cry ♪
- ♪ I know just where to find the answers ♪
- [Jonny grunts]
♪ And I know just how to lie ♪
- ♪ I know just how to fake it ♪
- [groans]
♪ And I know just how to scheme ♪
[can clatters]
- ♪ I know just when to face the truth ♪
- [phone vibrating]
♪ And then I know...
- Yeah?
- [Leila over phone] Jonny, hi.
This is Leila Hale.
[Jonny] Okay.
I'm James's wife.
- [cans clattering]
- Hi, James' wife.
Yeah, it's kind of crazy we've never met.
♪ And I know when to let you loose...
Crazy.
Listen.
Your father Walter...
I'm afraid he's passed away.
Figured he died years ago.
He died yesterday.
The funeral's tomorrow.
We're hoping you'll come.
I know it's been a long time.
[sighs] So James couldn't call me himself.
You two have a complicated history
with a lot of shared trauma.
Mm. You sound like a shrink.
Child psychologist, actually.
I'm not a child.
And I haven't talked to James
in ten years,
and I haven't been to Hawaii in 20,
so I'm good.
That's not how it sounds to me.
- Mm.
- [phone beeps]
I am a very respected police officer
on the reservation,
- and, you know...
- [urinating]
I've had Eat Pray Love explained to me
numerous times,
and I have many audiobooks
that I'm excited to listen to.
Like, you know, I'll be there,
but-but I'm--
- Oh...
- [door closes]
- What the fuck?
- [continues urinating]
Hello? Jonny?
- You guys got the wrong house, man.
- [urine splattering]
- Oh, shit.
- Ah, fuck.
- [groans] Oopsie. [chuckles]
Detective Jonny Hale, 26 Arrowwood Lane.
[urinating slows to a stop]
Two-six... Okay, it's the right house.
Your father Walter sent you a package.
Where is it?
Walter's dead, man.
And you'll join him right now
if you don't give me the package.
- [Jonny sighs]
- [urine splashes briefly]
I haven't talked to Walter
since I was a kid,
and whatever you're looking for,
he wouldn't have sent it to me, okay?
- So just...
- [urine splashes briefly]
Fuck, I can't go when you're watching me.
Fucking weirdos.
Okay, hey, hey, hey.
Ooh, easy. It's sharp.
Whoa.
- Sword fight. [chuckles]
- [slapping]
- [groaning]
- [speaks Japanese]
Be cool, man, all right?
Be cool.
You know what this is?
A badly drawn horse.
It's a dragon.
Looks like an angry horsey.
It's a dragon, asshole.
It's a dragon's asshole?
You know what these tattoos mean?
Hai.
Yakuza.
That's right.
And even an idiot like you knows
you don't want to fuck with us.
Listen, you broke into my house,
Naruto over here put a sword to my neck,
and now, legally,
I'm allowed to kill both of you.
Just give us the fucking package!
Bro, I've had the worst day ever.
- My girl just broke up with me, okay?
- Shut up.
This other lady's trying to tell me
I have daddy issues.
I said just shut up.
- Now you fucking clowns are--
- Shut the fuck up!
[groaning]
♪ Every time I see you,
all the rays of the sun ♪
♪ are all streaming through
the waves in your hair ♪
♪ And every star in the sky ♪
♪ is taking aim at your eyes
like a spotlight ♪
[yelling]
♪ The beating of my heart
is a drum, and it's lost ♪
♪ and it's looking for a rhythm like you ♪
[grunts]
♪ You can take the darkness
from the pit of the night ♪
- ♪ and turn it to a beacon ♪
- [gun clicks]
- ♪ burning endlessly bright ♪
- [gunman yells]
What's up, Zuko?
♪ I've gotta follow it
'cause everything I know ♪
♪ well, it's nothing
till I give it to you ♪
[yelling wildly]
[yelling fiercely]
♪ Every time I see you,
all the rays of the sun ♪
- ♪ are all streaming through ♪
- [Jonny laughing]
♪ the waves in your hair...
[panting] Fuck. Hold on.
[shouting in Japanese]
♪ The beating of my heart
is a drum, and it's lost ♪
♪ and it's looking for a rhythm like you ♪
[rhythmic slapping]
Helicopter.
- Fuck.
- [yells]
♪ I can make the runner stumble ♪
♪ I can make the final block ♪
♪ And I can make every tackle
at the sound of the whistle ♪
♪ I can make all the stadiums rock ♪
Oh, shit!
♪ But I'm never gonna make it
without you ♪
♪ Do you really wanna see me crawl? ♪
[laughs] Oh, fuck yeah.
♪ And I'm never gonna make it
like you do ♪
♪ making love ♪
- ♪ out of nothing at all ♪
- [blade whooshing]
♪ Making love ♪
♪ out of nothing at all ♪
♪ Making love...
[Jonny] Hey, man, wh-wh-- Hey, hey, hey.
Just, th-that's... Hey, that's my mom...
that's my mom's shrine. Don't--
♪ Making love ♪
♪ out of nothing at all ♪
[screaming]
- Oh, shit!
- ♪ out of nothing at all ♪
- ♪ Making love ♪
- [groans]
- ♪ out of nothing at all...
- [screaming]
Oh, yeah, motherfucker!
[flesh tears]
- [groaning]
- ♪ Making love ♪
♪ out of nothing at all...
"Thanks for nothing"?
Xuxuzinho.
- [grunting fiercely]
- Bro!
♪ Making love...
[Jonny] Whoo!
"Wu-Tang Clan ain't nuthing ta fuck wit!"
[groaning]
♪ Making love ♪
♪ out of nothing at all ♪
- [yells in pain]
- ♪ Making love ♪
♪ out of nothing at all ♪
♪ Making love...
[both yelling]
[straining]
- [yells]
- [flesh squishing]
- [grunting]
- [squishing continues]
- [gasping weakly]
- Oh.
Whoa.
Oh, yeah.
That is a dragon.
♪ Making love ♪
♪ out of nothing at all ♪
- [groans]
- ♪ Making love ♪
- ♪ out of nothing at all ♪
- [song fades]
- [quiet, tense music playing]
- [breathing heavily]
Fuck you, Walter.
[melancholy music playing]
[kahuna speaking Hawaiian]
[kahuna] ...Walter Hale.
[kahuna continues in Hawaiian]
[continues in Hawaiian]
[James] Hmm.
Mr. K's Syndicate boys.
Interesting crowd.
Yakuza, Syndicate.
Walter was a private detective.
I guess he walked a fine line.
There was no line.
Not with him.
So no Jonny?
Nah. Wrote Walter off years ago.
It's his father.
Something in him must want to be here.
You don't know Jonny like I do.
And you don't know him
like you think you do.
[squeals excitedly] Cousin!
[laughing]
- Hey, Nani.
- I missed you so much.
- [Jonny] Oh, you grew up.
- [Haunani] Ooh!
You called him?
It's for your own good. Family's family.
- Jonny, hi.
- Hey.
I'm Leila. We spoke on the phone.
- Yeah.
- Lani, Kai.
This is your Uncle Keo.
- So you're my dad's brother?
- [Jonny] Half.
How come I never met you?
'Cause your father doesn't like me.
Why not?
Because I'm better-looking.
You have more hair.
So much more.
Can I braid it?
No.
Aw. Man.
- [Jonny grunts]
- Jonny.
James.
[kahuna continues speaking Hawaiian]
Oh, good.
I was worried this would be awkward.
I'm sorry, I know your wife
actually does the talking for you.
Oh. If she did, she'd probably ask
why you're dressed
like a gorilla at a gay bar.
Oh, shit.
- You got sand in your vagina.
- [kahuna stops talking]
[both] Sorry.
[sighs]
Please. I'm sorry.
[groans] You got old.
You got fat.
I can lose weight.
You're still gonna be old as fuck.
Oh, are we gonna keep measuring dicks,
or can we be civil for a minute?
Haven't decided yet.
Tell him.
I should've called. I'm happy you're here.
Couldn't hear. You were mumbling. What?
Oh. Thanks, Jimmy.
No, I'm not. Leila told me to say that.
Can we just get on
with the fucking funeral?
You're the puppet.
Just have her shove her hand up your ass
- and tell you what to say.
- It's a fucking funeral. Shut up.
Gentlemen. Please.
Sorry.
A close family friend,
Governor Peter Mahoe,
has come here to share a few words
of remembrance about Walter.
[both inhale deeply]
- Mahalo. [speaks Hawaiian]
- Aloha.
[speaking Hawaiian]
My dear 'ohana...
Oh, Keo.
You got pretty, brah.
Long time, brah.
Thank you all for taking the time
to mark the end of one journey
and the start of another.
Walter Hale was by no means a simple man.
And I'd be lying if I said
he hadn't made mistakes.
But since he has departed so suddenly,
the families still face many challenges,
one being that sacred code
of ho'oponopono, or forgiveness.
[gentle music playing]
You kept Malia's house?
[James] Yeah, I took over the mortgage
after she passed.
It's a lot smaller than I remember.
Nah, it was always small.
- She made room for you anyway.
- [scoffs]
Yeah, and you fucking hated that.
What are you talking about?
Jonny the Bastard.
What?
Yeah, I'm the walking reminder
that he fucked around on your mother,
and you never let me forget it.
Oh, Jesus Christ. This again?
That's not what I was saying.
- What are you saying?
- Walter left Malia for Kim.
It broke up my family.
All right? I was just a kid.
I'm sorry if it took me
a fucking minute to get over it.
Yeah, maybe you still haven't.
And maybe you're still a bastard.
- Mm.
- Well, this should be fun.
Yeah, I'm fucking pumped.
- [belches]
- [gasps]
Well, it's nice to have you boys
under the one roof.
Your mother would've been very happy.
Yeah, I was sorry to hear
that Malia had passed on.
Yeah, you should've come back, then.
You were like a son to her.
- I wasn't her son.
- [Haunani] I know that, asshole.
- That's what "like a son" means.
- [kids laughing]
- Oh, my God, Haunani. Every damn--
- [Lani] "Asshole."
[Haunani] Literally, you fucking dumbass.
- "Like a son." That's what it means.
- [Leila] Loves to talk rubbish.
What? What? Oh, shit.
[Haunani] Don't copy Auntie.
[laughter]
Uh, so... are you seeing anyone, Jonny?
Hmm?
Yes.
No. I-I don't know.
Sounds serious.
Well, I think Walter would have
really appreciated you being here.
I'm not here for him.
I came to find out who killed him.
Killed him?
- What are you talking about?
- Yeah, it was a hit-and-run.
I don't think so.
Okay, kids, go get ready for bed.
It's just getting interesting.
- Hey! Don't talk back to your mother.
- Whoa.
Good boy.
What the hell are you talking about?
They came into my house last night,
- and they tried to kill me.
- Who tried to kill you?
I'm betting half of Oklahoma
wants to kill you.
There's not a lot of yakuza in Oklahoma.
There we go. I knew it.
I knew you couldn't come back here
without stirring shit up.
- Oh, f--
- Wait, wait, James.
Nothing changes with you.
Even after all these years,
you're still looking for new ways
to get yourself killed.
- Mālie. Mālie.
- Yeah, don't worry about it.
- I don't expect you to help me.
- Nothing to help with.
That's the same thing you said
about my mother.
[clears throat]
[sighs] Let me talk to you outside
for a second.
Nah, I'm good right here.
No, you're not.
Go.
[softly] Go.
[Jonny groans softly]
[somber music playing]
- Wow.
- [Haunani] Mm.
I see he still knows
how to be a real dick.
Just cut him some slack, Nan.
He's... you know he's been through a lot.
[wind gusting]
Sure you don't want to go any further?
What's the matter? Truth hurt?
You need to get your head out of your ass.
Oh, that's a great note, James.
Someone killed Walter?
You haven't seen or talked to the guy
in over 20 years,
and all of a sudden, you want to go
sniff around in his business?
You're just gonna stir up trouble.
That's what you do.
It's like your fucking superpower.
That's what I do because I'm a cop.
- Not here you're not.
- You don't have to worry about it.
I see it. You got your...
your beautiful wife
and your kids and your job with the Navy.
I'm sure you're real fucking popular
around here.
Fuck you. You're not gonna make me
apologize for that.
Why don't you trust me just fucking once?
You couldn't find the guy
who killed your mother,
so now all of a sudden,
you decided someone killed your father.
- Fuck you.
- So you got to find that guy.
Fuck you, man. You don't get it.
- There's nothing to get.
- Just go back to your life.
- It was a hit-and-run.
- I'll figure it out myself.
At least I got a fucking life
to go back to.
["Ordinary World" karaoke track playing]
[off-key] ♪ Came in from
a rainy Thursday ♪
♪ on the avenue ♪
♪ Thought I heard you talking softly...
Hey, baby.
You want to go
to private singing room with me?
I don't sing.
Oh, I can make you sing.
[snickers]
Uh... maybe another time.
[scoffs, mutters]
Woof.
- You look like you can use it.
- Do I?
Oh.
[sighs]
Mmm.
I knew I smelled shit.
[chuckles softly]
Jonny Hale.
Alekai.
You know, I didn't think that even you
were dumb enough to come back here.
I look a lot dumber than I am.
[scoffs]
I see they managed to put your...
face back together.
Mm.
Mr. K says hello.
[clicks tongue] That old fuck still alive?
Still the Syndicate kahuna,
still alive and kicking.
He wants to see you.
Hard pass.
Well, do yourself a favor.
[echoing] Don't try to run
when it kicks in.
[ominous music playing]
Sorry, hon.
[Jonny, distorted] You roofied me?
[grunts]
Pussy. [coughs]
["Eyes Without a Face"
karaoke track playing]
[Mr. K speaks Hawaiian]
[groans]
[Mr. K sighs]
Aloha, Jonny Hale.
Mr. K. [sniffs]
Good to see you.
You know, you showed a lot of character
bringing your father's spirit here
to rest.
I like that, bruddah. That's pono.
- I respect that.
- Thank you.
And that is why you can still take a piss
standing up, brah.
You know, the Syndicate has
a long memory, bruddah,
and you hurt a lot of my guys.
You killed my mother.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
And, brah, if you think you're gonna hang
around over here... [speaks Hawaiian],
my guys are gonna take that personally.
It's not gonna be good for you, Jonny.
It's not gonna be good for them, either.
And that is why I am here right now
offering you free passage.
It's a better deal than you'll get
from the yakuza.
I mean, if you send your men for me,
I'm gonna put 'em in bags.
Except for the fat shit over there,
you know, because he won't fit.
[chuckles]
I'm trying to do you a favor, Jonny boy.
Why don't you just go back home
to where you came from?
I'm from here.
No, you're not from here, brah.
Not anymore.
Let's go, boys.
Get him. Let's go.
Ah, f-- Come on, man.
All right, all right, listen.
- Oh, no. Shit.
- Come on.
- Goddamn it.
- Hold him down!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
- [Mr. K] Hold him down.
You don't listen, brah.
You no listen.
You like doing your own kind of thing.
- Yeah, bruddah.
- Oh, fuck! Come on!
[Jonny groaning]
You're gonna wear my mark now, brah.
- You're gonna wear my mark.
- [pained grunting, whimpering]
You're gonna be safe now but not for long.
I'm gonna give you seven days.
Seven days, and then if you're not gone
by that time, brah,
you're gonna go for a long swim.
Do you understand me, Jonny boy?
I hate swimming. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm good.
[Mr. K] Get him up!
[waves crashing]
[groaning]
[seabirds squawking]
[coughs]
Ow.
[lively chatter nearby]
[somber music playing]
[lively chatter continues]
[groans]
[sniffs]
[grunts]
[belches, groans]
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct police radio chatter]
[James] Detective Rennert.
- Detective Rennert.
- Hmm?
How you doing?
Commander James Hale.
- Walter's son.
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry for your loss, truly.
- Thank you.
But I am late for a briefing.
- You mind if I walk with you?
- Sure.
I was hoping to get a look
at the police report.
You can, but I can tell you
you're not gonna find anything in it.
Why's that?
'Cause he was hit in Kalihi.
No one talks to the cops over there.
No witnesses, no forensics, no nothing.
Traffic cams?
Uh, one. Wasn't working.
- That's pretty convenient, isn't it?
- [chuckles]
Half of them are out across the island.
We got, like, what,
two guys in a truck fixing 'em?
Budget cuts.
So a private detective with known ties
to the criminal underworld
gets killed in a dead zone,
and no one's giving it another look?
There is no reason
to believe that this was
anything other than
a straight hit-and-run.
You guys don't investigate hit-and-runs?
Sure, we do. All 46 of them.
[sighs]
What about his personal effects?
You can stop by the desk sergeant
on the way out, sign for 'em.
All right. Thanks.
Commander Hale.
I know who you are.
Navy SEALs and all that.
Let's just say your brother's reputation
precedes him.
Now I got two badass sons
looking into their father's death.
Guy like Walter, well,
it would be a big mistake.
I can almost guarantee you
that you'll end up poking a bear
that doesn't want to be poked.
Detective Rennert...
with all due respect,
you don't really know who I am.
So you're gonna have to take
my word for it when I tell you
that I'm the fucking bear.
[intriguing music playing]
Thanks for your time.
[jackhammering]
[rummaging in bag]
[metallic clinking]
Hmm.
[suspenseful music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[lively chatter in distance]
[dog barking in distance]
[door creaking]
[muffled music playing in other room]
[siren wailing in distance]
Impressive.
[takes deep breath]
- Please have beer.
- [clattering]
[sighs in relief]
[cap pops off bottle]
[cap clatters on floor]
[long sigh]
Oh.
Nice little hand-me-down.
All right.
[locks clicking]
[tense music playing]
[door creaking]
[door closing]
- [knocking]
- Holy sh-shit!
[Jonny] Ah, fuck.
[energetic music playing]
[groans]
[laughs]
Hey, suck my boto, you fucker.
Well, fuck you, fat Jackie Chan! Fuck!
♪ ♪
- [bystander] Whoa!
- [lively chatter]
[panting]
- [whooping fiercely]
- [groaning]
- Hey.
- [groans] Cunt! Fuck!
Say, boto.
- Fuck. Oh, wait.
- Come here.
Wait, wait, wait! Oh, my God, somebody!
Somebody help me!
It's all right. I'm a cop.
Now, what were you doing
in Walter's apartment?
You trying to rob him?
Hey, fuck you, okay?
Walter was like a father to me.
Walter wasn't a father to anyone.
Yeah, how the fuck would you know?
Because I'm his son.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
You're Jonny.
Wow. Uh, hey, look.
I just worked for your dad, okay?
Hacked emails and tapped the phones
and took fuck-pics of people. That's it.
You know who would've wanted him killed?
[scoffs] How much time you got?
Walter was a fucking disruptor, brah.
What's the last thing he had you doing?
[sighs] Uh, get a job with Nui Loa.
Who's that?
No, no, it's a fucking catering company.
Like, a high-end kind.
You know, like, I've been carrying around
shrimp toast on trays
for the last two weeks.
Why would he want you doing that?
I don't know, brah.
He just told me to get the fucking job.
I got the fucking job.
[yells in pain]
Fucking motherfucker,
that fucking hurts, brah.
You swear a lot.
Fuck you, cuz.
- Fucking--
- What's your name?
Pika.
That's a stupid name.
Well, good news, Pika.
You work for me now.
Come here. Come here.
- [screams]
- [crunching]
It's fixed. You're welcome.
- [whimpering]
- Here.
- It'll help your balls drop.
- [sighs]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [horn honks]
[takes deep breath]
[intriguing music playing]
♪ ♪
[♪ Tommy Cash sings "Untz Untz"]
[Duke] Aloha, pervert.
Oh. Do I know you?
No.
No, I can't say that I've been in before.
Well, you know, the hardest part
is coming through the door.
What's your kink, man?
We're running a special on the anal beads.
Two for one.
You look like you could handle
a couple of ropes.
No, thanks. I'm stocked up.
Okay.
I was, uh, just noticing
your security camera system.
I was thinking maybe
the camera out front probably has
a pretty good view of the street.
I was hoping... I could get a look at it.
Uncle!
Huh? What is it?
[Duke] Got a sexy soldier out here.
Uncle?
I was hoping to get a look at some
of your security camera footage
from a couple nights ago,
between 12:00 and 4:00 a.m.
[chuckles]
Can't help you, friend.
Oh. Not really a friend.
More of a paying customer.
You think you can buy me for 300 bucks?
Get the fuck out of my store,
you fucking squid.
Well, the cash isn't really for the help.
I'm gonna get that for free.
It's for the damage.
[chuckles] What damage?
[screams]
- [Jonny] Did you shoot these?
- [Pika] Yeah.
You're a little pervert.
It was for your dad, okay?
And also, twisting my nose
does not fix my nose.
- That beer will.
- [Pika groans]
[intriguing music playing]
Did Walter surf?
Nah. He had bad knees.
The fin's on wrong.
- Oh, shit.
- What the hell?
What the fuck are you up to, Walter?
[Peter] The Hawaiian people
have been waiting far too long
to be given what is rightfully yours.
[crowd] Yes!
Good turnout, considering the weather.
Yeah, the governor's been trending up
in low-income neighborhoods.
Hawaiian people are living in tent cities
when they should be living
in their own homes on their own land,
- on their own 'aina.
- [cheering]
Uh, I'm gonna take this.
- You go up and stand by with him.
- Copy that.
[Peter] So I need each
and every one of you to come...
I'm at work. What do you want?
Hey. What is it you actually do
for Peter again?
Uh, PR, emails,
plan events, dinners.
Pretty much wipe his ass at this point.
Why?
So you're an assistant. Listen.
I found some plans or a survey
or something in Walter's apartment,
and it's got this government seal on it,
but I have no idea what it is,
- so...
- And this matters because?
Because they were jerry-rigged
into a fucking surfboard.
He was hiding them.
I can access the database
when I get back to the office.
There should be an eight-digit file number
on the plans-- text them to me.
I got it. Okay. Listen, I see it.
I just need you to do it
as fast as you can
- because I-I was--
- [phone beeps]
You hung up on me, you fucking...
If you were a man,
I would punch you in the face.
[inhales deeply, chuckles]
Family, right?
I mean, you've got probably lots.
Oh, my God, bro, I can't even--
- Even in the same house.
- Whatever.
That was racist. My bad.
[sighs] Huh.
[Pika clearing throat]
Okay, well, looks like you got stuff
to figure out.
Uh, I'm gonna go to the clinic
'cause I'm pretty sure
- you gave me a concussion.
- [door rattling]
- Oh, sh--
- [grunts]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa.
Whoa, man. I almost killed you.
Bullshit.
[pained gasp]
- You were still reacting.
- [Jonny] Reacting?
That's why my gun was out, huh?
Where'd you get the gun, anyway?
Family heirloom.
[Pika exclaiming]
Cocksucking fucker!
- Who's Uncle Fester?
- [Pika] Fuck you!
I have alopecia, okay?
That's Pika. What are you doing here?
Same thing as you, I guess.
Huh. I thought it was a hit-and-run.
Yeah, I'm being methodical.
You should try it sometime.
I got here before you, didn't I?
Yeah, maybe, but you don't have that.
[intriguing music playing]
[Jonny] This is the stickiest computer.
Gross.
Oh, man.
Just mowed him down like he was nothing.
- [sighs]
- [taps key]
- There's no license plate.
- [James] He didn't even brake,
not till way after the hit.
When someone crosses your path,
your natural reaction is brake and swerve.
Unless you're aiming for him.
Yeah.
Did Walter have any connections
at the DMV?
Uh, yeah, but I don't know who it was.
All right, well, ask around. I need a list
of every blue van on the island.
What was the name of the caterer?
- What caterer?
- Uh, Nui Loa.
All right, well, give me a list
of all the events
they had over the last week
and what they have
- coming up for the next two weeks.
- Okay.
I'm just being methodical.
[Pika] Uh, so...
there's, like, the matter
of compensation, yeah,
so we gonna discuss that right now or...
Shoots. I'm just gonna head out, then.
I guess we're not gonna get
any punani this month, huh?
[door opens]
[door closes]
[James] You live your whole life just
to end up in a shitty little apartment
that smells like ass and...
with no one here to miss you
when you're gone.
Hey.
He fucking deserved it.
[closes laptop]
Come on.
Grab your little pee-pee.
[mocking] "Grab your little pee-pee."
Bro, you said it yourself:
The van never even slowed down.
That just means it was a hit-and-run.
That's not the same as saying
it was a targeted assassination.
Walter's apartment was just
torn apart by someone.
Yeah, or Walter was a fucking slob.
Jesus, Mary and Joseph
and all the fluffin' saints.
My God, you're as useless
as a bag of limp dicks, I'll tell you.
- [James groans]
- Talking to you is like pushing rope.
[James] Then stop talking to me.
[Jonny] Come on.
Hear me out.
The busted traffic cam, half of the cast
of Dragon Ball Z's at my house,
the no headlight on the van.
Something's rotten here, man.
It could be something,
or it could be nothing.
[mocking] "It could be something,
or it could be nothing."
Yes, Jimmy, you're absolutely right.
Look, I'm not ruling it out.
Then why does it sound to me like you are?
I don't know,
'cause you're not very bright.
I'm fucking brighter than you are.
Dude, I've been a rez cop for 15 years.
I know what the fuck I--
- [crashing]
- [both grunting]
- [engine revving]
- [tires squealing]
[screams]
[grunting]
Fuck! Go, go, go!
- Come on, you piece of shit.
- [engine whining]
- [tires squealing]
- [exciting music playing]
[shouting in Japanese]
Oh, shit.
- [engine revving]
- [tires squealing]
[grunts]
[people screaming]
[shouts]
[grunting]
[shouting]
[shouts]
Shit. Bulletproof.
[shouting continues]
[grunts]
[groans]
[grunting]
[yells, grunts]
Fuck.
[yells]
- [gun clicking]
- Oh, fuck.
Oh. [grunting]
[heavy gunfire]
- Everybody down!
- [people screaming]
Stay down!
- [grunting]
- [bullets whizzing]
[people screaming]
- [yells]
- [screaming continues]
[shouts in Japanese]
- [grunts]
- [yelling]
[shouts in Japanese]
- [gunfire continues]
- [bystander groans]
[grunts]
Get off!
Jump!
[yells]
- Oh, shit.
- [metal screeching]
You good?
[breathing heavily]
[operator over phone] Nine-one-one.
What is your emergency?
Shots fired on King and Alakea.
Please send emergency services and backup.
What the fuck?!
Gee, James, you still think
it could be nothing?
- Are you out-- [panting]
- [sirens approaching]
[grunts in frustration, continues panting]
You blew up my car.
You blew up my fucking car.
No, I blew up their car,
and then it landed on yours.
[explosion]
[Jonny laughing] Oh, shit!
I just blew up your car.
[panting]
You're welcome?
I saved your life, man.
Come on. Help me.
You fucking asshole.
I fucking loved that car.
[Rennert] What the actual fuck
are you guys thinking, huh?!
Those are four yakuza hitters
you-you turned into toast back there.
You want to tell me why
the yakuza wants you dead?
You'd have to ask them.
Yakuza? That's who that was?
Mm-hmm. So this is the brother
from Oklahoma, the cop?
That's me. [chuckles]
[mocking chuckle]
Not according to your boss.
Suspended with pay,
pending an investigation for...
- What the hell is he talking about?
- ...excessive force.
- I'm getting paid?
- What the fuck, Jonny?
- Sweet.
- Could you shut the fuck up?
I'm trying to help you here.
[James] If you want to help, here.
Take this. It's a security cam video
of the hit-and-run.
It'll give you the make and model
of the van you're looking for.
How the hell'd you get this?
By doing your job.
- Yeah.
- [Jonny clicks tongue]
This kind of shit,
that doesn't happen here every day.
So you consider this your final warning.
I can't have two guys who look like
they eat steroid pancakes for breakfast
turning my island into Beirut!
Detective, that is uncalled-for.
Are you gaslighting us?
'Cause I feel emotionally targeted
right now.
Now, you two stop doing
this wrecking crew shit,
or I will fuck you harder
than you've ever been fucked!
Again, uncalled-for.
Yeah, with my boundaries
and all that fucking, I feel triggered.
Yeah, I'm, uh...
I'm gonna go take a piss.
[crunching]
Don't be here when I get back.
[heavy sigh]
Is Mercury in retrograde, or is
Detective Sergeant Boomer just an asshole?
He's a fucking asshole.
I don't think he likes me very much.
Does anyone actually like you?
Fuck you.
I'm just saying, you could work on
your people skills a little bit.
- [Jonny mumbling mockingly]
- [sighs] Jesus Christ.
"Can't understand what I'm saying
'cause I'm farting out of my mouth."
Do you ever shut up?
[Jonny making fart noises,
mumbling mockingly]
[James] It's like you're getting paid
by the fucking hour.
What?! Say what?!
What do you charge to not talk?
[Haunani] Uh, I tracked down
the original architect
and found that these were for a property
on the east side of the island, up north.
They were commissioned
by the Robichaux firm.
Who's that?
Marcus Robichaux is a big haole developer.
Hotels and resorts are all over here,
Asia, Europe.
His family controlled
the sugarcane industry
on the island for generations.
So you think Walter was working
with Vampire Lestat here?
[Haunani] Mm, Robichaux is big-time.
If he needed P.I. work, he'd hire, like,
I don't know, ex-CIA or Mossad,
not a bottom-feeder like Walter.
No offense.
So Lestat's building more hotels. So what?
It's not a hotel. It's a casino.
- What?
- What do you know about casinos?
Nothing. I just know how to read.
It says Sacred Princess Casino
on the back.
Hot damn. Look at that.
Show-off.
That makes no sense.
Gambling is illegal here.
I think we should have a talk
with Mr. Robichaux.
[Jonny clicks tongue]
He's actually hosting his annual
fundraiser for the art museum tomorrow.
- [James] Sweet.
- Mm.
No, you can't. You can't go.
Sounds like fun.
It's invitation only, for big donors.
And you two big fuckers
don't exactly blend in.
- Oh, we're big donors, and, uh--
- [Haunani] N-No.
- Ew.
- [Jonny] Don't worry.
We blend.
Where do you think you're going?
I'm going to a motel
so I can get some rest.
- No, you should stay here.
- [mouthing]
Right, James?
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
[both mouthing]
[Lani humming
"Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star"]
[chuckles]
What are you doing?
You look beautiful.
[Lani chuckles]
[scoffs softly]
Oh, Lani, go back to bed, baby.
You're no fun.
Oh, bad Lani.
Hello.
One twenty-one.
Ooh, ta-ta-ta.
What is James doing with you?
Too big.
[engine starting]
[chuckling] Ooh!
- Don't even think about it.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm just gonna take a ride down
to Robichaux's construction site.
Not on my bike.
That's the bus, just like the olden days.
Jonny, get off my bike.
Forget a tie?
You look good, though. Good job.
You want to tell me why you got suspended?
Nah.
Uh, I shot a dealer who was selling meth
to kids on the rez.
Okay.
Okay?
Yeah.
Still can't ride my bike.
You can ride this one.
[Jonny] Oh.
- Walter's old piece of shit.
- Yeah.
- It's from, like, the '40s.
- Mm-hmm.
[Jonny] It's all rusty
and probably doesn't even run.
He used to call it a knucklehead.
- Like a dime a dozen.
- Yeah.
It's pretty crowded in here.
I could get it off your hands
for like, I don't know...
300 bucks.
No chance. Nice try, though.
[♪ Ka'ikena Scanlan sings "Brains"]
[song continues with spoken word
in Hawaiian]
♪ Well, it's not the same,
it's not as simple as before ♪
♪ It's not our bodies but our brains
they're using for their war ♪
♪ Confused and in pain,
we don't know what we're fighting for ♪
♪ So they watch us kill each other
as we pile up on the floor ♪
♪ So what's the future
to the youths of today? ♪
♪ 'Cause I said I'm looking
for the truth ♪
♪ but I see them look
to the books and pray ♪
♪ With YouTubes and Facebooks,
them can't look away ♪
♪ Don't let our culture die
in the museum display...
[Jonny] They're really gonna
put a casino here?
[James] I don't see any construction site.
- You sure you got the right address?
- Of course I did.
- Look.
- [rooster crowing]
Yep. Weird.
[man] You boys look lost.
That depends. Where are we?
The Kingdom of Hawaii, brother.
Yeah, I mean this valley-- who owns it?
You do.
And I do. We all do.
But everybody's welcome here.
[man] Auntie.
- [Olina] Mahalo, boy.
- [James] Huh.
Didn't know this community was here.
Nobody does.
- Here.
- [grunts]
Come on, boy.
[Jonny] Remember this?
- Oh, fucker.
- [kids shouting playfully nearby]
[groans]
[Olina] Being here is about
more than just family by blood.
It's about ohana of community.
That's why we need to protect it.
These are Hawaiian Home Lands.
Why didn't the government do anything?
For ten centuries, the Aha Moku
have been responsible for this land.
They think we live here
because we don't have any homes.
But the haoles,
they will come for this land.
And when that happens,
we'll be ready to sound the alarm.
You know something we don't?
[scoffs] More than I want.
Less than I should.
You Hawaiian?
Half.
[Olina scoffs]
There's no half.
You're either in or you're out.
Hmm? Your brain's not confused.
Just your spirit.
Be one with your spirit.
[phone ringing]
Come on, let's get back to work.
Mahalo.
It's Pika.
Hey.
Shit. We got to go.
Cops pulled a blue van
out of the surf off Makapu'u.
[Rennert] So, our John Doe is Simi Iona,
low-level accountant
in the governor's office.
Went missing a few days ago.
Uh, does that mean anything?
- No?
- Nope.
Damage to the front grill of the van
makes it a contender for our hit-and-run.
Yeah, not to mention someone went through
the trouble of dumping it in the ocean.
Yeah. No plates.
But I do have a list
of all the blue vans
registered on the island.
Any... any familiar names leap out to you?
Can we keep this?
No!
It's police business, as in my business,
as in not yours because--
and-and this bears repeating--
you're not a cop here.
And you, you are not a cop anywhere.
Yes? Yes?
Yes? What?
Pika.
[indistinct conversation]
- Hey. Focus.
- Ow. Whoa, what? What?
I'm right here.
We need you to find out what you can
about this Hayashi Imports.
What's that?
It was the only Japanese name
on Rennert's blue van list.
- We can at least start there.
- Whoa. Hey, come on, guys.
We got... we got the Robichaux party
in a few hours.
We're not invited.
Don't worry. I know the caterer.
[♪ Elia y Elizabeth sing "Alegría"]
[Jonny] Of course you know the caterer,
you fat fuck.
- [song continues over speakers]
- [lively chatter]
[song continues with singing in Spanish]
Fucking Japanese yakuza clowns.
[partygoer] Hey! Marcus!
- Hey.
- There you are, Robichaux. Come on.
- Oh, cheers.
- [conversation continues indistinctly]
Hey, where you guys stay? He's here.
- Can you hold this really quickly?
- Whoa, what the hell is this?
I just got to go
to get something in the back.
- Where are you going?
- I-I'll be right back.
- Hey, brah!
- Oh, my bad. My bad.
- Oh, hey. How are you? Hey, hey.
- Hi.
All right, all right.
Hey. You guys are late.
[Jonny] We blend.
Shit, Magnum P.I. ain't got shit on us.
- [Pika] Come on, let's go.
- [James sighs]
Nice place.
- What's this?
- Hayashi Imports.
- Oh.
- It's owned by a whole slew
of Japanese holding companies.
- You know what that means: yakuza.
- Yakuza.
So it's a front?
- Doesn't have to be.
- [partygoer] Oh, thank you.
The yakuza got plenty
of legit businesses here on the island.
Okay. You guys good?
- Yeah.
- I got to get back to work.
Hey, split up.
You guys look like The Rock
fucked himself and had twins.
[groans]
Uh, I hate to admit it--
kid's probably right.
Jonny.
[sighs]
This fucking guy.
Hey. James. Hey.
Stop standing around.
You look like a fucking narc.
[quiet chatter]
[snaps fingers]
I really like your scarf.
Hello, my good man. Give me a Kalohe.
- [bartender] You got it.
- Oh.
Didn't see you there. Aloha.
Vodka and Guinness?
You call that a Kalohe?
Yeah. It means, uh...
Mischievous. Yes.
Or a rascal, which, um, seems appropriate.
- Who, me?
- [chuckles]
[Pika] Make sure you use soap,
and fix your collar, brah.
[sighs]
Yo, give me a plate.
I hope you won't be offended,
but you don't, um...
you don't look like you belong here.
Jonny Rascal.
[laughs]
You look like all kinds of trouble to me.
No, it's Hale. Jonny Hale.
- Hale?
- Mm-hmm.
As in Walter Hale?
Yeah, he's my father. You knew him?
Yes.
Wait. What do you mean, "knew"?
Has something happened to him?
He's dead.
[grunts]
[speaking Japanese]
[sniffing, taking deep breaths]
[Monica] How did he die?
Violently.
How-how did you know my father?
Look, please, can you...
I hired him to look into
my husband's activities.
Who's your husband?
I'm sorry. I...
I assumed.
I'm Monica Robichaux.
You're Marcus Robichaux's wife.
Awesome.
- Yo. Can I help you?
- Hey.
Hey. Dropped that.
Hayashi Imports. Small world.
What do you know about it?
I know that you guys misplaced a blue van.
Are you a cop?
No.
U.S. Navy.
You're the frogman.
You got a little something.
[sniffs]
So, why would you hire Walter
to investigate your husband?
We're getting a divorce.
Without some leverage,
things won't go well for me.
You mean financially?
No, Jonny.
I do not mean financially.
So, what does a frogman want
with a blue van?
What does the yakuza want
with a guy like Robichaux?
[chuckles softly] I don't know
anything about yakuza,
but a man who works at Pearl Harbor
should know better
than to fuck with the Japanese.
I think you're forgetting
how that story ended.
[chuckling]
[speaking Japanese]
- [others chuckling]
- [Jonny] Well, if you're getting divorced,
what the hell are you doing at this party?
Look...
[hushed] I can't talk here, okay?
It's not safe.
Come and see me tomorrow.
I'm staying at the penthouse
of Kiani Towers in Waikiki.
You know, there's a famous
Japanese saying:
"The child of frog is still just a frog."
Huh.
Interesting.
What's that mean?
It means that frogs never look both ways
when crossing the street.
[phone vibrating]
Oh.
I got to go, frogman.
See you around.
I look forward to it.
[Nakamura sniffs]
Sir?
- Come with us.
- Whoa. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
[tense music playing]
[under breath] Oh, fuck.
What's up, fellas? Get you a drink?
Would you please come with us, sir.
Uh, I still got a stack of dishes.
Mr. Robichaux would like a word with you.
Yeah.
- [Jonny exhales loudly]
- [glass shatters]
[Jonny inhales sharply, clears throat]
[belches]
Fucking prick.
[Robichaux] Ah. Gentlemen.
- [door closes]
- Come in.
This is very exciting.
We never have gate-crashers
at these events,
and I think you can understand why.
Because, honestly,
who the fuck would want to go
to a fundraiser if they didn't have to?
I don't know. Food's pretty good.
Open bar.
Yeah.
Looking at you, the two of you,
big men, big muscles,
but I assume that most people,
when they see you, will think,
"What a pair of lumbering idiots."
Hmm.
Am I right?
But not me. Not me.
I look into your eyes, and I can see
that you are smarter than you look.
[Jonny] Well, not him.
Well, that's obvious.
You are the clever one.
Mr. Robichaux, I'm James Hale.
This is my brother Jonny.
We're Walter Hale's sons.
I hope there's not a problem.
I paid Walter in full,
and I even gave him a bonus
for his... for his discretion.
You hired Walter?
I did, yes.
Walter's dead.
I'm awfully sorry to hear that.
Are you?
I don't think you are,
'cause I think you knew,
and I think you knew who we were
the moment we showed up.
That's why you invited us down here,
so you can see what is what.
Now, I know he's the clever one,
but is he implying
that I had something to do
with Walter's death?
No.
- No?
- Mr. Robichaux--
- 'Cause that would be absurd, my friend.
- I'm not implying shit.
I'm saying it direct to you, "Robi-cocks."
Jonny. [sighs]
If you don't mind me asking, what was
the nature of your business with Walter?
Not that it's any of your business,
but my beautiful wife here,
I suspected she was cheating on me,
so I had Walter tail her.
There's a lot of that
going around. [laughs]
[Robichaux] Well, it turned out
that she was not.
He presented a quite comprehensive report.
Can I please ask you to put that down?
That is a French F1 grenade
from World War I.
Sacrebleu!
Who cares?
Well, you might
when your hand's been blown off.
Oh.
Is that, uh...
how you ended up with those fingers?
Oh, my.
I guess the help has forgotten
to take out the trash.
[Robichaux chuckles]
I-Is that all?
I really need to get back to my guests,
so is there anything else
I can do for you?
- Uh, yeah, actually--
- That was a rhetorical question.
All righty, then. Thanks for your time.
Please, feel free to exit
the way you came in.
[scoffs]
- That was the wife?
- Yeah, well, the ex-wife.
Interesting.
Did you finish the dishes?
No, I was interrupted
by some coked-up yakuza.
- Well, that explains the fingers.
- Right.
[door opens]
[laughing]
Oh, honey.
Now what the fuck have you done?
[ominous music playing]
- [horn honking]
- [indistinct chatter]
Hey, hey. Stop, please.
Thank you.
[indistinct chatter continues]
[officer] Just gonna need you all
to stand back.
[chatter continues indistinctly]
[horn honking]
No.
Hey.
Excuse me.
- Excuse me. Excuse me.
- [officer 2 over radio] Twenty-two?
- Yeah. Yeah, 22. Go ahead.
- Copy, 22.
- [radio chatter continues indistinctly]
- [officer] Stand back.
Behind the line. Stay right here, please.
[tense music building]
[tense music crescendos, then stops]
[♪ Keauhou sings "Kewalo Uka"]
[song continues with singing in Hawaiian]
Robichaux!
You French fuck!
Hold it there. You're on private property.
- [song continues]
- [muffled grunting]
- [electrical crackling]
- [groaning]
- Ah, shit!
- [groans]
- [Monty] Hale!
Oh, it's fat John Cena.
- [electrical crackling]
- [groaning]
- Oh, yeah.
- [door opens]
[breathing heavily]
Sweet dick, bro.
Mr. Hale...
I'm starting to develop
a very strong dislike for you.
You killed her...
I know you fucking killed her.
Who is it I'm supposed
to have killed today?
You killed your wife.
You killed my father, you fucking asshole.
Mm-hmm.
Mr. Hale, I think perhaps you're confused.
Call the police.
- [thud]
- [song stops abruptly]
[distant door rattling]
[keys jingling]
[door opens]
Let me guess.
James sent you.
Nani called me.
Oh. She shouldn't have.
Well, lucky for you,
she saw it differently.
I managed to convince Mr. Robichaux
to drop the charges.
He killed his wife.
If that's true,
it's none of your business.
Let the cops handle it.
That's their job, not yours.
I loved Walter.
But there was something inside him.
A darkness.
Caused him to destroy
everything good in his life
over and over again.
He did it to Malia, to Kim, to you.
Himself.
And that darkness, it lives in you, too.
And James.
But the two of you,
you have something he never had.
A brother.
[melancholy music playing]
It'll take a few minutes
to process you out.
Love you, Jonny.
Uncle.
Mahalo.
Just like old times.
Asshole.
- Jonny.
- [thunder rumbling]
Hey! I'm talking to you!
You can't just come back here
tearing shit up,
doing whatever the fuck you want.
Leave me alone, James.
This is my home.
Fucking shit up is not gonna
bring your mother back.
- Hey! What the--
- Motherfucker.
[grunting]
[Jonny] Ah, fuck.
[groans]
[pained yelling]
Ah! Fuck you!
[yells]
[groans]
[thunder rumbling]
Come on!
[both yelling]
[panting]
[grunting unsteadily]
[groaning]
[panting]
[wheezing]
[coughs]
Fuck!
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
- [groaning]
[thunder rumbling]
Fuck is wrong with you?
[groaning]
What kind of man
abandons his little brother
when he needs him the most?
That's not what happened.
- No?
- No!
You sent me away, James.
You were going to prison.
The Syndicate was gonna fucking kill you!
If they didn't do it
when you were on the inside,
they would've got you
the fucking moment you got out.
Goddamn.
I was trying to fucking protect you.
I didn't know what else to do.
You wouldn't fucking listen to me.
It was, uh... it was the only thing
I could think of to save your life.
You have no idea what it's like
to look at your mother,
dead in the streets,
and she's staring into your eyes.
Fucking haunts me.
I couldn't protect her.
I couldn't do anything.
You were all that I had left,
and you fucking...
[somber music playing]
[sighs]
I know I let you down.
I fucked up.
I'm your big brother,
and I fucking gave up on you.
If I could, I'd...
I'd do everything differently.
I'm really sorry, Jonny.
I'm really...
...really fucking sorry.
I'm so fucking angry.
It's all I got.
Why are you chasing this so hard?
Walter wasn't any kind of father to you.
I never found the man that killed my mom.
Now someone killed my father.
It...
Someone's got to give them justice.
I'm all they have.
No, they got me, too.
So do you.
I'm not gonna lie to you, man.
You hit, like, fucking hard
- for an old fucker.
- [chuckling]
You think I punch hard?
You have no idea what's coming.
You got to be kidding me.
He started it.
Seriously?
You're supposed to be the adult here.
Hey. What about me?
You're a developmentally
arrested narcissist
- with anger issues.
- [James snickering]
And do you really want
to pull my focus right now?
No, don't laugh.
Don't get me started on you.
You're a passive-aggressive control freak.
I'm passive?
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah.
- Shut up.
- You're both juggling enough
crippling daddy issues to keep you
in therapy for the rest of your lives,
but instead, you just pound
on each other like fucking cavemen.
[Kai] Mom, guess what. I just--
[Leila] Oh, Kai.
Whoa. What happened?
Me and your dad just beat up
on the bad guys.
Looks like they beat you up.
Nah, we wrecked those guys.
Your mother did this to us.
No, you don't get to do that.
- Yuck. Get a room.
- [James chuckling]
- [phone vibrating]
- [kissing]
[sighs]
- Told you I have a girlfriend.
- [Leila and James] Mm.
- Latina. Spicy.
- [Leila exhales sharply]
Okay, I got to go now.
- Cute.
- I was just thinking about you. Oh, God!
[Jonny groaning]
"Spicy."
Ah, damn. [panting]
Ah, mi amor.
- I miss you.
- [Valentina] Why is your house
a crime scene?
- Oh, shit. I forgot about that.
- [scoffs]
You know what? I don't want to know.
Millie said your mail was piling up,
so I stopped by to pick it up.
You have a package and...
a bunch of overdue bills--
no surprise there.
- There's a package? Who's it from?
- Uh, someone...
- from Hawaii?
- Holy shit.
It's the package
the yakuza was looking for.
What's in it?
You think I'd open your mail?
Nenê.
- It's a thumb drive.
- Okay, baby, listen.
- Don't call me that.
- I need you to bring me the thumb drive.
I'm gonna send you a ticket to Oahu.
You're in Hawaii?
This whole time?
I wanted to go there with you.
You told me you were never going back.
I will explain everything
once you get here.
- I promise.
- Oh, okay. Great.
- [drops mail on seat]
- Except I'm not going to Hawaii.
- Nenê.
- I'll FedEx it to you.
No, listen. It's too important.
You have no idea what's going on here.
And I don't want to know.
- Xuxu.
- What did I tell you
- about calling me that?
- Xuxuzinho.
Hey, no. You listen to me.
There is no way in hell
I'm coming to Hawaii.
[man over speakers] Aloha.
Welcome to Daniel K. Inouye
International Airport.
If you've just arrived,
we hope that you enjoy...
Ah, man, I can't believe I wore this.
It's hot, hot.
We're in Hawaii,
and I got a leather coat on.
I look stupid. Do I look stupid?
- [James] Just take it off.
- Take it off? Take it off, right.
The muscles. How do my muscles look?
- Yeah, you're good.
- Show the muscles?
You're good. You look jacked.
I just feel like you're trying
way too hard.
[Jonny] There she is. Holy shit.
There she is. Goddamn, she looks hot.
Not bad, boss.
I underestimate you.
- Chili pepper water.
- Yeah, she's hot.
She's so spicy.
[James] She's spicy, brah.
[Jonny] Hey, Valentina.
Aloha. Hey, how are you--
[Jonny grunts]
We're not getting back together.
I'm staying for a day,
I'm going to the beach,
- and then I'm gonna go home.
- Okay.
Is that your brother?
- Yeah.
- Hey. James. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
He looks like you, only smarter.
- [chuckles]
- Hey, aloha, beautiful.
I just want to introduce myself.
My name is Pika.
If you need anything, let me know.
I'm your guy.
Bro, she's not your guy.
Did you bring the flash drive?
[woman over speakers] Welcome to
Daniel K. Inouye International Airport.
[announcement continues indistinctly]
I can't thank you enough.
This is... lifesaver. Got it.
- You can handle this?
- Yes, no worry.
- You look so beautiful. I just--
- [Valentina] Nope.
Not gonna happen.
Damn, right in the olos, huh?
[James] I like her.
Might want to pick up your balls.
Get my balls? Yeah?
Just our love language, bro.
Treats me like shit, and I love it.
- [♪ Player sings "Baby Come Back"]
- ♪ Baby, come back, oh, baby...
[Valentina] So, you're telling me
your estranged father,
who you haven't even spoken to
in 20 years,
was murdered by the yakuza
for this thumb drive?
[Jonny] Did I tell you
it's really good to see you?
Like, really good.
- Can you get in?
- Of course I can get in.
Fuck me.
I can't get in. Shit.
- Why? What's up?
- [sighs]
I don't know, some kind
of banking firewall or something.
It's a cold wallet.
It's digitally encrypted.
The drive is the key.
So whoever's account this is,
they need the drive
in order to access their money.
And Pika, if he hacks it,
then we'll be able to get the money,
we'll find out who it is.
Yep. Except he can't.
He needs the seed phrase--
randomly generated 12 words
that only the account holder has.
How many words?
Twelve.
Try these.
- Where'd you get that?
- It was in Walter's stuff.
So, uh, you two been chasing murderers
in a minivan?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he blew up my other car.
- Yeah, doesn't surprise me at all.
- That's not what happened.
- Literally what happened.
- No, it's not. I actually saved your life.
Remember when I saved your life,
- how cool that was?
- No, you didn't.
- [Pika] Can you two shut up, please?
- Remember?
I'm trying to focus back here.
- This is what I've been dealing with.
- Oh, dude, trust me, I know.
- I lived with him.
- Thanks for saving my life, man.
- You're welcome.
- So heroic of you.
She's hot.
Really hot, dude.
- Spicy hot.
- Yeah, hot.
You know I'm sitting right here, right?
[chuckling] Chili pepper water.
Chili pepper water.
[James and Jonny grunting rhythmically]
Do you all have fucking Tourette's?
- What's wrong with you?
- [tires squealing]
- [heavy gunfire]
- Oh, shit!
What the fuck?
- [Pika] What the--
- [Valentina] What was that?
- Uh, oh, my God.
- [intense music playing]
Oh, my... oh, my God.
- It's a fucking helicopter.
- Fuck.
Here, grab Leila's gun. [grunts]
Holy shit.
What the fucking Bullet-Tooth Tony
is this?
Less talk and more shooting.
- [Pika] Oh, shit!
- Your wife's amazing.
[Pika] Oh, shit!
[Valentina screams]
[all grunting]
[Pika] Shit!
- [tires squealing]
- [Pika] Oh, shit!
- Let me fucking drive! Trust me!
- [Jonny] Seriously, bro, let her drive.
- Come on.
- [Jonny] Go, go, go, go, baby.
Go. Go, go, go, go, go.
- [tires squealing]
- [horn honks]
[Jonny] Where is it? Oh, fuck.
I've been here for less than an hour,
and already people are shooting at me.
You know these fuckers.
Of course they want to kill them.
- I know I do.
- Baby, you look so beautiful.
Fuck you!
- Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
- [Valentina] I got it.
Shit!
[tires squealing]
[screaming]
Shit.
- [yelling]
- Shit.
[tires squealing]
[horn honks]
Oh, fucking ninjas on bikes with guns.
- Cool.
- Oh, my God!
Fuck you, ninjas!
- [Pika] Oh, my God!
- [groaning]
- Hold on!
- [Pika] What?
- [tires squealing]
- [yelling]
- [Pika] Oh, shit!
- [Jonny] Oh, shit.
[panting] I love you.
- I know.
- [tires squealing]
Oh!
- [Valentina screams]
- [Pika] Oh, my God!
- [Jonny] It's a ninja!
[horns honking]
Shit!
- [tires squealing]
- [horn honks]
[tires squealing]
- [groans]
- [Pika] Oh!
[Jonny yelling]
[Pika] Whoa!
[Pika whimpering]
[straining]
[Valentina screams]
Oh! His fucking arm came off!
[Jonny and Valentina groaning]
[door alarm chiming]
- Get him, bro!
- [Pika] Oh!
- [Jonny] Yeah! Woo-hoo!
- [Pika] Oh, shit! Holy fuck.
[Jonny chuckling]
[horn honks]
- Holy shit, he's erasing his head.
- [Pika] Oh, shit.
[James yells]
[horn honking]
Oh, shit.
Oh, damn.
[Jonny laughing]
[dramatic music playing]
- Oh, shit.
- Fuck.
[door alarm chiming]
- [door alarm stops]
- You thinking what I'm thinking?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Hold on to that thing.
- Oh.
- [James] I got two shots.
- I'm gonna lay it down.
[Valentina] Hey.
- [sighs]
- Don't you miss.
I'm gonna kill them all.
- [gun clicking]
- [groans]
[cocks gun]
[alarm blaring]
- [laughs]
- [chuckles uneasily]
[alarm continues blaring]
- Go! Go!
- Fuck!
Go, go, go, go! There's a helicopter--
I know!
[Jonny] Why doesn't your fucking car
go faster?
Mommy!
[all breathing heavily]
Oh, my fucking God.
[birds chirping]
[engine squealing, rattling]
[brakes squealing]
[metal clanging]
[attendant over speaker] Aloha.
Welcome to Zippy's.
What can I get you today?
[quiet chatter]
Oh, my God. That's so good.
It's so disgusting. It's all disgusting.
Got blood everywhere. You're eating?
[grunts loudly]
[scoffs]
Leila's gonna kill me.
It's not that bad, bro.
- It's got bullet holes in it.
- Looks good.
- [computer chiming]
- [Pika] Oh, my God.
I just got in. I just got in.
Uh, but, uh, I-I...
- I don't know what I'm looking at.
- [Valentina] Here.
These are international wire transfers.
- See, these are SWIFT codes here.
- [Pika] Mm.
Wow, $12 million going into
the same account over three years?
Whose account?
I'm trying to see.
It went through several offshore accounts
and then into the same account
in the Cayman Islands,
uh, belonging to a...
[sounding out] "Mayhoe" P.A.
Peter Mahoe. No fucking way.
Bro.
You know him?
Know him? Brah, everybody knows him.
He's the governor.
Holy shit.
[Haunani] Governor.
[suspenseful music playing]
Governor.
- Hey.
How's Jonny doing?
Ah, he's Jonny.
Thank you, by the way,
for getting him out of jail.
Well, the trick is not getting him out,
it's keeping him out.
- Right?
- What was he thinking,
attacking Robichaux like that?
That's what I wanted to talk to you about.
I think there might be more to Robichaux
then we first thought.
Robi-cocks wants to build
a casino resort in Hawaii
but he needs someone to legalize gambling
and he wants to build it
on Hawaiian Home Lands.
Right, so for $12 million
he buys himself a governor
and then he brings in the yakuza
for extra muscle.
But Walter's kicking up dirt
for Robi-cocks's wife
and stumbles across
the freaking motherlode.
These are plans for a resort and casino
to be built on Hawaiian Home Lands
no less.
Well, he can draw up
whatever plans he wants
but I'm telling you, Nani,
it's not going to happen on my watch.
Tomorrow, I'm gonna ask
for a comprehensive review
of all Robichaux's projects on the island.
- Okay.
- Good work, Nani.
- I'll take these.
- Oh. Thank you, Uncle.
♪ ♪
[James] And then that kid,
the one that Rennert brought up
from the ocean...
- Simi Iona.
- Right, the government accountant.
Walter must've found him, and he got him
to download all those dirty transactions.
Maybe blackmail?
- Maybe he's a whistleblower?
- Snitch witch.
- Either way, he gave Walter that drive.
- Right.
Peter figures it out so he's got to
get it back before everything comes out.
He calls Robichaux,
Robichaux calls the yakuza...
Then they torture the accountant
who gives up Walter.
And then they kill Walter.
- Then they kill Walter.
- Shit.
[engine squealing, rattling]
[intriguing music playing]
[Jonny] Excuse me. [sighs]
[Pika] I can set up anywhere or...?
- [James] Yeah, table.
- Okay.
[Valentina] Thanks.
- By the... volcano.
- Put your stuff here, baby.
[Jonny sighs]
[James] Baby, we're home.
I would love to make you a drink.
- Something strong.
- Strong.
[James] Kai? Lani?
- [Jonny] Okay.
- [Valentina sighs]
Um, I'm probably gonna need a shower.
- Yeah, there's one down the hall.
- Sorry. Okay.
- Leila!
- First in the shower, I love it.
[phone line ringing]
[phone vibrating]
- [line continues ringing]
- [vibrating continues]
[tense, mysterious music playing]
- [phone beeps off]
- [vibrating stops]
[Jonny] James.
James, what's going on?
Lani! Kai!
Kai!
[breathing heavily]
[Lani screams, gasping]
- [Lani whimpering]
- Come here, baby.
[breathing heavily] Kai, are you okay?
- Kai.
- They took her.
I-I tried.
- [Lani crying]
- They-they took her.
I'm sorry, I should've protected her.
[James] No, it's okay. It's okay.
- I couldn't do anything. I...
- No, it's okay. Come here.
- I should've... I should've protected her.
- No.
You did the right thing.
I should've done something.
- [James] Okay.
- I should've done something.
[Kai] I should've protected her.
I should've...
- I'm sorry.
- [James] It's okay.
[Kai] I tried to protect her.
[gentle music playing]
- I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- All right, come on.
[Kai speaking softly]
- [phone chimes]
- I'm sorry, Dad.
I should've done something.
[Kai crying]
I'm sorry.
Hey, why don't you guys go with Valentina.
- Okay. Okay.
- It's gonna be all right, bud.
- Okay.
- Come here. I'm Valentina, guys.
[Robichaux recording] Jonny,
this is me, Marcus.
And here it is, live from the basement,
the Robichaux show
and we have guests on the show today.
[Haunani panting]
Get that camera out of my face,
you haole piece of shit!
- [blow lands]
- [Haunani grunts]
[Robichaux] Feisty as fuck.
Look at all this mess you have made
and all for a father
who does not give a shit about you.
Oh, more people are coming in.
It's a party.
- Look who's here.
- [Leila grunting]
- Nani! Nani!
- [Haunani] Leila. Leila.
[Robichaux] That's a little something
for you, James.
[overlapping shouting]
All right, Jonny,
I think you get the idea.
The drive for the women.
I want you to bring it over here
- and I want you to do it fucking now.
- [Haunani and Leila gasping]
You know where I live.
Toodles.
[ominous music playing]
♪ ♪
Fuck me.
Grab a bag. Stack up.
[clicks]
[tense, energetic music playing]
You know he's not gonna trade.
Neither are we.
[clicks]
♪ ♪
- [automatic gunfire]
- [grunts]
[grunting]
[static crackles]
- [silenced gunshot]
- [grunts]
[Jonny] All right, quick recap:
in and out in 15 minutes.
[James] Let's go get the girls.
Let's go kill 'em all.
[tense, energetic music continues]
- [knife slicing]
- [muffled grunting]
[body thuds]
[zipper whizzes]
[urinating]
- [silenced gunshot]
- [grunts, body thuds]
♪ ♪
- [silenced gunshot]
- [grunts]
[body thuds]
- [glass breaking]
- [alarm wailing]
[horn honking]
[alarm and honking continue]
[silenced gunshot]
[body thuds]
[silenced gunshots]
[alarm and honking continue]
[alarm, honking stop]
- [gunshots]
- [grunting]
[silenced gunshot]
[glass pings]
Oh, shit.
- [gunshots]
- [guards grunting]
[grunts]
No.
[bullet whizzing]
Dummy.
[music slows, stops]
[Craig over radio] Post one, acknowledge.
Post one?
Post two, acknowledge.
Post five, come in.
What's going on?
[Craig] Guys, what the hell
is happening out there?
- [power winding down]
- [lights clicking on]
[light bulbs pinging]
Oh, they're playing with the lights now.
- Craig.
- Sir.
[door opens]
[crickets chirping]
[exhales]
- [static crackles]
- Home base, come in.
[Robichaux] Home base.
The wires have been cut.
[radio beeps]
Can you restore the power?
Negative. Like I said, they cut the wires.
Generator's offline
so I'm gonna go see if I can...
[water sloshing gently]
- Craig.
- Oh, fuck.
You're cutting off, darling.
- We're under attack.
- What?
We're under attack.
I repeat: we are under atta--
[chocking gasps]
- [Robichaux] Craig?
- [body thuds]
Craig? Craig?
Uh, no, there's no Craig here.
Jonny.
[Jonny over radio] Robichaux.
[Robichaux laughing]
Jon, boy, what are you doing?
Nothing. I thought we were just
saying each other's names.
I'll see you in a sec.
'Kay, toodles.
[radio beeps]
[splashing]
[water burbling]
[radio static, clicks off]
Nakamura, go do your thing.
[intriguing music playing]
[speaking Japanese]
[others respond in Japanese]
[shouting in Japanese]
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
[clicks]
[clamoring]
- [♪ RZA sings "Like a Drum"]
- ♪ There's no place to run ♪
♪ when I step to you, son ♪
♪ I'm banging on your head like a drum ♪
♪ Banging on your motherfucking head
like a drum ♪
♪ Brap, you hear the cracking sound
of bones snappin' ♪
♪ pop lockin',
chessboxin' gods back in action ♪
♪ Try to add it up,
you get struck with subtraction ♪
♪ Reduce your whole fucking crew
down to a fraction ♪
♪ Breaking bodies down
to the smallest compound ♪
♪ Slam dunk your crown,
now there's no rebound ♪
♪ ... heads on the ground,
legs and meds on the ground ♪
♪ Your whole house is surrounded
like the feds on the ground ♪
♪ This is fatal, whirlwind,
human tornado ♪
♪ Chop-socky, Green Hornet and Kato ♪
♪ Hard body, big back,
impact of a shotty ♪
♪ Godbody probably do karate
at the party ♪
♪ Naughty by Nature
when I'm facing with a hottie ♪
♪ Honey, lemon chaser,
sub bourbon in my toddy ♪
♪ There's no place to run
when I step to you, son ♪
♪ Bong, I'm banging
on your head like a drum ♪
♪ Banging on your head like a drum ♪
♪ Banging on your motherfucking head
like a drum ♪
♪ Brap, banging on your head like a drum ♪
♪ Banging on your motherfucking head
like a drum ♪
♪ I'm banging on your head like a drum ♪
♪ Sledgehammer bust through your lung ♪
- ♪ Recoil from the blast of my gun ♪
- Hey!
[clicks]
♪ Me and my brother,
we stand here as one ♪
♪ Banging on your head like a drum ♪
♪ Banging on your motherfucking head
like a drum ♪
- [grunting]
- ♪ Banging on your head like a drum ♪
- Hey.
- [panting]
- [song stops]
I think he's dead.
[panting]
Don't tell Leila.
Obviously psycho runs in the family.
[quietly] Leave the hammer, okay?
Now let's go.
[muffled shouting]
Ah.
Goddamn it.
[Jonny] Oh, no.
Oh.
What took you so long?
You're bleeding. I'm so sorry.
- [Haunani] You were right.
- The kids.
Yeah, yeah, they're safe.
- They're okay?
- They're with Val.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
He went that way.
- [James] Baby. Yeah?
- Yeah.
- [James] Hey.
- [kissing]
[Haunani] Yeah, I'm-I'm okay.
[James] Jonny.
Let's go.
[Jonny] Robichaux's running, man.
Fuck.
[sighs]
- What are you doing?
- [Jonny] Hey, James?
I'm getting you out of here.
I got this. Go with Jonny...
[Jonny] I'm going after him, bro.
...and show that haole he fucked
with the wrong family.
[intriguing music playing]
You go.
[running footsteps]
[gunshots]
[grunts]
[tense, dramatic music playing]
Frogman, did you miss me?
[Nakamura] I just met your wife.
[sniffs]
She was very good.
Oh.
[clicks]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[music slows]
Are you ready?
Let's dance.
[intriguing music playing]
Robi-cocks.
A gun?
Come on.
[intense music playing]
[grunting]
[Nakamura yells]
[intriguing music playing]
[laughing]
You are a whole lot harder to kill
than your dad, I'll give you that.
I've had a long day of fucking up
all your businesses
so why don't we skip the foreplay
and just get right to the banging.
- Sure.
- Ready? Fuck.
[tense, dramatic music playing]
Ah, fuck you, Van Damme.
- [Robichaux grunts
- [Nakamura grunts]
[metallic ringing]
[grunts]
[Robichaux shouts]
[yells]
[grunts]
- [strained grunting]
- [music slows]
[tense, dramatic music playing]
- [crunching]
- [grunts]
[Robichaux grunts]
- [Nakamura grunting]
- [low, intense music playing]
[screaming]
- [grunts]
- [Nakamura groans]
[breathing heavily]
[tense, dramatic music playing]
[tense, dramatic music continues]
[screams in pain]
[cries out]
[grunts]
- [bone cracking]
- [screaming]
[screaming in pain]
[yelling]
[screaming]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[music fades]
- [pained yelling]
- [tense, dramatic music playing]
[pained yelling]
- [cracking]
- [cries out]
[music slows]
[screaming]
[laughing] Did you really think
you could stop me?
That meatheads like the two of you
can stop a man like me?
You stopped nothing, Jonny,
'cause you are nothing.
That's what you are.
All you ever did was annoy me,
like a mosquito buzzing in my ear.
[buzzing]
In a minute, you'll be dead, Jonny.
And within a year,
my casino will be built.
And there's no one on this island
to get in my way.
[laughing] So you and your brother
and your pathetic father...
...you all died for nothing, Jonny.
[gun clicks]
You tried to take something that's mine.
But nobody takes anything from me.
[panting]
Fuck.
I did take one thing from you.
Yeah, and what's that?
[tense, dramatic music playing]
[laughing]
[multiple explosions]
[explosions continue]
Jonny!
[gentle music playing]
[exhales]
[coughs]
I got you.
I got you, brother.
[exhales heavily]
[Jonny groans]
[James exhales heavily]
[flames crackling]
[bluesy, melancholy music playing]
[Jonny weakly] I'm gonna cry
if you're crying.
[James chuckling]
[distant sirens wailing]
[sirens approaching]
[sirens wailing]
- [tires screeching]
- [sirens stop]
[Rennert] Peter Mahoe!
You are under arrest
for conspiracy to commit murder.
- What they hell are you talking about?
- [handcuffs rattling]
[Rennert] Yeah, we also got you for
bribery, but, uh, we can get into all that
- back at the station, yeah?
- [handcuffs clicking]
- This is ridiculous.
- Let's go.
- The audacity of it all.
- Uh-huh. Mm-hmm.
- All of this mess, it's all Robichaux.
- Mm-hmm.
- I was set up.
- [quiet, tense music playing]
Nani. James.
Jonny.
You've known me all your lives.
I was trying to protect you.
I've given everything I have for you!
I was more of a father to the two of you
than Walter ever was!
So don't stand there and judge me!
Nani.
Please, Nani.
Don't turn your back on me now.
Nani.
I will clear all this mess up!
Nani! We're family!
All right, that's enough.
Get him in there.
[low chatter]
[♪ HAPA sings "Ka Uluwehi O Ke Kai"]
[song continues with singing in Hawaiian]
♪ ♪
[music fades to background]
Hey, Mom.
I'm sorry it took me so long to come home.
I'm sorry about a lot of things.
I think...
I think maybe staying angry
this whole time was my way of just, um...
holding on to you.
But I know that's not what
you would've wanted for me.
[sighs]
- [James] Who's hungry?
- [Valentina] Yes!
[Jonny] She's a great woman.
You would've liked her a lot.
I don't know if I'll get
another chance with her...
because she's stubborn, like you.
But if I do...
...I'm gonna try
to get it right this time.
[Mr. K] Hey, Jonny boy.
I see you still on my island, brah.
Yeah, well, it turns out
it's my island, too.
Everything's cool, Jonny.
Much aloha.
Mm.
[Mr. K chuckling]
Oh, that healed up really good, brah.
- Do you like it?
- I like it.
Yeah, that's cool.
[feigns laughing]
You know, brah, all the illegal gambling
here in Hawaii nei
goes through the Syndicate.
But then there's the yakuza, brah,
who make a deal with Robichaux's team.
So what am I to do, brah?
Well, I could pick a fight
with the yakuza, a war,
and plenty of my people die, they make.
So you let us do it for you.
Right.
You could've helped.
Yeah. I let you live.
[paper rustling]
What's this?
A little token of my aloha, brah.
It's the name of the man
who killed your mother.
And it wasn't one of mine.
This does not make us friends.
I think it does.
Fuck you, fat shit.
Sorry, Mama.
[♪ Phil Collins sings "Take Me Home"]
What was that about?
- He's just flexing.
- Hmm.
Nah, but he gave me this.
♪ I'm an ordinary man...
It's the man that killed my mom.
♪ So I find out all I can...
Not gonna try and stop me?
The way I see it...
...there was a time I should've been there
for you and I wasn't.
I'm here for you now.
Whatever you decide, I got your back.
♪ And it helps to keep me warm...
[sighs]
♪ So I, I don't mind...
I just always thought there'd be a time
where me and Walter could get it together
and sit down and have a few beers.
I'd figure out a way how to forgive him.
You, uh, you ever wonder
why Walter sent that flash drive to you?
It was the last thing he did.
♪ No, I....
I think maybe he was calling you home.
♪ I don't mind ♪
♪ So take...
Twelve million.
♪ Take me home...
A lot of money. [laughs]
[laughs] A lot of money in a little penis.
It's a lot of money for a little penis.
[laughs]
Twelve million to buy back our childhood.
♪ 'Cause I don't remember ♪
♪ Take, take me home ♪
♪ Oh, Lord ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been a prisoner
all my life ♪
♪ And I can say to you ♪
♪ So take ♪
♪ take me home ♪
♪ 'cause I don't remember ♪
♪ Take, take me home ♪
♪ Oh, Lord ♪
♪ Well, I've been a prisoner all my life ♪
♪ And I can say to you ♪
♪ But I don't remember ♪
♪ Take, take me home ♪
♪ 'cause I don't remember ♪
[music fading] ♪ Take, take me home ♪
[upbeat rock music playing]
♪ ♪
[drum driven beat playing]
[tempo winding down]
[song ends with a flourish]
[electric guitar playing mellow melody]
[music ends]