Please pay close attention
to this important announcement.
Millions of people
have been affected by crime.
Civil unrest
was at an all-time high,
and mass unemployment
and homelessness
drove Los Angeles
into a crime epidemic.
Prisons were overcrowded
citywide Red Zones
were established
to restrict individuals
implicated
in violent activities,
and still, hundreds
of our heroes in blue
were killed in the line of duty.
Now, extreme circumstances
call for extreme measures.
We need the Mercy Court,
and I will be encouraging
my colleagues
on both sides of the aisle
to support it.
After two years in operation
this program is the reason
you can sleep
peacefully at night.
Violent capital offenders
are now judged
by artificial intelligence
which reduces
the need for lengthy trials
by acting as judge
jury,
and executioner.
In this fully
autonomous courtroom
suspects are presumed guilty
unless proven innocent.
Mercy analyzes it all
with pinpoint precision
drawing on an immense
range of data
including evidence
provided by the LAPD,
and its quadcopter team.
Since launching this program...
Mercy has already
impartially judged
sentenced and executed
18 individuals
cutting crime in the city by 68%
saving billions of tax dollars
due to the accuracy
and efficiency
of the program.
Mercy uses hard facts
and a wealth of evidence
to ensure justice is served
within hours of a murder
being committed.
It's the ultimate
crime deterrent.
The freedoms that
all Americans cherish
are now protected by a system
designed to eliminate threats
quickly and efficiently.
The future of law enforcement
is Mercy,
and you are its next case.
To ensure a fair trial
you, the accused,
will have access
to crime scene evidence,
and your complete
digital footprint.
Holy shit.
- Hey. Hey.
- You will have a chance
to defend yourself...
- How the hell did I get here?
- but understand...
Mercy does not make mistakes.
Your city thanks you
for participating
in the Mercy program.
Your contribution will restore
peace and stability
to our communities.
Mercy is justice
- for a better future.
- Get me out of this chair.
You have been assigned
- case number 19.
- Hello?
Hello!
This is the Mercy Capital Court.
I'm Judge Maddox.
I will preside
over your trial today.
Wait. No, no, no.
What are you talking about?
There is no trial.
I'm Detective Raven.
Please exhale a deep breath.
Hold on. Just wait a...
Wait a second.
- Identity is confirmed.
- Okay...
Please exhale a deep breath.
I put eight people
in this chair.
I'm Chris Raven
from robbery-homicide.
I don't belong here.
Please exhale, Mr. Raven.
Thank you.
Your blood alcohol level
has now reduced
sufficiently for trial.
Wait. How long was I out?
- 5 hours, 26 minutes.
- Man.
Before we proceed,
you must swear
that all testimony
you give this court
will be honest and truthful.
Wait.
Hold on. Just hold on.
Wait a second.
This can't be real.
I assure you, this is very real.
You must swear an oath.
Look, if you think
that this is real
you are making
a very big mistake.
And if there is a mistake,
I will uncover it,
but you must comply
with the rules before I can.
Okay, fine. Fine. I swear.
What do you swear?
Well, to tell
the damn truth, okay?
And maybe you can tell me
what I'm supposed
to be telling the truth about
- because whatever it is...
- Christopher Raven,
you're before this court today
charged with the murder
of your wife.
Nicole Raven.
- Where's the vic?
- In the kitchen.
Over here!
- We need a medic!
- What?
Is anyone else in here?
No. There's no one
else here. It's just me.
Yeah, we're comin' in hot.
There's no one here.
It's just my mom!
- Yeah, are you all right?
- Yeah...
Paramedics on scene.
I don't know
what happened to her!
Female,
stab victim, suspect unknown.
Ma'am, you're gonna be okay.
Try to stay as still
as possible. Okay?
Yeah, I'm trying.
Please help her!
Who did this to you?
Please help my mom.
Who?
Chris.
That's impossible.
Oh, my God.
This court will now present
an opening statement
evidencing your extensive ties
to the victim.
- Oh, my God! Oh, Jesus Christ!
- Culminating today
when you and you alone were
in the house with Nicole
at the time that
she was stabbed to death.
You're lying to me.
I urge you
to check for yourself.
Voice commands
and touch-sensitive controls
are available to you.
Okay.
Mr. Raven
voice commands
and touch-sensitive controls
- are available to you.
- Just search...
Can you search Nicole Raven?
LAPD Officer Chris Raven
has been arrested today
for the murder of his wife.
Raven and his partner,
Jaq Diallo
were early supporters
of the Mercy program,
and were responsible
for arresting David Webb,
and bringing
the murderer to trial
as the first participant
in the Mercy Court
just two years ago.
I'm proud to have sent
the first suspect
for trial here,
and I will continue to send more
until the message
- is received.
- This is really incredible.
One day he's sending people
to the Mercy Court
the next day, he's there.
Mr. Raven, how do you plead?
Not guilty.
I'm not guilty.
I can't be.
I wouldn't hurt her.
Based on available evidence...
I have already judged your
probability of guilt to be
97.5%.
This is 17.5% above
the 80% threshold
to trigger a Mercy trial.
This is the Los Angeles
Municipal Cloud.
Every private citizen
and organization
is mandated by law
to connect their devices to it.
I have full access
to the servers during trials.
It is the foundation
of my ability
to reach verdicts.
You may use
any and all resources
available to this court
to provide me with evidence
of your innocence.
Should you be found guilty
you will be executed
in precisely
- 90 minutes.
- No.
- Your trial will now commence.
- No, no, no.
This is wrong.
Everything is wrong!
You gotta shut this thing off!
You know I cannot do that.
AI Systems are prohibited by law
from any direct involvement
in taking of a human life.
The chair's on a closed system
and I have no control over it,
but it will not deliver
the fatal sonic pulse
if I end the trial before
the time limit is reached.
For that to happen,
your probability of guilt
must fall below
the 92% threshold
of reasonable doubt.
I'm not a murderer,
I'm on your side.
I'm on your side!
Do you remember David Webb?
Who started this?
I started this!
I know precisely who you are.
I know everything
that you have done
to serve this court,
and I thank you.
- Okay. What?
- But what you have done
in the past...
is no longer significant.
Here, the facts alone
will hold you to account,
or, perhaps, save you.
You arrived at work
at 8:51 this morning,
but you never
got out of your vehicle.
Instead, you returned
to your home.
You need to walk away
from the house.
I'm done.
Open the door.
I'm not opening the door.
You can talk to me
through a lawyer.
I have keys in the truck.
I'm gonna go get my keys
and unlock the door.
Why don't you just
- be a grown-up?
- Chris, do not do that.
Do not come in here!
Get out of my house!
You spent 26 minutes
inside the house with Nicole.
Your daughter returned
from a sleepover.
Mom?
Crime scene data confirms
that around this same time...
Nicole was stabbed
by a right-handed man,
and the single stab wound
was so aggressive
that it chipped
a vertebra in her spine
in addition
to piercing her liver...
No, no, no.
And severing
her mesenteric artery.
- That's not me.
- You are right-handed.
Traces of your wife's blood
were found on the clothes
you wore today,
and the traces are fresh.
After leaving the house,
you drove
to the Harbor Master Bar,
and began drinking heavily.
No. No!
Are you thirsty?
Yes.
- Do you have a headache?
- Yes.
Well, your dehydration
and headache
are the result
of your blood alcohol level
being 0.16 at the time
of your arrest.
No, no way. No.
No, I don't go to bars!
I don't go to bars!
- That's not possible!
- You were arrested
at the Harbor Master Bar at...
You're lying. You're lying.
I do not lie,
nor do the facts.
Yeah, Officer.
That's the guy.
Hey, Chris.
Everything okay here?
Detective, we need to go.
Nah. I think I'll stay here
and have another drink.
- You've had enough.
- Let's go!
Get off me!
Hey, just what...
Back the fuck up!
Chris, stop.
Don't do this.
Okay. Okay.
Shit!
Hey, you! No! Stop!
Come on, Chris.
That's enough.
Hey, get him. Get him!
- You, stop!
- Hey, hey!
- Get out.
- What are you...
Get off! Let him go.
My God! Leave me alone!
Stop this, Chris!
Stop running!
If you don't get outta the...
Turn him over.
Well, it is possible that
the excessive alcohol
that you consumed,
and the blow to your head,
may have impaired your recall.
I don't remember the...
I don't remember the bar.
I don't remember.
I mean to say that
you may simply not remember
killing your wife.
Pick him up, guys.
On his back.
Calling it in.
Or you could be the one
who is lying.
I have learned one constant
in this court and that is that
everyone lies.
Why did you return home?
I didn't. I don't...
I don't remember anything!
Why don't...
I gotta get outta here.
And there's only one way
to do that,
- so please focus.
- Get me outta here!
Did you argue?
About your drinking
or about your daughter?
Oh, God. Britt.
Let me talk to her.
I need to talk to her.
Unless they are a witness
to the act
of a crime being committed
juveniles are excluded
- from the Mercy trials.
- Okay, she's my little girl.
- My...
- You are, however,
free to review your daughter's
statement... if you wish.
Her mom is dead
and she needs me.
She is with
your late wife's parents.
I want... to talk
to my daughter!
I want my personal call.
Now. Right now.
You may send
a request for a call.
The rules
of this court stipulate
that if the deceased
was known to a person
there must be a written request
to contact them
in time of grieving.
So, you may dictate one.
Okay. Okay.
You may dictate one now,
Mr. Raven.
I heard you... the first time.
Hey, Britt,
I need to talk to you.
Uh...
I know you'll be hearing
bad things about me,
but they're not true.
Just... uh...
Just strictly...
Delete, delete, delete.
Start over.
Hey, kiddo.
I did not hurt your mom.
I would never...
Delete it. Delete it.
Shit.
Perhaps I should
send an automated request
without a personal message.
Yeah. Yeah, do that.
Generic request has been sent.
Despite the severity
of your alleged crime
this court mandates that you
must have an opportunity
to speak with your sponsor,
and you will do so
before we proceed any further.
Oh yeah.
- Rob.
- Chris, hey.
Rob, I don't remember.
- I don't remember anything.
- Chris, stop, stop, stop.
I don't remember what happened.
Look
they want me to stick
to the AA stuff, so...
You just...
You're supposed to call me, man.
If you're thinking about...
If you're even
thinking about drinking.
- Okay, it doesn't matter, Rob.
- You're supposed to call me.
It doesn't.
- It doesn't matter.
- So, what...
- Brother, Nic...
- Chris.
When she didn't show up
for her shift this morning...
I just...
I called the depot
as soon as I heard.
Everybody here is
real messed up about this, man.
I could not have hurt her, dude.
I swear to God.
You know, Chris,
I believe in karma. So
no matter what
you have,
or haven't done
she's either gonna be
your best friend today,
or the worst bitch you ever met.
Thank you, Mr. Nelson,
that's all the court
- requires from you.
- Wait. Hold up.
- Wait, wait, wait, I...
- Hey, can you hear me?
Wait...
Where did he go?
Mr. Nelson
was only made available
to address your relapse.
You chose not to avail
of his support.
He knows me, he knows Nic, okay?
Get him back on.
Get him back on, please.
He'll... I mean, he'll tell
you that Nic and I were happy.
I'm already acquainted
with the state of your marriage.
What's that supposed to mean?
You began dating Nicole Martin
20 years ago.
After three years,
you were married
in a ceremony on Redondo Beach.
You know, Chris has always
been the best man that I know.
And then Nicole came along,
and somehow she made
Chris even better.
To Chris and Nicole!
Ready or not
it's gonna be a boy.
I gotta say, guys,
I know she's a girl,
but Ray is a strong name.
Nah.
Your daughter, Britt Raven,
was born one year later.
And here we have the new
beautiful family Raven.
I'm your Uncle Ray.
That's Uncle Jimmy.
Your home life was stable
until you endured
a traumatic incident
in the line of duty.
What happened?
What happened, baby?
- Ray's dead.
- What? Baby, I'm so...
And your partner's death
would upend everything,
- for you and for your family.
- I just need you to say
where you are.
I've been worried about you,
and now I'm worried...
What's so important
you had to call me then?
That this shows
you're clearly drunk.
I mean, you know I was banking
on the lieutenant's spot
- to pay for it.
- Britt needs her own space.
You've been promising it
for months.
It's a basement.
All it needs is drywall.
I just didn't think
I'd be a divorced mommy.
All right.
That's enough. Stop!
- Stop it!
- It's very hard.
That's her personal shit.
Nicole detailed
you losing your temper
57 separate times
in messages and calls
with her family and friends
over the past six months alone.
Nonetheless,
the words of your family
indicate that your marriage
was straining from
your outbursts of anger,
and Nicole
was considering divorce.
I loved my wife.
Well, what human beings
experience as love
is merely a neurobiological
phenomenon
characterized by the release of
dopamine, oxytocin,
and serotonin.
Anger is also
a neurobiological phenomenon,
and it can readily
overwhelm affection.
- Sorry. Do you have a point?
- Well, the fact that
you may have loved Nicole...
does not prohibit
- the possibility...
- There you go!
That you lost your temper...
Just let me do it
how I wanna do it.
No, because you're screwing
it up like you always do.
- Jesus damn Christ! Chris.
- and murdered her.
Whether you remember
doing so or not.
Nic, get back here.
Come on, sweetheart. Let's go.
Sorry, Mom.
Are you all right?
- Nic!
- Jesus Christ.
I can be a little fiery.
That's a family trait. Okay?
It doesn't mean that I killed...
Mom's in her bed crying.
Dad legit scared the shit
out of us yesterday.
Telling you, dude's dangerous.
I can come get you
outta there if you want.
You know,
I can make that happen.
Who the hell is this guy?
I mean, it's not like
your mom could stop me.
Yeah, maybe.
I heard my mom
talk to her friend
about getting a divorce.
Really hope she meant that shit.
Shit, you hear that?
I think my dad's home.
I'm out.
Hey, wait.
What the hell was that?
We follow Britt's socials, okay?
She didn't post
any of this stuff.
Your daughter has
two active Instagram accounts.
It appears that she kept
this one from you
along with several
other online profiles,
but they're all linked
to her cell phone
on the municipal cloud.
Jesus.
For crying out loud,
she's 16 years old.
This isn't Britt.
This shit is haunted.
I mean,
it's a freaking ghost haunt,
or I'm ripped off my tits.
Call Zak Bagans, guys.
Your daughter has accepted
a request to speak.
Hey. Hey, kiddo.
Mom's dead.
I know.
God, there was so much
blood and...
I mean, I tried to stop it.
I knew not to take the knife out
because you always
told me that...
- Hey, hey...
- but it didn't work
- and she died, Dad.
- You did everything right.
- She just died.
- Listen, I... You did...
You did everything right, okay?
And she knows it.
- Your mother knows it.
- But it didn't work!
Why are you there?
I mean, why do they think
you killed her?
You were at work, right?
Why would they think you did it?
They made a mistake.
Okay? That's all.
That's all this is.
It's a big misunderstanding.
Grandpa says
you don't get the Mercy trial
unless you're guilty.
Don't... listen
to your grandfather, okay?
I know how this works,
and mistakes do happen.
And that's all this is, okay?
- Then come home.
- It's a mistake.
Okay. Please just come home.
I will as soon
as I clear this up.
Britt, you sure
you wanna talk to him?
Your father is there
for a reason.
Please come back.
- Leave her be, Chris.
- I will, Britt.
Okay, Jeff,
can you back off for a moment?
Britt, listen to me, okay?
Listen to me.
Britt, give me the phone.
Whatever happens today,
I need you to know
that I did not
hurt your mom, okay?
- I couldn't.
- Britt, listen to me.
So, you gotta promise me
you're always
gonna remember that,
and promise me
- no matter what happens...
- That's enough.
Jeff, Jeff.
Britt. Hey, Britt!
God!
Oh, he's such an asshole.
And that will count
as your call.
Why did she have
to be with them?
Pending the outcome of the trial
your late wife's parents
are now her closest
living relatives.
Did you hear
what he was saying to her?
He's trying to turn her
against me.
I was never good enough for Nic.
Mr. Raven, this is not
progressing your case.
I must remind you
that the clock is ticking.
'Cause they'd only approve Mercy
if it looked like people
had an opportunity
to defend themselves!
You and I both know
that this clock
is bullshit.
You make your decisions
about the people
in this courtroom
before they're even
in this chair.
I'm fucked.
Anger is not helpful to you.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, my wife is dead,
and my daughter's been told
that I killed her, okay?
So, yeah, maybe I need
a minute. All right?
Do you understand that?
Do you?
I was not designed to feel.
My job is to assess the facts.
So, no, I do not understand,
- but I comprehend.
- Oh...
You comprehend. That's...
Well, that's great.
Okay. You comprehend.
Hell of a bedside manner
you have there.
I also comprehend that
you're being distracted
by emotions,
and you have
one hour and eight minutes
to reduce
your guilt probability by
5.5%.
If you are innocent,
prove it to me.
Otherwise, Britt will lose
both of her parents today.
Okay.
Mr. Raven.
I need my partner.
Give me Jaq.
You may contact whoever you wish
at any point during your trial
providing your purpose
is to gather evidence,
or ask that they provide
character testimony.
- Which one is it?
- Okay.
I wanna to talk to my partner.
- Which one is it?
- The second one,
character stuff.
Jaq knows me and Nic.
- Yeah, hello.
- Detective Diallo
you're speaking
to the Mercy Court chamber
where Christopher Raven
is standing trial
for his wife's murder.
I know, I know. They told me.
Chris, you're in
a hell of a mess, man.
Jaq, I couldn't have done this.
You gotta believe me. I...
Wait. Who was first on scene?
Uh... Air unit.
Hey, am I clear to enter?
Yeah. Go right in.
- I'm inside.
- Good, good.
I need us to walk the scene.
Jaq, come on.
Hey, listen, Chris.
- Jaq, show me what...
- Mr. Raven,
what are you doing?
You must present evidence or...
I'm looking for evidence,
and I'll present it
as soon as I find it.
I need the crime scene files.
All right, Jaq, come on,
- let's walk it.
- Hey, listen, Chris
we need to get something
really clear here first.
You know I'm down for this,
but if it ends up
looking bad for you
that's exactly how I'm gonna
say it looks, okay?
You know, we need every Mercy
trial to send a message,
and if that message today
is that cops
aren't above the law...
I won't like it,
but I'll sleep good tonight.
Nobody's more important
than that court.
- Fair enough.
- Detective Diallo,
you may proceed.
Okay, then.
Let's walk it.
Can I see
the scene scans, please?
Your Honor.
There you go.
Now rendering
immersive reconstruction
based on available footage.
Can you zoom in on that?
Give me full resolution.
Broken vase.
I mean, defensive, maybe.
Think Nicole
took a swing at them?
We got it right here.
I'm gonna...
rotate it right now.
Make sure you double check that
against the dispatch logs.
Chris? You think
Nicole took a swing at them?
Yeah. Yeah, maybe.
Hey, can you
clear this out, please?
You got it, Detective.
Jaq, get in the kitchen.
I don't think
you wanna see this, Chris.
Jaq, show me what we got there.
You may enter
the kitchen, Detective Diallo.
Whose footprints are those?
They belong to your daughter.
Jesus.
We got a struggle here.
What's that?
Up by the countertop?
Right there.
Far corner. Get close.
Generating scene reconstruction
from trajectory data.
See that?
I bet Nic threw that plate.
Puts the suspect in the kitchen.
I mean, Nic's backing up.
Maybe throwing plates
as she goes.
He lunges. So,
he's already got the knife.
The knife was an easy grab.
All right,
let me see the prints.
Nic was kinda scared
of that knife.
I always did the prep.
What about fibers?
Fibers all match stuff
in the closet, Jaq.
My hair, my skin,
my DNA's all over the place.
You're thinking it. Spill it.
It's a classic crime
of passion, Chris. I mean
the explosion of violence
grabbing the nearest weapon
the blood.
And it all points right at you.
- Mr. Raven?
- No, she's right.
It's a textbook
crime of passion.
If that's what it is,
we need to work it like one.
Can I see Nic's phone records?
This is an interactive
virtual copy
of Nicole's cell phone.
The password has been bypassed.
All right, I need to see...
Can I see the call history?
Yeah... any number
she hasn't saved.
33% of calls and messages
were to and from
your cell phone...
26% were Britt's...
10 to her parents...
the remainder are
to friends and colleagues...
- at Viking Shipping.
- Wait.
That night we fought,
she was texting someone.
Can I see Britt's videos again?
I mean, you know I was banking
on the lieutenant's spot
- to pay for it.
- Britt needs her own space.
You've been promising it
for months.
It's a basement.
All it needs is drywall.
You need to back off of me!
Back off?
Write a damn blog about it.
- Who are you talking to?
- See, right there?
- Nobody.
- I knew she was.
It's work.
Find out who
she was texting. Right there.
I have scanned her phone.
There is no record of her
texting anyone at that time.
What about her work phone?
I have no record
of a second phone.
Hey, you find
another cell in here?
Nope.
No other phone.
Of course they didn't.
They weren't looking for one.
I mean, can you call it?
- I don't know the number.
- Have you ever called it?
What? You're in my phone?
It's registered
to the municipal cloud
and available
to the court so, yes.
Well, Viking gave it to her...
I think six months ago,
I might have called it then.
Yeah, that's it.
I was held up in juvie court.
She wanted me to come home,
and look at furniture
for the basement.
I mean, maybe it's on silent.
Detective,
we got a phone out here.
Detective Diallo,
could you please ensure
the Bluetooth on your phone
is switched on?
Hold the two handsets together.
This is not a work phone.
This is a black market SIM unit.
You would call it a burner.
It's not registered
to the municipal cloud,
and could not have been provided
by your wife's company.
There is only one number
in the call history.
The other number
called from this handset
is also a black market SIM
not registered to the cloud.
Two burners.
Chris, I mean...
- Yeah, it's all right.
- I mean,
if it was a guy
she was calling...
Yeah, I know.
Any suspect's
a good one right now.
Can you locate the other phone?
It's not active on any relay.
Well, can you wake it up?
You're speaking
with the Mercy Capital Court.
Please state your...
The phone is somewhere
in the vicinity
of the Hollywood Red Zone.
Shit. With traffic
that'll take me 30 minutes.
Okay, Jaq, you won't make it
through traffic in time.
You need to get in the air
for me, fast.
Detective Diallo,
please proceed.
Okay.
Hey, get my vest out of my unit.
You already suspected your wife
may have been
keeping things from you?
Yeah, maybe.
So, what, right?
Come on, everybody lies.
Apart from you.
This is Detective Diallo, RHD...
I'm entering your airspace
over the Hollywood Red Zone
tracking the suspect.
All units, be on standby
to give me backup
if I call for it.
I should inform you now
that your probability of guilt
has reduced to 96.7%.
Wow, that's peachy.
Control to air four,
we have tally on Red Zone LZ.
That zone is hot and active.
Multiple 415s.
Detective Diallo,
be advised you're entering
a Red Zone.
Maintain altitude.
Hostiles may try
to hijack the copter.
I'm a minute out.
You're putting me right
on the edge of a Red Zone.
- Get up.
- Shit.
It's gonna be impossible
to find him through that mess.
Reed, where are you?
We're almost caught up to you.
Chris, you gotta give me
an exact location.
Come on. Where is he, Maddox?
I'm gonna attempt
to reset the tracker.
Cell phone signal lock acquired.
Phone is inside
the Hudson Hotel.
It appears he's attempting
to exit the building
via the rear service doors.
Detective Diallo, do you copy?
Got it.
Stop, LAPD.
Stay where you are!
We got him, Jaq.
Stop right there!
Patrick Burke, 36.
Sous-chef at the Hudson Hotel.
He's late on his rent
and has been investigated twice,
for Social Security fraud.
How's my guilt looking now?
Holding at 96.7%.
Are you kidding me?
Come on, guilty people run.
As do frightened people.
I'm guessing this asshole's
a little bit of both.
Hey! Hey!
Where'd he go?
Well, where was he?
Yo, what's going on, everybody?
You're in the kitchen
with Chef Burke.
Looks like
he's comfortable with a knife.
Jaq, that's him!
Chef, Chef, I need you guys
to cover for me, okay?
They're chasing me.
I don't know why.
- Move, now!
- Where's that door go?
- Where'd he go?
- Undetermined.
There are no cameras coverage
in that area.
Damn it!
Hell, Detective Diallo,
I'm really sorry
- we lost him.
- Shit!
Releasing the tracking drone.
Wait, are you still
tracking his cell?
Signal is intermittent,
but appears
to be moving upwards.
Detective Diallo, do you copy?
Copy.
Jaq, we're headin' your way now.
I don't see him.
Chris, you guys see him?
Jaq, he's at your 6 o'clock.
LAPD. Stop! Stop!
- Go to the other side!
- Go.
- Go around, go around.
- No, no, no.
- Go, go, go.
- Hey!
- Hey, stop!
- Burke!
- Hey!
- He's slowin' down!
Jaq!
Come on, Jaq.
Jaq, Jaq,
I don't have time for this.
I need to talk to him right now.
Stay right there!
Don't move!
- Don't move!
- Mr. Burke,
you're speaking with...
the Mercy Court chamber.
You must be truthful
at all times.
Listen, I didn't
do anything, all right?
You have to believe me.
I didn't do anything.
If you didn't do anything,
why the hell are you running?
What do you mean,
"why the hell"?
Listen to me...
I got a call from some lady
talking about Mercy.
So yeah, I freak out, all right?
Then I check my news feed,
and I see that Nicole's dead?
I'm not sticking around
for that shit to land.
That's why I ran.
- All right, relax.
- What a deadbeat.
- What?
- I said,
"What the hell is Nic doing"
"with a deadbeat like you?"
Mr. Raven.
- What was she doing with me?
- You need to relax.
What was she doing with me?
She was getting everything
that you couldn't give her.
- That's what!
- Shut...
- All right.
- Mr. Burke, remain calm,
and I expect no further insults
directed at Mr. Burke
from you.
Why don't you just tell me
about you and Nic.
Okay.
We met at the farmers market
that she goes to and...
I don't know. She's...
She's beautiful, all right,
so you know how it is.
I hit her
with a few compliments.
Then I see her
a couple of weeks later,
and then I ask her
to meet me for coffee.
We met up just like that
a few more times
a few weeks apart
that's all.
- Why'd she have a burner?
- Listen, she said that
we had to be
able to talk privately.
Okay?
So, I told her that I knew a guy
that could get her a phone
off the grid.
None of that cloud shit.
Records show that you own
a cloud registered phone
in addition to
your black-market handset.
Yeah, I've got two phones.
So what?
Wait, what are you doing?
Accessing his cloud
registered device,
and correlating his movements
with Nicole's
based on tracking data.
Mr. Burke, could you outline
the contact with Nicole Raven,
please?
We met here once a week.
She loved it
when I cooked just for her.
Oh, hey.
I missed you.
That's enough.
I get it, I get it.
Where were you
going this morning?
I was here
running breakfast service.
All right?
And there's a whole team here
to back me up on that.
- It's not him.
- Stop moving.
You're not putting me
in that chair.
I said, I said stop moving!
Move it! Move it!
Mr. Raven,
please speak clearly.
I said, it's not him.
Yeah, that's what I've been
trying to tell you.
Thank you, Mr. Burke.
The facts do not lie
and neither have you.
This court is very satisfied
that your version of events
is accurate.
You really blew it,
you know that, right?
She just needed
somebody to talk to.
Somebody to listen to her,
- about your daughter...
- Enough, enough.
About all that crap at work.
All you had to do
was focus a little bit more
on your kid and your wife,
- but instead you killed her.
- Okay, enough, enough.
I guess she was right about your
- anger problem.
- Cuff him. Arrest him.
- Now. Arrest him.
- Arrest me for what?
- He just said I was...
- Resisting arrest.
- He just said it wasn't me.
- Pissing me off!
And making my officers
run around like assholes
chasing you around
the whole building!
Your probability of guilt
has now risen to 98%.
How'd that happen?
Instead of providing the court
with another suspect
you have provided it
with a strong motive
of why you may have
committed the crime.
Well, at least it's not 100%.
It is not statistically possible
to exceed 98% in this court.
Did you really believe that
you would find evidence
to exonerate yourself?
Or did you just simply
want to meet the man
that your wife was seeing?
You think I killed Nic
'cause I found out
she was seeing someone?
What, you think
this is all an act?
I think there's more
that you're not revealing.
You were very quick
to look for an affair.
'Cause I suspected something...
Maybe. I mean,
I didn't know for sure,
but I'm not surprised.
Not now. Just, it's...
I guess I just kept
lettin' her down.
Even today.
Today?
She found my booze stash.
I keep a... flask in my car.
I mean, flask sounds fancy.
It's an old soda bottle.
It's brown, so you can't
tell it's whiskey.
Smart, huh?
How long have you been
drinking again?
Well... about a year.
What's going on in here?
This has to stop.
Why are you filming me?
Don't come any closer.
I'm not giving you the phone.
I said...
- "Don't come any closer."
- Why were you filming me?
- I am filming you because...
I am filming you
because I need you
to watch it when you're sober.
All right?
They were all so damn proud
of me after I got sober.
Nic, Britt, Rob.
Called AA. I'm going to
my first meeting on Tuesday.
I miss you.
I miss you both.
One year.
- And one day.
- One year and one day.
I got it yesterday.
That went by fast.
You did so well.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
I don't think
I can do it four times,
so I might have to start
drinkin' again.
I couldn't shake it.
It kept getting on top of me.
Mr. Raven,
what are you talking about?
Ray.
Your former partner's death?
No.
What I should
have done about it.
Whiskey-45,
we're 11-96 on that possible
hit-and-run SUV.
California plates
three David, Henry, Ida, 832.
PCH south of Topanga.
Well, looks like
- they dumped it and booked.
- Yeah.
Vehicle confirms
- for wants and warrants.
- 10-4.
All right, let's check it.
Yeah.
Can't talk, Nic.
No, no, no.
Talk to your woman.
I got this.
Yeah, yeah. No, he's good.
No, I didn't, babe.
No. Nic, Nic, just...
Honey, you gotta dial it back.
What do you want me to do?
You want me to walk
into my chief's office
tell him my wife's
got a petition for him?
She wants us to reopen
a slam dunk investigation?
"She's got a lot of signatures."
"She'll ask really nicely?"
No, I'm not. It's just...
Baby, it makes it worse
that your dad's defending...
Gun! Gun!
- There's two of 'em!
- Ray.
- There's two. Chris! Chris!
Ray!
You sure you're good, brother?
I make one turn,
we're at UCLA ER in five.
No, it's not broke!
Stay on 'em
and get that piece of shit.
Officer Vale
has been shot. I'm gonna pit.
I need a medivac now!
Ambulance
is en route. Over.
Hey.
Hey, hold on, Ray.
Hey, stay with me, Ray.
Ray!
Ray! Ray, talk to me, Ray!
Officer down! Officer down!
This is Henry
one-three. Copy that.
Hey, get on the ground!
We got a runner.
Police! Stop!
I shoulda done it myself
on that beach.
Stop!
Get over here! Freeze!
Turn around.
Put your hands on your head.
I should have killed him.
There isn't a day that goes by
that I don't wish I had.
Verdict 4-B, we the jury
find the defendant, Alex Varga
not guilty of the murder
of Ray Vale.
I thought I was doing
the right thing.
Catch the bad guy
let the courts punish him,
but they didn't.
I guess getting a buzz on
just kinda... dulled it.
Mr. Raven,
you're losing your focus.
Could you just tell me
what you really remember?
I pulled up to work this morning
reached for the bottle.
It wasn't there.
I knew straightaway
she found it.
So, I drove home.
And you argued with her?
Of course I argued with her.
She went crazy at me
for falling off the wagon.
I went crazy right back at her
'cause she'd already thrown
my bottle in the recycling.
Do not come in here!
Get out of my house!
Don't you dare.
You locked me
out of my own house?
It is not your house!
Tell me where you put it.
Where is my flask?
So, I broke her favorite vase.
I threw it on the floor
'cause I knew how much
it meant to her.
Some of the glass shot up.
It cut her.
I tried to help, but I figured
that's how I got
her blood on me.
And why did you not
admit this earlier?
Oh, come on. Not a good look.
Everything I just told you
is only making this
worse for me.
And after that...
I truly don't remember...
anything.
I'm in the house
arguing with her.
Next thing you know...
I'm watching a frickin'
commercial for Mercy Court.
Mom?
I guess if she got mad
enough to tell me about Burke.
I'm just saying
maybe you got a point
about motive.
Mr. Raven...
If I was already angry,
maybe I grabbed the knife...
If you admit guilt
this court obligates me
to lock a verdict,
and then you will simply just
watch the clock count down.
98%. Maddox, come on.
If your memory of the events
that transpired in the house
with Nicole is truly incomplete
then an honest confession
of guilt
is beyond your capacity.
Your guilt percentage, however
remains more than high enough
to result in your execution,
but you still have
my full capabilities
at your disposal.
So, if you are to die today
do you not want to at least
attempt to uncover
the truth with certainty
before you do?
Even if the truth is dark.
Well, that's just it.
Maybe I don't wanna
know for sure.
I mean, the way
I see it right now
the only thing left
that makes me think
maybe I didn't kill Nic
is wondering
how the hell I could
commit a crime of passion
when there was no passion left.
Shit.
I... I mean, do you think
that could be it?
I do not know what "it" is.
Maddox, I'm just
thinkin' out loud.
Thinking is inherently silent
due to the brain's...
It's an expression, Your Honor.
So, I can keep going?
I can keep looking
for evidence, you're saying?
Providing you do not
inadvertently confess to murder
yes, you may use
the remaining time.
Who?
Why?
- How?
- Mr. Raven?
Still thinkin' out loud, here.
Can you show me everyone
Nic had regular contact with?
The protocols of this court
require me to point out
that embarking on a full-blown
murder investigation with just
40 minutes available to you...
- Good. Wow.
- carries with it
an extremely
low probability of success.
You know... What?
You want me to sit here,
and wait to die? You just
stopped me from confessing!
This court is simply ensuring
- that you are fully aware...
- All right, you really
- had me going there.
- of the fact that you...
I thought, for a second,
this place might not be
a kill box after all.
This is every individual
your wife
had regular contact with.
Thank you, Your Honor.
With a planned murder,
you usually know
the victim well.
We can lose Burke already.
Parents, too.
Can you split friends and work?
25 people.
Add 'em to the board.
Come on, Nic, who was it?
Well, I guess he was right.
- Who?
- Burke.
If I'd been there for her,
maybe she'd have told me
about some of the...
Somebody to listen to her,
about your daughter...
All right, enough, enough.
About all that crap at work.
All you had to do was
focus a little bit more on...
Burke! I need Burke. Now.
Mr. Burke is being
processed at... 77th Street.
Processing.
Yeah, who's
your booking officer?
- Me. Who's asking?
- Chris Raven, RHD.
You got a Patrick Burke there.
I need him.
He's getting printed.
Hold on, you say Raven?
Aren't you the guy
- who stuck...
- Yeah, yeah, that guy.
Well, I don't think
I should be puttin' him...
Officer, this is Judge Maddox
at the Mercy Court.
Please give Mr. Burke
your cellular phone.
Uh, I'll get Burke now, uh...
Thank you.
Okay. Wanna call my HMO after?
Health Maintenance
Organizations are
notorious for their red tape
and frustratingly
slow functioning.
So, you were making a joke.
Look at you, thinkin' out loud.
Hey, Burke!
- Yeah?
- You got a phone call.
Who?
- Raven?
- You talk to me,
or you talk to the judge.
You said Nic needed
someone to listen.
What was on her mind?
Any problems with friends?
Nah.
You know, it was the usual.
The one with the baby thinks
the world revolves around her.
The other one
never splits the bill fair.
What about work?
Wow.
Bro, you really dialed out,
didn't you?
All right, look, I told her
it was no big deal,
but she got
crazy stressed over it.
She didn't like the snooping.
- What are you talking about?
- She didn't tell you?
You know, the snoopin'.
Looking into her coworkers
because of that...
stuff went missing.
I can't remember what
she said it was called,
but it was some chemical
that they were shipping out.
- All they ship is chemicals!
- Yeah, I know.
I know, but I don't remember
what it was called, all right?
But I do know that her boss
he was worried that
someone was swiping the stuff.
I mean, it wasn't even much.
It was, like
what? A couple grand worth
every few months?
After that, some customer got
into it with him over it,
so that's when they asked
Nicole to check it out.
And, like I said, she wasn't
comfortable doing that.
That's all I know, all right?
Look, you wouldn't
even have to ask me if you...
Hey, Burke?
Go screw yourself.
Okay, we can lose the friends.
All right,
where are they all today?
They're all at work.
Nobody's been within a mile
of your neighborhood
since Sunday.
Yeah. We had a, we had
the barbecue. Where's Jaq?
Detective.
All right, we're gonna
come at this fresh.
Looks like
a crime of passion, right?
Textbook,
which only points at me.
But what if it wasn't?
The scene, though, Chris?
I mean, the blood.
Look, we got 37 minutes,
Jaq, just play along.
Detective Diallo,
please cooperate.
- Okay, okay.
- All right...
I'm playin' a hunch.
You need to get
to Viking Shipping Depot.
Yup.
You're playing a hunch?
What is a hunch?
Trusting my gut.
And I'm beginning to think
this court could do with
a little human intuition...
This court deals only in facts.
The facts aren't where
the investigation ends.
It's where it starts.
Facts are black and white.
The truth is always
in the gray in between.
I guess this court
overlooked that.
Or were you just
programmed wrong?
Okay. I can't even remember
who half these people are.
Did Britt film anything
at the barbecue?
- Hello.
- How are ya?
- Good.
- That'll get you likes.
- Oh, yeah. Yes.
- Huh? What do you think?
- So many likes.
- What do you think?
- It's...
- Do it this...
- Smile, Holt.
- Not right now.
Holt can't smile.
He put all his money
on the wrong horse.
Okay. Can you ID the others?
Are we missing anybody?
You can see for yourself.
Hey!
All right,
who wants some watermelon?
if one of these did it
maybe the barbecue
gave 'em a chance
to scope out the house,
find an entry point.
Nobody has been in the vicinity
of the house since then.
Nobody's cell phone has.
Doesn't mean they haven't.
The available cameras show that
46 vehicles entered
your street between
9:00 and 10:30 this morning.
None of them stopped.
How about the streets behind?
Someone could have come in
through the back, right?
I processed
all available cameras
nobody entered
your neighborhood this morning
who is not accounted for
with an alibi.
Wait. Bill Peterson.
House behind ours.
He's a bird nut. He's got
a camera out back. It's, uh...
It's online. It's...
I think
it's petersonsyard.com.
That's it. That's my fence.
I will extract the footage
from this morning
from the cloud.
Negative. William Peterson's
Internet provider
has experienced an outage.
The footage is still archiving.
This will take some time.
So, nobody's been anywhere
near my house today?
Correct. Not this morning.
- Wait. What did you say?
- Correct. Not this morning.
Okay, so who drove?
The barbecue was Sunday,
2:00 p.m.
Can you check who drove
their own vehicle there?
I can identify four vehicles
registered to employees
of Viking.
Robert Nelson's vehicle
entered your street
at 2:30 p.m.
There's what?
Three people riding with him?
Okay. I need to talk to Rob.
I'm not following.
Please, just get Rob
on the phone.
- Hello?
- Mr. Nelson,
this is Judge Maddox
- in the Mercy chamber.
- Yeah, I saw the number.
Hey, Rob.
Buddy, I'm on the clock.
Who'd you give
a ride to on Sunday?
- To the barbecue?
- Yeah.
Carla, Marie, and Leo.
Okay. Did any of them
not leave with you?
None of 'em.
You know, there wasn't
really a plan, so...
I ended up taking home
Bill and Debra.
Everybody else must
have found their own way.
Got Ubers.
Yeah. Yeah, that makes sense.
Hey, did anybody not show up
to work yesterday?
Anybody missing?
Nope. No one that I know of.
Okay. All right.
Sorry, man, I gotta go.
Okay. Let me know
if you need anything else.
All right.
This still could be it.
Please, can you
clarify your meaning?
Just give me a second, okay?
All right, can you give me
Britt's video again?
The one with the sleazebag?
Mom's in her bed crying.
Dad legit scared the shit
out of us yesterday.
Telling you, dude's dangerous.
I heard my mom
talk to her friend
about getting a divorce.
Really hope she meant that shit.
Shit, you hear that?
I think my dad's home.
I'm out.
Hey, wait. Hey...
When was this recorded?
Last night
at 9:15 p.m.
- I know how they did it.
- Mr. Raven?
Access department logs. Uh...
Check hours for yesterday.
See, look, I wasn't home.
That wasn't me.
I gotta talk to Britt again.
Unless juveniles were witness
to a crime being committed...
That's just it,
she was a witness.
Maybe not to the murder,
but she saw something, okay?
I know it.
LAPD Detective
- Chris Raven's Mercy trial...
- Hey, Britt!
- Britt, you there, kiddo?
- has now been underway
- for nearly an hour.
- Go away.
This footage of his arrest...
What's goin' on?
Did Grandpa say something?
I told you
don't listen to him, okay?
- This is all a mistake.
- You're a liar.
No, Britt, I'm not lying.
It's all over the web.
You were arrested at a bar.
Ask yourselves this,
is this how
- an innocent man would behave?
- You were drinking again.
- Britt...
- Is that why you've been
such an asshole?
This whole past year?
- Did you do it?
- No.
Do you hear me?
I didn't kill your mom.
I swear to God.
Well, everyone
on the Internet's saying
you must be guilty
if you're at Mercy.
There are polls and stuff.
I mean, everyone says
you must have done it.
They don't know
what they're talkin' about.
Britt, who are you talking to?
- I'm going. I'm going.
- Wait, Britt, Britt, Britt.
Britt, wait,
this is Judge Maddox.
We think you should be with us.
Your father is
mounting his defense, Britt.
- He requires your assistance.
- He killed my mom.
Not necessarily.
Britt, are you listening?
Please come out, right now.
We need you out here, please.
Okay, I need a minute, Grandpa.
- Okay.
- Britt, last night
you heard a noise in the house.
- How do you know that?
- You were online talking to...
- That's my private stuff!
- I know, hon.
No. Why are you
looking at my stuff?
I know, kiddo.
I shouldn't have, honey.
Okay, okay, it's not right.
I'm sorry, but
you gotta tell me,
what did you hear?
Was it your mom? Did she come
downstairs or something?
She was in bed, okay?
It sounded like a door closing,
- but there was nobody.
- Did you hear anything else?
Another noise after,
but I checked the house,
and it was nothing.
Then Jenna picked me up to go
stay at her place. That's it.
I need her Instagram.
Secret one.
This shit is haunted.
This has got to be a ghost.
- Oh, my God.
- Okay, this is last night.
It's so dark in here.
Britt, you recorded it, right?
You put it up on your Instagram.
You posted about
looking for a ghost?
Yeah, after I heard the noise.
I mean,
it's a freaking ghost haunt,
or I'm ripped off my tits.
- Call Zak Bagans, guys.
- Pause. Pause it.
Britt, honey, were you
in the basement last night?
No.
You sure?
And you didn't check it?
Dad, you know
I don't go down there.
We always keep that
door closed. Play it again.
I mean,
it's a freaking ghost haunt,
or I'm ripped off my tits.
- Call Zak Bagans, guys.
- Pause.
Can you clean it up?
He never left.
He came for the party.
Rideshared to get there.
Everyone thought
he got a lift home
with someone else,
but he didn't.
He hid in my basement
for two days.
Wait, there was someone
in the house?
I gotta go, kiddo.
- I love you.
- No, Dad. Who killed mom?
I don't know,
but I'm gonna find out
and I'll call you back...
I promise, and I love you.
I love you, honey.
Okay, so it looks like a man.
So, we rule out the women
and the people who drove.
They had to drive themselves
home from the barbecue.
Why hasn't my guilt dropped?
What appears to be a man
in your basement
could simply be a shadow.
Oh, for crying out loud.
- Mr. Raven...
- I'm thinking.
No, you're not.
Excuse me?
You are following your "gut",
but processing evidence
requires clear, linear thinking.
You must move from one piece
of the puzzle to the next
and you have missed a step.
Okay. Do you want
to enlighten me?
You're looking for a suspect
of Viking Shipping
because Burke told you
about Nicole's investigation
into missing chemicals.
You have not addressed
that investigation.
Shit. You're right.
Okay, we need to get into...
This is the Viking Shipping
internal computer server,
and the search function
is available to you.
Not bad.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Search Nicole Raven.
Let's start with the emails.
Open Nicole's inbox.
I'm looking for missing stock.
Wait,
what is that? "UG"?
It most likely
refers to urea granules.
Synthetic urea
appears frequently
on Viking's records.
All right, still looking.
Who's "the three of us"?
There's an email from the sixth.
UG. Holt knew.
How much was missing?
For the past six months
every delivery to Biobeauty
has had a discrepancy.
Each shipment
has had an additional
50 kilo container
of urea granules
listed on the delivery docket.
So, they're getting overcharged?
No. The physical order
is correct,
and they're being
charged appropriately.
It's only the delivery docket
that lists an additional
50 kilo container.
Someone's gaming
the stock records
to cover up the fact that
urea granules are going missing.
Six months at maybe
six missing containers,
what's that?
Three hundred kilos.
What's that worth to someone?
Synthetic urea is a component
of several
dermatological products.
It can also be used
in agricultural fertilizers,
and in the production
of methamphetamine.
Drug use is endemic
in Red Zones across the city.
There is an extremely
lucrative black market
for industrial-grade urea.
These are the people
who are committing crimes,
and we want to separate them
from the others in society.
So if someone took it
and sold it, they made bank.
Sure as hell wouldn't
want to get caught.
So maybe Holt found something,
didn't get a chance to tell Nic.
Open Holt's inbox.
Search Nicole Raven.
Okay, this was Friday,
2:30 p.m.
It's gone too far already,
we should just go to the cops.
I can make things right!
Just give me a few days.
It will not be a problem.
- Cool?
- No, it's not cool.
It's not that complicated!
It is complicated.
My job is on the line!
Holt's always
had a gambling problem.
I need Holt's financials.
Can you give me
the last six months?
Bank, credit card,
anything you can.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit, he's in big trouble.
Rob's been bailing him out?
Well, this is it.
This is it, right?
I mean, we got him.
You're not serious.
Money is a motive,
but it's only in theory.
You have no concrete evidence
as to how Holt Charles might
have committed the crime.
Let me talk to Rob.
Holy crap, Chris!
They told us you were
at that Mercy place. You okay?
This is Judge Maddox.
You're indeed speaking
to the Mercy Court
where Detective Raven
is standing trial
for his wife's murder.
Yes, ma'am.
That's what I heard.
I believe Detective Raven
wishes to speak
with Robert Nelson.
Yeah. I'll just go find him.
I was just walking by,
I saw the call
open on the computer.
I guess he left the app open.
And, Chris...
Good luck, pal.
Gimme a second.
Son of a bitch.
Hey, Fred, can you
drive me around the yard?
If he is involved, he may flee,
and time is very short.
All right.
We're gonna have
to make him talk.
Jaq's gonna have
Where is she?
Detective Diallo
is four minutes away.
Maddox, can you track
where he was this morning?
I am having trouble
verifying a clear alibi
from his whereabouts
at the time of the murder.
I'm tracking his phone in case
he does attempt to flee.
Okay, good.
Hey, do you have a status
on Peterson's bird cam footage?
I mean, if he was at the house,
the camera might've caught him.
Loading.
Almost there.
Yo, any idea where Rob's at?
I have this morning's footage
from Bill Peterson's
bird camera.
I'm afraid there's nothing.
What? Nothing?
All right, just show me.
Slower.
Slower. Slower.
Wait, what? What's this one?
The timing's right.
The camera
was motion activated at
10:08 a.m.
God damn it, is that...
That's all?
The camera was not
triggered again until
11:43 a.m.
All right, well,
he still had to get out.
Did Bill go anywhere today?
Phone tracking shows
that Bill Peterson
left his home at
11:23 this morning.
The Internet outage
in Bill Peterson's grid
affected traffic cameras
in that area, too.
We will have to wait
for them to update.
Hey, Chris, you there, man?
I said I needed Rob.
Yeah, I wasn't able to find him.
Quit stalling.
Whoa, I'm not stalling, man.
Chill.
Bullshit.
I was gonna ask...
Rob to keep you there,
but the cavalry is about to
- break your goddamn door down.
- What?
I know about
the missing chemicals.
I know about the hole
you're in with the bank.
You stole product,
and you murdered Nic
so she couldn't talk.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
I didn't hurt anyone, man.
This is nuts.
I was just trying to help him.
- I owed him one.
- Owed... who, what?
Holt, what are you
talking about?
- Holt!
- Rob, okay?
I owed Rob.
- What?
- Me and Nic found out
he was making product disappear.
And, I mean, shit, we all know
what the stuff that comes
through here is worth,
but he's been good to me, man.
To all of us.
Hell, he's your sponsor,
for Christ's sake.
Where is he?
I don't know, dude.
- I can't find him.
- Holt, where is he?
Carly said he took off
in one of the trucks, okay?
He just got back from a sick day
she figured
he wasn't feeling good,
- and he left. But...
- Wait, Rob was off yesterday?
Yeah. He didn't come in
until he was done
at the port this morning.
Last time I saw him
was at your place on Sunday,
and he said he wanted
to talk to Nic
the way he talked to me.
Let her know it was all gonna
be cool, you know?
But... wanted to do it
after everyone else left.
Even got me to drive
his car home for him,
so the folks he gave a ride to
weren't left waiting.
He stayed on,
and you drove his car?
Yeah. Like I said.
Son of a bitch.
I tried talking to him
at your place the weekend...
Viking trucks are all tracked?
Okay. Uh...
There. That one.
The one in Los Feliz.
That is Robert
Nelson's home address.
The truck is not moving.
Jaq, are you hearing me?
- I'm touching down at Viking.
- No, scratch that.
You need to get
to 698 Tracy Street.
We're going after Rob Nelson.
Your Rob?
All right, I'm on my way.
SWAT unit four,
head over to 698 Tracy Street
- stat.
- Roger that.
Local units
and the nearest patrolling
SWAT team have been alerted
I helped Rob
get a gun license last year.
He's got weapons at the house.
The footage of Bill Peterson's
car journey has buffered.
What, still?
In the absence of new,
verifiable facts
your guilt is holding
above the threshold.
Do you honestly think
that I killed Nic?
The facts are all that
I'm permitted
- to consider.
- Come on. What's your gut say?
I do not function that way.
What about
what you said to Britt?
You told her that
maybe I didn't kill Nic.
- You remember?
- No, I was merely
- acknowledging the...
- Bullshit!
I'm just asking,
what do you think?
I cannot...
I'm not...
I'm not supposed to...
This is the Mercy Capital Court.
I'm Judge Maddox,
and I'm going
to preside over your
court, I'm Judge Maddox,
and I'm going
to preside over your...
- You all right?
- I am.
I'm functioning
within normal parameters.
Thank you.
Okay.
Let's just
put a pin in that one.
This is Ten-David,
Lieutenant Vogel.
We're en route to your lead.
All right, Dan,
I'm glad it's you.
Chris, we're about a minute out.
What do you got us getting into?
I've identified a suspect
in my wife's murder.
Robert Nelson.
He owns an AR-15,
and a semi compact
nine-millimeter.
Roger that.
All right, guys,
we're en route to location.
Suspect armed with an AR-15.
Go, go, go!
Occupant of 698
this is Lieutenant Vogel
with the Los Angeles
Police Department.
Exit the residence
or we will make entry.
All right, Chris,
we're going in.
Diallo, touching down.
Never late for
the action, huh, Jaq?
LAPD!
We have a search warrant.
Open the door!
We made entry, Jaq.
Give me two in the bedroom!
Lock it down!
LAPD, we have a search warrant!
Living room, clear!
Move, move!
Give me some people
in the backyard.
- Kitchen, clear!
- Let's go!
- He's not there.
- Spread out!
And where's the damn truck?
The vehicle's GPS
is at the house.
Yeah, 'cause he took it off.
- Can you scan traffic cameras?
- I already am.
The license plates of the trucks
are not being detected
by any cameras in the city.
He probably ditched 'em.
Jaq, I need you
to put out an APB
on a Viking Shipping Truck.
- Can we track it?
- No, we gotta go old school.
All units, be on the lookout
for a Viking Shipping Truck.
Could be anywhere in the city.
Chris, there's nobody
in the house. It's empty.
Just a bunch of hoarded crap
and memory lane stuff.
Wait, wait, wait.
Bring that back.
Stop. Stop right there.
What's that picture
on the right?
Robert Nelson was
raised in a children's home.
His records were lost
in a data hack,
but this image most likely
dates from that time.
Can you pull that out?
Look at his arm.
There's someone else
in that picture with him.
Can you cross reference
and find a match?
Searching for a match.
This may take a few minutes.
Can you pull any
cameras from earlier today?
Vogel, get outside.
Check the garage.
Roger that, Chris.
Jaq, did you get that?
We're out back.
Initiate.
- Move, move, move!
- All right, move in.
- Go! Go!
- Go, go! Go!
- Corners clear.
- What we got here?
Active fire.
Ten-David, clear.
Looks like he's been planning
something for a while.
He's burned all the evidence.
He's cutting and running
with the chemicals, right?
There's gotta be a good reason.
One last payday? Selling them?
There are four known
Red Zone drug lab operations
in the city.
No, he'll never get that rig
in the Red Zone.
He'll get mobbed.
What if he cooked
the drugs already
and he's hauling
finished product?
If he has manufactured product
the estimated street value
would be in excess of
16 million dollars.
I mean, could he have?
Could he have? He made drugs?
Rob Nelson achieved
a master's degree
in electrical engineering.
There are potentially
transferable skills
from that to chemistry.
Yeah, we gotta figure he's
headin' to a supply meeting.
Take the cash, disappear.
Hey, Jaq, can you go back?
Go back.
See that? He wasn't at Viking
last time we called him.
He was already here.
What, to your house?
To the barbecue?
Hey, Lieutenant,
take a look at this.
Carla, Marie, and Leo.
Chris, we might
have something here.
Some kinda chemical in here.
Those contained urea granules.
So he was cooking product.
Holy shit.
Chris, what the hell?
See that? He took
the plates off the truck.
It was all here, hidden away.
He's completely offline,
no digital trail.
No wonder you missed it, Maddox.
Some sort of handbook.
Checking it out.
And what are we looking at?
This is a terrorist's handbook.
- What?
- Urea can be combined
with nitric acid
to produce urea nitrate
which is an extremely
high explosive.
Viking ships nitric too.
It was all there for him.
He's made a bomb.
Dan, he's got a bomb
in that truck.
We need to know
what his target is.
All right, guys.
Drop it, toss everything,
look for a target.
Shit just got real, Jaq.
Chris, I have it.
Dan, I'm going after our sub.
Roger that.
How much explosives
is he carrying?
Based on the ride height,
the load on the suspension
appears to weigh
in excess of 3,000 pounds.
All right. Where's
he going in that thing?
He's heading south
on the 101 towards Downtown.
Wait, did he just speed up?
His speed is increasing.
Sixty... 70 miles per hour.
He will reach Downtown
in three minutes.
Chris, I have a match.
Can you find out who that is?
Wait.
David Webb?
David Webb was taken
into care of child services
along with his older brother...
Robert Webb.
But they were parted
when Robert was adopted alone.
They changed Rob's name when
he was adopted by the Nelsons.
Meeting me at AA, sponsoring me
it all came after
the Webb trial.
This was never about Nic.
It was about me and you.
His target is the Mercy Court.
Jaq, his target is Mercy.
He's doin' it for revenge.
Rob is David Webb's brother.
What?
I processed Webb myself, Chris.
I'm detecting
a second heat signature
in the cabin of the truck.
Sending in a drone
for visual confirmation.
Did he just talk to someone?
If he speaks again,
I'll attempt to decipher it.
Who the hell is that?
I'm back tracing the truck's
route before we acquired it.
Wait. Can I talk
to Britt quick?
Please, Maddox.
- Hello.
- Jeff, put Britt on.
You had your chance
to talk to her, Chris.
- You'll never get another one.
- I didn't do it, Jeff.
- I'm not gonna listen to this!
- And I've got the guy who did.
Did you hear me?
I didn't do it.
- Wait, you mean...
- Now put Britt on.
Uh...
She went out front
to get some air, I guess.
I'll be back in a sec.
Maddox, pull up
Jeff's doorbell camera.
No. No way.
No, he wouldn't.
- No! What are...
- Just take...
- No.
- Grandpa!
No, no way. No.
Jaq, it's Britt.
Get in the air,
you gotta get on that truck.
Jaq, we got a timer!
Dan, get out!
Get outta there!
Avalanche!
Avalanche! Avalanche!
Get the hell outta there.
Everyone, move!
Get outta there!
Now, now, get out!
Put it out, put it out!
Jaq?
Jaq, Jaq?
Could that have been it?
Could that have been the bomb?
Maddox?
That was only a small volume
of the explosive materials
that he likely had available.
If he detonates
fatalities could number
in the thousands.
Oh, my God.
Jaq, you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm okay, Chris.
The SWAT team, Vogel...
We can't let him
- get away with this.
- I know.
He's gonna pay.
I'm sorry, but you gotta move.
Get after that truck.
We gotta stop him.
I will stop the trial
immediately... and the chair
- will release you.
- Wait. No, no.
- I have to.
- You stop the trial,
we cut off.
Right? We lose cloud access?
- Yes, correct.
- No.
No way.
We gotta stop Rob first.
- I'm staying in the chair.
- The SWAT team are all dead.
If the SWAT team are dead,
and Nic is dead,
and if Rob gets away
with whatever he's planned
then they will all have
died for nothing.
- The rules of this court...
- To hell with the rules.
- No. I cannot... No!
- Break 'em. Bend 'em!
And if you stay in that chair,
you're going to be executed.
Everything you deduced...
The facts
made it appear impossible.
Impossible.
Your...
gut instincts were
- right.
- Yeah, I was right.
What if I...
failed them?
If you failed any of them,
then I guess
we're in the same boat.
Turns out I've failed
the people I love the most.
I've been a deadbeat husband,
a lousy father...
So, it looks like we both
need to accept the fact
that we failed people.
But we've got this one chance
to make up for it.
We can make up for it
by stopping Rob
from hurting anybody else.
And we need to stop him,
the same way we found him.
Together.
Okay.
LAPD units are in position.
The stolen big rig
here now on the highway,
you can see it. Looks like...
Suspect is exiting the 101.
Jaq, we gotta
get him out of Downtown.
It's too populated.
Yeah, well, I'm all open
to ideas here, Chris.
We've got units
in place at the off-ramp
ready to intercept.
Oh, shit!
- What can I do to help?
- Can you bring up the map,
so we can track his route?
Now!
If his target is the Mercy Court
we will not have
much time to stop him
before he reaches
the Mercy building.
Okay, I need tactical.
Get Havelock on the line.
Hold back! Goddamn it!
I'm tailing him.
Backup's just arrived
on the scene.
Captain Havelock with
tactical has been notified.
We will establish
a communication line
with him shortly.
We're gonna go live to
our news chopper right now
give us some more information
and a better perspective
of this chase
that's going on through
Downtown, Los Angeles.
Police say it is very dangerous.
It is being chased
by several LAPD squad cars.
Okay, we are warning people
to not go outside,
and try and take pictures
of this chase.
Devastating situation
right now on Grand Avenue.
Chris,
you're live with Havelock.
Go ahead, Havelock.
This is Captain Havelock
with tactical.
If you push him east
on 6th Street,
I can have a blockade
set up in five.
It's far enough out of Downtown
that we could try to stop him
and retrieve the hostage.
We'll have units surrounding him
at the end of the bridge.
SWAT will come in
with a helicopter
to get your daughter out.
Chris?
Do it.
Diallo to all units,
I need you code 100
on the intersection
of South Grand and 6th Street.
Cut his options.
Force him east on 6th.
All right. We got him.
He's going for it.
Havelock, I hope you're ready
'cause we're sending him
your way.
All set here, Diallo.
As long as he stays on 6th
you'll lead him straight to us.
Roger that.
All units, keep him on 6th.
Do not let him turn off.
Prepare to initiate plan A
on my command.
Control, suspect is now heading
towards the Viaduct Bridge.
Over.
Chris,
the SWAT team is arriving.
Very dangerous situation here.
We're looking at a...
Aerial unit is in pursuit.
Havelock, are you ready?
Affirmative.
Tactical is clear
to begin rescue operations
as soon as he reaches
the viaduct.
We'll have 60 seconds
before he clears the bridge.
Okay, he's being
directed towards the bridge.
Take a look at this. Wow.
Okay, SWAT officers
are now on the scene.
They are dropping in...
Easy does it, boys.
No, Jaq.
Tell 'em they're too close!
Pull back! Pull back!
Not too close now.
Target is boxed in.
Aerial unit is touching down...
Oh, shit!
Fall back! Fall back!
Abort! Abort!
No, no, no!
All units,
this is Detective Jaq Diallo.
As ranking officer,
I'm taking over
incident command.
If he clears the bridge,
he'll turn back to Mercy.
Havelock, send in the ordnance.
Take him out.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no. What?
If he gets that bomb back
into a populated area,
he will destroy the...
Britt is in the truck,
and he's using her as a shield!
Chris, any other day
you'd make the same call.
I'm sorry.
Jaq, you gotta call
Havelock off. Jaq?
No, no, no!
Get me on with Havelock.
You have a channel to him now.
Havelock, it's Raven
he's got my daughter in there.
I'm sorry, Detective.
I have my orders.
It's the wrong move.
It's the wrong move
and you know it.
Havelock, send it now.
No, no, no!
Havelock, listen to me!
We've got the smartest judge
in the world here.
Let her make the call.
If he approaches
at sufficient speed
everyone in this building
and in the truck will be killed.
Please, Maddox. Maddox?
No.
Not Britt.
Chris, I should not
interfere with this.
Havelock, don't do it!
No!
- Shit!
- Misfire, misfire.
No detonation! No detonation!
Move out! Move out!
No detonation! Clear out!
Clear out! Get in! Get in!
Was that you?
We're all out of options.
Chris, do you hear me?
He's turning back towards Mercy.
He is three minutes away.
I'm gonna issue
an order to evacuate.
Please evacuate immediately.
All teams, move in.
- Jaq, I need you.
- For what?
We're gonna try talking to him.
Maddox, you with me?
Detective Diallo,
please put your air unit
in front of the truck.
I require the driver's face
on your camera.
Get as close as possible.
Copy.
You are now live
on the base radio channel
he was listening to before.
Rob? Rob, you hear me?
- Hey, holy shit.
- It's Chris.
You're not gonna
talk me down, Chris.
- Dad, help! Help!
- Rob
you can stop this.
You could let Britt go.
When you walked
into that AA meeting...
I knew exactly who you were.
You had been haunting
my dreams, Chris.
My brother had problems,
but I could a helped him.
I could a gotten him straight.
You started all of this, man...
If it's about me
and the judge, why did you...
I needed you in that chair.
You had to suffer in that chair,
knowing that you were innocent.
- Same way that my brother did.
- Your brother was a murderer.
- No, he wasn't!
- Don't listen to him, Dad!
If he wasn't, how do you think
that this helps him?
You're killing people
in his name.
Innocent people.
You think that's gonna
set things right?
No, no, no. I tried.
I called. I spoke to...
We can't let him
get away with this!
And she,
she told me that if I...
Shut your mouth!
Jaq! Was that...
What are you doing?
This is bullshit!
What do you think?
I had a shot, and I took it.
Britt is in the truck.
- Are you nuts?
- I said stop!
Oh, Jesus. Oh, God!
Power interrupted.
- Backup battery activated.
- Maddox!
What the hell is happening?
Systems operating
at 40% efficiency.
Get me out of here! Maddox!
- Systems operating...
- Dad!
At 40% efficiency.
- Britt.
- Efficiency.
- Maddox!
End the trial.
I have to get out there!
Move! Move!
This is the Mercy Capital Court.
I'm Judge Maddox,
and I'm going
to preside over your...
Maddox! Maddox, end the trial.
I'm programmed to remain online
until I stop
the trial recording.
And I still have
internal network access.
Christopher Raven to the lobby.
Christopher Raven, you are...
- Maddox! End the trial!
- wanted in the lobby.
Now.
Maddox!
I will assist you however I can.
Please evacuate the building.
Please evacuate immediately.
Evacuate the building quickly!
Rob Nelson,
this is the LAPD
hostage negotiating team.
Come on. Talk to me, Rob.
No need for anybody
to get hurt here.
Chris!
- You got me, Maddox?
- Yep, I have you.
We know
you have Britt Raven in there.
- Bring her on out, Rob.
- You got a visitor.
Can't do this, Rob!
About two years
I've been planning this!
Okay, wait.
Two years since you
put an innocent man
to death in that chair...
He wants to think
that his brother
was not a murderer, so
give him an opportunity
to try to prove it,
and buy me some time
to figure a way out of this.
If I commence
an official court hearing
to take his testimony
- on the record...
- Chris!
I can bypass the firewall
and restore cloud access.
All right. Do it.
Nelson, put the gun down.
Chris, get out here! Now!
- Dad!
- Okay!
- Dad! Please.
- It's okay!
It's okay! It's okay, kiddo.
I'm not gonna let anything
happen to you.
Let her go, Rob.
You can do anything
you want to me,
just... just let her go.
You said that Nic was necessary.
Britt is not. You know it.
Shut up! It ends here.
You, the judge, this place,
and everything it stands for.
- Dad, he's got a bomb.
- No, he doesn't.
That bomb was working,
he'd have blown it.
He's just an angry man
with a gun.
What makes you think
that it's not workin'?
Dead-man switch.
Did you think I was really gonna
blow this thing
before I made sure
that you were
still in the building?
So, here's my verdict.
You're guilty of executing
an innocent man.
It's over.
No, no, no!
Mr. Nelson, I'm Judge Maddox.
You claim
your brother was innocent?
Before you destroy me
and this court
I suggest that
- you put your case...
- What?
On the record.
This is a chance for you
to clear your brother's name.
If you believe you can.
Of course, I can!
That's the point.
Then I, hereby, declare this
addendum evidence hearing
in the trial of David Webb...
open.
Okay.
In that case, please. Proceed.
About two years ago,
I found him.
June 15th, Third and Hobart,
about four in the afternoon.
He was... all full of shame
high out of his mind.
I was all shook up.
I gave him some cash and then
I gave him a phone so that...
I could call him
when I came up with a plan.
Next thing I know,
you're saying
he killed this lady.
But here's the thing,
I called him
the night of the murder!
Same time you said
he was killin' that lady...
I was talking to him!
- His detonator appears to...
- Okay?
Lack any arming mechanism.
Go on back and check
my cell phone records.
I know you got 'em.
There's an 82% chance that
pulling the battery pack...
- Are you even listening?
- will render it inert
- without detonation.
- You are not listening to me!
I am listening very closely,
- Mr. Nelson.
- No.
The body of Valerie Bennett
was found in an underpass
at 6:00 a.m.
She had been stabbed to death
at approximately 10:00 p.m.
the night before.
Your brother
was found with her body
with his prints on the knife,
and he did not have a phone.
No, I just told you.
I was on the phone with him
at 10:00 p.m.
We talked for over an hour!
You do not care about the truth!
You are just a heartless
killing machine!
This place
is just a slaughterhouse!
I'm sorry,
Mr. Nelson.
Your evidence has failed
to reduce
the probability of guilt
that led to
your brother's execution.
Britt!
No!
Dad!
On your knees!
Turn around!
Chris! No. Don't.
He murdered Nic!
He's gonna pay.
Now, get up!
This doesn't fix anything.
- Shut your mouth.
- Dad, don't!
Please.
Dad!
I was on the phone with him
the whole time, Chris.
I called your precinct.
No, Jaq.
Not now! Nope!
- Let me finish this.
- No, Jaq!
Hey! Hey!
Back up. Okay.
- We're okay.
- I called the station.
I spoke to some lady,
and she told me
that she would give me
a call back as soon... God!
Maddox, verify.
It was July 15th.
- Hello?
- Hey, buddy, it's me.
It's Rob.
Do you think I can maybe crash
at your place for a while
just till I get back on my feet?
Of course.
Anything you need.
I'm always here for you.
I told a woman at the precinct
to check my call history!
Whoever booked him
knows what happened.
Wait
do you know if someone
called about an alibi?
Did you know?
I was trying to get through
to someone the whole time!
No one would listen!
You processed Webb.
Did he have a cell phone?
- Jaq?
- Stop.
- You need to hear me, Chris.
- You took him in, Jaq.
I have tracked the cell phone.
It was at the scene
when David Webb was arrested.
Then at the station.
Maddox, bypass the LAPD firewall
with my login.
Don't do this.
Check the evidence room.
And show me Jaq's bodycam.
Phone tracking records show
the phone in the evidence room
at this time.
But it wasn't processed.
Why is it missing, Jaq?
Did you drive straight home
that night, Jaq,
or should we check?
Maddox?
You buried the phone.
We needed the first trial
to be a home run.
We need Mercy, Chris.
We need these scumbags scared.
Look at what it's done for us.
You'd destroy it all
if this gets out.
We need justice, Jaq.
Not this.
Detain Detective Diallo
and Robert Nelson.
Let's go.
Let's move on out, guys.
Get up. On your feet.
- Dad.
- Britt, hey. Hey.
You're okay. You're okay.
- Hey, are you hurt?
- No.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah. I'm okay.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry I ever thought
you could hurt Mom.
I got you. I got you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Chris...
What have we done?
We just did what
we're programmed to do.
Human or AI.
We all make mistakes,
and we learn.
Yes, we do.
Maddox?