[menacing music]
- I was walking
under the overpass
as primly dressed secretaries
and weary window washers
march onwards and upwards
to start their days.
The cold winter wind
whipped in my face,
and a card caught my eye.
I flipped it over
to find joker.
Joker, joker.
- [car horn blares]
- Go, go, go, go!
- All things in life
are rarely here to stay.
The good and the bad.
So worry not, me.
I smile at the cards
I'm dealt.
Just like the snow,
it shall melt.
What are you hearing,
Indianapolis?
It is Tuesday, February 8th.
The time is 8:45
and 55 seconds.
I'm DJ Fred Temple.
And this is Deodato.
[♪ Also sprach Zarathustra
by Deodato]
[music stops]
[groan]
Fucking...
[suspenseful music]
[wind whistling]
[sinister music]
[muttering]: Ah, fucking thing.
[reception din]
Hello, sir.
Where's Barb?
Barb usually sits this desk.
Are you new?
- I am new,
thank you for asking.
I'm Doreen.
And you are?
- Um, I'm Tony. I have a meeting
with Meridian Mortgage.
- [Doreen]: Great!
- M.L. Hall.
Oh, Tony...
- Tony Kiritsis.
- Kiritsis... Kiritsis.
- Yeah.
- Kiritsis, okay.
Oh, Mr. Hall will be with you
in just a moment.
Feel free to wait
on the couches over there.
Right over there.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
Okay.
[phone rings]
[Doreen]: Uh-huh.
Uh-huh. Yeah, yeah,
he's here.
Uh-huh...
Mr. Kiritsis?
I'm so sorry.
It seems there was a bit
of a scheduling kerfuffle.
M.L.'s actually
in Florida right now.
[indistinct chatter]
Your burrito, Mr. Hall.
- Oh, oh, oh!
No, no, no, no.
I'm sorry, sir?
- Well, you should be,
because this is wrong.
[waiter]: Oh, uh, it's the same
order as yesterday, sir.
It's a grilled chicken
with rice and sautéed spinach.
- No, but this is a whole
burrito cut in half.
I always eat my burrito
cut in thirds.
And most importantly,
on Tuesdays...
Tuesday he doesn't eat meat.
- I don't eat meat.
No meat on Tuesdays.
That's right.
So while you were close...
certainly no cigar.
- What?
[Doreen]: He's in Florida.
Boy, I tell you, sure wish
I could be in Florida right now.
- It is cold out there today.
- No, no, no, no,
I have a meeting with Meridian
Mortgage, it's on the books.
- You still do. His son
Richard's on his way down now.
[Richard]: Tony!
I'm so sorry I'm late.
[Doreen]: I told him, sir,
M.L.--
- It's a last-minute work trip.
- He's, he's very sorry.
- Last-minute work trip, my ass.
He's dodging me
and the winter.
- Tony, I know that you and Dad
have had some disagreements.
You can say that again.
- But why don't we just keep it
all calm, understand, huh?
- What happened to you, Tony?
- Oh, oh.
- Oh, this thing?
- Yeah.
It's nothing.
I was pulling some stumps
on my property, and...
and the damn cable broke
and nipped my arm.
Would you believe that?
We are so sorry to hear that.
[Doreen]: So sorry.
It's awful.
Hey, uh, listen,
uh, why don't you and me
go up to my dad's office?
You know, the one you like,
with the conference table.
Does that sound
like a good idea?
Would you like that?
- M.L.'s office?
- Yeah. Let's do that.
- Alright, Dick.
You're the boss.
- You want a mint?
- No.
- [elevator dings]
- Here we go.
Sorry about that.
Just go around
to the left, Tony.
Morning.
Watch your step here, Tony.
[phone rings]
Good morning. Thank you.
How you doing?
Hey, Barb. How you doing?
You remember Tony?
- Oh, hi, Tony.
- Oh, hey, Barb.
- This is where you are.
- Yeah, moving up.
- What happened to your arm?
- Oh, no, it's nothing.
- Hey, uh, Barb, do you mind
if we use Dad's office?
We're just gonna
go through some things.
- Good to see you, Barb.
You've always been nice to me.
[Richard]: Come on in, Tony.
- Um... Hey, Dick, do you mind
if I shut the door?
- I could use the privacy.
- Oh, yeah, sure thing.
My shorts have been riding up
past East Market Street,
and I don't want anyone
catching a look.
You know, that costs extra.
[Richard chuckles politely]
Pretty little family
you got there.
So, Dick, um...
do me a favor, will you,
and, uh...
and open these plans
over there on the table.
- Sure thing, Tony.
Of course.
So I imagine you want to talk
about the land
and everything
that you and Dad
have been going through.
[Richard mumbling]
[gun hammer cocks]
Wait, hang on a second.
Now, you turn around.
[suspenseful music]
- Hey, Tony...
- This is serious, Dick.
Real serious.
[shuffling]
I'm gonna wire this here
shotgun to your neck.
- [laughs nervously]
- Hey, now, Tony.
Put it away.
Tony, you...
You don't want to do that.
This company's done me wrong.
So I'm gonna let
the world know
what you and your dad
have done to me.
Simple as that.
What do you want?
- I want you to turn around.
- I'm not gonna--
- Turn around!
- Okay. Okay.
I'm turning around.
You take your sport coat off.
Take it off
along with your necktie.
- Tony, I don't--
- Let's get comfy.
- Okay.
- Take it off.
- Goddamn sport coat off.
- Okay, okay, okay.
Now...
Oh, right, here we are.
Take it off.
There you go. Okay.
- Okay.
- Oh, right here we are.
Fucking...
Here we go.
Yeah.
Tony, what is this?
This here, Dick...
is a dead man's wire.
If you faint, stumble,
or try to run...
There it is.
This will blow your head off.
- Now listen, Tony,
no one's seen us, okay?
You've made your point.
No. I'm just getting started.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey!
- Tony, Tony, Tony,
they can't see--
They can't see us, not through
Dad's windows, okay?
Don't matter anyhow.
Pick up that phone.
Pick up.
[Fred]: That was
the Polish maestro,
Theo Marzynski.
[phone line rings]
I'm DJ Fred Temple.
WCYD.
[phone line ringing]
[operator]: 911 emergency.
[Richard groaning]
- [Richard]: Uh... uh...
- Yes?
[Richard]: Just a...
Just a moment, please.
[Tony]: H-H-Hello?
Sir, this is a real
serious thing.
I've just taken a prisoner.
This is not a crank call.
- No, no, no, sir.
What problem you got?
- G-Get me the highest-ranking
officer you got.
Ah, fucking thing.
Sit down, Dick.
You just sit down here slowly.
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
Like your life depends on it,
because it sure
as hell does, buddy.
- Uh...
Sir, what's your problem?
- I've got a shotgun wrapped
around a man's neck. Yeah.
- Let me tell you something...
- Chrissy, I got an 0-1 here.
- They have fucked me around
for four years.
[knock on door]
Hey... Oh!
Tell her to get out of here.
[Barb]: What's going on here?
[Richard]: Barb, just, just,
just give us a moment, please.
Everything's all right.
- Yeah, everything's
alright, Barb.
Thank you, Barb.
Yeah, I-I'm a little upset.
- Okay. Okay,
just take it easy.
Now, I'm not a bad fella.
I'm a mean motherfucker,
and I'm mad.
Yeah.
Now, if anybody yanks on me
or yanks on that gun...
he'll die.
You understand?
- Where are you at?
What's your name?
- Write down the full address.
The full address.
Yeah. Careful now.
- Please give me
some slack, Tony.
Careful.
[operator]: What's your name?
My name is Tony Kiritsis.
K-I-R-I-T-S-I-S.
Now let me tell you
something else.
I'm very concerned
about this man's family.
Not particularly
this man's father,
who I treated like
a goddamn father myself
on many occasions,
and he treated me
like a fucking dog.
And this guy here
did the same thing.
- Okay, we're gonna try and get
someone out there to help you.
Okay?
- Yeah, they fucked me around
for four years.
Millions of dollars involved.
Now I've got his son here.
Dick Hall.
A big shot here.
Yeah.
- Hey, baby.
- Urgh.
I thought of that.
Give it--
Give it here!
Alright, so it's
129, East Market Street.
Uh, now I'm on
the fourth floor...
in the, in the executive office.
You tell those motherfuckers
to play it cool
because this is
a real fucking McCoy.
Yeah, I signed those papers
when they cornered me.
You see, I've been trying
for four years
to get away
from these motherfuckers.
They set you up to try to take
everything that you've got.
Like the Mafia.
- Were they a loan company
or something, sir?
You're goddamn right.
Biggest devils there are.
Loan companies.
Hello?
[alarm buzzing]
[sirens]
[indistinct chatter]
[Richard breathing heavily]
- So what's your plan,
Tony, huh? What's next?
- Well, the plan was to drive
back to my place.
But the damn key broke in
the ignition walking in here.
- Would you believe that?
- Okay.
- But hey! You're parked
in the garage, right?
We'll just take your car.
- Tony, I'm parked about
two blocks over on Earl Street.
It's a long story, but it's...
It's where I get my muffin
because they carry
the sugar-frees.
- The sugar-frees?
- Yeah.
Well...
- Listen--
- It's a nice little walk.
- Tony, I don't know if we want
to make a scene like that.
The scene's already started.
[distant police sirens]
Look at this. Look at this.
[sirens wailing]
[tires screech]
[sirens chirping and blaring]
[police whistle blows]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Beautiful.
Where are your car keys?
[coughs]
Hey, I call shotgun.
[Richard]: Okay.
- Oh, hey, hey!
Hey! Hey!
You got the memo?
- I got the memo.
Take it easy.
- Move it.
[officer]: Stay calm.
- You stay calm.
- Take it easy.
Excuse us.
Squeezing through.
Oh! Whoa, whoa! Hey.
Okay... Alright.
It looks like
the party's started.
Move it.
Okay, officers.
Don't mind us.
We're just going
for a little walk.
Yeah, hands where
I can see them.
Steady. Easy now.
Easy now.
This is locked and loaded.
Easy.
That's right, officer.
Officer. Officer.
- Walk with me.
[officer]: Slow down.
- That's right.
- Tony, slow down.
- Come on, Dick.
We're moving.
Okay.
- Whoa! Whoa!
- Hey! Hey! Hands! Hands!
Hands where I can see them.
[Richard]: The garage
on Earl and Blankenship.
[Tony]: Just keep moving.
[Richard]: Tony! Tony!
[Tony]: Hey, they got
a gun on us!
[Richard]: We got to go...
We got to go that way.
- Okay?
- Alright, good call. Move.
[dispatcher]: Officers
on East Market Street...
- Nice and easy, officers.
Nice and easy, officers. Okay.
- This man is armed
and highly volatile.
Hostage is rigged to a shotgun
without a safety device.
I repeat, hostage
is rigged to a shotgun
without a safety device.
Exercise extreme caution.
Yeah, yeah, sure thing.
Yeah, we'll be right there.
Thanks.
It's finally paying
to be on this early shift
on this side of town.
Police activity
on Market Street.
- Market Street! Let's go,
let's go, let's go.
- Hey!
- Yeah?
Maybe it's a robbery.
A girl can only dream.
[laughs]
[engine starts]
Whoo! Let's go!
Okay. Okay.
[siren blurting]
Oh, God.
Sir. Sir, if I may...
- Move it, pal!
- This is not the way.
What?
Purify me with your spirit,
and I will be cleansed.
Wash me, and I will be
whiter than snow. Psalm 51.
- Why don't you
wash my ass, Father?
Nice try.
It's Tuesday, not Sunday.
Now get lost!
[Richard whimpering]
[Grable]: Jesus fucking Christ.
You sure they're saying
it's Tony Kiritsis?
- [dispatcher]: Apparently.
- Tony Kiritsis?
The Chatty Cathy
from 8th & Rail?
That's what they're saying.
- With a shotgun?
- Yes, sir.
There's no way it's Tony.
Fucking Tony fucking Kiritsis.
Holy shit.
[tires screech]
[Tony]: Hey, whoa!
[Richard panting]
Hey, hey, hey! Hands.
Hands, or this trigger
gets pulled. Stay back!
- It's all right, Tony.
It's all right. I ain't armed.
Look, I ain't packing, man.
No weapon. It's okay, Tony.
It's me, Mike Grable.
- [Tony]: Mike?
- Mike Grable.
From 8th & Rail.
The cop bar.
I'm a cop, you know?
We know each other.
- Oh, hey, Mike.
Good to see you.
I know this guy.
He's a friend of mine.
- Tony, why don't we, uh...
Why don't we go somewhere?
Listen to me, listen.
- No, you listen.
We're going to Pearl Street--
- Earl Street.
- Earl Street,
to get into this man's car
and drive back
to my apartment.
- These guys,
they're not gonna let you
get behind the wheel of a car.
- Get in the left.
Get in the left.
- Get in the left!
- I can't.
- Get in the...
I see people gathering.
- Get in the left! Wait! Wait!
- Shit. Whoa!
[tires squeal]
[indistinct police
radio chatter]
[Grable]: Come on, why don't
we just talk about it?
Come on, Tony.
You don't want to do this.
[Tony]: Hey, hey!
[Grable]: Hey, hey, hey!
- Hey! Hey!
- Holster that weapon!
Holster that weapon!
[Tony]: Put the gun down!
[Grable]: Holster it right now!
Put that gun down!
Fucking idiot!
- Back up. We're just talking.
- A fucking idiot!
[Grable]: He's an idiot,
alright? It's okay, it's okay.
He's got a gun.
[Grable]: We're just gonna talk.
[Tony]: No, Mike,
you're gonna listen!
- Get your camera rolling.
Come on.
[Tony]: He's a fucking
idiot, Mike! Put it down!
- Alright, he's an idiot.
He doesn't know better.
- We're gonna get
in this man's car,
and you're gonna let me.
Now if anyone yanks at us or...
or tries to run away,
this trigger gets pulled.
Did you get that?
You, you following, pal?
[Richard breathing heavily]
- [Grable]: Stay back. Stay back.
- Oh, shit.
[Grable]: Back up, back up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Stay back!
[Grable]: Lower your weapons!
Lower your weapons!
[car horn blares]
[officer]: Go. Move it.
Fuck Earl Street.
Hey, kid, give me
your handcuffs.
[young cop]: Wait, what?
- Give me your fucking
handcuffs.
I'm taking your car.
- You, you can't,
you can't take my car.
- I see the key in the ignition.
It's running. Don't play dumb.
Give me the fucking handcuffs.
[Richard]: Give them to him.
Okay. Okay.
- And I ain't got no bone
to pick with the police.
Some of my best friends
are police officers.
- Ain't that right, Mike?
- That's right.
- Stay back! Stay back!
- Okay.
- I'm not taking your car
for good.
I ain't no thief.
Okay.
- I'm going to the Crestwood
Apartments, okay?
Crestwood Apartments. Yeah.
Yeah, and don't you worry.
And then if you can follow me,
you follow me if you need
directions.
Get out of the way.
- Tony, no.
- I'm going first.
We can't do this, Tony.
Let me just...
[Richard]: Slow down, Tony.
Slow down.
Okay. Okay.
[tires squeal]
This is unbelievable.
[police shouting indistinctly]
This is some real shit.
[producer]: What's going on?
I'm hearing a robbery?
- Uh... Looked like a white guy
strapped a shotgun
to another white guy's head.
Jesus, a shotgun?
It's a circus.
And they just left.
What do you mean, they left?
Well, the guy with the gun
made that little blonde fella
steal a cop car just now,
and it feels like the police
are just letting it happen.
- Alright, well,
thanks for being there
on such short notice, Linda.
I'm gonna tell
the whole department,
and we'll get the A-team
on it from here, thanks.
Why don't you come on down
to the studio
and uh, we'll make sure
you get lunch.
- Well, hold on now a minute,
I, I, I heard the name
of the apartment complex
that they're going to.
I know some folks
in that building.
I could be there as soon
as they land.
What apartment complex?
I'll show you on camera, hmm?
And you'll let me report
some real news for once,
not some fuzzy feel-good
charity segment
that people will tune out,
how about that?
Linda?
Fucker.
Head south towards Seward now.
- You heard her.
Let's go, guys.
- We're gonna head north...
as soon as they clear out
towards Crestwood, not Seward.
It's a little out of the way,
but we'll cut through
the traffic.
♪ Sitting in the back seat
Of my car ♪
♪ With my arms
Around my guitar ♪
♪ And the rain falls
♪ From the roof
Of the world ♪
♪ Nothing around
♪ Just the trees
And the ground ♪
♪ There's a bird in a tree
♪ Singing a song
Just for me ♪
♪ Just for me
♪ Ah, da-da-da
♪ La-da-da
da-da-da ♪
♪ Da-da
♪ Da-da-da
♪ La-da-da
[radio crackles]
♪ Ah, da-da
da-da-da ♪♪
You listen to 105.2?
WYCD?
Duck in the Morning?
Smooth Jazz Sundays?
Fred Temple?
Do you just drive to work
in silence?
You fucking psycho!
That would
make sense for you--
Tony, I listen to 105.2, okay?
I'm just... I'm just trying
to focus on the road.
I love Fred Temple.
I like his takes, you know?
Great radio host, Tony.
- Heart and soul of Indiana--
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
[tires screech]
This guy's out of his mind.
- Tony, just give me
some slack, okay?
I'm trying to get us there
in one piece.
- Oh, the cavalry's a-comin'.
Whole city's gonna know
how big a crook your dad is.
How does that feel?
Let's go. Keep going straight.
[Richard]: I think
it's a left up here.
You said a left before.
Am I taking a left?
[Tony]: Don't think I know
where I live? Goddamnit!
- Shut your fucking mouth.
- I'm just trying--
- It's a left here,
you're right.
♪ I know I'll be down again
With my old friend ♪
♪ This friendship
Never ends ♪
♪ The blues
Is always the same ♪♪
That was some
good driving, Dick.
Some good, good driving.
Yeah. Yeah.
So what now, Tony?
[police radio chatter]
This thing have an intercom?
- I would not have
the slightest clue.
- How do you turn it on?
- I do not know, Tony.
[siren blares]
[Tony]: No.
[siren horns and wails]
[dogs barking]
- [sighs]
- Fucking shit show.
- [siren blares]
- Ah, fucking thing. This one?
- Tony, if you're looking
for the radio,
unhook the gray device
from the console
and press the red button
to speak.
[siren blares]
Thank you.
- Now, Tony, we got men
in your apartment.
A lot of worried folk
out here.
Bullshit!
If any of your men so much as
stepped foot in my apartment,
this whole place
would be up in flames.
The only smoke I smell
is the one you're trying
to blow up my ass.
I'm calling your bluff, Mike.
I rigged this sucker
for this very moment, got it?
Well, you can't blame me
for trying
to de-escalate, Tony.
- Can blame you,
and I will blame you.
Now listen.
This is...
This is what you're gonna do.
You boys are gonna let me
and Mr. Hall here
walk into my place.
Then you're gonna
get Joe Collins,
or Frank Love,
or hell, Chief Gallagher here
to talk to me.
This is above your pay grade
now, okay?
Okay, Tony.
[Richard]: Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Where are we going, Tony?
[Tony]: Right here.
Where are we going?
Holster that gun!
- Back up or I'll shoot!
- Holster that right now!
It's all right, Tony.
[Tony]: Keep your distance!
Keep your goddamn distance.
I ain't playing around.
[Grable]: It's okay, Tony.
It's all right. It's okay.
- Tell them just to stay back!
[Grable]: Get back. Get back.
[Tony]: Mike, tell them
to stay back.
Okay.
Here. In here.
In here. In here.
- Okay.
- Open the door.
Shit.
Alright, secure the perimeter
right now. Let's go.
Up here.
- Uh, there. In the glass.
In the window.
Do you see them
going up the stairs?
Yeah, got 'em!
- We are the A-team now.
Prime time.
[cameraman]: Fuck, yeah.
[chuckles]
[apartment din]
[Tony]: Okay... Yeah.
[Richard]: Okay, Tony,
- where are we going?
- Right here, right here.
Right here.
Just stay right there.
Okay.
Hey.
Yeah. Okay.
Here you go.
Here we go.
- Ladies first.
- Okay.
[Tony chuckles]
Yeah, get in there.
Get in.
Stop, stop, stop.
Come back.
Come back. Back up...
while I get this thing on.
[metal clinking]
Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
[lights buzzing]
We're home, Dick.
We're home.
Yeah.
I'm gonna set you up
over here.
- Here! Sit your f...
- Okay, Tony. Okay.
- Sit down. Hands down.
Hands down.
I don't want to see
your hands anywhere.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah. Okay.
Now sit back. Sit back.
Let this rest.
Okay, Tony.
[distant police sirens]
Now, don't you move, Dick.
I'm gonna put this...
Look at this, Dick.
Look where it goes.
On there.
This goes on here.
You see the line, right?
Now remember,
I got this, Dick.
So no funny business,
alright?
Alright.
Hands down. Hands down.
That's it. That's it.
Nice and easy.
[Tony whistles]
[grunts]
Yeah.
You ain't going nowhere.
- [office din]
- Alright.
Hey, what's up?
How you doing?
Alright.
You still owe me five dollars.
Don't look at me like that.
[punk music blaring
over headphones]
Hey.
Hey!
Oh! Hey there, Fred.
- What's up? How you doing?
- Good, good. How are you, sir?
- You know they pay us to play
the radio, not listen to it.
Um... It's just...
I told my New York friend
I'd listen to this band's demo.
Uh, it's, uh...
It's punk.
[Fred scoffs]
- Play Gil Scott-Heron
up in here sometime, alright?
Uh, yes, sir. Absolutely.
- You know who
Gil Scott-Heron is?
Yeah. Love Gil.
- Anyway, um...
any mail for me?
- Hmm?
- Mail!
Mail. Carrier pigeons,
envelopes.
- Oh! No. Uh, slow day, sir.
You know, Tuesdays.
You're high, ain't you?
- N-N-No, not at all.
It's cool.
Just not so much.
[Fred]: It is said that
before entering the sea...
[groans]
Oh!
Oh, goddamn!
That was some
good driving, Dick.
[laughs]
That was some really, really,
really good driving.
Yeah. Feels good to be home,
don't it?
[Tony sniffles]
Want something to drink?
You want some milk?
Sure thing, Tony.
You like ice in your milk?
No. No ice, Tony.
- Good, 'cause I don't remember
if I filled the tray.
This morning was a whirlwind,
let me tell you.
I did fill the tray.
[chuckles]
I like ice with my milk.
I'm weird like that.
Let's see.
[ice clinks]
You sure you don't want any ice?
No. No ice, Tony.
- It's cold anyway
from the fridge.
[Tony sighs]
Oh, yeah.
[Fred]: It is said...
- Here you go, Dick.
- ...that before entering the sea,
a river trembles with fear.
Oh, careful now.
- She has traveled from
the peaks of the mountains,
the long, winding road...
[Tony]: Yeah, that's good.
Yep. Oh, fuck.
And here you thought
I'd be a bad host, huh?
[chuckles]
Do you like this little
contraption I made?
I rehearsed this thing
for weeks and...
it worked.
It fucking worked.
[Fred]: But there is
no other way.
[jazz music]
The river cannot go back.
Nobody can go back.
To go back...
is impossible in existence.
[♪ Compared to What
by Roberta Flack playing]
I love this song.
- I've got some Roberta Flack
for you.
Coming at you now.
- [cameraman]: Great spot.
- It's a good spot here.
We are outside the residence
of Tony Kiritsis--
[cameraman]: Look, look, look.
- As you can see,
reporting live,
we're evacuating the premises.
[indistinct yelling]
This is an emergency
situation.
[Grable]: Everyone, let's go.
Let's go.
[Linda]: Coming to you first,
Channel 12 News.
[man]: Go, go, go!
[Grable]: Hey! Hey!
- You guys can't be--
- Sir, excuse me.
- No, no, no, you can't be here.
Clear the parking lot.
This place could blow
at any minute.
- Can you confirm that
authorities have confirmed
that there are explosives
on the premises?
[Grable]: Now what?
We're just taking
every precaution,
so we're evacuating the area.
You guys need to get behind
the barricade. Let's go!
- And the hostage situation?
- Ma'am, please.
Behind the barricade.
Let's go.
Hey, chief.
[Gallagher]: What's this
I'm hearing about explosives?
- I'm Linda Page,
reporting to you live
from Crestwood apartments...
- He says he's got the place
wired to blow.
Pal of yours, right?
Yeah, I know Tony.
♪ I said we're
Chicken feathers ♪
♪ All without one gut ♪
What the fuck are they doing?
[indistinct reporting on TV]
Hey, hey! Hey!
Hey! I got lines rigged
to the glass!
Any of you sharpshooters
get cocky,
we go up in flames!
Explosives.
[reporter on TV]:
...just put a shotgun
at the head of mortgage
company executive Dick Hall,
marched him from his office,
down the streets
of downtown Indianapolis,
marched him into
a stolen police car,
and drove here, drove here
to Tony Kiritsis' apartment...
[Tony]: I saw something in
that land that no one else did.
Because I'm a man
of the people.
I know the people.
[phone rings]
And I've paid my dues
slinging ice cream as a kid,
selling used cars,
trailer park maintenance.
You name it, I've done it.
- Tony, no one is saying
you haven't.
[phone ringing]
Tony, your phone.
- Fuck.
You...
you and your dad and that
godforsaken mortgage company
deterred those renters.
I know it!
[Gallagher]: Hello, Tony?
This is Chief Gallagher.
- One second, pal. You're gonna
want to listen to this.
You think you can
milk me of interest
and then just
hang me out to dry?
- Tony, Dad offered
to buy you out.
Exactly!
He knew I was onto something,
staking that land,
providing services
and groceries for those
y'all normally wouldn't take
two seconds to pay mind to!
[heavy breathing]
Power's in leasing,
not selling for a loss.
I don't need
to explain that to you.
That's power
in this world, equity.
But you couldn't let the little
guy get a win, could you?
Chief Gallagher?
- Tony, uh, can we talk
next step?
Gallagher, you listening?
I want a written agreement
from Meridian Mortgage
and the county clerk's office.
I want my debt forgiven
and financial compensation
for all the money
I would have had by now.
And I want to walk out of here
a free man.
No jail time
and no psychiatry bullshit.
And most importantly...
You getting this?
I want an apology.
I want a formal apology
from Meridian Mortgage
and this poor man's father,
you copy?
Now fuck off.
[sighs]
[heavy breathing]
These cuffs are awful tight.
- Well, I'm sorry, Richard.
I ain't got no keys.
[heavy breathing]
I'm sorry, Richard.
I-I-I really am sorry.
I'll work on getting you on
a call with your family later.
How does that sound?
Sounds good.
No, you're gonna listen!
We're gonna get
in this man's car,
and you're gonna let me.
Now if any one of us
goes running
or gets yanked away,
this trigger gets pulled.
You get that?
[reporter]: Red Cross volunteers
handed out coffee
and ham sandwiches
to media people and law
enforcement officers.
More than 50 gallons
of coffee disappeared
and 200 sandwiches...
Tony had a piece of land,
I think it's 17 acres in size,
that he wanted to develop
into a shopping center.
He claims the mortgage company
took them to other sites
rather than recommending
the site he had.
Of course, the mortgage
company was waiting
and expecting him to pay off
on the mortgage.
The squad car came here,
and I lost
what I was gonna say.
The squad car came here
to Crestwood Village
in the North...
What part of...?
[sighs]
[beep]
- I'm sorry if this
is scaring you.
Yeah, well, appreciate you
taking the call
at a moment's notice.
[Ibby laughs on phone]:
Yeah, like I'd let you go
to the answering machine.
[she laughs]
You know what I mean.
[whispering]:
Tell her how sorry I am.
Truly.
Yeah, sorry...
- Tony...
[sighs]
We are sorry, and, uh...
And we'll be in touch.
I promise.
I know.
I love you so much.
I love you so much, baby.
Goodbye.
[Tony mutters]
[Tony inhales
and exhales sharply]
[phone rings]
Hello?
- Tony, it's
Eugene Gallagher again.
- What's up, amigo?
- Talk to me, chief.
I just did a real good thing
putting this man on
with his wife.
We heard.
And we have some good news
as well.
Uh, your brother
is on the way.
We've just sent
a helicopter for him.
Jimmy? Jimmy!
[laughs]
Jimmy!
[Gallagher]: And also, I have
George Martz here with me.
George is the deputy
county prosecutor
who's going to go over
the logistics of this deal
since James Kelly's
out of town.
Um... Um, um, a prosecutor?
It's a formality, Tony.
Uh... Here, I'm gonna
put him on the phone.
Hello? Tony.
I'll get down to brass tacks.
Everything that we're
about to discuss
is contingent
on Richard Hall's
health and safety.
Understood?
- I'm listening.
- We have a prepared statement
that absolves your debt
accompanying the property
in question.
Meridian Mortgage
has already sent a notice
to the county
recorder's office.
And what about my apology?
That's really important to me,
you know?
You near a TV, Tony?
Channel 9.
[TV reporter]: ...where
the hostage situation
is unfolding.
[Martz on TV]: As you know,
you've made certain
specific demands.
And in attempting to comply
with those demands...
I've requested Cliff Chapman
to make a statement to you
on behalf
of Meridian Mortgage.
Hello.
I'm Clifford Chapman,
head of finance
at Meridian Mortgage.
This statement has been
authorized by M.L. Hall.
This is a public apology to...
[Tony]: Why are
they parading Cliff?
[scoffing]: Where's M.L.?
What, they don't
have cameras in Florida?
[Cliff]: ...relationships
in this great state...
- Cliff's... VP, Tony.
- He's a fucking nobody.
- ...Meridian Mortgage
or Hall Hotel
have committed in respect
to Mr. Kiritsis.
Thank you.
What, that's it? That's it?
[screaming]: What, that's it?
That's it?
[clears throat]
It is our ongoing...
- Huh? I want an apology
from Meridian Mortgage.
That means M.L. Hall.
Not empty gestures
from some fucking lackey.
Some goddamn catharsis!
Some genuine guilt!
- Now, Tony, we delivered
on our end.
The fuck you have!
- That note's debt has been sent
to the recorder's office.
You can shut up now.
- Then how do I know these
aren't just empty promises?
You're a prosecutor,
chief says, yeah?
That's right, Tony.
- Yeah! Well, I want a lawyer
of my own,
with eyes on all
of the paperwork
you're teasing me with,
Jimmy too.
And I want a real apology
from the big man himself.
I want to hear it from
M.L.'s fucking lips.
[TV reporter]:
And since that time,
Tony Kiritsis has held
Dick Hall hostage.
The big demand
has been immunity.
First, the opportunity
to voice his complaint
against the mortgage
company...
[Tony]: I need the people
to know my side of the story.
My side of the story.
The real side of the story.
The fucking truth.
[funky soul music]
- Time keeps on slipping,
doesn't it, Indianapolis?
Hope that rush hour traffic
isn't too brutal for you.
But if it is,
we're right here with you.
Tony?
No, I don't... no.
Are you scheduled to talk
to Mr. Fred today?
This has been Fred Temple.
Let's remember
to become the ocean,
not fear disappearing into it,
alright?
I thank you for listening.
Take it easy.
Love on somebody.
- Forty-one?
I could try to catch him
when he's coming out.
He's just about to leave.
Good night, my brothers.
- [James]: Uh, Mr. Temple?
- Yeah.
- Excuse me, um...
sir, you have a caller.
- I have dinner in 30 minutes,
is what I have, James.
- We vetted it with
the operator, confirmed it...
[Fred]: Brother, one day,
you're gonna understand
that when you have a wife,
dinner at 6:45
means dinner at 6:45.
Not 7:00, definitely not 6:30,
and absolutely not 6:46.
- Fred, that Tony Kiritsis
fella's on the line,
and he's asking
to speak to you.
The guy with the shotgun
in the man's neck.
Wait.
You should have opened
with that shit, James.
- Oh, uh, sorry.
I thought you knew.
- Wait, he's on the line
for me right now?
Yes, sir.
[sighing]: Fuck.
Okay, listen, I'm gonna
need you to call my wife.
Alright?
Tell her I'm gonna be late.
I don't know which call
is scarier.
[inaudible chatter]
Hello?
- H-Hello? Ahem, hello? Hi.
[Fred]: Hello, Mr. Kiritsis.
This is Fred Temple.
[sighing]: Hi, Fred.
It's an honor, Fred.
Longtime listener,
first-time caller.
[Tony laughing]
- Yeah. I hear you wanted
to speak with me.
- Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Is, is, is this on air?
No, but it's being recorded.
But we can consult
the proper authorities
and take it step-by-step.
- If that's okay with you.
- Okay. Sounds good.
What's on your mind, brother?
Talk to me.
These people betrayed me.
They set me up and schemed
to ruin my life.
Well, let me tell you
something else.
I'm not a rich man.
I'm a poor man.
And that never bothered me.
I could go gliding along
and being poor
and working like a dog
and breaking even
and being happy as a dog
in dog heaven.
But fuck these people.
They played God and they lost.
I'm a man that's fighting for
everything that he owns, sir.
Now...
Now, do you have a wife
and family, Fred?
- Uh, yes.
Yes, I do.
And do you love them?
- Uh, yes, I do.
I do.
Very much so.
Say that they set you up.
Said they're gonna
take your cars
or your house or your wife,
your children,
and then they're gonna
laugh at you.
Now would you be ready
to kill, Temple?
Well, I...
I'd be awfully...
mad, brother.
- You'd be ready to kill.
Don't lie to me.
I don't lie.
Why would you lie?
You'd... you'd kill
in a minute.
[heavy breathing]
These people,
they've ruined my life.
I'm not gonna be intimidated
or humiliated by anyone.
I've been a patsy
my whole life.
And that never bothered me.
But I told
these motherfuckers
to document everything
that they've done.
- Okay, Tony. Hey, let me
tell you what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna stop the tape
right now, alright?
Okay, now I'll tell you what
I will do.
I will play this tape tomorrow
morning after we're clear.
Alright?
How does that sound to you?
- O-Okay, well,
I'll be listening, baby.
Thank you, Fred.
And I'm sorry for my language.
[stammers]
Oh, shit.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
- What are we gonna do
about all those fucks, Fred?
[sighing]: Oh, man. Shit.
[lighter scratches]
- I was just on
with Fred Temple.
Fred motherfucking Temple.
Hell yeah, baby.
[chuckles]
They're gonna air it
in the morning.
[Tony on recording]:
I told these motherfuckers
to document everything.
[Fred]: Okay, Tony. Let me tell
you what I'm gonna do.
Alright?
I'm gonna stop the tape
right now.
Alright?
Oh, boy. Thank you, Fred.
[Fred on phone]: Sure thing.
[he sighs]
Have you spoken to him since?
- No, he's not interested
in talking anymore.
- Uh, we're at a bit
of a standstill
while we formulate
some paperwork
with his lawyer,
John Ruckelshaus.
- Okay, so what do you
want me to do?
[Gallagher]: Maybe get
some rest, Fred.
- Shit, you don't got
to tell me twice.
I mean, but in regards
to the airing.
- Well...
[sighs]
...every moment Tony spends
listening to himself
or talking to Fred...
is another moment we have
to formulate a plan.
If Fred accommodates
Tony's idea of immunity,
entertains his crusade
against Meridian,
that in no way
binds us legally.
I mean, the words and opinions
of a DJ are not binding.
No offense, Fred.
And none taken.
[Gallagher]: So what
are we saying?
- Since he refuses
to talk to us...
are you comfortable
letting him call you?
- Yeah, if my talking
to this fella
keeps this poor guy safe,
I guess I ain't got no choice.
- Thank you.
Someone from the FBI
should be able
to take the reins soon.
Yeah.
[sighs]
[indistinct reporting on TV]
I have to use the restroom.
Number one or two?
I'd rather not say.
Well, I'm gonna find out
either way.
Let's go.
Enjoy the privacy.
Get some rest.
[Richard]: Tony?
[door closes]
Tony?
[ominous music]
[Tony on radio]: Let me
tell you something else.
I'm not a rich man.
I'm a poor man.
And that never bothered me.
I could go gliding along
and being poor
and working like a dog
and breaking even
and being happy
as a dog in dog heaven.
But fuck these people.
[laughing]
They played God
and they lost.
I'm a man that's fighting for
everything that he owns, sir.
[helicopter blades whirring]
[suspenseful music]
Jimmy?
[reporter]: You've known Tony
for a number of years.
What kind of guy is he?
- Well, he's always been
a kind of reasonable man.
He just seems
to be excited over...
He's felt he's being beat out
of some money
over this real estate deal.
[reporter]: He's still to put
forward his feeling
that his mortgage company
has swindled him.
He has purchased
this 17 acres of land,
cleared many
of the trees himself,
hoping to start
a shopping center.
He said he had
some commitments
from a grocery store chain
offering about $3 million
to start a center.
Then he says the mortgage
company moved in...
[cameraman]: I got a ham
and cheese.
You want half?
- No, thanks.
[chuckles]
[sirens wailing]
[cameraman]: Pretty good.
[Linda]: Aw.
Look at this.
Looks like a fed,
walks like a fed,
quacks like a fed.
Must be the feds.
Wake up, sleepy boy.
How'd you sleep?
You get some rest?
Oh, you don't look too good.
You want some?
- No, Tony.
- Hmm?
- No.
- Have one.
They're not stale, Dick.
I got them from Gordon's
two days ago.
I don't want any!
- What, are you watching
your figure?
Don't worry, we'll get you
an extra pallbearer.
This morning
has been crazy, man.
They aired my interview
with Fred.
Fred's on my side,
and the people are listening.
I must have had five friends
call into Fred's station
this morning.
Crazy.
How does that feel? Hmm?
To know that the voice
of Indianapolis
is chatting with me.
Life's crazy, man.
[reporter]: We're seeing
movement here
at the Crestwood
apartment complex,
where it is day two
of the hostage crisis
that captured the imagination
of Indianapolis
that will hopefully
come to an end soon.
The Army bomb squad is here,
and has begun to try to think
of ways to somehow get in
without setting off
the explosives.
- We're told, unofficially...
- Are they making moves?
These sneaky motherfuckers!
[dramatic music]
Clear out! Clear out away from
the motherfucking building!
I said clear out!
[laughing]
[phone rings]
Alright.
Hello?
- Those motherfuckers
just dropped bombs
on your TV affiliate,
and now they're trying to lie
about it, and I don't like it.
They said it was coming
to an end.
You heard what I heard, right?
[Fred]: No, brother,
I didn't hear.
I just woke up.
I slept like a log all night.
I'm just trying
to catch up, like...
Man, you know
I wouldn't lie to you.
[Tony]: Mr. Temple, please, sir,
I respect you.
You've been a hell of a man.
[panting]
Now if those cocksuckers
are honest,
you tell them all
to clear out.
Okay, alright.
So, uh, what do you
want me to do?
- Tell my brother Jimmy,
or George Martz,
or whoever the fuck,
I want a live press conference
on national television
so I can talk
to the people directly.
You tell that command post,
Mr. Temple.
I like you, okay?
[line disconnects]
[Richard]: Tony.
[Tony]: What, Dick?
What do you want?
Shut up, then.
[♪ Love To Love You Baby
by Donna Summer]
- Well...
[chuckles]
...he likes you.
- Ha!
[laughs]
Shit.
I don't need him to like me.
- Special Agent
Patrick Mullaney, FBI profiler.
- [Love]: Frank Love.
- Mike Grable.
Eugene Gallagher.
- So talk to me about
Mr. Kiritsis.
- Well, he has
his mortgage broker
at the end of a shotgun.
Frank, why don't you
bring him up to speed.
- You've been
the point of contact?
- Well, I go back
with Tony, sure.
Chief and I both
were trying to talk to him
until Tony said he only wanted
to talk to Temple.
And you're Temple?
- No, I'm George Martz,
County Prosecutor's Office.
Fred Temple's WCYD, 105.2.
[Fred]: I'm DJ Fred Temple.
WCYD.
WCYD?
It's our local radio station.
Fred's a DJ.
The voice of Indianapolis.
Frank, you know Mr. Kiritsis.
You have a grasp on his
psychological background?
- Well, he comes
from a big family.
Tough fella, tough people.
I think he's known
to make for a good friend,
but also a bad enemy,
if that makes sense.
No links to organized crime
or anything.
- Talk to me about...
Tony's psychology.
He's mad.
- Why don't you
wash my ass, Father?
Woo!
He's out of control.
He's after money and immunity.
[Tony]: Try me, motherfucker!
Try me!
A real shit show.
Based on what I've seen,
the order of his taxes,
the intricacies
of that device,
it seems like he's a man
who has quite the attention
to detail.
It seems he's after
maintaining control,
not a man that's out of control.
Let's, uh, map out Tony.
I'm gonna start a mood chart.
[laughs]
I'm sorry, do you have
one started
that I should work off of?
Like we said...
his mood is angry.
Mad as hell.
Except for when he chums it up
with Temple man.
Shit show.
- He's angry because
he's feeling betrayed.
- They were all ready to sign.
I had them.
And then, poof,
gone in the dead of night.
Gone.
Disrespected.
- You rig the game
with your math
and your mountains of money
in the bank
in order to bleed us dry.
Humiliated.
[Richard]: You know, Tony,
I've been patient with you.
You know how many times I could
have lunged for that revolver?
Squish us both to the ground.
Try it, motherfucker.
- And, yes, you put
all this together, and...
- You silver spoon-fed
cocksucker.
Miserable piece of fucking shit.
[Richard]: Go on.
- It's all about
giving him respect.
Let's get him the call
he so desperately wants.
[phone rings]
And he'll be eating
from our hand.
[phone rings]
- Hello?
- Tony, it's Chief Gallagher.
What's up?
- I've got M.L. Hall
on the other line.
Oh, do you now?
[Gallagher]: Yes, and he would
like to speak with his son.
- Well, I'd like
to speak with him first.
- No, Tony, he needs to hear
Richard's voice.
He needs to hear
from his son's own mouth
that he's okay.
You copy?
When do we talk terms?
[Gallagher]: After Mr. Hall
speaks with his son,
we can continue our dialogue
and find a resolution.
And hear his apology?
- Tony, hand the phone
to Richard.
Hand the phone to Richard.
Your daddy's on the line.
He wants to know when
you'll be home for supper.
Go on.
Hello?
Is this Richard?
Yes.
- Well, we'll patch M.L. in.
- Okay.
- Mr. Hall, you're on with
Richard and everybody else.
Richard, how you doing?
Are you hurt?
- I'm hanging in there.
Tony is a fine host.
You know,
all things considered.
- He's out of his mind,
that's what he is.
- [laughs]
- He's right here with me,
and I'm sure he'd love
the chance to, you know...
sort some things out with you
after we catch up.
Tell me, how's Mom?
- She's an absolute wreck,
of course.
Climbing the walls now.
Come down from there!
- Right.
[sniffles]
Hey, uh...
Listen, Dad, do you think
there is a solution
we can sort out here?
- Well, of course.
- Now, I just, uh...
I mean, regarding his terms.
- You and I don't need
to brainstorm this thing.
You know, the lawyers are
gonna draft whatever contract,
and you and I need
to just follow their lead.
- Okay.
- That's all.
- It's... Ahem.
- Can you do that?
[Richard]: It's just that
from where I'm sitting,
which is, you know...
behind a, uh...
a shotgun, mind you,
one of the main points
is, is, is an apology.
- Well, I thought
Cliff read one.
You know, there's no amount
of sorry
that're gonna satisfy this man.
You know that.
Well, I'm sorry
he missed payments
and decided
to commit a crime.
Truly, I'm sorry.
And I'm sure as hell sorry
that you're in this situation.
- Okay, Dad.
So Tony's here with me.
And if you wanted to take
a moment to apologize, I...
I think it would go
a long way, you know,
and possibly expedite
this release process.
So if you wanted to do that,
then it might be a great idea.
[M.L. chuckles]
- Apologize for what
exactly, Richard?
[Richard]: Well, you know,
possibly setting up a deal
that wasn't in his interest.
And milking him of interest.
- And Tony's saying,
"And milking him of interest."
- Apologize for how
interest works?
I mean, you miss a payment
and your debt increases.
That's in the terms.
- How am I supposed to--
- By saying sorry to Tony.
He thinks you're--
- I know. I know.
- He's, he's...
he's saying he knows
we deterred potential tenants,
that we were setting up a deal
that wasn't in his interest.
Okay. And that we were purposely
waiting him out
and defrauding him,
and he wants to hear you admit
that and say you're sorry.
- He has a gun
to your neck, son.
Why are we
the ones apologizing?
What, you have
that Stockholm syndrome
setting in you already?
No, Dad.
- I could say sorry
a thousand times over,
but this is a recorded line.
I have to treat this
as if I'm under oath.
I'm not gonna admit guilt
to something I didn't do.
- This claim he has is baseless.
- I don't...
And I will not be complicit
in his slander of this company.
- It sets an awful precedent...
- What's he saying?
Is he gonna apologize?
[sighing]: Fuck.
- [M.L.]: Richard?
- Is he gonna apologize?
- Yeah, I'm here, Dad.
Yeah, I'm here.
- Can we, uh, can we send
anything to you?
You know, make you
a little more comfortable?
- No, no, no, he's been clear.
He won't allow any--
- I wanna talk to him.
I wanna talk to him.
Give me the phone.
- Give me the phone.
- No, no. No talk. No!
Give it to me.
- It's inappropriate!
- Hello, sir.
Now, you and I
were supposed to have
a little chat yesterday,
but you decided to go
on a fancy little vacation,
didn't you?
Must be nice.
[Richard sighs]
I've never been on a vacation
in my entire fucking life.
I have nothing to say to you.
You see, we Halls
are stoic people.
Humble God-fearing people.
The fuck you are.
You're greedy fucking people.
Your souls are pi-pitch-black.
Now admit what you did.
Fuck your family.
Fuck the Halls.
Greedy sons of bitches.
What family you have, Tony?
Who are you providing for?
- Well, I-I...
I've told you.
My businesses are my children.
- A man out to make money
with no mouths to feed
other than his own
is no man at all.
But I do have empathy for you,
Mr. Kiritsis.
I believe in you.
I always did.
And your vision.
And your tenacity.
- They were ready to sign!
Goddamnit!
They were ready to sign!
Just, just apologize
for what you did.
Just fucking apologize.
You know what you did.
- You deterred them.
- No, Tony, no.
The fruit falls off the tree.
You don't shake it
before it's ready.
- Oh, fuck your riddles,
old man!
And fuck you!
[panting]
Just, just admit
what you are.
Just fucking admit what you
are and say that you're sorry.
- We're gonna get
this deal done,
and you're gonna
release my son.
Yeah, and what if I don't?
What if I shoot...
little pretty Dicky here
in the fucking face?
What then, huh?
Well, I'll...
mourn the loss
of one of my sons...
and we will all rue the day
you ever stepped foot
into the offices
of Meridian Mortgage.
Stay strong, Richard.
[disconnected line tone]
Hello?
[Richard chuckles]
Oh, Richard, Richard, Richard.
Yeah.
[soft music]
Want a cigarette?
Sure, Tony.
- What am I supposed
to make him feel like?
- I don't know. I don't know.
- Bend the knee?
Go down on all fours?
[Mabel]: No. No, I don't know.
- I'm on a telephone call
with a madman.
♪ Hey-ney, hey-ney, no-wah
♪ Witchi-tie-tie, gimee rah ♪
♪ Whoa rah neeko
Whoa rah neeko ♪
♪ Hey ney, hey ney, no way
♪ Water spirit feeling
Springing round my head ♪
♪ Makes me feel glad
That I'm not dead ♪
♪ Witchi-tie-tie, gimee rah
♪ Whoa rah neeko
Whoa rah neeko ♪
♪ Hey ney, hey ney, no way
[indistinct police
radio chatter]
♪ Whoa rah neeko
Whoa rah neeko ♪
♪ Hey ney, hey ney
[Tony]: I want one more
thing, Fred.
Like I said before,
I am very concerned about
this man's wife and children.
I don't want them to be
terrorized by any of this.
[Fred]: I hear you, Tony.
But holding on to anger
is like drinking poison
and expecting
the other person to die.
[distant police sirens]
[Tony]: Goddamn it, Fred,
it's like you're a poet
and a philosopher.
How did you come up with that?
[Fred]: I've got to credit the
Buddha on this one, brother.
♪ Water spirit feeling
Springing round my head ♪
♪ Makes me feel glad
That I'm not dead ♪
♪ Witchi-tie-tie, gimee rah
♪ Whoa rah neeko
Whoa rah neeko ♪
♪ Hey ney, hey ney, no way
♪ Witchi-tie-tie, gim-- ♪
[phone rings]
Hello?
[teenage boy]:
Holy fucking shit.
Hello?
Hey, is this Tony Kiritsis?
Who is this?
- You really got a gun
to that guy?
- I asked, who is this?
Goddamnit!
[teenage girl]:
Why don't you shoot him?
[teenage boy]: Yeah, pussy.
Blow his head off on camera.
[both giggling]
Fuck you!
Who was that, Tony?
[sniffles]
- There's some sick, twisted
people in this world, Dick.
[long breath]
Should we get some rest?
You rest, Dick.
You and I both know
I'm not getting a wink
until this is done.
[sirens blaring]
- Excuse me, sir.
- Oh!
- Hi there.
- Just needed a little caffeine.
Oh, is this for the media?
- Oh, no, no, I think
it's sort of a free-for-all.
I'm Linda Page
from Channel 12.
I noticed you were speaking
to Sergeant Frank Love?
Uh, yeah, we go back.
He's known our family
for years.
Your family?
Oh, I'm Tony's brother.
Well, one of the ones he doesn't
mind talking to, that is.
- Ah, you're the brother
of the man of the hour.
Um, Tony Kiritsis.
Yeah. I'm Jimmy Kiritsis.
And you know something?
Look...
it's not fair
what you news folk
have been saying, okay?
[Linda]: Okay.
Well, we would be
more than happy
to give you the opportunity
to set the record straight
if you'd like, Mr. Kiritsis.
- I'd like that very much.
Thank you.
Okay, well, let's do it.
Alright? Let's...
John, why don't we just
go over here by this van.
And, uh, you ever been on live
television before, Jimmy?
- First time for everything,
sweetheart.
When you stand long enough
outside of Tony Kiritsis's
apartment,
you have time
to do a lot of thinking.
And I've been thinking
about men, something like him,
men who are...
are desperate.
I don't mean desperate enough
to put a shotgun at the back
of somebody's head.
- Is there anything you'd like
to say to our viewers?
- Uh, yeah, he's...
he's not a desperado
like he's been painted out
to be. Uh...
He's... he's not a thief.
- There are people who think
that they've been wronged
or who have been wronged.
And sometimes there isn't
much difference
between the two as far as
their feelings are concerned.
He's not asking for $5 million
like it's being reported
by some stations.
Uh, and, and, and we're
quite concerned
with the profile
that's been painted of him.
Now, we got
an attorney, John,
on his way to help
sort this out.
So, uh, thank you.
And, uh, maybe we can, uh,
resolve it tomorrow morning.
Chop it up and set it to air.
Prime time.
[Linda]: ...as of now,
still in his apartment.
It's looking like
it could be a long,
tense, and very cold night.
- When you stand out here
long enough,
you got time to think.
And sometimes that's good.
Have a good evening.
[gunshots on television]
[man on TV]: Look out.
[gunshots continue]
[Richard]: Give me
the strength...
[mumbling prayer]
[tense music]
[sighs]
[news anchor]: Childcare expert,
Dr. Lendon Smith
has some tips for you.
Today, it's on medical checkups.
If there's one important time
that somebody should go
to the doctor
is when we're five years
of age.
Perhaps again
the next time...
[indistinct police
radio chatter]
[thud]
[Tony screams]
Tony?
[gunshot]
[Tony]: Get down!
[repeated gunshots]
Oh, my fuck!
[Tony]: Let me get
the fuck off you.
I was just...
You thought I was...
[continuous gunshots]
[indistinct yelling]
Somebody help!
Help!
[door creaks]
The fruit falls off the tree.
You don't shake it
before it's ready!
[gasps]
[pants]
[water bubbling]
Do you have any pets, Dick?
We have a dog.
Golden retriever.
[laughs]
- Of course he's
a golden retriever.
[laughs]
You... you got a white
picket fence too?
Wow. I don't think you need
to worry your head off.
I'm sure your family's
feeding Sparky and--
Max.
What's that?
His name is Max, uh...
After Maxinhall Lake.
He loves it
when we take him there.
- That's right.
Your dad owns that plot too.
Must be nice.
Let me guess.
You got a boat.
- We do have a boat.
- Yeah, that's what I...
Yeah, it's looking good
out there.
Fred must have talked sense
into them.
We're lucky we have Fred.
[Richard]: Mmh...
- Radio hosts probably
make for good fathers.
Mm, talk sense
into those kids.
Doesn't beat it into them.
- Any plans to be
a father yourself, Tony?
I told you.
My businesses
are my kids, Dick.
- Hmm, there is no
lucky lady out there
that might, uh,
help you change your mind?
- Plenty.
Plenty of fish in the sea.
No shortage of options,
let me tell you.
[Tony chuckles]
I've had my fair shot at love.
Hmm.
I'm a hell of a dancer,
you know.
Mm. Is that right, Tony?
Oh, yeah, baby.
I got some moves.
I got that soldier's rhythm.
[Richard]: Hmm.
I'm not a formally trained
dancer or anything,
but I'm a f-fun dancer.
But oh, boy, would I get
an ass-whooping
for trying to dance
as a kid, though.
I bet you...
Fred allows dancing
in the...
in the Temple household,
being a radio host and all.
Some folk have it good.
Never forget that.
- Tony, being raised
by my dad...
it wasn't a walk
in the park. I...
I recognize the privilege
financially, I do, but...
- You recognize how your daddy
gave you that corner office
and that fancy little
president title of yours?
- Yes.
- Well, that's good.
- Yes, I do.
- Mm-hmm.
But it, uh...
it wasn't all sunshine
and rainbows growing up
as his son, okay?
You heard the phone call.
[sighs]
What's your mom like?
Long brown hair and...
big smile.
How about you?
She's good.
I'll miss her.
Oh, let's turn that frown
upside down.
Okay.
Oh!
Take a page out of
Fred Temple's book,
shall we?
[funky music]
♪ Some people say now
♪ We're living in a joke
♪ Ha
[humming]
Yeah.
♪ Yes, they did
♪ This country's
Going up in smoke ♪
♪ Ha
♪ I got a message
♪ They need to know
♪ Ha
[snapping fingers]
[laughs]
Oh, yeah, baby.
♪ And let a man be a man ♪
♪ Gotta let a woman
Be a woman ♪♪
[Fred]: Talk to me,
Indianapolis.
Talk to me, baby.
[woman 1]: I'm not saying
what he did is okay,
but, uh, does he have
a girlfriend?
[woman 2]: I know Dick.
He goes to my church.
He's a good man.
[man 1]: He is a goddamn
hero is what he is.
A national treasure.
[man 2]: Finally,
somebody had the balls
to stand up to these parasites
getting rich off the good
people of Indianapolis.
[Fred]: That was
Let a Woman Be a Woman,
Let a Man Be a Man.
And speaking of our man,
Tony Kiritsis,
we found out he'll be giving
a live press conference
as part of the terms for
the release of Richard Hall.
Peace and love, y'all.
Peace and love.
- Alright, let's walk
through this.
As we've seen,
the key is to make him feel
as if he has an audience.
So the networks have agreed
to air the event live.
But we need a contingency plan
for Richard's utmost safety.
Grable, we'll put you...
on his right shoulder.
Same as the shotgun.
We'll be sure to have Fred
in his peripheral vision
as well
so Tony can feel his presence.
[Gallagher]: If things go south,
I have this handkerchief
in my coat pocket,
if I pull it,
that's the signal.
And your job
is to secure the barrel
away from Tony to the ceiling.
- Just give the word and I'll
drop him bullheaded, chief.
I'll pull my gun.
And, well...
what does the bureau
say the most efficient way
to do this is?
To make it painless, you know.
- Base of the skull
behind the ear,
angled up so it passes through
and exits the frontal lobe.
- Behind the ear.
Angled upward.
Okay.
[Love]: You guys will
have to excuse me.
[retches]
[gargling]
Ah!
[sighs]
[Tony]: You want
some cologne, Dick?
No, thank you, Tony.
- Oh, yeah, your shit
don't stink, does it?
- That's not what
I'm saying, Tony.
- I can smell you
from here, pal.
- Yeah, well, it's been
a long couple of days.
I think they'll forgive me.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[man]: Whoa, whoa, whoa,
watch out.
[indistinct chatter]
Good evening.
I'm in a room near
the police headquarters
outside of Tony Kiritsis'
apartment,
where he is currently
holding Richard Hall hostage.
We have been
requested air time
in order to give an address
by Deputy County Prosecutor
George Martz,
an address apparently directed
at Tony Kiritsis himself.
- Now here's Mr. Martz.
- Thank you.
At this time, I would like
to read a letter
from the office of
the Marion County prosecutor,
James F. Kelley.
It's entitled,
Letter of Immunity Granted
to Anthony George Kiritsis.
[Martz clears throat]
"Mr. Kiritsis, on this day,
February 10, 1977,
in the state of Indiana,
Marion County prosecutor,
James F. Kelley,
does hereby confer and grant
to Anthony George Kiritsis
immunity from prosecution
with reference to
the abduction of Richard Hall
and all subsequent
acts done...
- Goddamn right.
- ...or alleged
to have been done by the said
Anthony George Kiritsis.
- You know, I think I used
to be jealous of you.
[Linda]: I'm Linda Page,
reporting live...
- But now, I wouldn't trade
nothing to be in your shoes.
When we're done and this deal
is finished down there,
the whole world is gonna know
who you and your father
really are.
And they're gonna pay me
five million for it.
[chuckles]
[police siren blares]
[indistinct chatter]
[phone rings]
- Hello?
- Tony, it's Jimmy.
- Hi.
[indistinct]
Alright.
Alright, Jimmy.
Now, they got
the promissory note? Yeah?
Uh-huh.
Alright... Okay.
[inhales sharply and exhales]
Let's get these cameras rolling.
Let's see if we're on
national television.
Tony, is it over?
[TV turns on]
Tony?
[orchestral music]
[music ends]
[audience applauding]
[Tony]: Fucking John Wayne.
Thank you.
- How am I supposed to compete
with John Wayne?
- Tony, is it over?
[knock on door]
- Tony, it's Mike.
We're ready.
Tony, please.
Please!
- [Tony]: Okay.
- Oh, thank you, Tony.
Now, listen, I-I-I'm happy
to do anything that you want.
And I can make it happen.
And I have sure as hell
learned my lesson here.
And, and, and I'll implement
some changes
and, you know,
do all kinds of things.
And, and, and I thank you
and the Lord and, you know...
[John Wayne]: My thanks to you
and Charlie Blair
for traveling...
- Wait, Tony,
what are you doing?
- Time to shine, Dick.
- No.
No, Tony, I'm not,
I'm not going out there.
Tony, no, no, no,
you're just gonna...
- You, You're gonna--
- Curtain call, baby.
- Unlock me, Tony.
Unlock me.
- Curtain call, baby!
- No, I'm not going anywhere.
- Tony!
- Get up!
Get up, Dick!
[Richard]: I'm not going out
there, Tony.
- Move!
- No! No!
[grunting]
I swear to God,
I'll shoot you right here,
right now.
Don't try me, motherfucker.
Mike!
[knocking on door]
What's the deal, Mike?
- All three networks
are gonna roll cameras.
NBC, CBS and ABC.
- Tony, they're gonna shoot me
and shoot you.
[grunting]
[John Wayne]: Thank you.
- If I die, you die.
- I'm not going out there, Tony!
- [applause]
- I'm coming out with Dick.
[gunshot]
[grunting]
...my peers, my friends...
[Richard]: Tony,
they're gonna shoot me!
...and honored by the people
is about as much
as a fella can ask--
[announcer]: We interrupt
our regular programming
to bring you a special
live report
from day three of the
Indianapolis hostage crisis.
Anthony Kiritsis is about
to address members
of the press and law
enforcement...
- Tony, here's that statement
from M.L.
and Meridian Mortgage
you wanted.
- Good. Give it to Dick.
He's gonna read it.
- What?
- Get it, Dick.
[announcer]:...he will free
Mr. Hall unharmed.
Please keep in mind
this is a live broadcast,
and we do not know
how events are to unfold.
- Almost impossible not to,
coming from the gunman.
This is a live report.
[officer]: Everybody back,
please.
[indistinct chatter]
- We have no control
over what is going out
over the air right now.
[indistinct chatter]
[Tony]: Turn the cameras on!
Turn the goddamn cameras on!
Move it. Move it.
[camera shutters clicking]
I'm gonna show you something.
From the lawyers.
Read it.
You read it.
I want it on all
national channels.
I've been called a kidnapper,
an extortionist,
and everything else.
Now I'm a goddamn
national hero,
and don't you forget it.
I want it on all three
national channels.
Are we rolling?
Are they rolling?
Hmm? I got friends
all over the country!
Read it.
"February 10th..."
Okay, Tony, loosen it
a little bit.
"February 10th, 1977.
A statement is being made
to try and--"
- Hold it. Where's Fred?
[Fred]: I'm over here.
- I'm here.
- Fred.
- Hey.
Hey, you're a hell of a man,
Fred. Come here.
- Come here. Good to see you.
- Alright, alright.
[Tony]: The voice of
Indianapolis.
[Tony chuckles]
Good man.
Yeah. Where's Jimmy?
Where's Jimmy?
- He's coming. He's coming.
- Yeah? Yeah.
- [Jimmy]: I'm here.
- But where's...
Hey, hey, Frank, Frank.
I-I've known this guy
for I don't know how long.
You're a hell of a cop.
Hell of a cop.
Well, let's, uh, settle down
and let this gentleman read.
Read it.
[Richard pants]
"February 10th...
1977.
This statement is being made
to try and state the items
that Mr. Kiritsis alludes to--"
- Hold it. I need water.
Give me a glass of water.
I want this goddamn thing
understood!
I'll read it.
"February 10th, 1977.
This statement is being made
to try and state
that the items
that Mr. Kiritsis alludes..."
And I don't like that word!
I charge,
and they've admitted it!
"Alludes to being illegal
and unethical acts
of the Hall group."
Give me a drink, pal.
Give me a drink.
- Good?
- Yeah.
Yeah, and I'm sober, friends.
I had six drinks in 1976,
and I haven't had any
this year.
Don't miss them a fucking bit.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
"This possible lessee
was very interested
in the Kiritsis site...
but we found it impossible
to agree on terms
satisfactory to our
best interest."
Their best interest!
I went up there
to borrow money
and had multiple
prospective tenants,
and these motherfuckers
shopped it to somebody else!
Deterred each and every
last one of them.
It's a private equity trap
meant to lure in common folk,
give them a taste
of the American dream,
and then spit them right out!
And you're--
You're painting me a monster?
I'm just a little guy.
A lot of friends of mine
are here...
and they've seen me stressed.
For four years
and three months,
they had one,
one of these stuck
to my, to my,
to my ear.
Now it's the other way around.
Ain't that right, Dick?
[Tony]: You're a fucking...
Fucking...
[camera shutters clicking]
Now, I hope this thing
doesn't go off
because I'm having too much fun
with him. Yeah.
[suspenseful music]
You all right? You all right.
Okay. Oh, Dick, you're gonna
like this.
"Mr. M.L. Hall..."
this gentleman's father...
"personally takes responsibility
for these improprieties."
[dramatic music]
There it is in writing.
I'm gonna frame that.
[laughs]
Yeah.
Where's, where's Fred?
Fred? Fred?
Hey, Tony.
[Tony]: You're gonna be late
for work in the morning, Fred.
- I think I'll, uh,
I'll sleep in late.
[Tony]: I don't know if you can
get away with that. Can he?
[Tony chuckles]
Not really.
- I want to thank this...
this gentleman for...
for putting my interview
on WCYD
and letting my friends
call in.
If you hadn't done that,
I'd still be called
a common kidnapper.
And I don't know, I don't know,
how I'll ever thank him.
Alright.
[Tony]: Thank you for...
for doing that.
I've been a big fan of yours
for a long time, Fred.
[Fred]: Alright, alright.
- You're a hell of a man, Fred.
A hell of a man.
Supporting the little guys
is what you do.
I, I also want to apologize
to this gentleman's family.
Now I, uh...
I'm sorry I humiliated
this man this way,
even though he surely
had it coming.
He is the one holding the gun,
and he's crying
like a petulant child.
My son has the gun
strapped to his neck,
and his eyes
are dry as a bone.
Still and calm as that moon.
[tense music]
You see?
That's my son.
- I just wanted everybody
to know that,
by God, I was right!
- Do you have a plan
if he pulls that trigger?
- Pay the fine and watch
the ratings roll in.
Yes, okay.
I think that's it.
Let's get this deal done.
Frank, pull up my pants,
will you?
Yeah.
- Let's just get
the essential parties here.
- Mullaney, if you would just--
- Right.
Alright, alright.
Well, thanks again to everybody
who supported me,
and I'm sorry
about my language.
Yeah.
Alright, come on.
Let's go, let's go, Dick.
[tone beeping]
Come on!
Come on, come on,
come on, come on!
♪ Open wide, America
♪ We're gonna give you more
♪ Burger Chef
Has everything ♪
♪ We know
You're looking for ♪♪
[announcer]:
Open wide for Burger...
[dramatic music]
[Tony]: Jimmy, we good, brother?
Last steps, Tony.
Lawyers are just crossing
the T's and dotting the I's.
Alright, good.
[Jimmy]: We're very close, Tony.
Almost there.
[heavy breathing]
- I just need your signature
right here.
Alright.
[chuckles]
It's hard doing this
with the left hand.
Can you hold that for me?
Alright, there it is.
Five million dollars, baby.
[laughs]
[Grable]: Tony,
have a seat right here.
- Tony...
- Hey, hey...
If I may.
Yeah. Yeah, sure, sure.
Alright, Dick.
Oh.
[heavy breathing]
[screaming]
You hear that, Jimmy?
It's the sound of justice.
Ain't it beautiful?
[producer]: Find out
what the fuck is going on!
What was I supposed to do?
They kicked us
out of the room.
- Amateur shit, Linda.
- What'd he say?
- Christ, I've seen Boy Scouts
work quicker than that.
Get it off.
[wire snaps]
Yeah.
[officer]: Gun's clear.
[gunshot]
[screaming]
- Y'all thought
it wasn't loaded?
It was loaded the whole--
Get off me! Get off me!
I was just--
- [cameraman]: The hell is that?
- Shit.
- Did he shoot him?
- That's the shotgun. Go, go.
We have to get back in there.
Mikey, get off!
Get off!
Y'all get the fuck off.
It was just...
I was just... Ah!
Don't you fucking move.
[screams]
Wait, are you arresting me?
[Grable]: Yes, I am.
- You're arresting me? Fucker!
Fuck off!
You're not arresting me,
motherfuckers!
Get that thing off me, Mike.
Hey, Jimmy! You fucked me!
- I'm sorry!
[Tony]: You fucked me.
- Mr. Martz, can you give us
any details at all?
- The hostage is out, he's safe.
- What happened?
[Martz]: Uh... They went
into the command post,
negotiated, and released
Mr. Hall.
[reporter 1]: Who removed
the wire? Where's Tony?
I really don't know.
And I really don't
give a shit.
He fired into the air
to prove some kind of point.
Richard Hall is alive.
- Mr. Martz, any more comments
about his whereabouts?
[reporter 2]: Can you
give us something?
[Linda]: Is Tony alive?
[reporters shouting]
[reporter 3]: There he is!
[reporter 4]: Richard! Richard!
Excuse me! Richard, please!
[dramatic music]
[♪ Raindrops Keep Falling
On My Head ♪ by B.J. Thomas]
♪ Raindrops keep falling
On my head ♪
♪ And just like the guy
♪ Whose feet
Are too big for his bed ♪
♪ Nothing seems to fit
♪ Those raindrops are falling
On my head ♪
♪ They keep falling
[Richard]: Thank you.
♪ So I just did me
♪ Some talking to the sun
♪ And I said
I didn't like the way... ♪
[priest]: He shall be clean.
Wash him, and he'll be white
as snow.
Purge him with hyssop
and he shall be clean.
Wash him, and he'll be white
as snow.
♪ But there's one thing
♪ I know
♪ The blues
They send to meet me ♪
♪ Won't defeat me
♪ It won't be long
♪ Till happiness steps up
♪ To greet me
♪ Raindrops keep falling
On my head ♪
♪ But that doesn't mean
♪ My eyes will soon
Be turning red... ♪♪
[dramatic music]
- [Jimmy]: I'm sorry, Tony!
- Cheap shot.
- I'm sorry!
- Talking like a cheap shot.
Fuck you, Gallagher.
You fucked it up.
Fuck, fuck off!
Dammit... What?
- Thank you for keeping him
alive, Tony.
I hope you find peace.
Who the fuck are you?
Where's Mr. Temple?
Gallagher!
What about my immunity? Huh?
False fucking promise,
you sons of bitches!
Where are we going?
[soft music]
[news anchor]: We have
breaking news.
Any minute now,
Judge Michael Dugan
will call the jury
to announce the verdict
in the Tony Kiritsis
kidnapping trial.
How do I look, Johnny?
- [cameraman]: Sexy, baby.
- Thank you.
[sighs]
[judge]: You'll pass those
verdicts to the bailiff, please.
[man coughing]
Please rise, sir.
[Tony]: We're fine. It's fine.
Face the bench, sir.
[jury foreman]: We, the jury,
find the defendant,
Anthony G. Kiritsis...
not guilty
by reason of insanity.
[Tony]: Yes!
[sighs and laughs]
[Tony]: Jimmy!
[laughs]
I knew it! I knew it!
[Tony]: Come here, baby.
[Jimmy]: Can't keep
a good man down.
[♪ I've Seen All Good People
by Yes]
I've got to say one thing.
I've just got to say
one thing.
[judge]: Quiet.
[gavel bangs]
- I'm, I'm, I'm sorry,
Your Honor.
Sorry.
[judge]: We are still
in session.
[Linda mouthing words]
[cameraman]: Hey!
[Linda]: Uh, Mr. Kiritsis,
how are you feeling?
- Hi, Linda. How are you doing?
[Linda]: I'm good.
You're good?
[Tony]: Yes.
Just get him, just get him.
Tony, did you think
they'd find you guilty?
I, I, I did not.
But, but I'm not crazy.
- Mr. Hall, how are you
and your family
responding to the news
of this verdict?
- It's a sad day for justice
and, uh, Meridian Mortgage.
You know, a company which is run
respectfully and devoutly
and will continue to maintain
and uphold the...
[sighs]
...the values
of the great state of Indiana,
even if this verdict does not.
Uh, ahem. Thank you.
[clears throat]
That was Richard Hall,
the president
of Meridian Mortgage
and the man taken hostage
by Tony Kiritsis,
who was just found not guilty
by reason of insanity.
[reporters shouting]
♪ Yourself
♪ 'Cause it's time, it's time
In time with your time... ♪
[shouting and cheering]
[Linda]: As you can hear,
sympathies have been torn
across this city
as a result of this case,
and now even further
by this truly
remarkable verdict.
I'm Linda Page
reporting to you live
from Marion County
Supreme Court.
- Back to you.
- Chop it up and put it to air.
Prime time.
[excited chatter]
[cheering]
♪ Move on back two squares ♪
♪ Send an instant karma
To me ♪
♪ Initial it
With loving care ♪
♪ Don't surround
♪ Yourself
What a shit show.
♪ In time with your time
♪ And its news
♪ Is captured
♪ For the queen to use
♪ Do-do, do-do
Do-do, do-do ♪
♪ Do-do, do-do, do-do
♪ Do-do, do-do
Do-do, do-do ♪
♪ Do-do, do-do,
do-do ♪♪
[gentle music]
[Fred]: Richard Hall
and Tony didn't
see each other much
after that.
Except there was
that one time.
[chuckles]
It was in this, uh,
little market...
on Earl Street
where Richard bought muffins
because they carried
the sugar-frees.
[Tony]: No, no, not that one.
That one.
Not that one.
This one right here.
The one I pointed at.
That's the one I want.
Yeah, baby. That one.
[coins jingling]
Keep the change.
Have a good day.
[Richard]: Thank you.
[door slams]
[Fred]: They saw each other,
but, uh...
they didn't speak.
There was not
much more to say.
[♪ The Revolution Will Not Be
Televised ♪ by Gil Scott-Heron]
♪ You will not be able
To stay home, brother ♪
To plug in ♪
♪ Turn on and cop out
♪ You will not be able
To lose yourself on skag ♪
♪ And skip out for beer
During commercials ♪
♪ Because the revolution
Will not be televised ♪
♪ The revolution
♪ The revolution will not
Be brought to you ♪
♪ By Xerox in four parts
♪ Without commercial
Interruptions ♪
♪ The revolution will not
Show you pictures ♪
♪ Of Nixon blowing a bugle
♪ And leading a charge
By John Mitchell ♪
♪ General Abrams
And Spiro Agnew ♪
♪ To eat hog maws confiscated
From a Harlem sanctuary ♪
♪ The revolution
Will not be televised ♪
♪ The revolution will not
Be brought to you ♪
♪ By the Schaefer
Award Theatre ♪
♪ Will not star Natalie Woods
And Steve McQueen ♪
♪ Or Bullwinkle and Julia
♪ The revolution will not
Give your mouth sex appeal ♪
Get rid of the nubs ♪
♪ The revolution will not
Make you look thinner ♪
♪ Because the revolution
Will not be televised ♪
♪ There will be no pictures
Of you and Willie Mae ♪
♪ Pushing that shopping cart
Down the block ♪
♪ Or trying to slide
That color TV ♪
♪ Into a stolen ambulance
♪ NBC will not be able
To predict the winner ♪
♪ At 8:32 on report
From 29 districts ♪
♪ The revolution
Will not be televised ♪
♪ There will be no pictures
♪ Of pigs
Shooting down brothers ♪
♪ On the instant replay
[indistinct chatter]
♪ No pictures
Of Whitney Young ♪
♪ Being run out
Of Harlem on a rail ♪
♪ With a brand-new process
♪ No slow motion or
Still lifes of Roy Wilkins ♪
♪ Strolling through Watts
♪ In a red, black and green
Liberation jumpsuit ♪
♪ That he has been saving
For just the proper occasion ♪
♪ Green Acres
Beverly Hillbillies ♪
♪ And Hooterville Junction
♪ Will no longer
Be so damn relevant ♪
♪ And women will not care
♪ If Dick finally
Got down with Jane ♪
♪ On Search for Tomorrow
♪ Because Black people will be
Looking for a brighter day ♪
♪ The revolution
Will not be televised ♪
[indistinct police
radio chatter]
♪ No highlights
On the 11 o'clock news ♪
♪ And no pictures of hairy
Armed women liberationists ♪
♪ And Jackie Onassis
Blowing her nose ♪
♪ The theme song
Will not be written ♪
♪ By Jim Webb
Or Francis Scott Keys ♪
♪ Nor sung by Glen Campbell
Tom Jones, Johnny Cash ♪
♪ Engelbert Humperdinck
Or The Rare Earth ♪
♪ The revolution
Will not be televised ♪
Will not be right back ♪
♪ After a message
About a white tornado ♪
♪ White lightning
Or white people ♪
♪ You will not worry
About a dove in your bedroom ♪
♪ The tiger in your tank
♪ Or the giant
In your toilet bowl ♪
♪ The revolution
Will not go better with Coke ♪
[inaudible]
♪ The revolution will put you
In the driver's seat ♪
♪ The revolution
Will not be televised ♪
♪ Will not be televised
♪ The revolution will be
No reruns, brothers ♪
♪ The revolution
Will be live ♪
- Waiting on that settlement.
Waiting on that...
Waiting on that $5 million
that I just stole.
[man]: Pardon me.
[indistinct]
[Tony]: We ought to have
some more water.
- Here, Dicky.
- I'm on the job.
- Give it to Dick.
- Here, Dick. Got it?
[camera shutters clicking]
- If you don't get out in front
of them goddamn cameras,
you're not gonna be
in any more of my shows.
- I'm upstaging you. Sorry.
- You know that?
Sorry. Sorry.
You're doing a single.
My fault.
[gentle music playing]
[Grable]: What a shit show.