Greetings
May I have...
espresso.
and...
croissant
espresso.
Yes.
You have to be careful.
Keep your eyes open in Rome.
Sugar.
We'll take care of you. Ok?
Don't worry.
Is everything ok?
Do you have your wallet?
Thank you.
He's amazing.
He's alright.
Alright?
What're you talking about?
I can sing better.
Are you crazy? He's incredible!
I'm telling you...
Show me!
Go!
Go up there?
Yes!
No, no.
What?
Impossible.
Go away. Bye.
Make me a coffee, please.
And find me Gia.
If you answered my calls,
I wouldn't have to come here.
I know, but today
is not a day to talk.
We need to talk.
Very, very busy. Excuse me.
Here's a flower!
Who is he? Does he speak Italian?
No, he's American.
He doesn't understand Italian.
But we're just friends.
No, I swear. Really!
Can you paint a portrait
of both of us?
We came here on a tandem bike.
Good luck at the Palio, Andrea!
Thank you, Giglio!
We will win!
Gia, how are you?
Good, good. Thank you.
I wanted to talk to you the other day.
I had things to do.
Andrea, can we say grace, please?
Sure, it's a good thing.
Lord, we thank you for this food.
Bless this wonderful family...
And all our new friends.
We also add a little prayer
for our horse, Mistico.
Tomorrow, may he conclude
the Palio as a victor!
You always did have a hard
time seeing anything through.
What did you just say?
I guess that makes two of us!
Are you really giving up the cafe?
Yes, because now you'll have
no reason to see me anymore.
May the best horse win!
Good Luck.
Vincenzo, I already signed the lease.
You didn't have to come here.
I came to say hello...
And to make you an offer.
But why, Vincenzo? I lost the bet.
I know.
But I can't keep the cafe forever.
Thank you.
Thank you, Vincenzo.
You better go get him.
No, it's too late. He's already gone.
He's out there waiting
for you on a motorcycle.
Go!
This is beautiful.
Miss...
No smoking here.