W
Wa
Way
Wayn
Wayne
And what? Are things any better?
Leave it in God's hands.
You have a blessed night.
I don't understand why
they took our phones.
Do they not trust us?
Those Hialeah cops must have
scared the shit outta you.
Is the dog okay?
I can hear him but I can't see him.
Let me tell you,
since it is likely being recorded,
none of our members
had anything to do with
whoever attacked you violently tonight.
We also have no interest in the money
that may have been
discovered in that house.
Are you aware of the amount of money?
That's of no importance.
This is the chess game we play.
And tonight you are the winner.
And we don't want more
dead police officers.
The captain who was killed
has already hurt our business enough.
Did the cartel have anything to do
with the murder of Captain Velez?
Good luck, Detectives.
You will need a lot of it tonight.
Are you gonna pay child support
for my girls?
Is this the example
you want to set for them?
What does it matter…
I took a bullet for this money.