[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[ANIMALS CHITTERING] [CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[MAN HUMMING]
Hey, Ben. Doc Lambert here.
Now, don't worry. I brought snacks.
[LOCK CLICKS]
All right.
[BEN BREATHING HEAVILY]
Hey, pal. [BEN GRUNTS SOFTLY]
Not feeling so great, huh?
Ugh, you and me both, buddy.
I made the mistake of eating
gas-station sushi last night.
And I'm paying for that today.
It's okay, Benjy.
We'll get you feeling better.
The doctor is in.
[GRUNTS SOFTLY] Now
this won't hurt a bit.
[SOFT THUD]
[CREAKING]
[BEN WHINING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANS]
[BEN BREATHING SHAKILY]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY] You got a
bit of a hangover there, bud?
Come on, you've had shots before.
Okay, doc's orders.
Hug the bear and take the jab.
Trust me, this'll make you feel better.
Come on.
Come on, pal.
[GROWLING SOFTLY] Hey, buddy.
[SCREECHES] [EXCLAIMS]
[BEN SHRIEKING] [LAMBERT SCREAMS]
[GROANS, SCREAMS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
WOMAN 1: Hey! Do you know where
Dad is? I can't get ahold of him.
WOMAN 2: [OVER PHONE] Well, so
that's the reason you called?
[CHUCKLES] Come on, dude. Give me a
break, okay? I need him to pick me up.
WOMAN 2: Pick you up?
Pick you up from where?
From the airport.
I'm on a plane right now, doofus.
What, you're coming home today?
Oh. Shit. MAN 1: Got it. Oh.
WOMAN 2: Okay, well, he
never remembered Mom.
Sorry. My bad.
MAN 1: It's my fault. Uh,
let me just... [CHUCKLES]
Huh. Cute little guy,
huh? [IMITATES CHITTERING]
Sorry.
MAN 2: Sorry about him.
He's never talked to a real girl
before. [WHISPERS] What the fuck?
MAN 1: Not cool. MAN 2:
Dude, are you for real?
Sorry, where is he?
WOMAN 2: Where is Dad?
Hi. Where do you think he is?
Hi. Hi.
Let me guess.
He's in his office all day,
working. WOMAN 2: Bingo!
And he's going away to some, like,
work conference or something next week,
so you won't even see him.
They want to turn his book
into a movie. Who knows?
Wait. So am I even gonna
see him at all this summer?
Question is, am I gonna
see you this summer?
Of course you are.
[ANIMAL CHITTERING]
Look, I got to go, but...
I'll see you soon, okay?
Yeah. You got it.
[SIGHS] Well, Erin's pissed at me.
And I honestly can't even blame her.
I mean, I haven't been
home much since... Hey...
Don't be so hard on yourself,
Luce. You've been through a lot.
The whole family, you've
all been through a lot.
[INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER PA]
[CHUCKLES] But you got me, girl. Okay?
Uh-huh?[CHUCKLES]
Okay.
You're the best. I love you. [SCREAMS]
[EXCITEDLY] What's up, bitches?
MAN 1: Dude! That's
what I'm talking about.
[IN SING-SONG VOICE] Who's
ready for some vacay? [GRUNTS]
MAN 1: Hey, what the heck? MAN 2: Hey.
Can I get that for you? [IN
NORMAL VOICE] Oh. Oh, yeah, sure.
MAN 1: Always goin' first. WOMAN
3: Chivalry is not dead. [CHUCKLES]
So I... kind of invited her
to stay with me this summer.
Really?
It'll be fun. Yeah.
[SHRIEKS] This is exciting!
Um... Oh.
I don't wanna be this person,
but I think you're in my seat?
You want to do a little switcheroo?
That way I can talk to both of you.
I mean, the middle's the worst,
anyway, so I don't mind taking it.
Nice of you. Yeah. Come on in!
Thank you. Whoops! [IN
SING-SONG VOICE] Sorry!
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Oh. Okay.
Sorry. Lucky you! [BOTH CHUCKLE]
Lucky me. I'm so glad you're here!
[TIRES SCREECH]
Ah! My brother's here! Nick!
[SQUEALS] Welcome home, sis!
Nice to meet you. NICK: How's
school been? They kick you out?
KATE: Oh, my God. Finals were brutal.
I'm just so happy to be back home.
Hannah, right?
You're all that Katie speaks about.
KATE: Don't be such a dick.
Lucy-Lou!
Hi. NICK: You finally came back home.
[SOFTLY] Brother's kind of hot. Shut up.
So your dad can't pick you up,
huh? He's got some work thing.
Wait. Did you say your
dad's gonna be out of town?
Yeah.
Are you guys thinking
what I'm thinking? Party?
HANNAH: Maybe we should get,
like, shit-faced... KATE: Party!
...in your place!
[CAPTIVATING MUSIC PLAYING]
HANNAH: This is your
house? This is crazy.
LUCY: This is home.
KATE: Wait till you see the
view off the lanai. It's insane.
AGENT: [OVER LAPTOP] So, I've got
you a meeting with Walter Friedkin
after the book signing.
[IN SIGN LANGUAGE]
How are the presales for
Silent Death looking?
[IN ENGLISH] It's early days, Adam.
I don't want you worrying
about it. Just get out there.
[ADAM GRUNTS] Tomorrow's
book launch is gonna be huge.
HANNAH: This place is unreal. Okay,
wait. No, Kate, wait. Come over here.
[IN SIGN LANGUAGE]
We need this deal.
[CHUCKLES]
We were beginning to worry
we might never see you again.
How were finals?
Okay.
Just okay, huh?
[MOUTHING] [CHUCKLES]
[IN ENGLISH]
It's nice to see you.
[IN SIGN LANGUAGE]
You too.
[IN ENGLISH] Hannah. Oh. Sorry.
Hi! [CHUCKLES]
Uh, this is Hannah.
Uh, we are keeping...
Lucy company this weekend.
Let's go get unpacked.
Okay. Bye. [CHUCKLES]
KATE: Okay, room tour. HANNAH: Okay.
[IN SIGN LANGUAGE]
They're gonna unpack.
ADAM: Mm-hmm.
[IN ENGLISH] Hey, Mr. Pinborough.
I got to keep the girls safe.
[IN SIGN LANGUAGE]
He's protecting us.
How's it going with Alexandra?
[IN ENGLISH] Alex? Uh,
we, uh... broke up.
[IN SIGN LANGUAGE]
They broke up.
Now is your chance.
[IN ENGLISH] He says he's sorry.
It's okay.
[SIGHS]
[IN SIGN LANGUAGE]
Someone is waiting for you.
I'm glad to have you back.
Sorry to have to rush off for work,
but I'll be back in a few days.
It's fine, Dad. We're used to it.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey.
Erin? What's up, dork?
[SIGHS] What are you
playing? Can I beat you?
Look, I'm doing so much better
than you. [CHUCKLES] ERIN: Stop.
Stop!
AUTOMATED VOICE: Erin busy.
[LUCY SIGHS]
AUTOMATED VOICE: Lucy bad.
Lucy sorry.
You were gone forever.
I'm back now.
It was lonely here.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
I brought this teddy for someone.
But they probably won't want it.
[LOW THUMP] [BOTH GIGGLING]
[PANTING]
[CHATTERS, GRUNTS]
[GIGGLES]
[LAUGHS]
LUCY: Hi, Ben.
Hi, baby.
[LUCY GIGGLES] [BEN PANTING]
AUTOMATED VOICE: Lucy...
back.
Ben miss.
Lucy miss Ben.
[BEN CHATTERS] LUCY:
Yeah? You want to go?
Hey, Kate brought a friend.
Want to have some fun?
[HANNAH SCREAMS] [BEN SHRIEKING]
[GIRLS LAUGHING]
What? What is that thing? Did it...
LUCY: Come here. [STAMMERS] Did it
get in from outside or something?
[LAUGHS] HANNAH: What?
[CHUCKLING] No, I'm serious.
Oh, my God.
What is that?
This is Ben.
HANNAH: That thing has
a name? LUCY: Yeah.
He's part of the family.
[GIGGLES] What do you mean?
He wants you to shake his hand.
My... My ha... My hand?
-He wants to shake my hand? -Yeah.
HANNAH: He's kind of cute.
[LAUGHS] KATE: Yeah, right?
Hi, Ben. It's okay.
[PANTING] Is his name Ben?
Mm-hmm.
New friend! [BEN CHATTERING]
This is crazy. Oh. [ALL LAUGHING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[YAWNS]
[SWITCH FLICKS]
[EXHALES, GASPS] NICK:
Couldn't sleep, either.
What happened to Lucy's mom?
Oh, uh, she died last year of cancer.
I'm... I'm sorry, I didn't know.
No, no, no. It's... It's fine.
I mean, it's not... fine.
It was, uh... it was tough.
I... I take it you've met Ben, then.
Uh, yeah. [CHUCKLES]
I've met Ben. Mm-hmm.
Takes a beat to get
your head around, right?
[CHUCKLES] Yeah, what's the
deal with that, exactly?
Um, Lucy's mom was a
linguistics professor.
She was trying to get humans
and chimps to communicate.
One day, she just brought Ben home.
Oh.
Yeah, you know. Mmm. Mmm.
Take it.
For the jetlag.
Good night.
[LIGHTER FLICKS]
[EXHALES]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[BEN GRUNTS] [GASPS]
[EXHALES] You scared me, Ben.
[BEN PANTING]
[GRUNTING] [WATER RIPPLES ECHOING]
[GROWLS SOFTLY]
HANNAH: Ben?
[ECHOING STOPS]
Ben?
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHATTERS]
[GRUNTING]
[YELPS] Ow! Hey! Ow!
Ben, stop! Get off! Ow! [SHRIEKING]
Ben, you're hurting me!
[HIGH-PITCHED WHISTLE]
[BEN GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
[BEN CHATTERS]
[SOFTLY] "Weird around strangers."
Oh, okay, yeah.
[GRUNTS] [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
[BEN CHATTERING] Okay. Bye.
[EXHALES]
Fuck. [SIGHS IN RELIEF]
[ADAM GRUNTS]
[BEN GRUNTS]
[FLIES BUZZING]
[CHATTERS]
[IN SIGN LANGUAGE]
Have you been fighting
with the neighbors again?
[BEN CHATTERS]
Of course you'd deny it.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[BEN PANTING]
[WHIMPERING]
[YELPS]
[SQUELCHING]
[BEN WHINES]
HANNAH: [IN ENGLISH] No,
seriously. KATE: Wait.
I know, maybe he's like a player or
something. Oh, there's a new one.
Wait, who are those
girls? HANNAH: Oh, my God!
That guy is ripped!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[ERIN GASPS]
Uh?
[IN SIGN LANGUAGE]
Breakfast anyone?
[MUMBLING]
What is it?
A mongoose got into Ben's
enclosure and bit him.
[LUCY GRUNTS]
Is he okay?
It will get better in two or three days.
Oh, ok.
I'll send the mongoose in for testing.
See what it says. You never know.
I'll call Lambert later and see
if he can swing by after work
and clean out the cage.
Bring some antibiotics.
Leave Ben locked up until then.
I will.
[GRUNTS]
[CHUCKLES]
Are you excited Lucy is home?
She has her friends.
[ADAM GRUNTS]
The three of us will have
so much fun when I'm back.
Doing what?
I'll think of something.
Lame. Boring.
[SNORES, CHUCKLES] [ERIN CHUCKLES]
[IN ENGLISH] Morning.
[WHISPERS] Go.[LAUGHS]
[UPBEAT ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GIRLS SQUEALING]
[GIRLS SHRIEKING]
[EXHALES]
[SONG FADES]
Are you gonna be here
for the whole summer?
I don't know.
I might just stay here for a while.
Hannah.
Are you gonna call those
guys you met on the plane?
The ones you said you liked?
[BLOWS]
[CHUCKLES LIGHTLY]
Yeah.
Great idea, Lucy.
Kate, you have their numbers, right?
KATE: Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Okay.
"Hot Guys Plane."
Nice. Classy. [CHUCKLES] [LAUGHS]
Hey, you should do it.
Hmm? Go on, Lucy-Lou.
Come on, Lucy. HANNAH: Hmm?
Come on.
[LINE RINGING]
It's going to voicemail.
Hey, guys.
Um, these are the girls
you met on the plane...
yesterday. [WHISPERING]
No, say something sexy.
[KATE CHUCKLES] "Come over."
Um, we're all alone and waiting for
you to come fuck our brains out.
[ALL LAUGHING]
1500 Kapahulu Ave.
NICK: Whoa! KATE: Lucy!
Fuck! [WOMEN LAUGHING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
NICK: [CHUCKLES] Go
on, Lucy. Pick it up.
Whore Mansion.
[ALL LAUGHING]
WOMAN: [OVER PHONE] Lucy?
Mrs. Hodges.
MRS. HODGES: Did you
just say "Whore Mansion"?
What?
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY] No. I didn't.
Um, do you want to talk to Kate?
MRS. HODGES: Just tell
her to feed the fish.
I can't get hold of Nick and
I won't be back until Tuesday.
Sorry, Mom. Phone died.
MRS. HODGES: Well, charge it. [GAGGING]
[RETCHES] HANNAH: Oh!
MRS. HODGES: What was that? LUCY: Uh...
I'm gonna call you
back, Mrs. Hodges. Bye.
NICK: Katie, we can't take you anywhere.
Okay, we have to get her to the bathroom.
Come on.
HANNAH: Such a lightweight!
NICK: God, Katie, that smells.
KATE: Uh-huh. I want to go to...
...bed. Hey, you're okay.
We're almost there. So close.
Three steps.
[CHUCKLING] Two steps.
Okay, ready?
And we're gonna go...
down. [KATE GROANS]
LUCY: Okay.
Blanket. KATE: Thanks.
And... your phone.
Kate, if you're gonna be sick...
aim for this.
You see it? Okay.
KATE: Hey.
[LUCY SIGHS]
You're a good friend, Luce.
NICK: Poor Katie.
Boy, she's trying so hard to impress you.
Well, I think that Lucy is
trying so hard to impress you.
[SCOFFS] Don't be silly.
Lucy's like my baby sister.
So, it's okay if I do this?
[PASSIONATE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, Ben. Doc Lambert here.
Now, don't worry. I brought snacks.
[LOCK CLICKS]
All right.
[RAGGED BREATHING]
Hey, pal.
Not feeling so great, huh?
Well, let's see what we can do about that.
[BEN GROWLING]
[SHRIEK ECHOES]
[EXHALES, GAGS]
[THUMPING] [SHUDDERS]
[ANIMALS CHITTERING]
[SOFT THUMP] [GASPS]
[PANTING SOFTLY]
Hannah?
[BEN GROWLS] [GASPS]
[EXHALES] Ben.
What are you doing in here?
[GROWLING SOFTLY]
Ben?
What's wrong?
[GRUNTS]
Ben, it's me...
[GRUNTING] ...Kate.
[WILD CHATTERING, SHRIEKING]
[PANTING]
[GROWLING]
Lucy?
Lucy!
Lucy, you need to come down here now!
[CONTINUES GROWLING]
Kate? [BREATHING SHAKILY]
There's something wrong with Ben.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
LUCY: Ben?
How did he even get out of his enclosure?
[GASPS]
I thought he was gonna attack me.
Ben?
But he would never hurt
anyone. [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[HANNAH SCREAMING] [BEN SHRIEKING]
That's Hannah!
Hey. Stay here.
But I... Don't argue!
[CONTINUES SCREAMING] NICK:
It's okay. He won't hurt you.
HANNAH: Lucy! Kate! [BEN SCREECHING]
Where are they? The pool.
[NICK AND HANNAH SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
HANNAH: Oh, my God! Get it away from me!
[CONTINUES SCREAMING] [BEN SCREECHING]
NICK: It's okay. Just calm down!
Hey! Hey, listen! Go over there.
Go over there! Over there
now! [BEN SHRIEKING]
Ben!
[GROWLS, PANTING]
[BEN CHATTERS] Ben?
What's wrong?
[NICK BREATHING HEAVILY]
LUCY: What is it?
[GRUNTING]
Ben.
It's Lucy.
Hey, what happened? [FRANTIC GRUNTING]
What are we gonna do?
I think there's a rope in there.
Let's tie him up.
KATE: Hey.
[GROWLING]
LUCY: Ben?
Ben.
[LUCY CLAPPING]
[CREAKING] [BEN GROWLS]
LUCY: Ben.
[CRAB SONG PLAYING ON TOY] [NICK GASPS]
[GROWLS, SHRIEKS]
Turn it off.
[SHRIEKS]
Ben! Hey, hey, hey!
[SONG CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
[BEN GRUNTING]
Hey.
[NICK PANTING]
[GROWLS]
Here, Ben. Hey, Ben?
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
[GASPS] [BEN GRUNTING]
LUCY: Hey! Hey, hey,
hey! Okay. [BEN SHRIEKS]
LUCY: Uh, give it to me. Oh, shit.
Lucy.
Hey, hey, hey.
Tie the other end.
[BEN PANTING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey. [BEN GRUNTING]
I'm not gonna hurt you.
[BEN WHINING]
Ben.
It's me. Lucy.
[QUIET WHINING, PANTING]
[SOFTLY] Yeah.
You're not feeling good, huh?
I'm just gonna put this over your head.
Yeah.
[SOFTLY] Yes.
[BEN GRUNTS] [GASPS]
It's okay.
[SHRIEKING] [LUCY GASPS]
Okay, um...
[GRUNTING]
Hannah, hey. You okay? Nick!
[SCREECHES] [NICK GRUNTS]
Nick? [GASPING]
KATE: You okay? Yeah, yeah.
ERIN: We need to call
Lambert. [BEN GRUNTING]
I told you to stay upstairs.
Erin's right. We need to
call Lambert or your dad.
My phone's charging in my room.
No. No, I'm sorry. Don't
you have a gun or something?
[BEN SHRIEKING] You want to shoot him?
Yeah. Isn't that what you're
supposed to do with sick animals?
Fuck you.
[SCOFFS] Excuse me? Your nasty little
pet clearly needs to be put down.
I don't even know why
Kate invited you out here.
I knew you had a problem with me. Guys!
Listen.
[RING TONE PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
That's coming from Ben's enclosure.
[BEN GRUNTING] Shh. It's okay.
Lambert's here. Why isn't he answering?
LUCY: Erin? Get away
from him. [ROPE SNAPS]
[GROWLS, SHRIEKS] [ERIN SCREAMS]
[ERIN SCREAMING]
[ALL SCREAMING] [ERIN SHRIEKING]
LUCY: Erin!
[SCREAMING]
[HANNAH GASPING]
Get in the pool! Ben can't swim!
[BEN SCREECHES]
[MUFFLED GROANING]
[MUFFLED GROWLING]
[ALL GASPING]
[BEN SHRIEKING]
[LUCY SCREAMING] [SPUTTERS]
[GASPS]
Help! Help! Help! Oh, my God!
It's okay. It's okay. [GIRLS GASPING]
HANNAH: Oh, my God!
[BEN CHATTERING] NICK: It's okay.
[MUFFLED SPEAKING]
Listen, just be calm.
Come on. [ERIN GASPING]
HANNAH: We need to stop the bleeding.
[CHATTERING] NICK: We need
to get a bandage on it.
Try to get her to the
other side of the pool.
[ALL BREATHING HEAVILY]
Here! Use my shirt as a tourniquet.
[ERIN WAILING] LUCY: We got you.
It's okay. It's okay.
What's wrong with him, Lucy?
HANNAH: Wait. [BEN CHATTERING]
[SOFTLY] Wait.
Can chimps get rabies?
[ERIN GASPS]
If Ben has rabies, does
that mean I'm infected, too?
Hey...
You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay!
We're gonna get you to a hospital.
How?
KATE: We're trapped in here.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
There's no way out.
[GROWLS]
[GIRLS WHIMPERING]
Help! Help!
Anybody! Help! Help!
Hello! Hello!
Help!
Please, someone! HANNAH: Hello!
Hello! Help!
KATE: Please! Please!
Somebody help us, please!
KATE: Please, someone! Hello!
KATE: Please!
HANNAH: Hello!
LUCY: Help, please!
Help!
[SHRIEKS] [ALL GASPING]
[BEN CHATTERING]
[GASPING]
[GROWLS]
What are you doing?
We can push him over the edge.
No, no, Nick! No! No, Nick!
HANNAH: No! KATE: Nick, no!
[BEN SHRIEKING] [NICK SCREAMS]
[GASPING]
[CHUCKLES]
[BEN CHATTERING] [NICK SCREAMS]
KATE: No!
[NICK SCREAMING]
[CRUNCHES]
[ALL GASPING]
[CRIES]
[SHUDDERS]
[GASPS, SHRIEKS]
[GROWLS, PANTS] [GIRLS SCREAMING]
[SCREAMS]
[GROWLS]
[PANTING MANIACALLY]
I'll kill him! No, Kate!
[SCREECHES]
Come back! Get off me!
Get off me! Nick!
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[WHIMPERING]
[CRYING]
[GASPING]
We need to get the float.
Kate.
Kate, I need you to hold Erin.
Come here, come on. Please.
Hey, come on. It's okay.
KATE: [MUFFLED] I've got her.
I've got her.
I'm gonna be careful, okay?
Okay.
HANNAH: Lucy.
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay.
There, grab it.
Look. Come on, Erin.
Erin, get on it.
HANNAH: Lucy. Lucy.
Lucy. Lucy. [BEN GROWLS]
HANNAH: Hey, Lucy, what are you doing?
[WHISPERS] Hey! Lucy!
What are you doing?
[BEN GRUNTING SOFTLY]
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS SOFTLY]
[PHONE RINGING] [LUCY GASPS]
[BEN SHRIEKING]
Come on, Ben! Here! Come here!
Come on! Come on! Come and get
me! Come for me! LUCY: Kate!
[BEN SHRIEKING]
[GASPS]
Quick, Lucy, run!
Lucy, run! [BEN SHRIEKS]
[SCREAMS]
HANNAH: Are you okay? Are you okay?
[GRUNTING]
KATE: Give me the phone.
Give it to me. LUCY: Call 911.
KATE: The screen must've
broken when I dropped it.
The keypad's not working.
LUCY: Try recent calls.
[LINE RINGING] Yes, it's ringing!
BRAD AND DREW: Yo!
Brad? Drew? We need
help! BRAD: What's up?
We are getting so lit right now.
Listen to me! We need help!
BRAD: Oh, you need some help? DREW:
Do you need help getting laid?[LAUGHS]
Send us the addy, baddies. Come on.
Listen, you dumb fucks, we
need help, okay? Send some...
[BEN SHRIEKS] [SCREAMS]
[ALL SCREAMING]
[BEN CHATTERS]
[RIPPING]
[GASPING]
KATE: Are you okay?
Are you okay? [BEN GROWLS]
LUCY: Where's the phone?
Where'd it go?
Lucy!
LUCY: Here you go.
[ALL BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BEN CHATTERING]
It's dead.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Dead.
LUCY: The boys will send help.
KATE: It didn't sound like
they were gonna send help.
We're on our own.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Nick...
dead.
Why is Ben doing this?
AUTOMATED VOICE: Nick...
Nick...
dead.
It's not Ben anymore.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Dead. Dead.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING] Dead.
Dead.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[INAUDIBLE]
[PHONE VIBRATING]
[PHONE VIBRATES]
[INAUDIBLE]
WOMAN: Please could
you sign it for Phoebe?
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[QUIETLY] He's gone.
Hey!
LUCY: Hmm?
KATE: Ben's gone.
For how long?
I don't know.
Maybe he's dead by now?
I have to get her help.
Nick's phone is charging
in the living room.
I'm gonna go get it.
[WHISPERS] You're gonna be okay.
I got you.
[WHISTLES SOFTLY]
[SOFT CREAKING]
[GASPS]
[SIGHS]
[SHUSHES]
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
[KATE BREATHES SHAKILY]
Come on.
Let's go.
[GASPS SOFTLY]
[BOTH EXHALE]
[WHISPERS] Where is it?
It's got to be in here somewhere.
[WHISPERS] Lucy.
There.
[GASPS]
♪ Who's that super cool exploradora? ♪
[FOOTSTEPS THUMPING] [BEN SHRIEKING]
[SINGING CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
[LUCY GASPS]
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY] [THUMPING]
[SHUSHES]
[BEN GRUNTING]
[SHRIEKS]
[GRUNTING]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS SOFTLY]
[BEN GRUNTING]
DORA: [ON TV] We need
your help to stop Swiper.
You have to say, "Swiper, no swiping!"
Say it with us.
ALL: [ON TV] Swiper, no swiping!
Swiper, no swiping! [SHATTERING]
[BEN SHRIEKING]
[CLATTERS] [BOTH GASP]
[STIFLED WHIMPER] [EXHALES]
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTS, HUFFS]
[CHATTERING] [BOTH WHIMPERING]
[SHRIEKS, GRUNTS]
[THUDS] [BEN SHRIEKING]
[GASPS]
[BLINDS SHATTERING]
[BEN PANTING]
[GROWLS]
[DOOR RATTLING]
[WHIMPERING SOFTLY]
[PLASTIC CREAKS]
[GROWLS SOFTLY]
[BEN GROWLING] [WHIMPERING SOFTLY]
[BEN PANTING]
[BOTH GASPING]
They must be there by now.
Yeah.
They would have given us a sign.
[IN SIGN LANGUAGE]
Stay here.
[EXHALES] [TYPING]
AUTOMATED VOICE: [IN
ENGLISH] Lucy. [GASPS]
Bad.[GASPS]
[WHISPERS] Run.
[PANTING]
AUTOMATED VOICE: Bad.
Lucy.
Bad.
Lucy. [SHRIEKS]
[LUCY SCREAMS]
[BEN SHRIEKING] [PUNCHES LANDING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANING]
Get up! Come on, let's go!
[BEN WHOOPING]
[GASPS] [SCREECHING]
[BANGING]
[BEN SHRIEKING]
[WHOOPING]
[BEN GRUNTING]
[WHIMPERS SOFTLY]
[GRUNTS][GASPS, GRUNTS]
[STRAINING]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS][GASPS]
[YELPS][GASPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING LOUDLY]
[SNARLS] Go!
[BEN SHRIEKING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GASPS]
Lucy? [GROWLS]
KATE: Please, Lucy! Help me! Kate?
KATE: [SCREAMING] Lucy,
please help me! No!
[BEN GROWLS]
KATE: No, no! Please, Lucy!
LUCY: Ben! KATE: Help me!
No!
[BEN SCREECHES] [YELPS]
[BEN SHRIEKS] [LUCY SCREAMS]
[GASPS, SCREAMS]
No! No! Get off of her!
[SCREAMING]
[BEN SHRIEKING] HANNAH:
Lucy, I'm coming! [GRUNTS]
[BEN GRUNTING] [HANNAH GRUNTS]
[BEN SHRIEKS, GAGS]
[STRAINING]
[SNARLS]
[GASPS]
Come on, quick! Help me! Grab it!
[BEN SHRIEKING]
LUCY: That'll keep him. I'm coming!
Pull him! Pull him in,
okay? He can't swim!
Come on, you fucker!
LUCY: Pull him in! Hannah, pull him in!
It's working! It's working!
Pull it, pull it! [BEN SCREECHES]
LUCY: Pull!
[BEN GROWLS] [LUCY AND HANNAH GRUNTING]
LUCY: I can't hold it.
HANNAH: He's pulling us back.
I can't hold it.
[GRUNTING]
LUCY: Come on! Come on! Come on!
No, no! [EXCLAIMS]
HANNAH: No! No! No! [SCREAMING] No! No!
Fuck!
[EXCITED CHITTERING]
[HANNAH COUGHING]
[GROWLS]
HANNAH: Where's Kate?
Where did she go?
Kate?
Kate!
[MUFFLED SHOUTING]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
Walter was just saying
he wants you to come in
and meet the head of the studio tomorrow.
What are you doing?
Don't blow this.
[VEHICLE APPROACHES]
[CAR DOOR OPENS, SHUTS]
[BOTH SHOUTING]
What's up?
Hey!
Hello! Hello!
I don't know.
Yo.
[BOTH IMITATING DRUMBEATS]
[IMITATES CYMBAL] Dude, nice house.
[CHUCKLES] Ha!
[WHISPERS] Yeah.
[CLATTERS] [SNICKERS]
My dad loves those
shitty books. [BELCHES]
That's nasty, bro.
Mm-hmm. Ooh.
Mmm.
Yo, can you grab me a beer?
Hey, man, you sure this
is the right place?
Positive.
[CORK POPS] She said 1500 Kapahulu Ave.
Yeah!
[GROWLS SOFTLY]
Yo!
Bro, is it me, or is
something off with this place?
[MOCKINGLY] "Is it me, or is
something off with this place?"
Dude, shut the fuck up.
Come on! Ah.
You check downstairs.
BRAD: And what are you gonna
do? DREW: I'm going upstairs.
Probably waiting for us in their bedroom.
BOTH: Mmm!
BRAD: That's why I keep you
around, man. DREW: Mm-hmm.
[BEN GROWLING SOFTLY]
[CLEARS THROAT, HUMS]
[WHISTLES]
Damn. [SNIFFS] Mmm.
[QUIET RATTLING] [SOFT GRUNTING]
[HUMMING]
[BELCHES, EXHALES] [HEAVY BREATH]
Yo!
Drew!
There's nothing down here.
[LOW NOISE ON TV]
What? Oh. These girls know how to party.
Mmm.
DREW: Mmm.
Beware.
Keep that in mind.
Aw, dude. Eleven missed calls, man.
Damn! [THUDS, CREAKS]
Awesome.
[GASPS]
[IN SPANISH] Ay, caramba!
[LAUGHS]
[IN ENGLISH] Oh, my God.
Who the fuck has a pet chimp?
[BEN GRUNTING, PANTING]
Huh?
[ROARS][GASPS]
What the fuck? [PANTING]
[SOFT GROWL] [GASPS]
Hey.
Hey. Oh.
[VOICE SHAKING] Good boy.
Good.
[GROWLING SOFTLY] Oh.
Oh, oh, whoa, whoa.
Good boy.
Yeah. Oh.
Yeah, good boy. Oh, yeah.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Okay?[BEN GROWLS SOFTLY]
Look, look, look,
look, look. No, no, no.
Me no hurt. Me no hurt. Okay?
[EXHALES] Oh, God.
[DREW WHIMPERING]
I need you to back up, man.
[GRUNTS] [BREATHING HEAVILY]
Yeah, yeah. Easy, boy. Easy.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Yo.
[WHISPERS] Hey, hey,
hey. Hey. [JANGLES KEYS]
What's that? Look.
Jingle jangle.
Shiny, huh?
Yeah? Yeah? Look, look.
[IMITATES BEEPING, CHUCKLES]
Do you want it?
Yeah? You want it? All right! Okay!
[KEYS CLATTER] Fetch. Go get it.
All right, okay.
Go fetch.
[SNARLS] [YELPS]
[WHIMPERING] Oh, my God. Yeah.
You got to take me out to
dinner first before you...
[YELPS] Dude, dude, dude.
[STAMMERING RAPIDLY]
Hey, I'm a friend. Okay? Yeah?
[GRUNTS] [THUMPING]
[IMITATES WHOOPING]
[LAUGHS] Yeah.
[PUNCHES LANDING] [SHRIEKS] Oh, my God!
Whoa, Donkey Kong, you
are freakishly strong.
All right, I'm... I'm gonna go.
[GROWLS] I'm gonna leave.
I'm gonna leave, I promise.
Hey, hey. Oh, my God.
[WHIMPERING] Oh, my God. [GROWLS]
[GRUNTS]
[SOFTLY] Hey...
Get the fuck off of me.
[LOUDLY] I said, get the fuck
off me! I mean it. [GROWLS]
If you don't get the fuck off me,
I'm gonna call the Department of...
fucking Animals and
have them put you down!
You heard me.
They'll stick a needle so
far up your goddamn ass,
it'll come out of your fucking...
[BEN SHRIEKS]
[DREW SHRIEKING]
[SCREAMING] [BEN SHRIEKING]
[BONES SNAP]
[BLOOD SPLATTERS]
[DREW GURGLING, GAGGING]
[CHOKING]
[CHITTERING]
[SHRIEKING]
S'mores? Maybe? Maybe not?
Whoa.
[LAUGHING]
Hey, Drew! The girls are
down here, bro! Wake up.
Wake up. BRAD: Drew!
Wake up.
BRAD: Drew! Quiet!
[HANNAH SHUSHING]
He'll hear you.
Who? LUCY: The chimpanzee.
What are you talking about?
[CLATTERS]
LUCY: Wait, no. Come back!
He'll hurt you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
What the... LUCY: We
need your help. Please!
You need to call 911!
Hey! You need to call
911! What the fuck?
LUCY: Please! We need your help!
He'll kill you! Please
come back! [GASPS]
LUCY: We need... We need the
police! Please! [GROWLS SOFTLY]
[GASPS] Whoa!
[SIGHS]
[BRAD SCREAMING] [BEN WHOOPING]
Hey!
[BRAD GRUNTS] [BEN SHRIEKING]
BRAD: Oh, God! No, no, no!
Ben's distracted.
[BEN GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BEN SHRIEKING, WHOOPING]
[SHOVEL CLANKING]
[BEN SHRIEKING]
[GASPING]
[CRIES SOFTLY]
[SHRIEKING CONTINUES]
[GROANING]
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PANTING]
[EXHALES, LAUGHS]
[SIGHS] Okay.
Come on. [KEYS RATTLE]
[SIGHS]
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS]
[GASPING SOFTLY]
[GROWLS, SNARLS]
[GASPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BEN CHITTERING, GROWLS] [LINE RINGING]
OPERATOR: [OVER PHONE] 911.
What is your emergency?
You need to send the police. [CRYING]
[GROWLS] You need to send the police.
Oh, my God, he's gonna kill
me. Okay, what is your address?
Uh...
I... I don't know.
Can you check? He's gonna kill me.
Miss, who is trying to kill you?
Is someone attacking you? [GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS] [DOORS UNLOCK]
[GASPS, RAGGED BREATHING][GROWLS]
Miss, can I get your address,
please? [DOORS UNLOCK]
[CRYING] I don't know, okay?
Can't you just trace
this call or something?
I will, but I need some
landmarks and anything
that could help us pinpoint
your exact location.
It's like... Like a
glass house and it...
I don't know! Just please,
do something! [CRYING]
Miss, who is going to kill you?
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS] [DOORS UNLOCK]
[GASPS][GROWLS]
Listen. Listen to me.
I need you to stay on the
line with me. HANNAH: Please.
He killed all the others, okay? He...
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
PLAYING] [HANNAH GASPING]
I hear you, but I need you to
tell me who killed the others.
The chimpanzee!
He's got rabies!
Listen to me! You need to get here now
and fucking shoot him, okay? Hurry!
[GASPS] [DOOR OPENING]
[DOOR CLUNKS] Miss?
Miss, are you there?
Please, please stay with me.
[BEN SHRIEKING] [SCREAMING]
[HANNAH GRUNTING]
[GROANING] [BLOWS LANDING]
[GURGLING]
[BEN GRUNTING]
[HANNAH GASPING] [BEN SHRIEKING]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[DOOR CLOSES] [CAR ALARM CHIRPS]
Hey. [ERIN SHUDDERING]
Hey.
[SHIVERING]
It's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna get you help.
Okay?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[INHALES]
[LEAVES RUSTLING]
[GLASS CLINKS] [SCREAMS]
[GASPS, GROANS]
[PANTING]
[BOTH SCREAM]
[PANTING, WHIMPERING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
[INAUDIBLE]
[TAPPING ON WALL]
[BEN SHRIEKING] [GASPS]
Dad!
[GROANS]
[BEN WHOOPING]
[SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING CONTINUES] [BEN GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING, CRYING] [BEN GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
[GROWLS]
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNARLS]
[BEN WHIMPERING SOFTLY]
[BONES SNAP] [LUCY SCREAMING]
[BEN WHOOPING]
[BEN SCREECHES]
[LUCY GROWLS]
[GASPS] [THUDS]
[GROANING, GASPING]
[BEN PANTING]
[SHRIEKS] [CRYING, SCREAMING]
ERIN: Leave her alone!
[GASPS]
No.
[BEN GROWLS] [ERIN SCREAMS]
No!
Erin! [ERIN SCREAMING]
Erin!
[SCREAMS]
[GROWLS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SHRIEKING]
Go!
[SCREECHING, GROWLS]
ERIN: Lucy! [SCREAMS] Go!
ERIN: Ben? No.
Ben.
Ben!
[BEN YELPS]
Ben, no! Lucy! [CRYING]
[LUCY GROANS]
[LUCY SCREAMING]
[BEN SHRIEKS]
[LUCY PANTING]
[BEN GROWLING]
[LUCY CRYING]
[BONES CRACKING]
[GROWLING]
[HIGH-PITCHED WHISTLE BLOWS]
[SOFT GROWL]
[GRUNTS]
[LUCY PANTING]
[BEN SHRIEKING]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS] [BEN SHRIEKS]
[GROANING]
[BEN GROWLS]
No! No, no, no!
Ben!
Get the fuck away from him.
[BEN SHRIEKS]
[SHOVEL CLATTERS]
[GROWLS ANGRILY]
[GRUNTS]
Lucy!
[BEN WHINES]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[CRYING] [COUGHING]
[BEN SHRIEKING] [GROANING]
[GROWLS]
Dad!
No!
[CRYING]
ERIN: No!
[GROWLING]
[EXHALES]
[SHRIEKS]
[ADAM GRUNTS] [BEN SQUEALS]
[GRUNTS]
[SQUEALING]
[PANTING] [ADAM GROANING]
[GURGLING]
[BEN EXHALES]
[GIRLS CRYING]
ERIN: Dad.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBS]
[BEN WHOOPING] [SCREAMS]
[SHRIEKS] Lucy! Lucy!
[LUCY CONTINUES SCREAMING]
[BEN SHRIEKS] [THUDS]
[GROANING IN PAIN]
ERIN: Lucy.
[LUCY GASPING]
ERIN: We got you.
We got you.
[LUCY GRUNTING]
[ERIN CRYING]
[LUCY SIGHS]
[SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
PARAMEDIC: She'll be fine.
You're gonna be okay.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
[IN SIGN LANGUAGE]
Everything will be fine.
I love you.
I love you too.
I should never have left you.
You're here now.
[STRETCHER RATTLING]
AUTOMATED VOICE: [IN ENGLISH] Bad.
Lucy.
Bad.
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[MUSIC FADES]
[CRAB SONG PLAYING]
[SONG ENDS]