Hi.
Hi. How are you?
My name is June.
June, get a move on!
You don't want
to be late for your first day!
Uh!
I miss you.
Don't bite your nails, you're 18.
People will think you're uptight.
I am uptight!
I hate this uniform.
Why can't I wear trousers like the boys?
Because you're a beautiful girl.
I love you. Have a good day.
Be safe!
Wait!
Hey, you!
-  Hey!
-  Come here.
Yes.
Mh-mh.
Hi. My name is June.
Could you turn around?
Yeah, turn around. All the way around.
Like that?
Mmh...
- I can work with that.
- Yummy!
You're coming with us.
I can't let you get gobbled up
by some poser clique.
Yeah, I'm talking about you!
Mh... What's your name?
Speaking Italian
is discouraged on campus.
- But you were just...
- What?
- Where are we going?
- To school, silly.
Welcome to St. Mary's International School
in the heart of Milan.
Home of every rich kid
and nepo baby.
The children of financial gurus.
Are you rich?
- Um...
- Oh, you don't have to. You're pretty.
Right...
I'm June, by the way.
I don't know if I got your name.
I didn't give it to you.
Ignore Amelia,
she's in a frisky mood today.
- I'm Blaze.
- He burns fiercely.
So, June, spill some tea.
Oh, so, me and my mum just moved here.
- From London.
- Dramarama at 10 o' clock. Don't look.
June!
- What... What did you say?
- Stay away from James Hunter.
- Who? That fighter over there?
- Yeah.
- He's not my type.
- Better.
- Oh, let me guess, June White?
- Yes.
Professor Beckett.
Welcome to Humanities A1 Literature.
Take a seat.
Hi.
Are you okay?
I was just saving...
Never mind. Will.
I'm Will, you're June,
and I'm talking like a caveman.
Sorry.
I didn't know you were showing up.
You're in my seat. Move.
- Move where?
-  It's not my problem.
Are you always this rude?
This is me being nice.
James Hunter, not only are you late
but now you are disrupting my class.
Leave Miss White alone
and either find a seat...
or get out.
Okay, fools, you know the drill.
Pencils only.
You have... 30 minutes to finish the exam.
Oh, June. We're covering Othello,
so I don't expect you to show...
"I know, Iago. Thy honesty and love
doth mince this matter."
Impressive.
"Doubt that the stars are fire.
Doubt that the sun doth move his aides."
"Doubt the truth to be a liar.
But never doubt that I love."
- The Brit knows her Shakespeare.
- That she does.
Oh.
How chivalrous.
Chivalry is dead.
You are my competition.
- So now I'm your competition.
- It remains to be seen.
Bye.
- Is that all I get?
-  For now.
Is this poisoned?
I wouldn't put it past me.
"Parting is such sweet sorrow."
- "For I shall say goodnight till..."
- Shit!
Oh! Oh my gosh, I'm so sorry.
- You did that on purpose, didn't you?
- No, I... I was gesturing, and then you...
Are you saying it's my fault
you can't even hold a cup of coffee?
It was an accident.
You don't need to be rude about it.
I'll show you rude.
What are you...
I am not allowed in here!
Ciao. Hi, nice to meet you.
My name is June. Hi.
Hi. Hello.
Let go of me.
Oh my God... I'm so sorry.
I saw your willy.
Get out.
-  Hi.
- Yeah, lovely to meet you.
Alright, look, you've had your fun...
This is my first day here
and I don't want to get caught
in the boys' locker room.
-  What are you doing?
-  What?
Is Snow White too much of a virgin
to look at a pair of abs?
Or is she afraid to fall in love
at first sight?
In love at first sight? With you?
Hilarious.
You disgust me.
I swear to God, if you keep going...
I will kick you.
I want them washed
and pressed by Monday.
Do I look like your maid?
I'm not doing that.
Maybe a nice cold shower
will change your mind.
Cold water from the shower?
Okay, okay... Okay, I'll do it.
Easy on the starch.
Well, that didn't take long.
You're already
the most talked about girl at school.
I'm so humiliated.
Why? Because you were caught
in the boys' locker room?
What's with all the anger?
Is James on drugs?
I wouldn't be surprised.
Well, have a nice weekend.
If you need me,
I'll be doing James' laundry.
You're not spending your first weekend
here doing James' laundry.
What are you doing?
I'm calling myself.
We're going out tonight.
Text me where to pick you up.
Blaze and I will come get you,
and we don't take no for answers.
- You're seriously the best.
- I know.
-  Bye.
- Bye, see you later!
You've got to be kidding me.
No, I understand.
We can always do it another time.
When is he back?
That's not going to work now, is it?
-  One second. My daughter's back.
- What's going on?
Hi.
We're supposed to meet with a client
tomorrow afternoon,
but Jordan's nanny is ill.
-  Who's Jordan?
- I work with him.
- Tell him I'll nanny.
-  You've got school.
Tomorrow's Saturday.
Shit, you're right. That's brilliant.
Jordan? Hi, sorry about that.
June said she could help out
tomorrow afternoon.
She did it all the time back home.
Okay, fantastic.
Let me catch up with her
and I'll call you back.
Bye!
You're a lifesaver. I bet he pays well.
I'm happy to help.
Happy to help? What's the catch?
There's a party tonight.
Mmh... It's our first night here together.
It's technically our second.
And I really want to go to this.
How was your day?
Comme ci, comme ça.
Is that all I get?
I am not paying you
to tell me how your day went.
You are a rotten little girl,
you know that?
Bye, bye!
You just love
being in trouble, don't you?
Someone has to be, right?
- You never got caught?
- No.
- Never?
- Never.
Hi.
What?
So, how is it going?
Voilà!
-  Meow! Good job, Blaze.
- Thank you.
So, this is from my mum's slutty phase
after she got separated.
I'm pretty sure you're the same size.
- No, I don't want to be slutty.
-  Yes, you do.
Come on, robe off!
And away, we go...
It's nice.
Uh, and very short.
That's the point.
Mh...
Fine.
- Too '80s.
- Bleah.
-  Doll.
-  You look like a doll. Go.
Too fruity.
Next!
Mmh.
- That's it.
-  Yes!
-  Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
What's wrong?
I feel like my boobs
are going to fall out.
Oh, and that's a bad thing?
- Yes, that's a bad thing.
-  Come on!
- What is this place?
- It's got a little bit of everything.
In the face!
Fight's over!
Yes!
And the winner is... Alessandra!
Waiter!
Thank you.
- Let's get fucking wasted!
- Let's get wasted!
I'm pacing myself!
Boo!
-  Cheers!
Guys! Are you gambling?
Thank you.
You're cute when you do that.
- Thank you.
-  What is it?
It's a QR code that sends you to an app
so you can bet on the fight.
Guys, I gotta go warm up the crowd, okay?
You guys have fun!
Bye.
-  Who wants to bet? Okay...
-  Oh! Will! Will! Will!
Will!
June.
Fuck...
You... You're beautiful.
-  Thank you!
- Thank you.
How was your first day?
Yeah, it was good,
until I met your bestie.
- James.
- Yeah.
Yeah. I heard about the shower.
He was just teasing you.
He is so hilarious, trust me.
I love him.
Trust me, you'll love him too.
No, I don't know about that.
Here we go.
Let's get ready to rumble!
Guys, are you ready or not?
So make some noise! Come on!
Tonight, you'll see an incredible fighter.
From Rome, Luigi!
He's scary!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
You don't know what's happening.
And now,
the defending champion.
James Hunter!
He's the guy!
James! Hunter! Hunter!
Hunter! Hunter! Hunter! Hunter!
Let's go! Go! Go! Come on!
James, you got this!
You got this, bro!
Punch him and move away!
Kick him, come on! Kick him!
- Come on! That's what I'm talking about!
- My boy!
- It's easy, man.
-  Come on, devil!
Fucking great.
Hunter! Hunter! Hunter! Hunter!
To James.
Success is hard work, sacrifice
and love of what you're doing.
Aw.
Not to mention the 10,000 euros I made!
-  Cheers.
To Austin,
the best trainer around.
And Will, the best friend and sparring
partner I could've ever asked for.
- I love you, bro.
- I love you too, bro.
Cheers.
So proud of you, boy.
- Do you want to say hi?
- No.
No, no, you go. I'll hang back.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
You knocked him out in round one.
- I mean, is there anyone stopping you?
- I'm just getting started.
You know what, Willy?
With a bit more effort,
that could be you in that ring.
Tonight is about James.
- What's Snow White doing here?
- She's with me.
- Is she?
- Yeah.
Be nice to her, bro.
I like this one.
Mh.
It's not like Ari.
- I'll be fine.
- Alright.
I loved the way you kicked him,
it was like...
It was something like...
Mh...
I knew it.
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
I was looking for the recycling...
Well, I don't mind.
Okay.
You okay?
Is it Jackson?
He doesn't know he's gay.
Time to break out my superpower.
Yes!
- Is he looking?
- Like catnip.
- Can I tell you a secret?
- Sure.
- I hate dancing.
- What? Why?
Because when I dance
I feel like... a wanker.
- A wanker?
- Yes.
I'm going to hit the bar.
Do you want something?
- Just some water will be nice.
- Okay.
How's the happy couple?
- He's so nice.
- Yeah.
- What?
- Nothing.
He's a sweetie.
Who is that?
- Oh, that's Ari.
-  His ex.
She dumped him
and fucked him up bad.
But don't worry about her,
she's ancient history.
- Follow me, Blaze.
- Bye.
-  Enjoying yourself?
- I was.
Good.
- Time to say goodnight.
- Oh, good, you're leaving.
Not me. You.
- What? You're throwing me out?
- You catch on fast.
- What is your problem?
- You are my problem.
Look... you clearly have
some weird obsession with me.
Yes, I'm obsessed with getting rid of you
and keeping you far away from Will.
Why? Why do you care?
Who are you to tell me who I can date?
Why do you presume I give a damn
about who you date?
You can get the whole school to fuck you,
Snow White.
Just not Will.
- Does Will know about this?
- No, and he's not going to.
Will!
Don't let her back in.
How am I supposed
to get home?
You can keep the change.
How dare you?
Fuck you! Fuck you!
My shoes. My shoes...
I hate you!
So sweet.
Narcissist.
Oh God, he's hot.
Jeez.
Enjoying yourself?
You should...
Does the pillow have a name?
What time is it?
Almost ten.
Coffee?
Ta-da!
Best mummy ever.
- I don't know about that, but...
- Oh, sleepy.
No, no, don't go back to sleep.
I want to know how your first day was.
How are your classes?
Who's your new friend
who lent you a 3,000-pound dress?
And why do you have
a pile of boys' clothes?
Not to mention, who is that mysterious
pillow you're snogging with?
Nighty night.
You little shit!
You've got to tell me everything!
- Everything!
- Okay, okay.
I'm up.
You know, it's his birthday next Tuesday.
Isn't this supposed to get easier?
It doesn't.
Right, I better get back to work.
Trophy, little trophy.
Trophy, little trophy...
Ow!
Mum, August hit me!
She's being annoying.
My name is August White
and I'm so cool.
- All the ladies love me.
- You are the definition of annoying.
You're future is bright,
my brother.
-  This is Gae Aulenti.
-  "Gao Lenti".
-  Gae Aulenti.
-  "Gao... Gao Aulenti".
Yeah, more or less.
And you lived in Gae Aulenti
your whole life?
Yeah.
But you moved around a lot.
Milan makes it... seven.
No, wait, eight.
- Eight?
- Yeah.
And all new schools?
I travelled for MMA fighting,
but I'm a lover, not a fighter.
What do you like to do?
I like to read thrillers
and watch true crime TV.
I guess the dark turns me on.
And do you also write?
No, I journal, but it's an outlet.
I write occasionally... about my moods.
- You don't strike me as moody.
- Good, I fooled you.
James Hunter. Bleah.
One second, just one.
Hey, man. Can I call you back?
I'm just out with... my mum. Yeah.
-  "Mum"?
-  I'll tell her you say hi, yes.
Done.
Are you okay?
Just curious why you told him
I was your mum.
It's not worth getting into it with him.
He's been my best friend
since we were kids and...
"Best friend"?
Will, he's awful.
- He makes a bad first impression.
- First, second...
Third...
Yeah, they're all bad impressions.
When we first met in elementary school,
I was afraid of James.
I was shy and awkward.
He wasn't scared of anyone,
and I wanted to be like him.
Why?
You don't know how many times
James has made me lose my temper.
He does it with everybody, but then
he makes you fall in love with him.
Trust me, that would never happen.
Did you like that?
- Oh, shit.
- What's wrong?
Oh, I'm supposed
to be babysitting this...
- I'll call you.
- Okay.
- Thank you for the tour.
- Yeah.
And for the kiss.
Bye!
Hi.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
I'm June, Mister...
Jordan.
- And this is Jasper.
- Hi, Jasper.
Oh, thank you, Jasper.
I should be back in about two hours.
- Text me if you need me.
- Okay.
-  Bye.
Have a nice time.
So, Jasper, what would you like to do?
Do you want to play a game?
MMA, yah!
Ow!
Jasper?
Jasper! Seriously?
Jasper, please.
Jasper!
What the fuck.
Jasper...
Bloody hell.
Jasper?
Jasper!
Where the fuck is this kid?
Jasper?
Is this another prank?
Okay...
- No!
- Ow!
-  Fuck!
-  What are you doing here?
I live here, you imbecile!
Jasper lives here.
This is Jasper's house.
Yes, and he's my brother.
God, this couldn't get any worse.
Jesus!
- Never seen a man's genitals before?
- Of course I have.
-  You can look now.
- Thank you...
Oh God!
Snow White,
saying the Lord's name in vain again.
All that over a naked boy.
You must be quite repressed.
I'm not repressed, I'm repulsed.
Now get changed.
Your wish is my command.
I killed the bunny.
You want to try?
Do I want to pretend
to shoot defenceless animals?
Well, they're balloon animals.
Yeah, it doesn't matter.
The answer is no.
Nor do I think
you should be teaching your brother.
Well, if I don't teach him,
how's he going to learn?
What would you prefer, Snow White?
Teach him how to sew?
Oh, good.
I was wondering when you were going
to introduce sexism into the conversation.
They're here.
Jasper!
He's adorable.
Thank you.
We've been busy trying to find
a special school for him.
He won't go to St. Mary's?
No, he has a mild form of autism
so that might not be the best fit.
Where's his mum these days?
Did I say something wrong?
No, not at all.
She had a breakdown over a year ago
and she is in rehab.
- I'm so sorry.
- No, no, no, please.
She and I have not been together
for years.
She has a new husband, but...
He's not a good man.
What do you think you're doing?
Excuse me?
What gives you the right
to talk about my mother to some strangers?
You know nothing about her
and you're not exactly
the father of the year.
This is my son.
- Edward.
- James! It's James!
I prefer Hunter.
-  Where are you going?
- Out.
Could you be more specific, please?
A party.
Is that the same party
you were talking about?
What party?
June, James can give you a ride.
That's not fucking happening.
Excuse me.
-  Don't you dare...
-  What's wrong with that boy?
Who knows? Can we leave?
Now go apologise.
Then you can do whatever you want.
Is that clear?
May I give you a ride
to the party?
I'm not leaving for like an hour,
but I'd be delighted to escort you.
Cool!
Vaping.
Of course you vape.
What? Does Snow White mind the smoke?
It's not the smoke.
You're the one that bothers me.
I don't know why you're angry at me.
I didn't choose to come.
Can you please stop talking?
Believe me,
I would happily never talk to you again.
I get it, you like your girls mute,
so they don't challenge
your narcissistic personality.
Still talking.
What's this?
- It's called a motorcycle.
- I know what a motorcycle is.
I'm not getting on that with you.
Is the little princess afraid of the bike?
The bike? No.
You driving it? Absolutely yes.
- I'll drive.
- The fuck you are.
I'm not giving you lessons.
Yes?
Pietro?
Alright,
I'll destroy him by round two.
I'll be there in 20 minutes.
Hey.
- Bye!
- What are you doing, June?
Get out of the bike.
Get off the bike!
See you later!
- White! Stop it!
-  Whoo-hoo!
Here I come!
Not bad for 125ccs.
-  Are you serious?
-  Don't get me started.
For real?
- Hi.
What was that all about?
Are you guys together?
God, no.
Really? Because it looks like you were.
- It was nothing.
- It doesn't look like nothing.
- I came from his house.
- So, it's worse.
No, I was babysitting.
- Yes.
- It's a long story.
Do you want this? Maybe it's for you.
Stop. Come on.
Wait, we don't have to queue?
-  No guests.
-  Don't ask me.
What are you giving him?
Vitamins.
- It doesn't look like vitamins.
-  Excuse me, who the fuck are you?
No one special.
Nice.
Where are you going, beautiful?
Sorry, I don't speak Italian.
Only a little.
Mh...
Hey, babe...
Why are you in a rush?
-  Pietro!
- Get your hands off me!
-  What is your problem, huh?!
-  Mind your own business.
Help!
-  You piece of shit!
-  No! Stop!
Help!
Stop them!
The fuck are you doing?!
What are you doing?! Leave him!
He went after Will.
What did you expect me to do?
To fucking wait
until you were in the fucking ring
for the fucking fight
that is now fucking cancelled!
Do you have any idea
how much money I had on this?
- I was doing it for Will.
- I didn't ask for your help.
You were about to get your ass kicked.
- Someone had to defend her.
-  What did you say?
So, you are the reason for all of this?
Could you... Could you do me a favour
and get the fuck out of my face?
And then Jackson got involved.
It was crazy.
I can't believe I missed all the fun.
- Hi.
-  Hey.
How is everyone?
It's not the best night.
James is drunk.
I'm going to need some help with him.
Oh, James is drunk.
- Can you please...
- Fine.
- Now?
- Now.
The other side. The other side, bro.
Yes.
Let's put him in the back.
- Where did you get the van?
- My dad is the principal of the school.
Oh.
- Oh my God.
- Oh God.
That's rank.
Bring it back in one piece.
One piece?
That's funny.
Don't let him have this.
Where is my drink?
- You're not going to throw up, are you?
-  You know where my jacket is?
I'll get it. Be right back.
White...
Come here.
- What?
-  It's a secret.
Closer.
Have you always been this beautiful?
-  I'm not done with you.
- You're drunk.
Plus, God knows what they're sticking
into you with those needles.
Tell me the truth.
How bad do you want to fuck me?
Fuck you.
Not so quick, Snow White.
Anything else?
Sometimes you look at me that way.
What way?
That way.
The way you're looking at me now.
Give me that flask, Hunter.
Give me!
- No, I won't.
- Give me.
Give it to me.
Stop... Stop.
- You're ticklish.
- No, I'm not.
No? What's this?
Stop!
If you tickle me again,
I will bite your finger.
Mmh...
I dare you.
June.
What's going on?
Hi.
Nothing, I was checking
he was still breathing.
Do you want to stay in the back
or sit upfront with me?
I want to be with you.
-  Do you need me to walk you inside?
- I'll be fine.
Okay, goodnight.
Night.
- Did I do something wrong?
- I don't know. Did you?
Look, I'm sorry
for whatever has upset you,
but I'm not a mind reader.
So, either you talk to me
or we can end this now.
This whole night
has thrown me for a loop
ever since you showed up
riding on James' bike with James.
I told you I was babysitting his brother.
Yes, but then there was the thing
in the hall when Pietro was harassing you.
- So?
- So, I wanted to save you.
But I look like a total fucking loser
that needs to be rescued by James.
I can fight my own battles.
I don't need James every time.
"Battles"?
What does that make me, a damsel
in distress that needs to be saved?
- June, that's not what I meant.
- That's exactly what you meant.
And as far as James is concerned,
he's passed out in the back of your van.
June, look...
I don't want to debate you.
- I'm sorry I fucked this whole thing up.
- Yeah.
What?
Fuck it.
Maybe...
- Maybe it's better if I'm...
- Yeah, yeah.
Watch your head. Are you okay?
Okay...
Too fast.
- Do I stop?
- No, no.
Are you okay?
Fuck...
I've been out of practise.
- I just came on myself.
- Oh.
-  Fuck it.
Fuck it...
Five minutes
and I can start again.
Start what?
No, I didn't mean...
I don't think we are there yet.
- As in sex? No.
-  No.
- No, not for me, at least.
-  Sure.
- I should probably get him home.
-  Yeah.
Thank you for coming...
for a lovely evening.
God...
- Do you want me to walk you inside?
- No, I'll be fine.
-  Bye.
Fuck it! How could I do that?
Fuck it,
what a dumbass.
Hey,
what have you been up to?
Nothing.
I was waiting up for you.
I must've fallen asleep.
- How was your night?
- Mh...
Pretty uneventful.
I'm sorry about Jordan's older boy.
I shouldn't put you in that situation.
It was fine.
According to Jordan, he's quite the mess.
Do me a favour and stay away from him.
He gives me a bad feeling.
You've got nothing to worry about.
Oh, by the way...
I have to go to Paris on Monday.
Will you be alright on your own?
- Yeah, I'll be fine. I promise.
- Sure? Okay. Thank you.
Thanks.
-  I love you.
-  I love you too.
- Night night, sweetheart.
- Goodnight.
See you in the morning.
Dear journal,
James Hunter continues to be a pig.
So what if Will came on himself,
Will is perfect for me.
So, journal, can you please tell me
why I'm so attracted to the piggy?
What the hell is wrong with me?
I can convince myself to love Will
and hate James.
I just need willpower.
I must be strong, I must...
Oh my God.
Shit.
Put down your hand
and bring down your pants.
Start moving your hand.
Faster.
And stronger.
Let me hear you now.
Louder.
Yes.
You're welcome. Night night.
Over my dead body.
Oh my God, that was amazing.
Not a word.
Good morning, girl.
Oh-oh.
Someone's in a shitty mood today?
- We should not have done that.
- Done what?
- You know exactly what.
- I don't, I blacked out.
Good.
Then I saw this photo
you sent me after your orgasm
and all the memories came back to me.
- Give me that photo! Give me!
- No. No. Nope.
- No.
- Come on!
For the record, I faked it.
- You faked it?
- It's the truth.
There's only one truth, Snow White.
You came thinking of me.
Oh yeah,
you think you're so cool, don't you?
I bet you're proud of yourself,
stealing your best friend's girl.
"Stealing"?
Is that what you think I'm doing?
Listen to me, Snow White,
very carefully.
Everything I do, I do for Will.
What makes you think it wasn't a test
to see if you're worthy of him?
Is that all it was between us? A test?
A test that you failed.
The last thing he needs is a little girl
fucking around with his head.
Can I help you?
Sorry, you can't be in here.
What do you think you're doing?
That's cute.
If you touch me, I scream.
Well, I'm definitely gonna touch you.
And I'm almost positive
you're going to scream.
Where are you going to touch me?
Here.
And...
Interesting.
That's all you've got?
Oh, I'm just getting started.
I love school.
When are Taylor, Poppy and Tiffany
coming back from their trip?
Soon.
I've got the chance
to make my money back.
We're back on.
- When?
- After school.
Only problem is we can't use the club
so we're going to go with the back-up.
- Alright, I'll spread the word.
- And, James...
No more fuck-ups.
Fight's on. Back-up location.
Okay, I'm on it.
Let's go, come on.
Fast! Come on. Move!
We'll set up in that corner,
over there.
What is this place?
- I think it was a bunker in World War II.
- Oh.
Land mine!
Hilarious.
Oh my God,
you should have seen your face.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Feels different.
- Is it the same stuff?
- Nope, that's better.
Trust me.
- Always have.
- I know.
So, how much money is on the fight?
-  Over 6,000.
-  Very good.
Hey, what are you doing?
Nothing.
Alright, let's do this.
What a coincidence.
Should we go?
Hunter! Hunter! Hunter!
Let's go, bro! As usual!
You're going to wish you were dead.
You're my bitch! You hear me?
You're nothing but a bitch!
Hunter! Hunter!
-  Ready?
-  Kill him!
-  Fight!
-  Go, Pietro!
That's enough!
James! That's enough!
Who's the bitch now?
Stand up!
Whoa.
My champion! James Hunter!
Great, buddy. Great fight.
What's up?
- I'm fine.
- You're not fine.
You're having a reaction to the steroids.
Let me guess, your body itches,
you're feeling nauseous.
I feel...
- What are you, a doctor?
- Shut up.
You're about one-eighty.
- Is that good?
- No.
Here, drink this.
You need the electrolytes.
How could you know so much about this?
My brother
was involved in steroids.
- I didn't know you had a brother.
- Had.
It's not something I like to talk about.
-  Hey! Hey! How many times...
- He's having a reaction!
To whatever you doped him up with.
What have you doped him up with?
Is it Trenbolone Acetate
or Testosterone Cypionate?
I don't know.
You don't know!
How fucking stupid are you?
What did you say? Say it again.
-  Austin, chill.
- She can't fucking talk to me that way.
- Give us a minute.
- I'm not going anywhere.
Get out.
Now.
Alright, I'll go get the car.
I don't like that guy.
I think the feeling is mutual.
You're lucky you're a girl.
Oh. So, you think this is my fault?
He should be apologising,
and you should be thanking me.
It's not funny.
This whole macho thing is bullshit.
What's that?
It's the after party.
-  Hi.
-  Hi. Did you see June?
No, not since the fight.
- Okay.
- Bye.
-  Hey.
-  Hi.
Hi!
Will, let's go to dance. Come on!
I'll join you in a moment.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm okay. I'm okay.
You sure?
Alright. Oh, have you seen June?
- No.
- Where did she go?
Alright.
Anyways... See you on the dance floor!
Fuck it.
Do you know what you're doing?
I've done this many times before.
Ninety-five.
It would be lower
if you weren't touching me that way.
I can stop.
I don't want you to stop.
Ari.
Are you okay?
I'm fucking amazing.
You're not drinking, are you?
What do you think, huh?
I don't know.
You taste so good.
- Will.
- You smell like chocolate.
Will... What the fuck, Will?
No one wants me!
No one.
Will!
You don't have to stay with me.
Do you want me to leave?
I don't.
This is wrong.
What is it about you...
What is it about you?
Bro.
We've got a problem.
Everyone, get out!
Did you hear?
Get out of the way. The party is over.
Come on, go away!
You're okay, Will.
Fuck off!
I'll follow you on his bike.
Let's get him home so he's safe.
Okay, no worries.
Take my bike to your place.
I'll pick it up
as soon as I drop him off.
-  Is he going to be okay?
- I'll explain later.
I got you.
You're okay.
Miss White.
You startled me.
What are you doing here?
I need to talk to you about James.
Tell me what he told you about me.
Nothing.
You're his trainer.
I'm also his step-father.
James is very, very important to me.
The last thing I need is for some cute
piece of ass to come between us.
Okay.
Now I can see why the boys
are so enamoured with you.
You're very, very pretty.
May I come in for a moment?
I don't think that's... My mum is asleep.
Your mum?
I rang the doorbell, and no one answered.
So, we are all alone.
Oh...
Shame on me.
I made you sad.
Just keep
this our little secret.
Okay?
Maybe I'll come back later.
Miss White.
Hi, it's April.
Please leave a message...
Shit.
The police are on their way.
You should leave.
Can I get my bike keys back?
Hunter.
Are you alright? Was it something I said?
Do you take sugar, Hunter?
What are you doing in that?
If I'm going to be your bodyguard,
I have to dress the part.
You don't have to stay.
I can fend for myself.
Don't be stupid.
I can crash on the sofa.
Just don't try to take advantage of me
in my sexy new robe.
Are you going to tell me
what happened with Will tonight?
I don't think so.
Are you going to tell me
who threatened you?
No one threatened me.
Tell me what happened.
- You really do care about him, don't you?
- I care about a lot of things.
Tell me what happened with him tonight.
He's just going through some stuff.
We're all going through stuff.
What are you protecting him from?
Himself.
You know that girl, Ari?
- Yeah?
- Well, they used to be a thing.
Pretty serious. Then shit happened.
Will started getting too possessive and...
And Ari just broke things off.
He spiralled.
What do you mean, "spiralled"?
Look, he's fine now.
He has just to stay off things
that complicate his life.
Things like me?
Something like that.
- Does he know that you are doing this?
- Hell no.
Everything I do, I do for Will.
For Will?
Not for James?
He's like a brother to me.
I owe him my life.
- What do we have here?
-  What are you doing?
My turn to ask the questions.
Don't be cruel.
You liked cookies, huh?
Yeah, I still do, I'll have you know.
- I bet you were bossy.
- I was.
Is this your brother?
Yeah.
How long ago...
Almost two years now.
He was the one who taught me
how to ride a motorbike.
We were inseparable.
May I ask what happened?
One of his teammates
introduced him to steroids
and I guess steroids
turned into harder substances.
We were out driving.
He must have been on something...
and we had an accident.
I couldn't save him.
I'm sorry.
What a waste.
Fuck.
You'd think I'd stop getting
so emotional over this.
June, I'm really sorry about your brother.
But the stuff Austin gives me...
is entirely safe.
He just wants me to perform
at my maximum ability.
I'm not your mum.
You've got to do what you've got to do.
- God, you're frustrating.
- Why? Because I care?
You're better than that.
And how would you know?
You think everyone in this life
wants to use you.
And I use them right back.
Everything in life is a negotiation.
Do you think friends, relationships...
is all transactions?
One hundred percent.
- Love should be an unconditional feeling.
- It should.
But it's not. Never.
"Never"?
You're going in a dangerous direction.
As if you don't like danger.
I do.
But this is too much.
Even for me.
James?
Go to sleep.
I'll leave in the morning.
Are you sure?
Trust me, this is going to end badly.
Goodnight.
Please...
June, what are you doing?
Late night, huh?
Well, I have good news.
After you destroyed Pietro,
I can get you better fights.
We are going to make you a champ, J.
What happened
with you and June last night?
What are you talking about?
Did she say something to you?
I don't trust that bitch.
No, she didn't.
But you did.
Hey, hey... Hands on me?
- J., come on!
- You stay the fuck away from her.
Alright, take your hands off me.
I'm through with your fucking steroids.
Really?
You and I... we are done.
Come on, cool off and then we'll talk. J.!
Cool off and then we'll talk. J.!
J., cool off and then we'll talk!
-  This?
-  No.
-  Come on, it looks beautiful.
- Maybe.
Yeah, I thought it would go well
with my Ferragamos.
June? Opinion?
June?
Earth to June?
Sorry, what? What did you say?
My dress for my birthday party.
-  Yeah, that's beautiful.
- I know.
Brian got them for me in Paris.
My dad's a professor
and Brian's visiting him right now.
He's coming back next week.
Dramarama.
Oh, guys. Just... excuse me one minute.
James.
Thanks again for last night.
Last night never happened. Got that?
Nothing did happen...
Is everything okay?
- I can't do this with you.
- You can't...
You can't... do what with me?
- Hey!
- Hi.
Hi.
I missed you.
-  How are you feeling?
- Awesome. Last night was crazy.
Yeah...
Listen, I have to get to class, but...
Why don't I take you shopping
this afternoon
and buy you a dress for Amelia's party?
- Hmm?
- You don't have to do that.
I know I don't have to do that,
but I want to.
I'm going to make you happy.
Okay.
You're mine.
- Happy birthday!
- Thank you.
Wow, you've really outdone yourself.
I know! I know! I know!
Here are our drinks.
Here you go.
What is it?
It's called
a Dirty Little Virgin.
Taste it.
Oh, he's with Ari. Okay...
You can go and say hi to him.
I am not threatened.
I don't want to say hi.
I'm here with you.
- You sure?
- Absolutely.
I am borrowing her to dance.
No, I can't.
My mum said I'm only allowed one.
It's my birthday.
What are you doing?
Texting your mum.
Telling her you are staying over.
She's out of town. She won't...
There's no point.
Too late.
Don't be lame!
- Okay, okay.
- Have fun! Have fun!
Have fun.
- Are you coming?
-  Yeah, I'll be there in a minute.
- You got eyes on the birthday girl?
- She's with June, dancing.
♪ Hi, I'm a slut ♪
♪ I do what I want, I don't give a fuck ♪
♪ It doesn't matter if your dick's cut ♪
♪ Always swallow, I hear it's good luck ♪
♪ Hi, I'm a giant whore... ♪
June and James...
Oh my God.
One more! Come on!
She's so hot.
I can see why you want her.
I don't know who you're talking about.
Yes, you do.
-  Where did you get this?
- It doesn't matter.
It's not what you think.
Come on, man.
Can't you let me have this one thing?
Can you do that, just this once?
I never denied you anything.
I was keeping her from you to protect you
from what happened with Ari.
Okay, so you're telling me
you have no feelings for June, right?
Yeah.
- Wanker.
- Will...
Will!
June.
- Tell me what you want.
- What are you doing, Will?
You're made for each other.
♪ Hi, I'm a slut ♪
♪ I do what I want,
I don't give a fuck... ♪
- How did they get this?
- How would I know?
That's so fucked up.
How could you do this to Will?
You should leave.
Get out!
Oh my God. I just saw.
- Are you okay?
-  What do you think?
Will!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Don't you know what he's been through?
Oh, please! Like you've got
nothing to do with this!
What are you accusing me of?
Photoshopping that?
These are photos of me!
This is humiliating!
I'm not your scapegoat, June.
White!
Who made that video?
We've never even kissed.
Can I get you some medicine or water?
I'm okay.
Thank you for taking care of me.
It's my pleasure.
I'll crash in the guest room.
James, will you stay with me?
I don't want to be on my own.
I'll deal with her in the morning.
Thank you.
Everything will be alright.
Hey!
Hey, June! I'm home!
What the fuck?
June, get up!
Get up!
Are you going to talk to me?
Nothing happened.
How would you know that?
You were drunk.
Because I trust him
like you should trust me!
Why would I do that,
when everything that's come out
of your mouth has been a lie?
That's not true!
Have you any idea
of the damage you have done?
Jordan is my boss.
I asked you to babysit his youngest son,
not shag his eldest!
It's not fair.
Great, let's hope I still have a career
and we still have somewhere to live.
Amelia.
-  Good morning.
-  Have fun?
-  Oh, yes.
We'll be talking about this one for ages.
Oh, my battery died.
Do you mind if I take your phone
and call a taxi?
Yeah, sure.
- Do you want a water?
- No, I'm good.
Okay.
Oh... Amelia.
You promised to behave this year.
You good?
It's all good.
♪ Hi, I'm a giant whore ♪
♪ I've got boys and girls
always at my door... ♪
Mum?
- Blaze.
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
I have something to tell you.
That's it! Fight's over!
Yeah! Yeah!
Come on!
That's it! That's it!
You know who you are?
You are the one guy
that can take James fucking Hunter down.
Nobody will think you can win.
That's exactly why I'm putting
all my money on you to come through.
Hey, you okay?
I'm gonna pound him
to the fucking ground.
You got this.
Any problem?
Good.
And now
I present to you with its debut...
Will Cooper!
This is
all your fucking doing.
- I'm not going to fight him.
- That's your fucking problem, baby boy.
Fight! Fight! Fight!
What are you fucking doing?
I won't fight you!
Fight!
You're dead!
Will, please!
- Fuck you!
- Stop it, Will!
I'll fucking kill you!
If she thinks I fly economy,
she can fuck herself.
Ew.
You're not seriously
showing your face here.
Oh, shit!
Will! Stop it!
Stop the fight!
Will! Stop the fight!
Get rid of her!
No! Put me down!
Put me down!
Get in there!
Fuck you!
- Go, Will!
- Go!
Take him out! Take him out!
Fucking kill him!
What the fuck? No! No! Stay!
Please, leave the club,
keep calm and follow the emergency.
Stay! Fucking stay! It's not over!
My fucking money!
Attention, please
evacuate the premises calmly.
Grab him
before the police arrive.
Hey! Hey!
See how you like it!
Hurry.
Come on.
James!
Shit!
Will.
- I need your bike.
- For what?
For James.
Fuck off, June! What are you doing?
James would save you
if the roles were reversed.
I thought you two were like brothers.
Get out of my way.
No, wait!
June! June!
-  What are we gonna do with him?
-  I don't know.
I don't want him talking to the police
about our business.
Slow down.
Fuck you!
What the fuck?
We lost them.
Fuck!
Stop the car!
James!
Wait... Come here.
I got him.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Drop me here, please.
So, that happened.
Do you need me
to call you an ambulance?
You've done enough already.
So, I guess this means we're good?
Not even close.
Are you serious?
No, you've suffered enough.
Fuck you, Will.
I love you too, James Hunter.
You guys need a moment? A room?
You're still here?
Yeah, I saved your fucking life, you prat.
Whatever.
To quote Shakespeare,
"all's well that ends well".
Seems fitting.
We escaped death, Will forgave us,
and James and I
may finally get to have our first kiss.