She's still bleeding.
Stats?
Not good at all.
The blood pressure is very low.
Can you call Dr Geetika Sen, please?
It's urgent.
All personnel to emergency.
Code blue, code blue.
- Kate, I am leaving.
- Okay, ma'am.
All nurses to the nurses' station.
Code blue, code blue.
- Ma'am. Ma'am. Ma'am.
- Yeah?
- Emergency in Dr Cooper's surgery.
- What happened?
C-section delivery. Severe bleeding.
Post-part um haemorrhage.
Okay. Okay, calm down.
- We need you. We need you.
- Okay.
Coming, coming. I am coming.
I am coming.
Scissors.
Doctor, the patient has a history
of bleeding disorder.
Same thing happened last time
Stop. You have already made a mess here.
Napkin.
- Here you go.
- So nice.
It was just magical.
Cheers, guys.
- Hi. Cheers.
- Cheers.
She will come.
She should have been here by now.
She is a doctor.
She's allowed a few minutes delay.
It's okay.
Few minutes?
Your sister is two hours late.
And Meera is a doctor as well.
Yes, but
But when we were dating,
she would come two hours early.
- Even you used to turn up late.
- I still do.
- So what?
- Hi.
- One has no choice after marriage.
- Thank God, you're here.
- Looking gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- Who is he?
- Must be a friend.
Great job, ma'am.
Doctor.
Thank you.
I observed everything. And that was…
There are a few things
I know I should have probably…
It's okay.
Can you have the patient's files
sent to my cabin, please?
Let me take it from here.
It's nothing personal, Dr Cooper.
I think it's best for the patient.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Don't go by the colour. It's not spicy.
- You speak Hindi?
- Yes.
Angad, this is Sophie.
The Sophiana Spice Kitchen
that is on Central Street belongs to her.
I am sure you must have seen it.
To be honest, I haven't seen it.
But I do know that the Angara Kebabs
from Sophiana Spice Kitchen are not spicy.
Correct.
I will see you.
You have been threatening me
with a surprise all week now.
Can you finally tell me
what the surprise is?
You have waited for so many days.
Might as well wait a bit more.
Geetika should be here soon.
- Hello.
- Where were you?
She is here.
Geetu!
- Hello, hello.
- Hi.
Sorry. So sorry, guys.
I was late getting here.
In fact, Auntie Anju came from Manchester
and managed to arrive before me.
But, now that I have finally arrived,
let me tell you all
that this is the last party in this house.
New house?
New city, Disha.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah.
I have been transferred
to the Chester branch
of Chapelstone General Hospital.
It's not just a transfer.
She got a promotion.
They are appointing Geetika
as the dean of the hospital.
- I have said so before. Superior genes.
- Thank you.
Yeah, yeah. Right.
So, this was the good news.
I imagined a different kind
of "good news".
Actually, we do have your kind of
"good news" as well, Auntie Anju.
Because
Meera and I…
Are adopting a baby.
That's great! Congratulations!
Come on! Wow!
- Oh, my God!
- Congratulations!
- Oh, my God, that's great!
- Nice!
- This is the new house.
- Nice. This is good.
- Lovely.
- And that's the baby.
Oh, my God, such a cute baby.
Meera, you are going to make a great mom.
Listen, isn't that Sophie?
Why did Geetika invite her?
Prateek, that's not for you to comment on.
Which Sophie are you talking about?
You don't know?
Oh.
She is that Sophie?
Yes. Geetika's ex.
I will be back in a minute.
- Why did you have to say that?
- She was right in front…
Hi, Mom.
Where have you been, Meera?
It's been two days since we spoke.
Mom, I spoke to you just yesterday.
"Hi, Mom, I am busy now."
That is not a conversation.
- And what's the noise in the background?
- We're having a party.
- Why?
- Geetika got a promotion.
Oh, wow. My congratulations to her.
Now that she has been promoted,
ask her to get her own house.
Mom, this is Geetika's house.
Then why don't you get one for yourself?
We can look for a groom for you
in London if you want.
It's been three years
since you've been in London.
Can I talk to you tomorrow, Mom?
If you threw a party,
you should have called Rohit as well.
Both of you could have met each other
and your brother would have
enjoyed an outing.
Mom, I am meeting Rohit tomorrow.
- Okay.
- Speak to you later, okay? Bye.
Geetu.
Why is Simran
calling you in so early today?
I'm not sure.
She didn't say anything on the phone.
Perhaps it's something serious.
This evening is what is
going to be serious.
When Rohit meets you.
Nervous?
No.
A little?
No. You?
A little.
Come on.
You never told me.
- What?
- Last night at the party…
She is the same Sophie, right?
Your ex.
I didn't want to
spoil your mood at the party.
Why would it spoil my mood?
Of all the Indian restaurants in the city,
I had to go and hire Sophie.
You did good.
Everyone loved the food, right?
Yeah.
Looks like her restaurant is quite famous.
27,000 followers. Wow.
You are following her?
I am not.
You are.
It's just that I never unfollowed her.
Simran?
Yes. Yeah, I get it. I am coming. Okay.
- Okay, baby.
- Bye.
Bye. See you in the evening. Bye.
- Hello.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
- Morning, Dr Logan.
- Dr Sen.
- Long day?
- Every day.
- Hi, Emily.
- Hi.
Thanks.
- Morning.
Camera 24A.
Disabled.
- 24B?
- Done.
I know what you are going to say.
"Thanks for the surgery, but I can't
send you the patient file." Right?
Did Cooper file a complaint?
Coffee?
No, thanks.
What's going on?
I am not allowed to share this with you,
but I think you should see this.
What rubbish is this?
- Hi.
- Hi. Your table for three.
Thank you.
Sit here.
Table for three?
I want to introduce you to someone.
But you have to promise me one thing.
- That you will keep an open mind.
- Okay.
You are the first one from Meerut
I am sharing this with.
I see.
- Sorry, guys. I am a little late.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- I am good.
- Hello.
- Hi.
So, this is Angad.
-And he is–
-And he is your favourite cousin, Rohit.
And the first person from Meerut
who knows about the two of you.
No, silly.
We are doctors at the same clinic.
That is not a secret.
Sorry. I actually thought…
Don't worry.
Even I thought the same thing at first.
The board will now begin an investigation.
You already know the hospital procedure.
But you shouldn't do anything, Geetika.
You don't know anything about all this.
Okay?
So? Last two weeks?
The merchant navy exams are next week.
I see. And then India?
Yes, back to good old Meerut.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT??
Then I will just wait
for the selections to go through.
All the best, man.
I am really happy to have met you.
I would love to see you again
before I leave.
Of course. Whenever Meera decides.
WILL MEET HIM NEXT TIME…
I think I should get going, guys.
- So, I will see you later.
- Stay.
Again?
I will introduce you another day. Okay?
Why? What happened?
I didn't tell Rohit anything.
Meera…
I have always treated your family
as my own.
-Your every–
-Something happened, Meera.
HR has received
a complaint.
There have been complaints before, right?
People have said
all kinds of things about you.
Strict. Stern. Rude.
Yeah, but no one had called me
a sexual predator till now.
"Routine breast examination."
"Dr Sen has preyed on vulnerable women"
"describe as sexual molestation.
This behaviour is predatory…"
"Anonymous?"
Who is this?
Good morning, Gracey.
Good morning.
- Meera.
- Hi, sir.
Riverkings Children's Hospital
is looking for doctors.
I know you've resigned, you're relocating,
but you'd be perfect for the job.
You don't have to answer right away.
Think about it.
Riverkings is the best in the city.
Okay. Sure.
Guys.
- Huh. Nice.
- Oh! You got published?
- Congratulations.
- Thank you so much, Max.
I will have someone arrange a cake.
Is that for me or for you?
Always for me.
Read it and let me know.
Yeah, sure.
- By the way, congratulations.
- Thank you.
Meera.
Is everything okay?
You saw?
Only "sexual harassment."
Did something happen?
A complaint has been filed
against Geetika.
Some patient. It is anonymous.
Nothing to worry about.
I was checking what the HR policy says
under the circumstances.
Okay.
We have circulated the policy statement
in the hospital.
We are encouraging all the employees
to come forward
if they have anything to share.
Don't worry.
Your name will not be made public in this.
It basically states
that an incident has been reported,
which is the reason we want to reaffirm,
this hospital is committed
to providing a safe environment
Safe environment for all of its employees…
Free from sexual harassment.
I am sharing my story on a public forum
because I want everyone to know.
I was Dr Geetika Sen's trusting patient
and this is what she did to me.
"I trusted Dr Geetika Sen,
but she violated
the sacred doctor-patient clause."
What the fuck? Martina?
Anne, I'm done. You can help her clean up.
"She examined me
without wearing any gloves."
So, there is a slight complication.
We will have to induce lab our.
C-section. Within 24 hours.
- "I was so scared."
- Will I be fine?
Yes, of course. You will be fine.
Your baby will be fine. I will be there.
I trust you, Doctor.
"She made me feel uncomfortable
with her touch."
I'll see you guys in my cabin.
"She's a predator."
Dr Sen!
I am sorry about all this.
- "About all this"?
- I read those comments on social media.
Anyone with a phone
feels they are empowered with a voice.
Don't let this affect you.
And you know what they say
about good surgeons.
Their hands never shake.
Hi.
I got dinner.
I cooked.
Burnt garlic noodles with
spicy cottage cheese. Your favourite.
And your favourite,
potato with okra and seasoned lentils.
Geetu, I researched the HR policies.
Your hospital follows the Equality Act.
-For the–
-Prevention Of Sexual Harassment.
Pass me the noodles.
But it does not mean
that anyone can say anything anonymously.
Section 27 says, "Making
a false allegation in bad faith is not"
Meera,
can we talk about something else, please?
I saw what you just did.
What did I do?
You mixed the burnt garlic noodles
with the potato and okra.
Guilty.
- I did that.
- Really?
- And you should try it.
- No.
- Come on. Try it.
- No, no, no, no. I'm not trying this.
You never stop surprising me.
- Negacin has been given?
- Yes, ma'am. I will check it again.
Ma'am, Dr Cooper
is taking over the surgery.
What? What do you mean?
I just heard.
I think, whatever you need from us…
How can you change the surgery
at the last minute
It was requested by the patient's husband.
We had to change the doctor.
-But Martina has been my patient–
-It's a routine procedure, Geetika.
Dr Cooper will take over.
The hospital has even approved
your application for paid leave.
I'm sorry?
Geetika, in light of the allegations,
and the need
to keep the investigation impartial,
the Board has appointed Mr Bhargav.
And, Ms Geetika,
your presence in the hospital
will make it difficult
to keep the investigation impartial.
How long will this paid leave last?
A week, perhaps ten days, give or take.
I should be able to find out by then
if you are innocent or guilty.
I am sorry. Jaideep Bhargav.
Mr Bhargav is an ex-journalist
and fairly experienced in such cases.
Thank you for that.
To be honest,
despite so many years of experience,
I am a little nervous.
Actually, this is a first.
Normally, the women are victims,
but in this case
In this case, too, a woman is the victim.
Seems friendly.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, I will get this checked. Sure.
Dr Cooper, just wanted to tell you,
before Mrs Davis's surgery,
she has high blood pressure.
She's been on
Yeah. Don't worry, Doctor.
I got this. Yeah.
I know what's best for the patient.
I appreciate it. Thank you.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Okay. Have a good day.
My reputation is on the line, Simran.
You told me
that the enquiry was just a formality.
Is involving an outside investigator
also a formality?
It was a formality
when there was just one complaint.
Now there are two more emails.
Staff, interns, patients…
I don't know what they're saying.
They are all lying. Obviously.
Then let the truth come out.
You were confident till yesterday that
nothing will come out of this enquiry.
Nothing will come out, right?
- Geetika?
- Geetu?
Just a minute.
I will call you back.
Yeah?
Did you withdraw £5,000
from our joint account?
Yeah.
Well…
Nurse Lizzy's son
didn't get a scholarship.
It's a loan. She will pay it back.
Why do you ask?
You could have transferred it.
Why did you give it in cash?
What difference does that make, Meera?
Sorry, I am a little busy. One sec, I…
Geetu, how long
is this enquiry going to last?
I don't know.
What do you mean, you don't know?
Aren't you worried?
All the complaints are anonymous,
so there's nothing to worry about.
In the last ten years,
almost 50% of doctors and nurses
under Dr Sen have quit their jobs.
And your signature is
on all the exit letters.
Geetika has
a slightly different way of working.
She creates an atmosphere of criticism,
whereas young doctors need encouragement.
I tried talking to HR once, but…
I signed because that is my job,
not because Geetika is my friend.
HR operates based on
the hospital's rule book, Mr Bhargav.
And you can check.
All the cases were resolved and closed.
This does not have
Dr Martin Cooper's report.
He did tell you about
Geetika's harsh behaviour, didn't he?
What's happening?
Weren't you going to
drop me to the hospital?
That van is following us.
But why would anyone follow us?
You just said there is nothing
to worry about.
Yeah, but there were some comments
on the hospital's social media page
with my name on it.
What?
Yeah.
IT took them down, but clearly,
people must have read them.
Hang on.
Hey.
It was definitely following me.
There is an email
from the adoption agency.
Says it's urgent.
They scheduled a meeting at 2:00 p.m.
I have a surgery, Meera.
- I can't.
- And the baby?
Dr Geetika doesn't single out anyone.
She's always been the same.
Except… Except once.
Natasha.
Natasha
was an intern in the Radiology department,
around five or six years back. I think
Five years and two months.
A senior doctor. A young intern.
It must have been
a matter of concern for you, no?
We do not encourage office romances.
And when I found out about it
Sorry, but did you find out about it
or did Dr Sen tell you about it?
I found out.
Then there might be other cases
that you may not even be aware of.
Nazia, can you please talk to them once?
- You guys can't do that to us.
- It is not my decision, ma'am.
Your case manager decided on it
because you failed your background check.
How is that possible?
The background check must have
told you that
Dr Geetika Sen is the best doctor
in that hospital.
And you also know
she is best in whatever she does.
You are being unfair not just towards us,
but towards the baby as well.
With us, the baby will be happy.
Please trust me
The baby has found a family.
Your coffee, sir.
Chapelstone Hospital has
set up an enquiry.
I know.
They are investigating you.
Why did you want to meet me?
See, whatever happened between us
That's ancient history.
Yeah, but you had to leave your job
because of me. So…
If you feel that I am involved in this,
in any way, then let me clarify.
I have moved on from there.
Right.
Look, I need a favour from you.
It is possible that your name
might come up in the enquiry.
And they might even call you.
They might want to know
whatever happened between us.
If you could just…
Please just say, "No comment." You know?
I should go.
Wait.
Look, can I… can I trust you on this?
No comment.
Thanks for coming on such short notice.
Of course.
Meera, I hope you don't misunderstand me,
but if I were in your place,
I would definitely talk to Mansoor.
Mansoor?
We were in school together.
He was my senior.
He is now a private investigator.
Meera?
Shut up.
All okay?
Yeah.
Someone broke into the house.
- Someone was in the house?
- Yeah.
- Who?
- I don't know.
I don't know, but we should check
in case something is missing.
Give me two minutes. Let me just…
Don't you want to know
what the adoption agency said?
Baby, you are not listening.
Someone was in our house.
Geetu, what happened?
The door was open.
Maybe the lock isn't working.
The lock is working. I checked. It's fine.
Maybe it was left open by mistake.
You are getting paranoid.
I am getting paranoid?
I am imagining all of this?
-No, that's not what I meant–
-Listen,
I know what the agency told you, Meera.
They emailed me as well.
I failed the background check.
And I also know why.
Because there are four emails
in Simran's mailbox,
and another three in the complaint box.
All of this is real, Meera,
not my imagination.
I have spent 14 years
building my reputation
and it's falling apart
in front of my eyes.
You don't understand
because you don't have
Yeah, right.
I will not understand.
I do not have your reputation.
You are up pretty early.
Auntie woke me up.
She has called three times
since yesterday.
"Son, haven't you given
the pickles to Meera yet?"
Mom sent lemon pickles for me?
And ginger pickles, too.
Are you busy?
No, I am just making some coffee.
Okay.
In that case,
should we plan to meet today?
Hello?
Sis.
Yes, we can meet. I am free this evening.
Okay, great.
Will you message me the time?
Can you just hold on a second?
Someone's at the door.
- Rohit?
- And the plan is made.
- Can I come in?
- Come in.
This…
The two of you…
But we thought she was your flatmate.
Didn't you have a boyfriend in school?
Everyone on her side knows?
Coffee?
No matter how much you search,
you won't find anything on social media.
Geetika prefers to
keep her private life private.
"Geetika was showing me the wall of art,
when, suddenly, leaned into a kiss."
I wanted to stop, but she pinned my arms
on her chequered couch.
She pulled out a bottle of wine
from the red refrigerator in the kitchen.
We were both tipsy when
she started getting frisky.
"I froze and all I remember
are the hanging lights over me."
Geetika said
all the comments had been deleted.
Then this?
Hi. Come on in.
We get on just fine.
In fact, Dr Sen is on good terms
with all the HODs.
- Management, HR, Oncology…
- Yeah.
Sir, I have only been here for six months.
Seven.
Dr Sen keeps her personal
and professional life separate.
- Having said that, you have to try to…
- Kate.
I need ten minutes with Geetika.
Can you check if she's available?
Dr Meera, Dr Sen is on leave.
Since Monday.
Oh.
Okay.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Those are invites.
Only for very close friends.
The restaurant
will be a year old next week.
- I have planned a small get-together.
- Nice.
Will you come?
Oh.
One second.
You know how my secretary is.
She calls up without checking first.
It was Meera calling, right?
What did you tell her?
That there is an emergency?
You used to say the same thing
to me as well,
when you used to meet Meera, didn't you?
Sophie.
There were a lot of problems between us.
And when I met Meera,
this was all over.
It was over for you.
You never even asked me.
Anyway, now…
Thanks for this.
Dr Meera!
Ms Meera. Ma'am!
Ma'am, one moment.
Sorry to accost you like this.
Jaideep Bhargav.
Hi.
Ma'am, if you can give me
two minutes of your time,
I can clear up a few things
I am confused about.
What kind of confusion?
See, the people here do not know anything
about Ms Geetika's personal life and home.
And you don't know anything
about what goes on here.
Didn't Ms Geetika tell you
that she has been on leave?
Does she truly keep her personal
and professional life so separate that
The truth is that I do not have
to tell you anything.
Actually, I am meeting her tomorrow.
So, you don't worry. I will ask her
directly.
What are you looking for?
How was the surgery?
Good.
How was your day?
Rohit came by.
He was trying to appear cool,
but he was quite shocked.
He started Googling you.
Then he didn't even try to appear cool.
There is a lot of dirt about you
on social media, Geetika.
IT removed the comments.
Yes, but somebody put stuff up again.
I tried calling you,
but you didn't pick up my call.
-The thing is, my battery–
-You were not in surgery.
Kate told me.
There was some man named Bhargav.
He started questioning me.
"Why didn't Geetika tell you
that she is on leave?"
So, why did you not tell me?
I didn't say anything,
but everyone knows everything anyway.
And they are assuming
whatever they want to assume.
- No one wants to know what the truth is.
- What is the truth, Geetika?
If I ask where you've been going,
will you tell me the truth?
You want to know where I've been going,
or whether I actually did something?
Geetu, I am not accusing you.
In fact, I feel
we should hire a private investigator.
Angad has a friend. He is a very good
What will the private investigator find?
Exactly what is it
that you want to know, Meera?
Why people are saying
Isn't my word enough for you?
What you say isn't always the truth.
Fine. You go ahead
and hire the private investigator.
And while you are at it, tell him to find
one more thing you've lost. Your mind.
Dr Geetika, you have a stellar record.
You have the hospital's busiest OPD.
You are the youngest HOD.
You are also about to become
the youngest dean. Congratulations.
The highest revenue in the hospital
also comes from your department.
You must be their favourite.
What is your question?
The question is,
despite all this,
why don't people last in your department?
Because when junior doctors make
a mistake, I do not pat them on the back.
Right. If doctors start making mistakes,
what will become of the patients?
What mistake did Dr Natasha Khilnani make?
Where is that document? Ah.
She did four surgeries with you.
Everything went off smoothly.
But then, six months later,
why did she drop her internship and leave?
Actually, I know the answer to that, too.
Both of you got romantically involved.
And somehow, ma'am came to know about it.
To avoid a conflict of interest,
one of us was advised to quit.
But what connection does it have
to this enquiry?
There is a connection, ma'am.
Natasha had to leave the job, not you.
Because you were her boss, her senior.
You were the head of the department.
The connection is with power.
Power that is used, as well as abused.
Are you saying
that I took advantage of my position?
Natasha certainly didn't get
any advantage.
How old was she when this…
- What was her age? About 26?
- So?
Oh, I don't know.
I also met Dr Meera. She is quite young.
There must be an age difference of, what,
around 10 to 12 years between you two?
Are you suggesting
that I like younger girls?
- Mr Bhargav…
- That I have a type or something…Simran?
When did I suggest that?
You are the one saying it.
Fine. Are we done?
I suppose the meeting is done.
The investigation is just getting started.
You said you just wanted to talk.
You started to interrogate instead.
One interrogates criminals.
Whereas here it feels like
there was no crime committed at all.
The results do show
that the boys were more likely
to have seasonal allergies
than the girls, but overall,
in children, it reduces the swelling,
and should be relatively safe.
Meera?
Sir, is Riverkings Children's Hospital
still looking for doctors?
Meera, you didn't tell me
that you changed your mind.
So, you are not leaving the city?
Angad, that friend of yours,
the private investigator?
Mansoor.
I'd like to meet him.
Okay. I will give him a call.
Perhaps you are forgetting that, so far,
all the complaints are anonymous.
I know that. But the interviews of
the former employees are still pending.
But I have known such investigations
to suddenly turn around.
Someone sends an email. Someone agrees
to divulge their name in an interview.
Or, in this case, some woman.
Sorry, I didn't mean to be condescending.
Then your "alleged" and "anonymous"
will fly out of the window,
and we will be left with
"accusations" and "accused".
- Hello.
- I am Dr Carol Simmons.
I have a meeting with Mr Bhargav.
Right.
And what should I say this is about?
I was sexually harassed in this hospital
by Dr Geetika Sen.
An incident report was filed by you
last year on the 19th of November.
Dr Carol Simmons.
Anaesthetist.
Please, help yourselves.
- And some for you?
- Thanks.
- Here, have some. Please.
- Carol.
Carol!
I am getting married next week, ma'am.
Carol, this morning
you have punctured my patient's dura
with your epidural needle.
I am very sorry, ma'am.
My patient is experiencing extreme nausea.
She has not been able to walk
in I don't know how many days.
She can't nurse her new-born.
I really don't understand
how this happened.
Carol, this is not the first time
this has happened.
I am very sorry, but I am going to have
to recommend terminating your services.
They will be completing your formalities.
Dr Geetika
asked me out for a coffee once.
And I was uncomfortable with that.
I refused. Politely.
After that, she started picking on me.
Can that be verified?
Are there any witnesses?
Have you spoken of it to anyone?
Dr Simmons, please just understand
the delicate nature of this case.
So, try and state whatever you can,
that I can cross-check.
I have a text message
from the other night.
Take me to Harlton Inn Hotel, please.
May I see it?
- Here.
- You called her to a five-star hotel?
It's not what it looks like.
Let's plan.
She kept calling me over and over again.
It was Prateek's anniversary that day.
We were all celebrating
at the Harlton Inn.
This can all be verified.
That's not the point, Geetika.
You publicly humiliated an employee.
Then after that, sent her a text message
inviting her to a hotel.
You see how this looks?
What she wanted was for us
to take out the word "negligence"
from her termination letter.
Ma'am, please.
If you could just remove
that one word, "negligence."
I am sorry, but it is not in my hands.
I just told her,
"It's not in my hands." That's all.
She told me,
"We can check into
one of the rooms here at the hotel
and sort everything out."
Okay. Would you like to, maybe,
just go and sit in one of these rooms
and perhaps talk it out?
And that day, there was no one there
except the two of you.
That's her word against mine.
In situations like this, the Board
recommends going with the victim.
I think it's time
you hire a good lawyer, Geetika.
Excuse me? Hello?
Stop! Why are you following me?
Hey! What's wrong with you?
- Hey!
- I am sorry.
- What the hell?
- Why are you following me?
Are you all right, Dr Sen?
Do you need help?
We are just podcasters, ma'am,
working on some material.
Just gathering some information.
Yeah, about you and some other
sex offenders in the neighbourhood.
Watch it.
Sorry, ma'am.
If I see you again,
I am calling the police, okay?
Watch out. Get out of here now.
Pass it.
Pass, Ziad, pass.
Don't hold on to the ball.
How are you?
About eight or ten
alleged victims, Mansoor.
And the comments keep flooding
social media.
What do you feel about it?
Geetika and I met two years back.
If it wasn't for Geetika, I would still be
suffocating in some closet
in a small town.
No, no, no, no, no.
I mean, what do you feel about this case?
All the questions
They don't pass.
Sorry.
I have partial answers
to all the questions.
I know that Geetika isn't
going to the hospital.
But where she is going…
She is meeting Sophie. Why is she
meeting her? What is she hiding?
I just don't know.
Sophie is Geetika's ex.
If I tie up these questions
with my suspicion…
Then my suspicion will become my reality.
What do you want to know about,
the sexual misconduct or the cheating?
The truth.
£200 per day.
Food and fuel will be charged separately,
on top of other expenses.
It was a good goal.
- Who hit the goal?
- Number 5.
- Is that your son?
- Yes, mine.
Whoo! Buddy, road to No. 9!
Yeah, what is it? Yeah, go ahead.
What? What do you mean?
How can you say that?
Simran, don't tell me to calm down.
Please! Fuck!
That was Simran on the phone.
They are making Logan the dean
at the new hospital.
But the enquiry hasn't even concluded yet.
One more complaint came in.
Do you remember Carol Simmons?
I can cook, but you will have to eat it.
Carol is not anonymous.
We will no longer be able to relocate.
I don't want to relocate anyway.
I have applied for a new job.
Where?
Here, in this city.
And you are taking it?
If they make an offer, yes.
I was ready to leave my job, this town,
for the baby, Geetika.
I have to think about myself, too.
After all, I have a reputation to build.
What the hell?
- Sir, I tried, but…
- But what?
Whose car is this?
Dr Logan, is this your spot?
You seem upset. It's annoying
when someone takes your place, isn't it?
Is this about the position of dean?
I didn't ask for it. It was offered to me.
Well, you offered me your support,
just to go behind my back.
I am sorry you feel like this.
But you would have done
exactly the same thing.
No.
I would have waited
for the Board to complete its enquiry
before behaving as if
the verdict is already out.
I would have had the courtesy
to at least check if…
Hey, are you filming?
Hey, are you filming this?
What are you doing?
- Are you filming this?
- No, no.
What do you think you are? An influencer?
Give me your phone.
Give me your phone. Are you filming?
Show me. What is your name?
Are you a resident here?
Which department are you from?
What do you mean?
I am calling the police right now.
…the verdict is already out.
I would have had the courtesy
to at least check if…
Hey, are you filming?
Hey, are you filming this?
What are you doing?
Are you filming this?
Who do you think you are? An influencer?
Give me your phone. Give me your phone.
Are you filming? Show me.
Yeah. Please come in.
I have parked my car in the North Block.
That's not your parking spot, is it?
Sorry. I saw that video.
Someone in our group posted it.
We have a group.
Doctors, nurses and interns.
For the questioning.
Now Simran ma'am has seen it, too.
Look at that.
This is my statement about
what happened with Carol the other night.
Luckily, I do not have to
make HR decisions.
Misbehaving with a senior doctor
in the hospital parking lot
could cost you your job.
Yeah.
Dr Geetika, just a sec.
I wanted to ask you a few questions.
The last time you met Dr Carol Simmons
was in that hotel, right?
- Right.
- And when did you last meet Natasha?
I don't know. Perhaps a few years back.
I met Natasha when
Why are you making my work this easy?
I spoke to Natasha.
Meeting the witness,
trying to influence her…
You might as well sign a confession.
And what else did Natasha tell you?
No comment.
Dad, my shoes tore.
- Okay. No TV. You sleep now.
- Good night.
- Hi.
- Yes?
Sir, I am very, very sorry
to be disturbing you like this,
but I have lost my Julie.
My cat. It's her birthday tomorrow.
She's been missing for a week.
I live right down the road.
If it's not too much trouble,
can I have a look at…
On the goalkeeper, the referee,
and the one who is falling back,
and the one that's coming from your right.
You have to keep an eye on everyone.
If you kick the ball
with your eyes closed,
how will you become Mbappé?
In fact, someone got inside the house
when your eyes were closed.
And through the window, at that.
Matt?
Matt!
- Where is everyone?
- They're right there.
Congratulations!
Congratulations, Meera.
- I got the job?
- You did.
- Thank you so much, sir.
- Proud of you.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- So happy for you.
He called me out of the blue.
Must be a breakthrough.
Last time he called so urgently
was when he got arrested.
You think he got arrested?
With Mark, all bets are off.
I am going to lose my job.
- You wait here. Okay?
- Okay.
Yeah!
To Meera.
- To Meera!
- Come on, guys. Grab the glasses.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Listen, Meera.
We have our own after-party later, okay?
- Really?
- I have invited Rohit as well.
Perfect.
Guys, everyone's drinking, okay?
There you go.
Just a minute, okay? I will be back.
Come on, Meera, not tonight.
Meera, are you at home?
I am at the clinic.
Meera?
Hello?
What's happening there, Meera?
I got the job
at Riverkings Children's Hospital.
Oh, wow.
We should celebrate.
There is a small party at the clinic.
And there's also an after-party later.
I see. Good. Listen, the thing
that I was going to tell you about
Meera, come on.
Everyone is waiting for the toast.
Meera?
Can you hear me? Hello, are you listening?
Geetika, there is a lot of noise here.
Can I talk to you once I get home?
Yeah, fine. Okay, see you later.
A new menu is on the cards,
and we are happy to bring on board
a cheat-day specialist chef, Sergio,
just for Indian desserts.
I love Indian spices more than sweets.
Oh, wait until you try our desserts.
Get him to taste
the gunpowder chutney sometime.
Are you from Chennai?
My parents are from Chennai.
I am from Good Food Daily.
Right. Sophie Sarandis. Nice to meet you.
Sophie, so good.
Here you go, darling.
Ms Sophiana, tell me something.
Why Indian?
I thought of an Indian restaurant because…
I fell in love with someone
from the same ethnicity.
Oh, dear.
And with that, I fell in love
with Indian food as well.
-And once you are in love–
-Everything else feels insipid.
I know. Is that person here?
Excuse me.
- Hi.
- You came.
- Yeah.
Such a lovely surprise.
"We are delighted to extend our offer
for the position of Resident Doctor
at Riverkings Children's Hospital."
- Very good. Good start, good start.
- We are also "delighted."
- Hey, when does it start?
- Yeah.
"Your expected starting date
is 1st of November."
1st of November.
That means just a few more days
with us at our small clinic.
- I am going to miss you guys.
- Yep.
"We will be offering you
an annual gross salary of…"
- What?
- Excuse me.
- Yes, ma'am.
Whatever these two are having,
it's all on me.
Whoa! That's a lot of celebrating!
- That's amazing.
- Cheers! Cheers to that!
- Don't forget you owe me.
- A bit.
- Which one is more spicy?
- I am sorry.
- I will take care of it. Don't worry.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Yeah, yeah. You are so fucked.
- Stop it, Mark.
- What?
Yeah, okay, okay.
- You are in this too.
- Are you trying to close my business?
You come to my restaurant
and spoil my evening?
Yeah, "your" evening. "Your" business.
- What you are doing is a crime.
- You think?
I paid you.
And you come back and you blackmail me?
- You are always acting like a cry-baby.
- You need to stop this.
This is not going to work.
You are always calling me…
After all these years.
Next time I want my candies, okay?
- I will see you on Thursday. Bye-bye.
- Right.
- Bye. See you.
- Thank you. Thank you, Doctor.
Meera.
You understood what he said?
- Hi, how are you?
- I am good.
- Mamma, you be there.
- Yeah, sure.
Mansoor was here.
- What is this?
- He left this for you.
What is it?
I think you should see it.
I got my hands on something, Meera.
This could clear my name.
Maybe the anonymous emails
that were sent to the hospital
were not from eight different people.
Which means I am being framed. See?
Even I got my hands on something.
You are misunderstanding this, Meera.
I got the hospital server hacked.
And the hacker I hired
is Sophie's brother, Mark.
The reason I didn't tell you
is because it is illegal.
Otherwise, you would have
been implicated along with me.
This! This is Sophie's building, right?
And the two of you
are going inside the building.
And you look pretty thrilled.
You were hacking the server
at Sophie's house all night?
You actually hired a private investigator?
You never tell me anything.
If I ask, you say you are in the hospital
and the hospital says you are on leave.
So, you thought…
- And this is not the first time.
- …you would hire a private investigator?
I never know where you are at any time.
If you never know,
then why snoop on me this time?
Because this time you wanted to find out
about the sexual misconduct, right?
What I want to know is this
Don't raise your voice at me!
Were you with Sophie the entire night?
If you had any sense at all,
then you would have just been
a little more available.
I should have been more available?
I didn't even know about your job.
I don't believe this.
I didn't tell you about my job,
and look how upset you are.
Did you ever ask me
if I wanted to relocate to a new city?
If I want to quit my job?
At least look at me!
Turning your face
will not end this issue, Geetika.
You always think about yourself.
You are the centre of your universe.
No one else is visible to you.
I don't even exist here.
If you don't exist,
then who was the baby coming for?
That was your decision.
I was doing it for you.
Now, all of a sudden,
you don't even want a baby.
Did you ever ask me? Did you ever think?
That a baby would completely change
our lives and our careers.
Whose career?
- I was leaving everything for our family.
- For yourself.
You were leaving your job
for yourself, Meera.
Okay? Look around you.
This is your home. This is your life.
You like to live in comfort, don't you?
It's very difficult, you know,
to build a career, a life, a house.
This is much easier.
And you always choose the easier option.
That is why you have been lying
to your parents to this day.
Don't go there, Geetika.
You said we would tell them together.
And you, of all people,
have no right to call me a liar.
I have no idea
what is true and what is false about you.
The truth is, your suspicion
has become your reality,
and I feel sorry for you.
And what is your reality?
Sex offender? Cheater? Which one, Geetika?
Ask the guy you hired to tail me.
Hi, you've reached Dr Geetika Sen.
I am not available right now.
Probably at work. You know what to do.
What is this?
People writing the emails
can be anonymous, but not the emails.
Every email has an IP address, right?
See, there were eight anonymous emails.
The IP address and Wi-Fi service provider
of the first email
narrows down the location to this place.
The public library at Barnard Street.
The second mail has come
from a café on Bond Street.
Third mail has come
from this restaurant on Newton.
The fourth and fifth mails
are again from the same public library.
The sixth mail is again
from the café on Bond Street.
Seventh mail has come from
this mall at Strand.
And the last mail, yet again…
Same public library.
What are the chances, Simran,
that four so-called victims
are members of the same public library?
And two of the victims
visited the same café?
The rest of the emails
are also from around the same area.
So, are you saying…
That these are not eight people,
but a single person?
Someone must have
hacked the hospital server
to trace the IP address.
This is a crime. How did it come to you?
Ironically, from an anonymous email.
What is IT's opinion on the matter?
They are verifying it as we speak.
If they confirm it,
it's a clear indication
that someone is framing Geetika.
And Dr Carol Simmons?
She is coming in to submit her statement.
You can ask her yourself.
Geetika was right.
Someone broke into our house that day.
There is nothing missing from the house,
except the details
that appeared in the mail.
The position of the wine cabinet,
the colour of the couch.
It is the same guy.
Look at this. This is from another angle.
This is David.
And this is his car.
I have found out everything.
Who he is, where he goes, what he does.
All I need to figure out is why he did it.
Then why didn't you tell me?
I did give all the details to Angad
the other day.
Angad didn't tell you?
Angad only told me about Sophie.
Do you know Sophie's brother?
- Mark.
The one who hacked the hospital server.
So, if he can hack into the server
to pull out a mail, then…
He can also plant it.
I just need two more days
to crack this case.
Make sure the focus is completely right.
Okay?
Dr Simmons, thank you so much for coming.
We're all really glad that you are here.
Very few people have the courage
to look into that lens
and speak the truth.
- Are we already recording?
- Ready in one.
In about a minute.
Your statement will be recorded
as primary evidence.
And it will be handed over
to the law enforcement agencies.
Whereby which you will be provided
with protection,
seeing as you are
our primary victim in this case.
I am sure the other victims
will also come forward?
The emails, as verified by IT,
are most likely fake.
And there are no other victims.
So, for now, we just have you.
Dr Simmons, if I may?
See, the "MeToo" Movement
is an important one.
And it has provided a serious platform
for several women
who have been exploited
by people in positions of power.
It is sad, but it is made
for victims such as yourself.
And I really hope your testimony comes out
and inspires hundreds of others
to come out and speak the truth.
Thank you.
We can start rolling, right?
- Yes.
- Lovely. Thank you.
Dr Simmons,
just look straight into the lens, right,
and just relax.
Can you tell us what happened
on the night of November 19th?
Why did Dr Sen call you
to that five-star hotel room?
Can I take a moment
to collect my thoughts?
Yeah, yeah, sure. Of course.
What do you think
based on your experience?
You think she will come back?
Meera, just give me a second, please.
Meera, at least listen to me once.
Meera, why are you doing this?
Just give me a second.
Listen, I can explain everything, okay?
- Meera, will you stop for a second?
- What do you want to explain?
Why did you not tell me about David?
You knew it could help
Geetika clear her name.
But you didn't want that. Why?
Fine, I didn't tell you about David.
But I don't think
Geetika is right for you.
Not just me. No one thinks
she is right for you, either.
And I don't know why you can't see it,
or you don't want to see it.
I was just trying to look out
for you as a friend, okay?
As a friend?
As a friend, what else have you done?
Come on, Meera.
Are you seriously suggesting
that I sent out those emails?
Whatever you have done
is not something friends do.
Meera…
I think the two of you need
to sit down and talk it over.
What do you think?
That Disha and I don't have problems?
Every relationship has its ups and downs.
What is important
is that you are still here.
And you still want to help Geetika.
Please ask Geetika
to move back into her own house.
I will figure out something.
- I didn't know…
- I had no idea…
Disha.
Carol has withdrawn her complaint.
Carol was the one trying to frame you?
I don't know.
It is possible that she was
taking advantage of this situation
to get even with me. I don't know.
This has the details of the person
who broke into our…
Broke into the house.
What?
You were right, Geetika.
There was someone in the house that day,
and all the details were there
in the allegations the next day.
Right.
I think this man can get us
to whoever is behind all of this.
Let's go to the police, Geetika.
Yeah.
His name is David Brown.
He works at Sogo Club
at Old Compton Street.
What did he take from your house?
- Nothing.
- Then there was no robbery.
- There was a break-in.
- But nothing was taken.
Information was.
Print of a couch?
It was misused. I could have lost my job.
Where did you get this?
These people will not do anything.
If they don't do anything,
we will come here again.
Don't do anything rash.
Don't be a hero, Geetika.
Yeah. Okay.
Bye.
He works at Sogo Club
at Old Compton Street.
I think this man can get us
to whoever is behind all of this.
In my experience,
it is most probably someone close.
Are you saying that these are
not eight people, but a single person?
Look, someone tried to frame me,
and this guy knows who.
Are you going to
do something about it or not?
Excuse me, you know this guy?
- Seen him?
- No.
- What the fuck, man?
- Sorry.
Hey, watch it.
Hey, wait! Wait!
- Sorry, sorry!
- Hey! Hey, you!
- What are you doing, man? Watch it!
- Sorry.
Stop!
- Hey! Are you crazy?
- Hey!
David!
David! David!
I just want to talk!
Stop! David!
- Oh, shit.
- Are you okay?
- Meera?
Okay. David, come on.
We have to get him in the car.
- Yeah.
- David, you need help.
Come, sit.
- The keys?
- In the ignition.
Code blue. Code blue. Can you hear me?
Code blue. Patient incoming.
- Here. Keep your eyes open, David.
- Core team, stand by.
Code blue. Core team, stand by.
- Keep up, David.
- Why did you come here?
Because I knew you would come.
Coffee?
Thanks for coming.
I am doing all of this
because it's the right thing to do.
Don't think that things between us
are back to how they used to be.
Yeah.
Dr Sen.
This patient is already registered here.
David Brown.
He is getting treated here
at our own hospital.
Gastric cancer.
Really?
Under whose care? Show.
Welfare program me.
Morning.
Didn't expect to see you here, Dr Sen.
Thing is, I have been cleared.
There is a cancer patient. David Brown?
Under the welfare program me.
So, he was made to commit a crime
and frame me
in order to continue his free treatment.
And why are you telling me all this?
Come, I will show you.
Please.
What's going on?
Can I have your phone and laptop, please?
I don't understand.
We can talk about it
at the station, Dr Logan.
I am afraid you need to
come with us now. Please.
You did all of this
because you wanted her job?
This is ridiculous.
Sir, please, let us not make a scene.
David Brown is a career thief.
And a worthless little piece of
Remember what they say
about good surgeons, Dr Logan?
Sir, please come with us.
Get your hands off me.
You are going to regret this.
I said, get your hands off!
Cheating. Impersonation. Cyber fraud.
These are some serious charges.
When they found pictures of your house
on Dr Logan's laptop,
he was forced to confess to the crimes.
Plus, we have also got the confession
from his patient, David.
In fact, Dr Logan believes
that no one is more deserving of
the position of dean than him.
Least of all, you.
Why? Because I am a woman?
Logan considered me undeserving.
But the others declared me guilty.
Dr Geetika, to be honest,
when I took on this case,
I did not have any preconceived notions.
You did have preconceived notions
in your mind, Mr Bhargav.
"Youngest HOD."
"First woman to become a dean."
Must have done something illicit.
You know, ironically, my ambition
was the reason all of this happened.
When a man is appointed the dean,
he deserves it.
But when it comes to a woman…
She must have taken some shortcuts. Right?
To be honest, I do not have
an answer to this at the moment.
Thank you, Mr Bhargav.
- For everything.
- My pleasure. Thank you.
Take my advice and think of
the last few days as a bad dream and
Forget it?
Easier said, I know.
But, the good news is,
the Board wants to offer you
the position of dean again.
You do deserve it, Geetika.
Dr Cooper will have
a different opinion, I think.
He messed up the surgery,
I handled it, but…
I didn't stop there.
I took away his patient.
I had to show him his place.
Because, you know, men like Cooper,
Logan, even Bhargav.
They think they are completely in control.
And I seem to have made it
my life's mission
to remind them
that they are not in control. I am.
With Carol, too, I could have…
Given her a warning
or a temporary suspension,
but I got her fired from the hospital.
Do you know why?
-Because during the surgery, Carol–
-Because Carol was weak.
Simran, I have worked really hard
to reach this position.
That is why, perhaps,
when I find a woman showing weakness,
I don't feel bad.
I feel angry.
But when a Cooper or a Bhargav
exploit some weakness in me,
then I am not just angry.
Then I have to teach them a lesson.
I have to watch them lose.
Perhaps this anger is good for you.
I mean, this is what is called
being ambitious, right?
Perhaps this is what is called…
Abuse of power.
You know, I felt that…
That as a woman with power, I would be…
I would be different.
I mean,
I didn't abuse anyone sexually, but…
But I don't think I handled my power well.
I don't want this position.
A power that can slip out of your hands
and go to your head.
My reasons for wanting to become a dean
were all wrong.
I don't think I'm ready
for this position yet.
I have a lot of work to do.
I already paid for this appointment.
Meera, you know, you were right.
I have always
put myself above all else.
All my decisions were only about me.
I mean,
I wanted to be the dean.
I wanted to relocate.
And I realised,
your decisions always include "us."
No, I mean,
you were willing to quit your job
because you felt it was better for us.
And…
And you agreed to relocate
so that we could be together
and live happily.
Meera.
They have offered me
the position of dean again.
But I have turned it down.
I don't want to be the dean.
I want to…
I want to work on this.
Do you remember,
the first time we met at that coffee shop,
I mixed up both of our mugs,
just so we could have a moment
at the counter.
Can we start from there again?
Please?
I am going to Meerut next weekend.
- Oh.
- Last I checked,
the seat next to me was still available.
Subtitle translation by: Natasha C Acharya