We'll bring you an update.
The number of correctional officers
being held hostage in the uprisings…
It's time, bro. It's time.
Yo. Make sure you watch your back.
-Let's get this done.
-They won't know what hit them.
-Let's put fire on this shit! Come on!
-No messing around.
-Let's get it.
-Focus on the mission.
Let's do it, man!
Hey, the system will collapse.
Right? We're the fucking Brotherhood.
CIVIL POLICE
CIVIL POLICE STATION
109th PRECINCT
Fuck!
Did smacking it work, babe?
This machine deserves it,
pissing off a pregnant woman.
-It pissed you off? Poor thing.
-Seriously, I mean it.
-Mm.
-I'm gonna kill someone today.
Hey, don't talk like that.
Hate fuels hate.
-I know, but some days are hard.
-Maybe take time for yourself.
-They're coming.
-No, forget it. Today is my--
Oh my God!
Our future momma!
Yes! Congratulations. It's almost time.
I'm done for. He's an amazing liar.
I had absolutely no idea.
Of course. He's a born actor.
For a good cause though, right?
Oh God.
I hope this kid follows
her godfather's advice.
I hope she's smart enough to ignore it.
Look, we have a surprise for Aurora.
That is really gorgeous.
You only threw this party for the cake.
-I know how you are.
-Give me a hug!
Ten years after the death
of their leader, Edson Ferreira,
known as Edson "Savage,"
the Brotherhood has cemented
its reputation for organized violence,
claiming responsibility for the riots.
There are 25…
No, now it's up to 29 prisons
where rioting has been reported…
And there's also this
for our heroic little angel.
Aw, you guys are so thoughtful.
Should I open it?
-Of course.
-Okay.
-Get down!
-Fuck! What was that?
-Was that downstairs?
-Baby, you okay?
I'm gonna check it out.
-What happened? What exploded?
-Check in the back.
-Stay there. Don't move.
-Watch out. Be careful.
What the fuck's going on?
Can you see anything? What do you see?
Fuck. It's one of our cars.
-These guys are attacking!
-We have to hold them back!
Dalva, take cover!
Dalva, stay behind the desk!
-We're coming for you!
-Dalva, get down!
CEPOL! CEPOL! Shots fired at Station 109!
-Dalva, stay there!
-We're under attack!
Fuckin' hell!
Bastards! Keep down, dammit!
Go, go, go!
-We need help!
-Move him back!
-Dalva!
-Romero!
-Dalva, what's wrong?
-Did you get hit?
-I'm bleeding. Romero, look.
Are you in pain? Can you feel her move?
-We gotta get outta here!
-Let's go.
Okay, come on. We gotta get out.
Get out! Get out! I'm covering you!
You okay? What's wrong?
My water… My water broke.
-Come on! Move it! Go, go, go!
-Come on, let's get outta here!
They blocked the whole street!
Send backup!
CEPOL! CEPOL! Precinct 109 is taking fire!
Clear the fucking channel!
We're under attack, goddammit!
Take cover! Take cover!
Let's fucking go!
Yeah!
It's the fucking Brotherhood!
Let's go!
Attention, all units.
We have orders to only go out
in armed teams, wearing bulletproof vests.
-Over here.
-They're moving to the street.
No, no, no. Not that way.
Over here. This way, you guys.
-Get to the back, now!
-Take cover!
Help us out!
-Watch out! Careful!
-Help! Over here!
Get out of the way! Go!
-Man down! We got a man down here!
-Help!
Over here, now!
Hold on.
-I'll get us out of here.
-Move it!
We'll have to do it here.
Let's go! Move! Move!
I'll bring a patrol car.
I'm coming with you.
-Let's go, now! Come on. Move it!
-Come on.
-Right behind you!
-They're heading round back!
-Okay, now! Run, run!
-Get your vest on!
Go! Go! Come on!
Come on.
Get in.
CEPOL, this is Unit 45.
Shots fired at military police.
Backup requested.
CEPOL, Unit 51 requesting support
in the pursuit of individuals…
…who attacked the military police.
-Roger that, Unit 51.
-Go, go, go, go, go!
Assistance needed. Clear the channel.
-I need three patrol cars…
-Open it! Open the fucking gate!
Go, go, go, go!
CEPOL, military police officer
shot near the park. Send backup!
-What the fuck was that?
-They're attacking everywhere.
Any patrol cars in the area?
CEPOL, do you copy?
There are reports
of a firefighter shot near Luz station.
-They're getting stronger.
-It's gonna be okay, baby. Okay?
-We're gonna get outta here.
-…any vehicles near headquarters…
-I can't make it.
-Copy that. Attention…
It's gonna be okay, babe. You'll be okay.
We're almost there.
CEPOL! CEPOL! Bronze 25 Echo.
-Get down, Dalva!
-What? Oh my God!
Get down!
Holy shit!
What the fuck is happening?
Goddammit!
My God! Go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go! Hurry! Hurry!
Go after them, dammit!
Fuck!
CEPOL, emergency! Emergency!
Shots fired at patrol car
behind Precinct 109.
Bronze 28 Echo.
Grenade attack at the Santana courthouse.
They're still coming.
We need backup immediately!
Dalva! Dalva, are you okay?
Are you okay? Breathe. Just breathe, okay?
QRX. Keep the channel clear.
Widespread attacks on police units.
Police vehicles are ordered to return…
-Fuck! Fuck!
-Officers are to remain stationed…
Move outta the fucking way!
-Fucking dammit!
-What is it?
Stop, stop, stop! It's happening!
-Stop anywhere!
-Okay.
It hurts so much!
Fuck.
-Hold on.
-Go!
Go!
Stop, stop, stop!
I can't do this.
I'm coming.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
I can't do it. It hurts too much.
-Yes, you can. Calm down.
-It hurts too much!
Babe. Babe.
Look at me.
You can do this.
Okay? You got this.
It's gonna be okay. I'm with you.
-Yeah.
-It's gonna be all right.
-Hmm? Come on.
Come on. Come on.
-I can't do it. It's too much. I can't.
-We can do it.
-Come on. Breathe.
-I need a doctor!
-Just breathe.
-I need a doctor! I can't do it!
I can't do it.
That's not possible.
Babe, it's just you and me.
-I can't do it. I can't.
-It's okay. It's okay.
You can do it. You can.
Everything's gonna be fine.
-I can't do it.
-Yes, you can, babe.
-You can do it.
-I can't do it. I can't.
Look at me!
Look at me. You can do this.
You can do it.
Come on. Now breathe.
Just breathe. And go.
Breathe.
Push. I'm here with you.
Breathe, Dalva. Breathe. Push now.
I'm with you. Keep breathing.
Keep pushing. Push now.
Push it.
Push.
Dalva, you're almost there.
Our daughter is coming. Almost there.
Push, Dalva. Keep pushing. Come on, babe.
Push, Dalva.
A little more.
Come on.
Go, go, go, go! Push harder!
Don't stop pushing! Keep going!
Keep pushing! Keep pushing!
Keep pushing!
Almost there.
STATE OF FEAR
2 DAYS BEFORE
Mm…
I'm really gonna miss
pagode nights with you.
Wow. I never thought I'd hear that.
You miss pagode nights?
Are you feeling okay?
I can never get you out of the house.
Mm!
All I know is, I wanna go out with you.
It doesn't matter where.
-Hmm?
-So I'm counting on you.
When you get out, we'll pagode constantly.
Ah…
It's a deal, Counselor.
When I get out,
I'm gonna love taking your orders.
-Hmm?
-Mm…
It's nice knowing
I have that much influence over you.
If the guys found out
just how much, I'd be screwed.
Time's up.
Let's go.
What?
You wanna trade places with me?
You live here and I'll go out there?
What's going on?
There's talk around here
about transfers again.
But it's nothing you have to worry about.
What do you mean, "nothing"?
Who's going to transfer? Where? When?
They're transferring a lot of prisoners
to RDD.
To RDD?
I mean, fuck you!
They wanna send me to solitary
to weaken the Brotherhood.
Calm down, sweetheart. Calm down.
I'm gonna meet with my Department contact.
-They've got no legal justification.
-Are you fucking kidding, Cris?
They don't give a fuck if it's legal.
We gotta talk, now.
-Ivan! Wait.
-Hey, Brotherhood, listen up.
-Ivan.
-Gather 'round, everybody!
-Come here.
-Ivan.
Brothers, Ivan has something to say.
Listen. I'm not done talking.
Hold on, Zica.
Don't lose your temper
and do something stupid.
You remember how much we grew
when we started doing business
instead of fighting?
Once we start tolerating humiliation,
then the Brotherhood is done, Cristina.
If you had spent
even one fucking day in here,
you'd know that respect can only be earned
through sweat and blood.
Ivan,
think about what's best
for the Brotherhood.
-Mom, don't.
-Excuse me, sir.
Cleber doesn't want me to say anything,
but I just had to thank you, sir.
My son moved to the semi-open program,
and we never could have afforded a lawyer
without your help.
That's what the Brotherhood is for.
Only those who have
lived through this hell
know why we're in this fight
and what real struggle is.
I'm counting on you outside.
We're in this together forever now.
You know that, right?
Mm-hmm.
-Come on, Mom. Let's go.
-Thanks again.
You neglected to tell her
your counselor here,
the one who doesn't know struggle,
got him in the semi-open section.
I may not know
what life is like in this foul hellhole,
but I'm out there all day, every day,
fighting for the Brotherhood.
Even if you refuse to see it.
Counselor, nothing will make
the governor change his mind.
The transfer's gonna happen.
That's just a fact.
Well, it is an election year.
Putting the Brotherhood leaders
in solitary is a smart play.
I just don't know
if riot images all over the news
will help the governor's campaign.
Because you know
the Brotherhood won't accept that, right?
Of course you do.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be here
drinking sickly-sweet coffee with you.
Counselor, you're a smart woman.
You know very well
the value of our friendship.
But if you wanna keep doing business,
you must give me a guarantee
there won't be any retaliation.
And how exactly could I give that to you?
Do you call the shots in there or not?
I thought that by putting the boss
in solitary, you'd take full control.
Was I wrong?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
MC Elisa strikes first!
MC Dig fires back!
What does the public want?
Blood!
Show me what you got!
Feeling victimized?
Complain to the management
Scientists are baffled
How the straight man got so arrogant
But seriously, dude
Y'all require therapy
Us girls are flying high
While you guys rely on charity
My rhymes are prime
But you're unmotivated
Won't even do your laundry
It's not that complicated
Whoa!
I should do my laundry?
Go suck your silver spoon
A maid takes care of all your shit
You've never touched a broom
Do us all a favor
Don't pretend this is your scene
Acting like you're from the hood
But you were brought up in Jardins
Hey, must be nice
Over there you get to choose
If you wanna judge my hustle
Walk a mile in my shoes
-Whoa!
-Whoa-ho!
That one hurt!
Okay, that's it
Now you're just being an asshole
I don't judge your situation
I don't care about your hustle
Yeah, I'm from the other side
That I can't deny
Insane I had to come this far
To teach you how to rhyme
Whoa!
Take him to school!
Go on, strike your princess pose
And act like you're classy
You can cake on all that makeup
But you still look fucking nasty
Listen up
You could never make me stress
We all know you're a slut
We can tell by how you dress
Are you kidding, dude?
Have some fucking respect!
-Stop!
-Fuck you!
Let these losers go! Just let 'em go!
Violence is for the coward
Ain't no way that's gonna fly with me
Let this guy attack
I'll take him down with poetry
-Whoa!
-You're calling me a slut?
That's a worn-out cliché
Macho shit you're spouting's
Gonna have to end today
You showed up with violence
But that will always fail
-Not always!
-I stand here armed with language
And what's right will prevail!
Asshole!
No, no, girl. Don't do it. She's bluffing.
-She's bluffing!
-She's got a good card.
-I can tell. She's got a good one.
-She's bluffing.
You're taking forever.
-Let's go.
-Where?
-Mm-mm. Don't show them.
-No, hold on. Let's see.
Think I'm bluffing?
I'm gonna jump in the pool if you are.
Then get ready to jump.
-You forgot I'm an outlaw!
-I told you!
I'm reminding you all again…
-…I'm the best liar.
-I told you she didn't have it.
I told you.
Oh, this looks hot.
-Nice!
-Guys, right?
What they're drinking, I want some.
-Those days were fun.
-They sure were.
Brings me back.
Elisa.
-Elisa!
-Turn that music down.
What do you want?
Watch out for the window.
Everyone can see you from downstairs.
Oh, whatever.
-Hmm.
-Done? Can I go back to what I was doing?
Mm. Okay, but listen.
You better not be hungover
at the interview tomorrow.
Oh, I forgot to tell you,
I won't be going.
What do you mean? Since when?
Oh, since I decided
I don't want to work there.
I won't be happy there, Cris.
Can we please talk about this later?
And what's your plan, Elisa?
Because you can't just sit around
smoking weed while I pay your bills.
That's not what I wanna do.
Then what do you want?
Please!
How many times do I need to tell you
there's a lot of people
who'd kill for your opportunities?
Hey, auntie.
-It's okay, Wesley. I've got this.
-Calm down. Calm down. It's cool.
What's up, auntie?
Did you know
your niece is a killer rapper?
She's an artist now.
I don't want your opinion.
I'm not talking to you.
-Calm down. I was just--
-Listen!
If you wanna go down, you can go alone.
Don't drag her down with you.
-Jeez, auntie is pissed. Calm down--
-I'm not your fucking "auntie"!
You cocky little shit!
Who are you to talk to him
like that, huh, Cris?
Hmm?
You're a goddamn hypocrite!
You act like you're perfect!
It's no secret where the money
for your designer bag comes from, is it?
Is that the path I should take?
I'm only trying to explain,
things aren't as simple as you think.
My dad wanted me to be like you, huh?
Counselor.
Must be rolling in his grave,
watching what you've done to his struggle.
No more justice, no more resistance.
All you care about these days
is the money.
You think you have the right to tell me
how I live my life? Gimme a break!
You don't know
what the hell you're talking about!
You have no concept of what justice is,
let alone what real struggle is.
-Let's go.
-Always had everything handed to you.
Who pays for the fun you have? Huh?
And what about those designer clothes
you're wearing? Who pays for that?
What about your private school?
You think you can
boss everyone around, don't you?
But you're not my mom,
and you're definitely not my dad.
And I'm not one of your goons.
Here we go!
Slow down!
Slow down, Elisa!
Elisa!
Elisa, goddammit! Slow the fuck down!
-Elisa, we're gonna crash, goddammit!
-Woo-hoo!
Whoo!
-Oh, fuck!
-Hold on!
Woo-hoo!
Holy shit.
Pull over!
Get off the bike, both of you.
Hands on your head.
Get over to the patrol car. Do it!
Come on, girl. You too.
-Calm down.
-I don't have all day.
-Any weapons?
-No.
-Where are you going?
-Just going for a ride, sir.
-Any priors?
-No.
Gimme your bag.
-Am I gonna find drugs in here?
-No.
Didn't you hear me?
Put your hands on your fucking head.
Turn around.
Put your goddamn hands on your head.
What's the deal with the fancy bike?
Who'd you steal it from?
It's my bike.
Well, it's in my aunt's name.
-But I have the reg--
-Hands on your fucking head!
Can I… get the registration?
Slowly.
Ah, guys, I'm sorry.
I know I was going a little fast.
You can give me a ticket.
I know you're just doing your job.
Hear that, Sarge?
She thinks we're traffic cops.
Here's the thing.
I'm gonna have to search the girl too.
Why? What for?
We don't have anything on us.
Nothing on you, huh? Nothing at all?
So then why do I smell weed?
Look.
Seems like your boyfriend just got busted.
-There's probably more inside.
-There's nothing.
-Shut up, junkie!
-Hey! He didn't do anything!
-Why are you hitting him?
-Whoa, whoa. Look at that.
That's not mine, sir.
Why are you doing this?
You planted that shit!
It's obvious you planted that!
That's not mine!
-Get off him!
-That's not mine!
Easy, easy, easy, Borges.
Easy. Let's stay calm. Relax.
-Why are you doing this? What do you want?
-Calm down.
Because we could settle this in a way
that makes everybody happy.
Nice bike you got.
Bet your godson would like it,
huh, Borges?
There's no fucking way I'm gonna
grease your palms. Is that clear?
Sir, please. Why?
We're taking your boyfriend
to the station.
Borges, put him in the trunk.
This isn't fair. Don't do this.
Why are you doing this?
-Go.
-Ruin my life over nothing.
-Ow! Fuck! You're hurting me!
-Take him.
-Move it, asshole!
-Ow!
-Just fucking go!
-Let me go! You're hurting me!
Why are you doing this to me, sir?
For God's sake!
-Wait a minute. Hold on.
-Let's go! Move!
I'm covered!
I've got family in the organization!
None of us want trouble.
Let's do the right thing.
We can all move on. Let him go.
You crazy?
Things just got interesting.
Tell me more.
What's your deal with the Brotherhood?
Well, I just know some people inside,
but I'm not directly involved.
I'm not a criminal!
You said someone in the organization's
from your family.
You better start telling me the truth,
or I might think you're messing with me.
It's my father, but he's dead now.
Who's your father?
Edson Ferreira.
Fuck.
You're saying…
you're Edson Savage's daughter?
Holy shit.
Let him go, Borges.
She's Edson's daughter.
-You're the one coming with us.
-What?
-You're coming with us.
-Wait! Wait! Where are you taking her?
Hey! You stay here, dammit!
Hey, shut up. Here's the deal.
We're taking your girlfriend for a ride.
If you really want to,
you can come with us.
Otherwise, you're free to go.
So… you going home or coming with us?
I… I wanna go home.
I knew it.
Your boyfriend is a coward.
I'm never wrong.
I'm just gonna grab my coke.
You can go home. Take him home, Borges.
Give him my regards.
Grab your bag. Fucking coward.
Move!
-Abandoning your girl?
-Let him go! You'll kill him!
-Stop with the violence!
-Go home!
Hey, calm down!
The daughter of the country's
biggest murderer
is asking me to stop the violence.
The Brotherhood exists
because scumbag pigs like you are around.
My father only wanted justice.
Justice is an excuse
for punk criminals to act like animals.
Your father's even
chopped people's heads off.
Didn't anyone ever tell you that story?
You're going in the back,
'cause I don't trust
the spawn of criminals.
Get in.
-You can't do that! I didn't do anything!
-Let's go.
Let me go! You're hurting me!
-Go. Go.
-Let me go!
Elisa.
What are you doing back there?
You're not supposed to be here.
You said you were getting Dad,
and I wanted to be there when you got him.
This is no place for kids.
For God's sake.
Where's Dad? Was he released?
No, he wasn't released. He wasn't.
You really shouldn't be here.
Be quiet. Quiet.
-I'm fucking free. I'm free.
-You did it, honey.
Why is the girl here, Darlene?
Go, go, go!
-Sweetheart, come here.
-Check in the back!
I missed you so much, baby.
-Do you see anything?
-Time to go. Come on. Move it. Go, go!
Do you see anything?
Shit. Get down.
-Fuck.
-Hide, Edson.
Cover me up.
-Cover me with something.
-Elisa, help him. Cover him.
My legs.
Cover me, honey. Hurry.
-Good evening, ma'am.
-Good evening, sir.
-Is everything all right?
-Yeah, fine.
Could you step out of the car, ma'am?
We just had a prison break.
I need to check the car.
It's for your own safety.
Sir, I… I'm in a hurry.
My daughter's not feeling well.
I'm taking her to the ER.
-Mom, it's getting worse now.
-Calm down, sweetheart.
All right, you can go.
-I hope she gets better soon.
-Thank you.
And… what's your favorite song?
Do you have one?
Let me go
I must wander
I'll go around
Searching
Smiling
So I don't cry
I want to see
The sun rising
See the waters of the river flowing
Listen to the birds singing
I want to be born
I want to live
Let me go
It's really beautiful.
Yeah.
And your favorite food?
What is it?
That would be feijoada.
It's got pork rinds,
sausage,
and farofa.
All those.
What's yours?
Instant noodles.
Nah, it can't be instant noodles.
What else do you like?
Instant food doesn't count, okay?
All right.
Hamburgers.
Yeah, I like hamburgers as well.
Hamburgers are pretty great.
And your favorite movie?
Favorite movie?
Well, sweetheart, it's been a long time
since I've seen a movie.
When I was your age, for example…
I always liked martial arts movies,
like with Bruce Lee.
You know the ones, like, "Yah! Yah!"
"Yah!"
What's that?
This?
A cut someone gave me.
Did it hurt?
Yeah, it hurt.
Dad…
Honey…
I know we're just
getting to know each other.
You probably have a lot of questions.
And that's totally normal.
Ask me anything you want.
Everyone talks about how you kill people,
so I wondered, is that true?
Sweetie…
I didn't choose this life I have.
But I've always fought
for dignity and justice.
And this fight has never ever
been easy for me, you know?
Want some ice cream?
Mm-hmm.
Hey.
Sweetie.
Hi.
What are you doing?
Leave the kid alone, Cláudia.
Hey, Lucas, isn't that our camera
she's holding?
Oh, it's okay. It's okay, little girl.
Just give me back what you took
and we'll forget about it.
-Give it to--
-I didn't take anything. It's my camera.
Yeah, it's her camera.
-Uh…
-Hi.
Are we good?
I'm her mother.
-Ah…
-What's going on here?
It's just that your daughter
took our camera
and was taking pictures of our son.
No, no. It's fine.
Kids do that kinda thing.
I have this little one,
but I also have a seven-year-old.
I know how it goes.
She insists on saying it's her camera.
But it is my camera.
My dad gave it to me. Tell her, Mom.
You've got it all wrong, lady.
-It's her camera.
-Ah, okay.
Are you calling my wife a liar?
No. Of course not. I would never do that.
But I think your sweetheart
had one too many.
They went to her head, made her nutso.
-What? Are you crazy? "Nuts"?
-Let's go, Darlene.
-Let's go to the car.
-Give it back.
What is it you don't understand, idiot?
The camera's hers, like I told you!
Damn, the thief's mom's
got some nerve, doesn't she?
What did you call her?
What did you call my daughter?
Only what she is, a thief.
But I'm not surprised,
with people like you as parents.
Listen, you pathetic little shithead,
only reason I'm not gonna fuck you up
is 'cause of my daughter over there.
Fucking asshole.
-Let's go, Darlene.
-You're gonna let him call her a thief?
-Come on.
-He called my daughter a thief!
-Fucking racist assholes!
-Bunch of fucking assholes!
-Darlene!
-You're all racist!
-Hey, come back here!
I tried being polite about this.
Now you'll have to deal with the police.
-Go fuck yourself!
-We'll get the police out here!
-Fucking police.
-Hey, give me that!
Get it, honey!
Motherfucker!
Give me this fucking camera right now!
-Get the fuck outta here!
-Don't touch me. Fuck you!
-Hey! Whoa!
-Give it to me.
Give it to me, motherfucker!
Give me the fucking camera!
The camera is hers!
-Now he's attacking people.
-Learn some manners!
He's walking off with our camera!
-Hey! Stop him!
-Give me my camera back!
-Ridiculous.
-Fucking animal.
-Shut up!
-You shut up!
Everybody, shut the fuck up!
Edson. Edson.
Edson, the cops are coming, Edson.
They're coming.
Get out of here. Run, Edson.
-I'm not fucking running.
-Run.
-Why do you have to go?
-Don't let them take you.
-Please don't, Edson. Don't go. Don't go!
-That's the guy! Get him!
You see all those fuckers
over there, sweetheart?
-Fuck you!
-Get this guy!
You see them, sweetie?
-He attacked that man.
-Shut it down, buddy!
They want us to grovel in front of them.
Lock him up!
And that's something we can never allow.
-Got it?
-Got it.
-Edson. Edson, please.
-Dad.
-For God's sake.
-Right there!
-Dad, don't go.
Edson, don't go away.
Dad!
You're under arrest.
Unbelievable, this guy!
Be strong, sweetie.
-Let go of my dad!
-Let's go.
It's over! You're done, fucker!
Dad, please, don't go!
Move, fucker.
-Get him out of here, yeah!
-Dad!
-Get in there. Get in.
-Dad, please!
Get the fuck in, motherfucker.
Bring my dad back!
Daddy!
Time to call your aunt.
It's for real.
It's not "if" anymore. Know what I mean?
-The question now is "when?"
-And the names of who's going?
We don't have them.
But it's over 500 brothers.
-All to RDD?
-All of them.
Complete isolation, man.
This is serious shit.
We're not talking small fish here either.
Our contact says
all the top dogs are going down.
So we're not gonna get visits or nothin'?
What the fuck?
They think we're a bunch of idiots?
It's all about them winning the election.
They'll isolate the command
and crack down on the hood.
That's the plan.
They wanna turn it
back into a concentration camp,
like it was before we revolted.
But we gotta make smart moves. You get me?
They're not fucking around, man.
There's a time to retreat
and a time to use force.
They're not fucking around?
We won't either.
It's a matter of survival
from now on, my brothers.
Either we show
that we're alive and ready to fight…
-…or we'll be erased from history.
-Damn right.
You guys just wanna sit
and watch us be humiliated?
-Nobody said "just watching."
-Fuck yeah! That's right!
-We wanna take action.
-They think we're stupid, man.
Evening, Counselor.
Counselor.
Counselor just showed up, Ivan.
She's on the call.
I'm glad you found
some time for us, Counselor.
The fucking pigs got Elisa.
What did you say?
Spit it out, Cristina.
Those damn cops.
They called. They want 700 grand.
-Motherfuckers.
-Savage's daughter, man.
You're not thinking about
paying the bastards, are you?
Of course not, Minor.
I told them to keep her,
even kill her, that I don't care.
Minor, what the fuck is that?
-Come on!
-Are we gonna take this shit lying down?
Just fork over money to the pigs?
If we do, they'll be kidnapping
our relatives every week, huh?
-Right.
-Mark my words.
You've paid them off before
and gotten much less in return,
and now you wanna show some backbone?
Are you kidding me?
Listen up. We don't know
how much time we have left.
Pay these motherfuckers
whatever they're asking.
We'll make sure they know
they fucked with the wrong person.
Sounds good.
I'll talk to those assholes, Cristina.
Everything's already arranged.
I'm paying them tomorrow.
Alone. And they'd be crazy
to mess with me.
Brothers. Listen up, everyone.
These assholes have crossed
every line possible.
First, this transfer shit,
which is for real, Cristina.
Then they kidnapped the girl.
The message is clear.
They want us to go to war.
That's right.
Wait, Ivan. Hold on.
The kidnapping has nothing to do with it.
There's no message.
It's just a dumb pig trying to make money.
Oh yeah? How do you know that, Counselor?
We've spent ten years
trying to reason with these pigs.
That's enough. It's over.
The Brotherhood was created
to fight for dignity.
It seems like everything we've ever done
is being destroyed by these motherfuckers.
We demand respect.
Now it's time
to start fighting back, hard.
Or watch in silence while
everything we've built gets demolished.
They gotta understand
that we're in charge.
Damn straight.
Either they agree to give up
on this transfer crap
or we fuck shit up on a massive scale.
Bro, here's the thing.
We're taking over the whole prison system.
All at once, in one move.
That will teach them some respect.
But commandeering the prisons
won't work. Not anymore.
No one cares about what happens in there.
The game's changed.
We could burn
all the mattresses in Brazil,
and no one would give a shit.
He's right, goddammit.
Prison revolts won't do a thing anymore.
They're treating us like shit,
so let's make sure we hit the fan.
We change our strategy, and attack them
where it hurts the most, outside.
-The game is on the streets now.
-Send them all to their graves.
Any pig on the streets is shot,
no questions asked, bro.
Wait, Ivan. Calm down, Calm down.
The Brotherhood doesn't work
like that anymore.
Please. It took years to prove
we could run without violence.
And everyone sees
that we're making more money
and helping our brothers in prison.
I'm negotiating
with the Department of Security.
-I just need more time, dammit.
-With all due respect, Counselor…
they kidnap your niece
and this is how you react?
Are you playing us for fools? Huh?
Precisely. Precisely, Minor.
The police have my brother's daughter,
who I raised as my very own.
And yet, somehow, I don't think
killing is gonna solve anything.
What about the brothers going
to solitary? What are we gonna do?
Handle it peacefully, through legal means.
I'll overturn the transfer in court
like I've always done.
For all 500 of them, Counselor?
Honestly, ma'am,
don't take this the wrong way,
but go take care of your family.
Show some respect, Gil.
Respect. Got it?
Ah, fuck!
We're fucked, Ivan.
First block's started.
Listen, here's the deal. They're starting
to move block one already.
-Fuck.
-I'm giving you just one order.
We take over the jails,
then we attack in the streets.
It's over, man.
It's about time we sent them a message.
He's right.
They gotta learn to respect us.
We're about to take down São Paulo.
The Brotherhood's going down in history.
-This is war.
-We're the Brotherhood.
Let's go!
Come on!
-Get up. Get up.
-Ivan.
-Time to go for a stroll.
-Ivan, are you there?
They're coming. It's going down.
Make some coffee. Get up.
-Ivan.
-Let's go!
Who's callin' the shots
when you're not here?
Time to pack. Time to get up.
While I'm out of the picture,
command goes to Minor.
Get up. Let's go. Come on.
Time to go for a ride.
Come on, punk. Your taxi is here.
Let me just get my stuff.
You're not taking anything.
Your stuff will come later.
Let's go, scumbag.
Come on. Get up.
-Get up! Get up!
-Go, go, go!
You're going for a little stroll.
Hey. I'm talking to you.
Get up. Let's go. Let's go.
-Move, move, move!
-Let's go! Move, move, move!
You heard him, dammit.
Send the order out.
-It's time!
-Yo, bro.
-That's right. It's going down.
-The whole system is going down.
Here's the thing, dude.
Go out into the streets
and cause some terror.
-Make it happen. No questions asked.
-Kill them all. Make an example.
-It's war. It's war now.
-Do not hesitate.
-Mess with us, it's war.
-Make it happen.
This is our time!
Make it work. They come here to test us?
That shit don't fly around here.
You heard me?
No one's giving the brothers
a dirty look today.
Things are gonna blow up everywhere.
We're the Brotherhood.
If they want war,
then that's what they're gonna get.
They're gonna learn the hard way.
They don't respect us,
so now they're paying the price.
They need to know we make the rules here.
You know what to do.
Come on, brothers. The call is out.
-Let's show them!
-The system is going down!
-This is war!
-It's the Brotherhood!
We are the Brotherhood!
-Come on! Let's do it!
-Come on! Let's go!
The riots that have been
taking place in the prisons of São Paulo
since early this morning
are in retaliation for the transfer
of a number of Brotherhood members
to the maximum security RDD unit.
That now, ten years after
the death of their leader, Edson Ferreira,
known as Edinho "Savage,"
the Brotherhood has cemented
its reputation for organized violence,
claiming responsibility for the riots.
There are 25…
No, now it's up to 29 prisons
where rioting has been reported.
The riots have spread rapidly
throughout multiple regions of the state.
This escalation is marked
by unprecedented coordination.
And public safety experts
have been warning
about this capacity for mobilization
for quite some time now.
Hey, buddy. Give me a latte, would you?
…the number of casualties
continue to increase by the hour.
As of now, we have noticed
that the prison riots
show no signs of stopping.
Uncontained.
Ten prisoners, two in Taubaté,
and eight in São Sebastião,
have died from burns sustained
after setting fire to their cells.
The Counselor, in the flesh.
It's an honor.
Where is she?
Are you alone?
I gave you my word, right?
Even though this meeting is
in front of a police station, I'm here.
You didn't really have
much of a choice about that.
With the rest of your pack in the zoo
making such a mess of things.
Where is she? Locked up at the station?
Or am I here just to be intimidated?
Relax.
The baby savage is fine.
First, you need to tell me
where my money is.
I wanna see if she's okay first.
What's that saying
you gangsters keep repeating?
Um…
"What's right is right."
Isn't that it?
Wait.
What the fuck is this?
-Elisa! Elisa!
-Requesting backup! Requesting backup!
Get back here, dammit!
Cris!
-What was that?
-Get down! Get down!
What's going on? See anything?
-Elisa! Elisa!
-Take her! Go! Now!
This is the fucking Brotherhood!
Get down! Get down!
Hey, hey, hey! Come here!
Go, kid! Go make a name for yourself!
Come on! Let's go! Let's go!
Get out of the way! Go!
Here you go,
you sons of bitches! Take this!
Take this you fucking pigs!
Go! Go, go, go, go!
Motherfucker, go!
Motherfucker! You fucking deserve it!
-Fucking bitch! You set me up, didn't you?
-I don't know anything about this!
Cris!
Elisa!
-Cris!
-Elisa!
Cris!
Elisa!
-Cris!
-Elisa!
-Get me out of here!
-Elisa! No!
-Cris!
-No!
Sir, is it possible to tell me
the account holder's ID number, please?
But I've given you
my ID number three times.
My problem isn't that hard to solve.
I just need you to check if--
My God. What was that?
São Paulo police are currently
being held hostage by the criminals.
The city now faces a day of chaos
with attacks happening in several regions.
Guys, look, isn't that the station
just down the street?
…was shot at about half an hour ago.
The atmosphere is one of tension and fear.
Everyone. Over here, please.
I need everybody's attention for a minute.
Look, because of the situation
on the streets,
I'm gonna let everyone go home, okay?
But don't panic. Just get your bags
and your stuff and let's go.
I'll try to take the subway.
-It's a nightmare.
-Are you getting reception?
Hello? I'm on my way now.
Stay there. Don't go anywhere.
Don't leave the house.
Move it, Grandma!
Somebody needs to be
home when they get there.
Incinerated buses,
banks, and security forces under fire.
Watch out! Come on! Move it!
It's a war. There's shooting happening.
The kids are in school!
I have to pick up my son!
-Get out of the way!
-Stay there! I'll be there soon!
Stay there. Don't move.
Give him some cover, man.
It'll be smooth as silk.
Just gimme a minute.
What's going on?
Here. It's an open line.
Hey, bro,
I've seen guys hide shit up their asses,
but in their fat rolls,
it's the first time.
Watch it, dude. Come on.
I wonder what else he's got in there.
-Hello.
-It's me. I'll be quick.
I need you in the negotiation.
Go back and talk to the secretary.
You need to tell him
that the price of peace
is for them to drop the transfer.
Negotiate with what?
Do you really think
that with all these riots going on,
with this many cops getting killed,
that they're gonna revoke the transfer?
The press is all over it.
That's the point.
If they don't agree to it, we keep up
the attack until they fucking surrender.
This shit has kept me
from paying the ransom for Elisa.
She should be home by now, dammit!
We'll send someone to find her
while you take care of this.
Who knows if she's alive, Ivan?
There are people dying
right now as we speak.
I need you to trust me.
The governor will give in.
Now tell me.
I need to know if you're gonna--
What I'm saying is that
I'll never forgive you
if something happens to her.
Dammit, Christina, listen for once!
I'm running out of time.
Just do your job.
Set up a meeting with him.
Negotiate this fucking transfer.
Now you wanna negotiate?
Why don't you send Minor?
Come on. Hide that phone, Ivan.
What's it gonna be, Cris?
Am I gonna be left to rot in solitary?
I won't even be able
to see you during visitation.
Is that what you want for us?
We're fucking there.
Make room for fresh meat.
The big boss is here.
Cristina.
You know there's no going back, right?
Ivan.
Big boss my ass.
That son of a bitch's reign is over.
-That's for sure.
-Cristina.
-Come on. Hide that phone!
-Cris.
-Do it now!
-Cristina.
While the population
hides behind locked doors,
criminals act with military boldness.
Organized crime has declared war
against the state.
Chaos has taken over the streets
and fear has spread like wildfire.
The city that never sleeps…
…is now living a waking nightmare.
Hey, Sarge. Where the fuck are you?
Tell me where you are, man.
I'm worried about you.
Did those motherfuckers
do anything to you, Anselmo?
Listen, I still have the package here,
but I can't keep her much longer.
I need you to tell me what to do.
Don't leave me alone. Call me.
Could I have some water?
Hmm.
Don't you think it's weird
he's not answering and he left you alone?
Shut up. Nobody asked you anything.
Well, it looks like he knew
the plan wouldn't work and he split.
He'll lay all the blame on you.
It's obvious you don't have
anything to do with this.
There's still time to fix it.
-You just have to let me go--
-Shut up! Shut the fuck up!
What do you think, that I'm stupid?
Do I look like an idiot?
Let you go.
No one's letting you go, dammit.
I'll only let you leave
when the fucking phone rings.
And you better hope… no, pray…
pray that nothing happened
to any of my partners.
'Cause if something happened,
you're gonna pay for it.
Wait, I also don't agree
with what the radio says
the Brotherhood is doing.
You don't agree, my ass, girl.
The fuck you don't.
You hate the police.
And I don't just mean thugs.
I mean everyone.
There's always someone like you
clapping and shouting,
lighting fireworks when one of us falls.
It's not hate.
It's fear.
We've always been more scared of you
than the criminals.
Ask anyone, they'll tell you the same.
The police
are out there to protect good people,
risking their lives and earning peanuts.
Now, as for the thugs,
with thugs, little girl,
we have to come down hard.
Or do you think
there's other ways to get justice?
Depends on what you think justice is.
Is this justice? Hmm?
That's all I needed.
Getting a fucking lecture from a thug.
Is that why you joined the police?
You're a coward.
Shut up!
The city is now officially in lockdown,
and public transportation
has been suspended.
Stores and banks are closed.
Classes have been suspended in schools.
Furthermore, the rebellions
inside the prisons continue to escalate…
Here's the address.
Shoot to kill, got it?
Remember, every cop has a gun at home.
-Don't screw this up, guys.
-All right, let's go.
-Let's go, brothers.
-Get outta here.
-Stay sharp. Let's go.
-Hey, Counselor.
-Justice. Let's move.
-Let's get this done.
Let's go. Come on.
Hey, Rui. I need your help with something.
You know I have
the utmost respect for you, right?
What is it?
Look, Counselor, I'm fully aware
that this family would never be what it is
if it weren't for your work.
But I just got orders from above
not to cooperate with you anymore.
Listen to me.
I got you into this family.
I'm responsible for your success.
You know I've always done the right thing.
I know that.
-But I got orders--
-But nothing.
The fucking pigs have my niece, dammit.
Her life is in danger.
So fuck Ivan.
Tell me what you need.
I just need you to get
the address of the pig who's got her.
Civil police?
Military.
If you know the area where he operates in…
60th Battalion.
The bastard didn't even bother to hide it.
I know his face. Pull it up.
Okay, I'll see what I can do.
-Son of a bitch.
-Is that him?
No, that one's gone. Keep going.
Here!
"André Luis Borges."
Got him.
Stores closed early,
classes were suspended,
and several bus lines are not running.
São Paulo faces a wave
of coordinated attacks by the Brotherhood.
The organization
has attacked several targets,
showing strength inside
and outside the prisons.
In the midst of the crossfire,
a curfew has been imposed in the capital.
It's not even 6:00 p.m.
and the largest city in the country
is now a ghost town.
I go down this street every day.
Today, it feels like a different city.
I've never seen anything like this.
They sent everyone home.
How am I supposed to get home?
I waited two hours for the bus.
Hands on your head!
-Everyone against the wall!
-You, in the middle.
-Everyone against the fucking wall!
-Come on!
-Go, go, go, go!
-Please, sir. I'm a working man.
-I just came--
-Who the fuck asked you?
You only speak when I tell you. Got it?
Anyone here got a record?
Do you guys speak my language or not?
Does anyone here have a record?
Here, Captain.
Turn around, dammit!
This one's a convict.
A Christian with tattoos?
-You got a record, right, man?
-I'm a working man, sir.
Hey, ma'am.
What the hell are you doing
out of your house, ma'am?
Get over there!
Go on, now!
-I've already served my time.
-Who fucking cares?
You mess with the cops,
you die, motherfucker.
Son!
My son.
André.
-André.
-Hey, Mom.
Oh, my son.
-Thank God you're okay.
-Mm…
Blessed be His name.
How come you're home so early?
Weren't you going to church?
People all over the city
are just getting murdered.
It's like a war.
You wouldn't believe
what I went through to get here, son.
-But are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
But I was worried sick.
What happened to your car?
Did someone shoot at you?
Long story, Mom.
You know I can take care of myself, right?
If I ever lose you, my son,
I'll ask God to take me too.
Don't even think that, Mom.
I prayed so much
for you to be a police officer.
But I don't know if I did the right thing.
There's so much evil in the world,
sometimes I think hell is right here.
Well, I think I need a shower.
No! Hey!
Uh, Mom, I…
I only had breakfast today.
I had a shitty day.
And the only thing that got me through it
was knowing that, when I got home,
I would get to eat Mrs. Ângela's food.
Oh, sweetie.
I was wondering if you could
make us some french fries.
Oh, sweetie, what I wouldn't do for you.
My God.
Fries, sweetie?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Answer, motherfucker.
Anselmo, where the fuck are you?
They're killing everyone,
and I'm alone with the girl.
I don't know what to do with her anymore.
I'm doing this for you, man.
Did they do anything to you?
Answer the fucking--
Fuck!
Fuck, man!
Get me out of here.
-What's going--
-Be quiet. Be quiet, dammit.
No.
Shut up.
Shut up. Shut the fuck up.
Quiet, dammit!
Shut up.
Shut up!
For God's sake! What's going on here?
Are you okay, dear?
Please tell me you are okay.
For the love of God! What's going on here?
Who is this girl?
What were you doing to her, André Luis?
-Tell me!
-Calm down.
I can explain, Mom.
André Luis, please,
just tell me what's happening.
What's happening, Mom,
is that all these men are out there.
There was a major issue at work
so I had to bring this shit home.
Now you do your thing.
Don't bother me. Don't meddle!
This was that partner of yours,
wasn't it, André Luis?
I told you that man is not your friend!
Of course he's my friend, Mom.
I'm his son's godfather.
But he's not a good person.
I know you'd never do
something like that alone.
What do you mean, Mom? Just look around.
They're all bad people, all thugs!
Look what they're doing to the city!
Oh, so now you're God?
Dealing out justice?
Stop it, André Luis.
That's not how I raised you.
Are you listening to me?
Look, you just stay here,
and I'm gonna go solve this problem.
You can't just leave her anywhere.
You worry too much, Mom.
You're gonna get me in trouble.
I'm going to get you in trouble?
Look what you've brought into our house!
What's that? What's that money, Mom?
It's the emergency money I saved.
You're a good boy, son.
I'm not going to let you ruin your life
over something you did
in the heat of the moment, André Luis.
It's decided, son. Go on!
Go get the girl upstairs.
Elisa! Elisa!
-Cris!
-Elisa!
-Help me. I want to get out.
-Thank God.
-Get me out. I'm tied up.
-I'll help you out.
-I'll get you out of here.
-Uh-huh.
Calm down.
Take it. C'mon, c'mon, c'mon.
Let's go. Get up.
What are you gonna do to me?
-Shut up.
-Let me go, for God's sake.
Shut up and get down there.
Stay there.
Calm down.
Be fucking quiet.
Calm down. There's still time
to get the money you want. Listen to me.
Shut up!
Nightly News is brought to you by Fresh.
Daily relief.
Fresh breath, guaranteed confidence.
Mom, what are you doing?
Don't take her hood off.
We're far from home.
Where are we going?
Calm down. Everything will be fine.
For God's sake. Where are you taking me?
You should thank God every day
that my mother crossed your path.
Hear me, pretty girl?
You have ten new voicemails.
To listen to your messages, press one.
Dude, where are you? I keep calling
and you're not answering, dammit.
I'm worried.
Did you hear about Anselmo?
Those Brotherhood motherfuckers
killed him.
His wife just got here.
I didn't know what to say.
They shot him in the face.
Call me, brother.
I hope you get this message.
Get out.
Come on. Are you deaf? Get out.
What are you going to do?
Take her to the station,
put her on a train.
No. You don't have to.
I can't do anything.
-I just wanna go home.
-Shut up! Shut up!
-Do you wanna die?
-No one is going to die.
We've talked about this.
Let the girl go. She's suffered enough.
Go, my dear. Go home.
Live your life. Forget about us.
My son is not a bad person.
He's just followed his partner
into this stupid mess.
He's easily influenced.
Think twice before you talk about Anselmo
in front of me again. You hear me?
Or I'll lose my patience with you too.
-What are you saying, son?
-Get in the car.
Get in the car.
-What are you doing?
-You stay here.
But please, son.
-Attention…
-Hey, hey, hey, hey!
-Not that way. Keep walking.
-…transfers between lines is suspended.
Calm down. Let's talk.
This isn't what we agreed on.
I don't make agreements
with fucking thugs. Just keep walking.
-Move, dammit.
-Where are we? What the fuck?
Move, dammit! Move!
-Wait.
-You people killed my partner, dammit.
You killed my partner. Is that justice?
Is leaving his son
without a father justice?
Please.
Who the fuck's that? Who's there?
You're gonna pay, motherfucker.
You think you can fucking run from me?
Attention.
Train service and transfer
between lines is suspended.
We appreciate your understanding.
I'm gonna get you, little rat!
You can't hide from me.
Motherfucker!
Cris! Help me! Over here!
Elisa!
-Cris!
-Run!
Run. I'm still gonna catch you.
Run all you want!
Run, Elisa! Run!
Attention.
Train service and transfer
between lines is suspended.
We appreciate your understanding.
Attention.
Train service and transfer between lines…
-Sh! It's me. It's me.
-Auntie! Thank God!
Are you okay?
I am, but he's crazy.
He's gonna kill me, Cris.
Where is he?
Fuck.
Come on. Come here.
Move. Go.
Get down, Elisa! Get down!
-Cris!
-Stay there. Stay there.
Attention.
Train service and transfer…
Go, go, go, go, go!
Run!
You're both going down!
Come on! Come on!
Let's go, Cris! Let's go!
Go. Go, go, go. Run.
Run and don't look back. Go!
Don't look back.
Oh God! Look out!
Get down.
Go! Go, go!
Get up there.
Attention.
Train service and transfer
between lines is suspended.
We appreciate your understanding.
I'll hunt you down to hell!
Where is my son? Where is my son?
Come on.
Come on!
Get in the car!
Let's go, Cris.
What are you doing? Please, let's go.
WHAT'S RIGHT IS RIGHT
I heard gunshots.
What's happening? Are you okay?
Mom, what are you doing out here?
I told you to stay in the car.
-Do what I say. Get in. Get in, Mom.
-Let's go home, son!
-Which way did they go?
-They went that way.
Stay here.
Tico, son, let's get out of here!
Mom.
Mom. Mom. Mom. Mommy.
No. No, Mom, no.
No. Mom.
Mom.
Mom. Mom. Mom. Mom!
Breathe, Mom. Breathe.
Look at me.
Look at me, Mom.
Mom.
I'm sorry, Mom. I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm gonna get you outta here, Mom.
I'll get you out.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Easy now. Breathe slowly. Breathe slowly.
Slowly. Mom. Mom. Mom, easy, easy.
I'm sorry, Mom.
-I'm gonna get you outta here.
-Enough.
I'm gonna get you outta here.
Come on. Come on. Breathe, Mom.
-Don't leave me here alone.
-We should go.
Mom.
-Stay with me, Mom. Please.
-Come on.
No, no, no, no, no. No, no.
Mom. Mom.
-I love you, Tico.
-Don't go.
Take her to the hospital, please.
Don't leave.
No, no, no. Mom.
Mom, breathe. Breathe, Mom!
Breathe, Mom. Breathe!
Don't leave me! Don't go.
-Come on. Hurry up.
-No! No!
No! Motherfuckers!
Motherfuckers!
He shot you.
How can I help? Fuck. Tell me, Cris.
Hurry!
You're bleeding too much.
It's too much, Cris.
Hurry, Cris!
Faster! Hurry, Cris.
We can make it. Come on.
Fuck. You're bleeding too much.
Fuck! Come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on!
Shit!
-Stop the car! Stop the car!
-What the fuck's going on?
Stop the car! Who the fuck are you?
-What are you doing here?
-I'm the Counselor.
-Turn the car around!
-Let us through! We have to go!
Are you fucking deaf?
Turn the fucking car around!
-Counselor?
-We own this city!
It's about time!
She's hurt. We need to go to the hospital.
It's the Counselor! She's injured, dammit!
It's the fucking Counselor!
It's the Counselor!
-Let them through!
-Clear the road!
-Come on! Open this shit!
-Let us through!
I'm Edson's daughter!
I'm Savage's daughter!
-The Counselor is in the car!
-Time to light it up!
We need to get to the hospital!
Let's fucking go! Where's the fire?
Help me out! Help!
-Someone help me!
-Brotherhood, baby!
Throw that thing already!
This is the Brotherhood! We own this shit!
-Brotherhood!
-It's the Brotherhood, bitches!
Come on! Hurry up!
That's enough! Let's go!
Come on. Come on. Let me drive. Come here.
Hold on tight.
Come on, come on. I got you.
They're coming! Get ready!
Here! Let's go! Come on!
Fuck, Cris! Talk to me!
You're the strongest woman I know.
You can make it.
Come on, Cris.
Edson…
He would be so proud
of the woman you've become.
Forgive me, Elisa.
Forgive me.
Stop, auntie. Don't do…
Don't do this to me. Stop, auntie.
Cris. Auntie.
You're all I have. Don't do this to me.
Don't do this to me. Auntie, look at me.
You're my family. Don't do this to me.
Auntie.
Auntie!
Auntie, come on! Auntie!
Auntie. Auntie.
Auntie, no.
Auntie. No.
No.
No, auntie. Auntie!
Auntie!
It's okay.
Let me go.
I must wander.
I'll go around, searching,
smiling…
…so I don't cry.
I want to see the sun rising.
See the waters of the rivers flowing.
Listen to the birds singing.
I want to be born.
I want to live.