Downloaded from
YTS.BZ
Official YIFY movies site:
[thunder rumbles softly]
[ominous music]
[car engine revving]
[song on car radio]
♪ All day long I'm racin'
♪ Get up to the floor
[chilling music]
- [car engine revving]
- ♪ Get me out
♪ Think I've lost control
♪ Get me out
[car engine revving]
[loud music on car radio]
♪ Get it out get it out
Get it out come on ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ I gotta run back run back
Around the sun ♪
[car engine revving]
♪ Get it out get it out
Before I lose my mind ♪
[loud thump]
[truck horn blaring]
[car tires screeching]
♪ ...I'm runnin'
- [James panting]
- ♪ Runnin' from my past
[Mary] Oh, come on.
- [running footsteps]
- [Mary panting]
You've got to be kidding me.
♪ Get me out
[car door opens]
[music stops]
I am so sorry. I--
Are you okay?
Yeah.
No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Here, let me help you.
[both panting]
Uh...
Sorry about all this.
[bus honking]
- [Mary] Sure, okay.
- [James] I got it.
The latch is broken.
[grunts]
Shit, that's my bus.
Hey.
Hey. Hey, hey! Wait!
Hang on, I got it.
[groans] Oh, fuck.
[bus honking]
You can just... Sorry.
[bus door closes]
[groans]
[bus departing]
[James] Well, I'm officially
an asshole.
Where were you heading?
[Mary] The city.
Where were you going?
Just up the pass.
I guess
it wasn't meant to be.
So what are you gonna do?
Can just head back
into town, I guess.
[James] What's it called?
[Mary] Silent Hill.
There's a trail down that way.
Cool.
What's that down there
on the water?
That's the Lakeview.
It's a hotel.
The view of the lake
from the rooftop is so pretty.
Pretty enough
they named a hotel after it?
You nearly run me down,
and now you're giving me
a hard time?
Yeah, shit. Sorry. Um...
[chuckles]
I deserved that, didn't I?
Mm. I'm James, by the way.
Mary.
Well, like, seriously, Mary,
let me drive you home.
I can save you
a sprained ankle or two.
I don't even know you, James.
All right. Well, I'm just
gonna have to stand here,
watch you go down,
make sure you don't fall.
Seems like
appropriate penance
for screwing up my day.
[birds chirping]
[sniffles]
So, are you coming or what?
[suitcases thudding]
[hood shuts]
[wind whooshing]
[ominous music swells]
[leaves rustling]
Silent Hill summer storm.
Doesn't happen often.
But when it does...
[gasps sharply]
[club music playing]
[phone vibrating]
[sniffles]
[beer mug clanks]
Think it's time to go.
All right. All right.
[James groans]
- Jesus!
- [glass shatters]
[James] Sorry.
Sorry. That's on me.
[Bouncer] Let's go, asshole.
[grunts and groans]
[furniture clattering]
- [phone vibrating]
- [Man] Ass hole!
[phone vibrating]
- [Man] Get outta here.
- [Bouncer] Let's go. Let's go.
[James] Yeah? Come on!
Come on!
Yo, get the fuck off me!
Let go of me! [grunts]
Fuck you! Fuck you!
[men grunt with effort]
[Bouncer] Nighty night, fucker.
[rock music playing]
[door slams]
[phone vibrating]
[James groans]
[M, over phone] There you are.
How are you?
[James, over phone]
Not so great.
[M] You've been drinking.
It felt like we were moving
in the right direction, James.
I know. [groans]
[M, over phone] You've got
to stop beating yourself up.
[James sighs]
Here's what I need you to do.
Get home, drink some water,
get some sleep.
Reset and come
to our appointment tomorrow.
Yeah, tomorrow.
Yeah. Okay.
[distant sirens wailing]
We'll see.
[claps of thunder]
[heavy downpour of rain]
[lock clicks, door opens]
[door slams shut]
[keys thud]
[James sighs deeply]
[rain pattering]
[disturbing music playing]
[sharp gasp,
groaning in pain]
Oh, God.
[bottle thuds, rolling]
[unsettling music]
[soft piano music]
[thunder rumbles]
[Mary] James,
so much time has passed.
- [keys jingling]
- I know that.
But I'm asking--
I'm begging you
to please come back.
To our place.
Something's happened.
Please, James. I need you.
Love, Mary.
[engine revving]
[soft piano music continues]
[breathing heavily]
[rain pattering]
[car engine reving]
[car engine stops]
[loud clap of thunder]
- Jesus.
- [car door shuts]
[rain pattering on car roof]
[James, voice-over] It's her.
It's always been her.
Mary.
[inaudible]
The girl of my dreams.
The love of my life.
[coughing]
[breathing heavily]
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
[crunching footsteps]
[birds chirping]
[door creaks open]
[low creaking]
[faucets clatter]
[pensive music]
[James, voice-over] Our place.
Our town.
[car beeps]
Our love.
It was here.
It was everywhere.
[uneasy music]
And now, they keep telling me
to let go.
To move on.
But how can I ever do that?
When you're calling me?
[ominous music]
[eerie music]
[rustling]
Hello?
[breathing heavily]
Grab a bag.
What?
[Woman] Careful.
They're heavy.
So, where's all this
coming from?
[Woman] This?
You mean the ashes?
[James] Yeah.
[Woman] It started with
the fires in the summer.
[panting]
Tore through the forests.
Some are still burning.
And then came the rains.
Right.
So, there's someone...
someone I care about,
and I need to find her.
[panting] You won't.
Floods overran
the water treatment plant.
When water
gets contaminated,
people don't stick around.
Look, I'm still going to try
and head into town
if you could just...
Well...
thanks, anyway.
Wait.
You don't find
who you're looking for,
you can always
come back and find me.
I'm Angela.
Angela.
Sure.
[soft dramatic music]
[Mary sighs]
[James] So, what if I...
moved here?
No museums. No clubs.
Zero anonymity.
Yeah, I'm just
as shocked as you are.
You'd really
want to move here?
I would.
Why?
Well, there's this girl.
And she's not much
to look at, but...
[kissing]
What?
You don't think we're ready
to live together?
There are parts of me
you haven't seen.
What if who I am scares you?
It won't.
I promise you.
[kissing]
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Hey now, now tilt
your head back.
[Mary groans]
[both laughing]
[Mary]
I can't believe this.
[James] It's okay. I got you.
I'm here.
I'll always be here.
I mean it.
[disturbing rhythmic drumbeats]
[ominous music]
[glass squeaks]
I don't understand.
[flies buzzing]
[panting]
[whispers] This is insane.
[running footsteps]
[breathing heavily]
[shouts] Hello?!
Can anyone hear me?
[soft music in the distance]
Is someone there?
[music on speaker]
Hello?
[solemn music
playing on speaker]
[faint music playing]
[running footsteps]
[music gets louder]
[man snoring]
Hello?
Can you hear me?
[metal clanks]
[static on radio,
distorted music]
[radio stops]
[breathing shakily]
- [James gasps]
- They're coming back.
- Who?
- You know they're coming back.
All that darkness,
you can't keep it away.
Just-just-just
get off me, all right?
[panting in fear]
[phone vibrating]
I wasn't expecting
a no-show, James.
I'm in Silent Hill.
[M, over phone] What?
I did--something's
happened here.
Something really, really bad.
[M] James.
Listen to me carefully.
This is getting out of control.
[James] I need to go home...
to Mary.
[M] What did you say?
I need you to come back.
There's no home
for you there anymore.
[signage buzzing]
[M] James?
James?
[groaning]
[crunching footsteps]
[signage buzzing]
[groaning]
[static noise from radio]
[creature screeches]
[club music playing on speaker]
[Mary] I thought
you'd never come!
- Everyone... this is James.
- Hi.
[Claudette] So Mary tells me
you're an artist.
[James] Yeah. Painter.
[Claudette] And you have
the perfect muse.
Our Mary,
she's something special.
Sparkling little apple
of her father's eye.
Oh, so you all know him, or...?
[chuckling]
Know him?
Joshua Crane.
Doesn't quite do it justice
when you say it out loud.
[in unison] He changed
our lives.
Mary's family,
they built this town.
Gave us purpose.
My life was spinning out
in all directions.
Helped me put my head
back on straight.
I think we all
have a similar story.
Mm.
We have a way of seeing things
here in Silent Hill.
But don't worry.
I'm sure
we'll find a place for you.
[screams outside]
[footsteps]
What is that?
[flesh squelching]
[radio crackling]
[creature snarling]
Who is that?!
[sinister music]
[creature shrieks]
[straining effort]
[creature screeches]
[trembling breath]
[tense music]
[metallic clatter]
[creature snarling]
[breathing heavily]
[static from radio]
[Man] This is the Silent Hill
Emergency Operations System.
This is not a test.
City officials have issued
a health emergency
for the city of Silent Hill
and surrounding areas.
Residents are being ordered
to evacuate
the area immediately.
I repeat, this is not a test.
What you are hearing
is not a test.
This is the emergency
alert system.
- Civil authorities are issuing--
- [emergency alert blaring]
[wings flapping]
[ground cracking]
[low rumbling]
[creature screeches]
[tense music]
[screeching]
[footsteps clanging]
[James groans in pain]
[rats squeaking]
[James grunts with effort]
[pipe clanging]
[squelching]
[insects chittering]
[footsteps clanging]
[eerie shrieking]
[tense music]
[squeaking]
[James grunts]
[straining]
[insects chittering]
[James grunts]
[yells in pain]
[panting]
[insects bustling]
[soft tense music]
[panting]
[soft squelching]
[eerie squeal]
[Mary, whispers] James.
Mary?
[soft, suspenseful music]
Hello, handsome.
How many times you get lost
this time around?
I just can't believe
how much stuff I had.
Come on, one last push.
Mm-hmm.
[kissing]
Let me help you with this.
Ooh, why thank you.
[Mary] [chuckles softly]
You're so welcome.
[tense music]
[footsteps approaching]
[door hinges squeak]
[white noise from TV]
[static buzzing]
[grunting in pain]
[screaming]
[loud droning]
[whimpering]
[groaning]
[phone ringing]
[James panting over phone]
Where are you?
[groaning]
It hurts so bad. I can't...
I can't make it stop.
It's gonna be okay.
Just tell me where you are.
[James] No. No.
No, I can feel her.
She's close.
- I think she's--
- [phone cuts out]
James? James?
[panting]
[groaning]
[thunder rumbling]
[heavy downpour]
[rain pattering]
[voicemail] The mailbox
is full
and cannot accept
any messages at this time.
Goodbye.
[phone thuds]
[phone clicking]
[Man] Hello?
It's me.
Yes. One of my patients
who's broken protocol,
I need a wellness check.
[Man] Which patient?
James Sunderland.
[Man] Is he a danger
to himself or anyone?
I wouldn't say dangerous but...
he's in trouble.
[rain pattering]
[metal clanks]
[door opens]
[James panting]
[wings flapping]
[James groans]
[James panting]
[tense music]
[door opens]
- [keys thud]
- Mare?
[distant chanting]
We understand completely
how you feel.
[voice echoes]
[overlapping whispers]
Love is not an easy thing.
[voice echoes]
You can get your head
all twisted around.
You can lose yourself in it.
[voice echoes]
[overlapping whispers]
But we need to stay focused.
[door creaks]
[whispering stops abruptly]
And here he is.
The man of the house.
What's going on, Jimmy boy?
What's going on here?
[footsteps]
[soft tense music]
Okay. What the fuck was that?
I'm sorry.
They just showed up.
Wait, they just showed up?
Twenty people
just showed up?
Again?
They're fucking weird, Mary.
They're my family, James.
They took me in
after my father died.
All right.
[uneasy music]
Is that him?
[blowing]
[closet door closes]
[sighs]
Please, James...
Please.
I want this to be
about you and me.
Always.
Always just us.
[tense music]
[wings flapping]
[James sighs]
Brookhaven Hospital?
[distant coughing]
[gagging]
[retching]
[coughing]
What the fuck?
[James] Are you okay?
It look like I'm okay?
[breathing heavily]
Who the hell are you?
I'm-I'm James. I'm--
Wait, why are you not sick
like everyone else?
What? No, I'm-I'm looking
for someone.
[Eddie] Ain't nobody here.
[James]
No, they're at the hospital.
[scoffs]
[laughing]
What's funny?
Look around, buddy.
Won't find anyone
at the hospital.
City's one big cemetery.
Oh, God.
What is happening?
You should have seen it.
No one could get their ass
in gear to react in time.
Poor fucks.
Whole town was rotten
before anyways, but this,
this was something else.
The fires...
the water...
everybody going insane,
bleeding to death
out on the streets.
All that crazy shit happened,
and then these things
start to show up.
[breathing hard]
Wow.
You've been lucky so far.
What?
Check this.
Jesus Christ.
[panting]
So, what is it you do?
What do you mean,
what do I do?
In life. What do you do?
I'm a--I'm a painter.
A painter, huh?
I ever heard of you?
I really don't know.
Always thought I had
the goods to be an artist.
You ever have weird dreams?
The shit that goes on in there,
you couldn't handle it.
[baby screaming]
[James] Do you hear that?
Hear what?
Sounds like a baby.
A baby?
There ain't no baby here.
[footsteps]
Can I ask a question?
Why would you stay here?
You kidding? Place is rid
of all these assholes.
It's heaven now.
Got the entire city to myself.
[distant baby cooing]
There...
What the hell is this?
Holy shit.
Uh-uh, be careful.
What are you talking about?
It's just a kid.
Hey, what's your name?
I'm James.
And this is--
Eddie.
I'm Laura.
[James] Laura?
Oh, you can't just stay in there
all by yourself, Laura.
Come on. I think
you might be small enough
to get through these bars.
Come on.
[Eddie] Let's get out of here.
[James] Come on, it's okay.
You can trust me.
You can trust me. Come on.
I'm telling you,
this is a bad idea.
[James] Come on, Laura.
I got you. Come on.
We can help you.
[loud crackle,
radio screeches]
We need to get
our asses outta here.
Come on, Laura.
It's all right.
We're not gonna leave
without you. Come on.
Just a bit closer.
- Come on, Laura.
- [distant growling]
- Come on.
- [Laura gasps]
[Eddie] Jimmy, let's go!
[James groans]
[metal scraping]
Would you look at that?
You're all fucked up
like everyone else.
[heavy footsteps]
Get lost, kid!
Why would you do that,
you asshole?!
[James groans]
[metal scraping]
What is it you called me
again, Jimmy boy?
An asshole?!
Oh, shit.
You did it, didn't ya, Jimmy?
You woke him up.
[panting]
[suspenseful music]
[Pyramid Head growling]
[groaning in pain]
[panting]
[metal bending]
[sinister music]
[crashing]
[sinister music continues]
[bones crackling]
[James] Mary?
[music intensifies]
[footsteps depart]
[creature growling]
[loud screech]
[panting]
[strains]
[grunts in frustration]
[distant growling]
[James bangs on board]
[spider squealing]
[closet door closes]
[breathing heavily]
[spider screeches]
[footsteps thudding]
[thudding]
[eerie squealing]
[door thuds]
[growling and groaning]
[thudding]
[stabs sword]
[James gasps]
[rapid punching]
[tense music]
[quavering breath]
[suspenseful music]
[shallow breathing]
[Pyramid Head growls]
[shuddering]
[footsteps stomp]
[emergency alarm blaring]
[both screaming]
[screams fade]
[James winces]
[breathing heavily]
What is going on here?
I told you not to come.
There are secrets buried here.
They need to stay that way.
What secrets? What secrets?
What you're doing...
it won't be enough to save her.
You can't save her, James.
What do you mean, save her?
Save her from what?
Stay where you are!
Wait, wait. I'm not
trying to hurt you. I...
Please...
You don't know what kind of
hell you have to face.
I didn't leave.
None of us left!
Don't touch me!
No one will touch me again!
Go.
Just go.
[Angela sobbing]
[somber music]
[running footsteps]
[distant baby crying]
[light buzzing]
Shh. You don't have to cry.
I'm right here.
You're gonna be okay.
Hey.
It's Laura, right?
How did you get yourself
up there?
He was crawling
on the ground.
Who was?
A monster!
I was very scared.
But I didn't cry.
- Catch me!
- What? [grunts]
[breathing heavily]
What is that?
Show me your doll.
Mary gave it to me.
What?
What did you just say?
Who gave you the doll, Laura?
Mary.
Mary? Mary Crane?
[distant clank]
That's him!
What?
Hey! Laura?
[running footsteps]
[footsteps approaching]
[ominous music]
Laura, wait!
[panting]
[soft brooding music]
[chuckles softly]
Stop, please!
[footsteps]
[distant whispering voices]
[tense music]
[whispering voices continue]
Laura?
Laura!
[footsteps]
Laura?
[Maria] I've been watching you.
You're not from here, are you?
I'm just looking
for this kid.
She's all on her own.
What?
Are you just gonna
keep on staring,
or are you going
to say something?
Sorry.
[Maria] So...
what's your plan?
My plan? Plan for what?
For getting us
the hell out of this place?
No, I'm not leaving.
I'm looking for the hospital.
Why?
Because my girlfriend's there.
Everyone got sick
in Silent Hill.
How long has your girlfriend
been in the hospital for?
I'm-I'm not sure.
I thought you said
she was your girlfriend.
We've been apart.
So, she was
your girlfriend?
Look, I just need to find her.
All right.
Got it.
Let's find her then.
Just wanted to make sure
you were real.
[tense music]
I don't get it.
Why are you helping me?
You're the first normal
person I've met in weeks.
Strength in numbers.
You don't look like
you've been here weeks.
[Maria] Why, thank you.
You, on the other hand...
[James] What?
You look fucked.
[scoffs]
[footsteps]
- [radio screeches]
- Shit. Come on.
- What?
- Every time this thing goes off,
something's getting close.
- Come on.
- What?
Shit. Come on.
Quick, this way.
[creature screeching]
Shh. Hide, hide, hide.
[suspenseful music]
[squelching]
[both shuddering]
[acid melting]
[pensive music]
[muted chatter]
[indistinct conversation]
[suspenseful music]
[tense music]
[gate rattles]
[poster tearing]
[gate clanks]
[James panting]
[footsteps]
[gate rattling, clanks]
[trash can sliding]
[hissing]
[iron door rumbling]
[footsteps]
[water dripping]
[distant voices chanting]
[Maria] James!
Hey, hey. You all right?
Yeah, yeah.
We need to go.
The hospital's close.
[soft, tense music]
[metal clanks]
[keyboard tapping]
[James] Everything's dead.
[folder thuds]
So, walk me through this.
You're looking for your
kind-of girlfriend.
That's right.
And how long has it been
since you've seen her?
I'm not sure.
And we're sure
she's still your girlfriend?
What?
A girl can get into
a lot of trouble in this town.
Where are you going?
Need to stretch my legs.
[receding footsteps]
Toxicology unit.
I think I found her.
[Doctor, on tape]
Patient admitted at noon
after collapsing in the street.
On admission, she presented
with severe anemia,
high-grade fever,
and significant
subconjunctival
and nasal hemorrhaging.
Initial blood work revealed
critically low platelet levels,
likely due to exposure
to an unidentified substance.
Fever since resolved,
patient remains stable
but physically weakened.
Miss,
do you remember your name?
[Mary, on tape] Mary.
Mary Crane.
[recorder clicks]
There were rumors.
There was this
religious group,
old-school
Silent Hill crazies.
Founded by this preacher
named Joshua Crane.
Even after he died,
they used to worship him
as some kind of prophet or God.
And his daughter,
they would...
Wait.
She's who you're looking for,
isn't she?
[distant voices chanting]
[Doctor, on tape]
Miss Crane,
this drug that they've been
giving you all these years...
[soft, suspenseful music]
[Mary, on tape]
It made me feel whole.
It made me feel part of them.
[breath shuddering]
[crowd chanting]
[shouts] Mary?!
[Doctor, on tape]
It's killed your free will.
[distant singing]
[shouts] Mary!
[Doctor, on tape]
And it's caused permanent damage
to your body.
[shouting] Leave her alone!
[Mary, on tape]
They loved me.
I thought they did.
[crowd] What was his
is now ours.
- [James] Mary!
- What was his is now ours.
[sobbing]
[Mary, on tape] My blood.
[white noise on TV]
[Mary, on tape]
All this blood wasn't mine?
[emergency alarm blaring]
[groaning]
[ground crackling]
[alarm continues]
[crackling]
- [blood splashes]
- [Maria] Let's go!
- [James] What?
- [Maria] Go!
[groaning]
[both panting]
[distant classical music
playing]
[walls crackling]
We've gotta find her.
Now.
[strains]
Come on.
[footsteps thudding]
[both panting]
[door opens]
[dark, suspenseful music]
[rhythmic metal clanking]
[bones cracking]
Come on!
[door opens, squeaks]
[monsters moaning]
[both panting]
[creatures squealing]
[screaming]
[elevator clicking]
Come on, come on.
[skull thuds, crashes]
Here.
[elevator clicking]
[creatures growling, screeching]
[both shuddering]
[growling]
[James grunts]
[shuddering]
James!
[groans]
[grunts]
[strains]
[elevator pings]
[screaming]
[elevator whirring]
[breathing heavily]
[whispers] Help.
Here. Let me see.
- [blood splatters]
- Oh, no.
[groans in pain]
[straining]
[grunting]
[effort grunts]
[Maria groaning]
[breathing heavily]
[James groans]
[doors squeak]
[panting]
- [squelching]
- [gasps, groaning]
You can say it.
What?
I look just like her.
No. No, no, no.
How would you know that?
It's how you look at me.
[breathing deeply]
Look, I'm gonna go upstairs.
I want you to stay here.
[grunts]
No, don't leave me.
You'll be safer here.
I'm gonna look for Mary,
and I'll come right back.
Promise me something.
If you find out she's gone,
we leave.
Together.
We don't look back.
[strains with effort]
[Laura] Who is she?
Just someone
I'm trying to help.
Now, Laura, you have
to tell me where Mary is.
Doesn't look like
you want to find her.
No, I do.
It's all I want.
Now, please, where is she?
My baby's sad!
[doll crying]
He's cold and sad.
Sad because nobody loved him.
Just like Mary.
What?
You left her all...
[shrieks] ...alone!
- Ah!
- [high-pitched ringing]
You have to get to her
before it's too late.
No, wait! Laura!
Laura!
[footsteps thudding on stairs]
Why are you doing this?
No one said
it would be easy.
[door opens, squeaks]
[panting]
No.
[door opens, squeaks]
What?
Laura?
[giggles]
- Laura?!
- [door closes]
Laura?!
Laura, open the door!
- [banging on door]
- Open the door!
[strange growls]
[loud shrieks]
[hospital bed sliding]
[bed clanking]
[Laura] Why'd you come, James?
What did you think you'd find?
[blood drips]
[James] Mary.
[pipe clanks to floor]
[James choking]
[Laura] Come back
when you're ready, James.
- [choking]
- [Doctor] Mr. Sunderland?
Mr. Sunderland?
Are you with us, Mr. Sunderland?
[heart monitor beeping]
What?
What's going on?
Where am I?
Brookhaven Hospital.
Silent Hill.
Where is she?
Where is who?
Mary. Mary Crane.
[footsteps approaching]
What?
Hello, James.
I know where she is.
[breathes heavily]
You need to let go of her.
She's gone.
She's dead, James.
She's been dead
for months now.
You know that.
Why would you say that?
[eerie ambient music]
[M] We've got a lot
of serious work to do.
But we'll get you through it.
You just have to
promise me something.
You need to want to
see yourself get better
as much as I do.
[emotional music]
[car approaching]
[door opens]
[Mary] Why are you
sitting in the dark?
[suitcase slides]
Pack your things.
I want us out of here.
Why are you acting like this?
[James] Guess what I did today.
I saw this girl
across the street...
so I followed her.
[Mary] Stop.
I went down this long
flight of stairs.
[Mary] Stop.
And I saw these monsters.
I saw them tear her apart.
- Just stop!
- [glass shatters]
How long?
Since I was a girl.
Why would your father
do this to you?
I don't know.
I never had a choice.
This is your last chance.
Walk out that door with me now.
Not when you're like this.
What am I like?
Scared.
You think I'm scared?
[raises voice]
I am not scared!
I am not scared of any of you!
[Mary whimpers]
But you're disgusted.
Say it.
Say I'm disgusting to you.
Say it!
That day, I was leaving.
I was leaving,
and then you showed up.
Why-why didn't you
just tell me?
Because I knew you'd walk away.
I see the way
you're looking at me.
That'll never change now.
I told you there were things.
You-you promised me.
[emotional music]
[footsteps receding]
[car alarm beeps]
[car door opens]
[car door shuts]
[Doctor] How is he today?
[M] Calm, I guess.
I've worked with vets,
all kinds of trauma,
but this is different.
He won't let me in at all.
How long have you been
treating him?
Almost a year.
But it's gotten worse.
That woman, Mary,
she was everything to him.
Since her lost her,
it's like he lost
his grip on reality,
and his desire to regain it.
Mary died after their breakup.
And he just won't accept it.
[birds chirping]
[emotional music playing]
It's good to see you up, James.
How are you feeling today?
James?
I just wish...
I wish I hadn't let her down.
You're blaming yourself, but...
all this chaos in your mind...
it's not real.
It’s not real,
and it almost destroyed you.
We can still fix this.
But it's got to be
your decision.
Thank you.
For everything.
[footsteps receding]
[tense, sinister music]
[wings flapping]
[emergency alarm blaring]
[walls crackling]
[Maria] You didn't find her?
Then we can leave.
Together.
[groans]
You promised, James.
[emotional music playing]
You look just like her.
I never told you my name.
It's Maria.
[kissing]
Or we can stay here together...
if you want.
Just us.
What is it?
Where are you going?
[breathing heavily]
James.
Wait for me.
You won't find her down there.
[elevator clanks]
[elevator pings]
Please.
[elevator door closing]
[elevator pings]
[elevator in free fall]
Why are you doing this?
[tense music playing]
You were free of all this pain.
James!
[elevator powering down]
[elevator door opening]
You can't go in there.
Let's go back.
We can still go back.
Please don't go any further.
It's over
if you want it to be.
Mary's not dead.
Not to me.
And you're not real.
You're just in my way.
No.
No, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Look at me, James.
Goodbye, Maria.
[lights flickering, clanking]
[screams in pain]
[wet squelching]
[blood spurting]
[rhythmic heavy clanking]
[bottle clanks]
[James groans]
[water splashes,
blooping softly]
[gasping for air]
[breathing heavily]
[flames roaring]
[roaring fire]
[distant thud]
[Laura] You're finally here.
Laura?
[Laura giggles]
[soft music playing]
[giggles]
[James] I'm not playing
anymore, Laura.
Do you think
you're ready to face it?
you're ready to face us?
[shuddering]
[doll cooing]
[James] Why are you
doing this to me?
To help you remember.
What's her name?
What?
Think, James.
[groans]
What's Mary's full name?
Our full name, James...
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
[Laura] It's time now.
[flames crackling]
And now,
there's nothing left to hide.
[flames crackling]
[door closes]
[eerie ambient music]
[Angela sobbing]
Haven't you had enough?
Disgusting.
You're disgusting!
You--you see.
Please tell me
you can see it.
I can't get away from him.
He'll never stop hurting me.
Let me help you.
Don't! Don't.
Stay away.
[sobbing]
Please.
[grunts]
[growling softly]
[James breathing heavily]
[tense music]
[growling softy]
[James] Mary?
[growling]
[whispers] I'm sorry.
[squeals]
- [door opens]
- [fire roaring]
Mary?!
No, wait!
[running footsteps]
[door opens]
[fire crackling]
[music playing on radio]
[M] You need to let go of her.
She's gone.
She's dead, James.
She's been dead for months now.
You know that.
[birds chirping]
[Mary] You came.
[James] Of course.
As soon as I could.
[Mary] It's okay.
I never should have left.
[Mary] Whether you would've
stayed or not,
I still would've gotten sick.
[James] Well, maybe
I could've helped.
No one could've.
My father poisoned me.
He poisoned me my whole life.
I tried to shield you from it.
I know.
[Mary] Can you help me lie down?
[James] Sure.
[emotional music
playing on radio]
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
[groans]
[silent sobs]
[glass breaks]
Come on.
There you go.
All right.
Just tell me
how I can help you.
You know.
[sniffles]
He's lived inside of me
for so long.
I don't want him there anymore.
I can't do that.
I want to be free.
Please, James.
Please.
Help me now.
[James sobbing]
[emotional music
playing on radio]
[crying]
[wings flapping]
[ground crumbling]
[ethereal music]
[emotional music]
[wings flapping]
That day, I should've
died with you.
[wings flapping]
You forgave me,
but I could never
forgive myself.
I was so selfish, Mare.
Selfish and scared.
[car engine revving]
[water splashes]
[James] I'm ready now.
No matter what it takes.
No matter where it takes us.
This time...
I won't let go.
[Doctor] Mr. Sunderland?
Mr. Sunderland?
[truck honking]
[Doctor] Are you with us,
Mr. Sunderland?
[truck honking]
[tire screeching]
[breathing heavily] What?
[Mary] Oh, come on.
[running footsteps]
You've got to be kidding me.
[emotional music]
I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Are you okay?
I think so.
It's okay. I got it.
The latch is broken.
How do you know that?
[distant honking]
Shit, that's my bus.
Hey, wait!
[suitcase latch snaps]
[horn honks]
Sorry, just...
[bus engine revs]
Where were you heading?
The next city.
Well, I just ruined your day.
Wouldn't be much of a gentleman
if I didn't try and help fix it.
A gentleman?
Didn't know
they made those anymore.
Gentleman named James.
- I'm--
- Mary.
I saw it on your case.
[chuckles]
[car hood shuts]
[wind blows]
You're a painter?
Yeah.
[car door closes]
What do you paint?
[car engine starts, revving]
[funky music playing]
[car tires screech]
[static noise]
["Letter - from the Lost
Days" by Akira Yamaoka]
♪ A letter to my future self
♪ Am I still happy? I began
♪ Have I grown more pretty
♪ Is Daddy still a good man?
♪ Am I still friends
With Colleen ♪
♪ I'm sure that
I'm still laughing ♪
♪ Aren't I?
♪ Hey there to my future self
♪ If you forget how to smile
♪ I have this to tell you
♪ Remember it once in a while
♪ Ten years ago
Your past self ♪
♪ Prayed for your happiness
♪ Please don't lose hope
♪ Oh oh what a pair
♪ Me and you
♪ Put here to feel joy
♪ Not be blue
♪ Sad times and bad times
♪ See them through
♪ Soon we will know
If it's for real ♪
♪ What we both feel
♪ Though I can't know for sure
♪ How things worked out for us
♪ So be happy
♪ For me
♪ For you
♪ Feel joy ♪
[soft piano music]