"Hail Mary, full of grace
the Lord is with thee."
"Blessed art thou among women"
"and blessed is the fruit of thy womb Jesus"
"Holy Mary
Mother of God, pray for us sinners"
"Now and at the hour of our death."
"Amen."
No, no.
No, no!
No, no, no!
No!
"Help!"
Help!
No, no, no!
Please...
help.
"No!"
"Help! Help!"
I'm sorry, but how much
longer will this take?
I've got to take my vows tonight
and I really can't be late.
- Do you speak English?
- Sorry for the wait.
It's extra work now
when someone arrives
without a return ticket.
Parli italiano?
I ask if you're learning Italian.
Oh, I'm trying, but it's
a lot harder than I thought.
Mm.
So this convent
they bought you the ticket?
Mm-hmm.
You're very young
to be a nun, aren't you?
What a waste.
Look at her.
It's a different life, yeah?
It must have been
a hard decision.
I don't think of it like that
as a decision.
Very well.
I hope you find what you're
looking for, Sister Cecilia.
Sister Cecilia
Apologies.
- I'm Deacon Enzo, come with me.
- Thank you.
- "How much longer?"
- We're almost there.
Right this way, Sister Cecilia.
Sister Cecilia!
Reverend Mother.
Your eyes radiate
the light of the Holy Spirit.
Like the angels delivered you
straight from the heavens.
We've been eagerly awaiting
your arrival, my dear.
I'm sorry.
She says you're pretty.
Grazie
I'm Sister Cecilia.
Isabelle.
Isabelle, will you please show Cecilia
to her room?
I have to help our sisters get ready
for tonight's celebration.
Mind your place and do as I ask!
Let me show you
to your room.
Our Lady of Sorrows was founded in 1632
as a refuge for elder sisters
before their transition to heaven.
- It's really beautiful.
- Yes, it is.
- Buongiorno, sorelle.
- Buongiorno.
And we work hard
to keep it that way.
Our sister's final
days should be
a pleasing environment
to help distract from all
the sickness and suffering.
All of this, it was built on
the catacomb of St. Stephen.
Catacombs?
It's off limits.
Hello, Sisters.
- This is our new novice, Sister Cecilia.
- Ciao.
The one in the wheelchair
her tumor has metastasized.
So we expect her to meet God
by the end of the week.
You talk about it so casually.
Death is a part
of everyday life here.
Have you seen my daddy?
Yes, let's go find him, shall we?
It's best to just play along
with their delusions
unless they get violent.
Be careful of this one
She bites.
I'm sorry.
Living quarters for the caretakers
are down there and upstairs.
Morning prayer begins at 5:00 a.m.
communal meal is after.
And if you have any dietary restrictions
we cannot accommodate them.
And this room is yours.
Thank you, Sister.
I feel honored
to serve alongside you.
- You're very sweet.
- Thank you.
I don't mean that
as a compliment.
I'm sure this must feel very romantic
but this is our life.
And I promise you, work is hard
physically and emotionally.
So if you're here to find yourself
there are easier ways.
I'm not.
Tonight, you do not
have to take your vows.
You can still go back
and God will forgive you.
I think he has
sufficiently prepared me.
The ceremony will start
at 1700 in the chapel.
Don't be late.
- Oh, ciao.
- Ciao.
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's fine.
I'm Cecilia.
Oh, I'm Guendalina
You can call me Gwen.
My room is there.
Where in the States
are you from?
- Just outside of Detroit, Michigan.
- Mm-hmm.
- Are you from around here or...
- Closer to Milan.
You're far from home.
Yeah, my parish closed.
Did the priest get in trouble?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
nothing, nothing like that.
Just low attendance.
And that church was
my family, my home.
Leaving, I felt pretty lost.
But then Father Tedeschi
he reached out to me.
Yeah
He has a talent.
Sniffing out broken birds.
Oh, I didn't want
to offend you.
I think that maybe we are all
head cases or runaways.
Which one are you?
Both.
Next time if you want
you can lock the door.
Thanks.
Sister Cecilia.
Father Tedeschi, it's nice
to meet you in person.
We all feel so blessed
to have you here.
How's the Italian coming along?
Così così.
It's fine
I will translate for you.
In the name of the Father, the Son
and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
Let us rejoice, for the marriage
of the Lamb has come
and his brides have
made themselves ready.
Sorella Cecilia.
Sister Cecilia.
Do you promise to follow Christ
more closely by living a life devoid
of material possessions?
Do you promise to free
yourself from the demands
of a human relationship
and follow with joy
when he shall come again...
A vow of poverty
chastity, and obedience?
I do.
May God give you the
strength to fulfill your vows
faithfully and joyfully.
May you shine his light
for the world to see.
- "How are you feeling?"
- Full.
Yeah, we don't...
We don't really have anything
like this back home.
Cecilia, this is your home.
I know, I know.
I felt the same way
when I started here.
I didn't grow up
wanting to be a priest.
My first career was
in sciences, biology.
I was almost two decades in
and I couldn't
understand the world any better than
back when I was in Sunday school.
And then God showed me a path.
He brought me here.
This is where I was meant to be.
I'm sorry
I'm so sorry.
Two glasses in and I can't
stop talking about myself.
- I'm so sorry.
- No, it's OK.
- It's OK.
- What about you?
I imagine it was
a difficult decision.
I mean, yes
it seemed so far away.
But the opportunities back in the States...
I didn't feel like
that's what God saved me for.
- If it's too personal...
- No.
When I was 12 years old
there was this part
of the Saginaw River
that would always freeze over.
And no matter how cold it was
I would always walk out onto the ice.
And I would do this thing
where I took my gloves off
and I would place my hands
right on the ice, and...
And I would hold them there
until I couldn't feel anything.
I don't remember
the ice breaking.
I just, I remember
this sharp pain of cold.
The paramedics
they tried to revive me
but my heart stopped
for almost seven minutes.
That sounds terrifying.
I know God saved me
for a reason, but...
I guess I'm still searching
for what that reason is.
Now will you...
Will you excuse me, please?
Ciao?
Are you OK?
I'll go get some help.
Cecilia.
Reverend Mother, I'm so sorry.
- I heard her crying and...
- It's OK.
Sometimes we get caught up in emotion.
You have a question.
All right.
What is this place?
Saint Helena, Mother of Constantine...
brought this back from Jerusalem.
Here.
He suffered on the cross.
Suffered?
This is the...
Yes.
For you, for us, for our sins
For our salvation.
We suffer.
In the name of His love.
It is a gift.
Suffering is love.
Are you alright, Sister?
In the name of the Father
and the Son and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
Bless me, Father
for I have sinned.
It's been three days
since my last confession.
I was...
I was careless last night.
I must have drank too much
wine and embarrassed myself
in front of Mother Superior.
I promise to carry myself with
grace because I want nothing
more than to belong here.
I'm afraid I've already
messed things up.
I'm sorry for these...
Yearnments.
Hello?
Good morning, Sisters
Today a new life begins.
But this new year will not be easy.
You will question your purpose.
You will question me
and why you have come here.
And some of you will not have
the spiritual fortitude for this life.
What did she say?
God is good
God is great.
- God, my head hurts.
- Too much blood of Christ?
Do you find this amusing, Sister Guendalina?
No, forgive me.
This side of the room is with me.
The other, will serve with Sister Isabelle.
No.
Shit.
What a blessing
to mentor you both.
Finish eating
We have work to do.
Looks like her vibrator ran out of battery.
What does that mean?
Oh, nothing
I really like her.
I'm super excited.
"Clean their back thoroughly."
And if the consistency
of their feces seems off
you let Dr. Gallo know.
- Ciao.
We want to hang the larger
items towards the front
and the shorter items
towards the back.
That way, the wind can
blow underneath it.
First you have to make sure
your knife is nice and sharp.
Otherwise you run
the risk of making a big mess.
I'm sorry, I can't.
"In the name of the Father and
the Son and the Holy Spirit."
"Amen."
Blessed.
Saint.
All of us adore you.
Sister, let's...
Let's get you to bed.
Blessed Saint Cecilia.
Good night, Sister.
"It could have been worse."
"She could have
given you bangs."
Gwen, I'm not joking.
She had scars
on the bottom of her feet.
It's not what you thought
it would be, huh, this place?
No, it's definitely different.
It's better than where
I came from, though.
What do you mean?
There is a boy
There was a boy, I mean.
What happened with this boy?
He hit me.
I hit him back.
Once I left him, I went to those
support groups, you know?
There were these nuns there.
And I thought, these women
have a very good life.
They have a place
to live, a job
where they can keep
their clothes on
nothing to worry about.
So I signed up.
Wait, so you don't
even believe in God?
Of course I do.
Life is so cruel
Only a man can be responsible.
Oh, my God, I was joking
Are you OK?
I don't feel good.
I'm going to call a doctor.
Sister Cecilia
Come with me.
Your Eminence.
Sit.
Could you please tell
Cardinal Merola your vows?
- My vows?
- Your vows.
I swore to three vows
when I got here
of obedience
poverty, and chastity.
- He's asking if you have...
- I understand.
I have, I have been obedient
your Eminence.
Have you kept your vow of poverty?
Yes, I, I own nothing
I want for nothing.
Have you remained chaste?
I'm sorry
why are you asking me this?
It's OK, just answer the question
if you would, Cecilia.
Of course, I've been chaste
your Eminence.
Before you arrived, did you
have congress with a man?
Congress with... no, no.
Have you ever had
congress with a man?
I've not broken my vows.
I've never been with
a man or a woman, nobody.
You'll not be punished.
- We just want to know the truth.
- I'm not lying, Father.
What is going on?
"When she arrived, Dr. Gallo
did you examine her?"
Her hymen was intact.
It's never been touched.
What are they saying?
"Mother Superior, have we had
visitors during these last few weeks?"
- No.
- What are you... What are you looking at?
One last time.
Have you ever had
sexual intercourse?
Why are you asking me this?
You are with child.
This child was...
conceived without sin.
As God as my witness...
we have been blessed with a miracle.
He believes you.
It's a miracle.
Out of all the women in the
world, why did he choose me?
You told me
who saved your life
who sent you on the path
that led you here.
Cecilia, you've been
searching for a reason.
God saved you.
This is it.
"Blessed are the meek"
"for they shall
inherit the Earth."
Cecilia.
No working.
Remember, your only job is baby.
How long before they
start calling you Mary?
It was supposed to be me!
Bitch!
Isabelle! Isabelle!
Sisters!
Stop it!
Leave her alone!
- No!
- Stop!
No, no!
We have to try again!
They have to try again with me!
Heartbeat is stable.
There's no bleeding.
Praise be.
We'll run some blood tests
to check for distress.
But he appears to be OK.
But... I'm not OK.
Father, Isabelle said
it was supposed to be her.
Why would she say that?
Well, Isabelle has been losing
her battle with mental illness
for a while now.
And seeing you and the miracle
it clearly triggered something
- whether it be jealousy...
- She tried to drown me.
You're right
You're right.
And I'll make sure
this never happens again.
I want to see another doctor.
- Why? Dr. Gallo...
- Takes care of old women.
I want to go to
a real hospital, please.
He's a licensed obstetrician.
Thursday through Saturdays
I deliver babies at Cosentino.
A hospital is not
what you need right now.
You're perfectly healthy.
I just puked up
one of my teeth.
Hospitals aren't the safest of places.
We wouldn't want you
to get sick.
Or for the word
to get out, you know.
The safest thing is for you
to stay here until the Savior is born.
Bless you, young mother.
Oh, Isabelle.
All of you, go.
Go away, I said!
Cecilia, you need
to stand up for yourself.
- Gwen, shh.
- Open your eyes.
I don't trust this place.
I don't think
we can just leave.
Cecilia, you're five months pregnant
and you haven't even
been to a hospital.
We can take care of this.
How can we trust
what's inside you?
- Maybe God is...
- God has nothing to do with this.
Sisters, is something the matter?
- I can see you...
- Don't touch me.
Fuck this.
How the fuck can you just stand there
as if nothing happened?
Cecilia's pregnant and we don't know how.
Isabelle killed herself
What the fuck is going on?
- Sorella...
- Let go of me!
I know when a man is lying to me.
And all of you, every single one of you
is so full of bullshit!
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Let go of me!
No!
Let go of me! I said let me go!
No! Let go of me!
No! No!
"For Satan himself often masquerades
as an angel of light."
Gwen.
"No! Let me go!
Let me go!"
"What do you want from me?
"No, no!"
"Let me go!
Let me go!"
No
No, I'm begging you, please.
Shh.
Blessed...
Santa.
Please help me
We have to leave.
You will never leave here.
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
Mother! Mother!
What's going on?
I don't know, father.
God in Heaven.
Call Doctor Gallo.
- It's not possible, it's Saturday.
- Call him!
- Something's wrong.
- I won't get a hold of him, it's Saturday.
We need to get her to the hospital.
- No.
- You must go, now.
- That's it, I'm calling an ambulance.
Stop!
Something's wrong.
I don't want to die
I don't want to die.
I don't...
What do we do if she dies
on the way there?
We must maintain hope.
- It ain't looking good.
- Then we shall pray.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
I understand.
Stop the car.
- What?
- Stop the car.
What are you...
What are you doing? Go!
Go, go!
Clean yourself.
Now you're ashamed?
Now?
Where was your shame when you
stuffed a dead animal inside yourself?
Shame on you.
Making us believe
the miracle died inside you.
What do you have to say for yourself?
God will never forgive you.
I want to apologize
if any of my actions
made you feel scared.
And I want to reassure you
that you're safe.
What did you do to me?
When you look at this
what do you see?
Some people might see just
an old piece of iron, a rusty nail.
For those of us who know
we see proof of Jesus' sacrifice
a symbol of his suffering.
And for 2,000 years
that's all it was.
But we looked closer
and we found blood
tissue, little fragments of bone
a genetic code.
All we had to do
was crack it...
The key to resurrection.
You're insane.
Let me show you.
It's taken us 20 years
of trial and error
20 years for God to deliver
unto us the knowledge
and the perfect fertile vessel.
Is this what's inside me?
No
These are all our failures.
What's inside you
is our success.
I left the field of genetics
because some people
disagreed with the ethics
of my experiment.
So many people have such
a narrow view of its potential.
But here in the church, here
they understood that a simple procedure
could bring us salvation.
- You're playing God.
- I am not playing God.
Do you know what it's like
to watch the miracle die
in the womb, to fail God
again and again and again
but find the strength
to keep going?
This is my calling.
And this, this is yours.
No.
What are you doing?
What's... what's going on?
What is that?
What are you...
What are you doing?
Please stop
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Please, please, stop
Stop!
May you never stray again.
No
No, no!
Stop!
"Blessed are the meek"
No, no, no
Please no.
- "For they shall inherit..."
- No, no, no, no, please, no.
- "The Earth."
- No, no!
No!
Wait... Wait.
Wait.
"Wait."
"Wait, wait."
Wait!
Sister Cecilia.
How long have you
been targeting me?
Please, si confessi.
Was it since the accident?
What's going to happen
when it's done?
You think it's gonna
what, save the world?
End it?
That's what Revelation says, right?
This is not God's work.
Very well.
If this is not
the will of God
why does God not stop us?
Any day now.
Hm.
He's moving.
Ah.
I'll be right back with her medication.
Would you care to?
Yes!
I'll be right back.
Such a beautiful mother
And those eyes, like sunflowers.
Blessed child...
it's all part of His plan.
You will save us.
"Blessed are the meek
for they shall inherit the earth."
God damn it.
Oh, my God.
Cecilia, what have you done?
Cecilia, this won't solve anything.
If you die, we'll find another.
You can end this.
All you need to do
is deliver our Savior.
No!
Cecilia.
Let go of me!
In the name of the Father
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
"Hail Mary, full of grace
the Lord is with thee."
"Blessed art thou among
women, and blessed"
- No, no, no.
- "is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus."
- "Holy Mary..."
- No, no!
"Mother of God
pray for us sinners..."
"Now and at the hour..."
No.
Fuck you.
"Ave Maria"
"Grátia plena"
"Maria grátia plena"
"Ave, ave Dóminus"
"Dóminus tecum"
"Ave Maria"
"Grátia plena"
"Maria grátia plena"
"Ave, ave Dóminus"
"Dóminus tecum"
"Ave Maria"
"Grátia plena"
"Maria grátia plena"
"Ave, ave Dóminus"
"Dóminus tecum"
"Ave Maria"
Subtitled by:
"Professional Captioning House"