You would have thought one
example would be enough for them.
Let's see
if you can convince them.
Pick it up.
Now.
Don't leave them!
Stop!
Stop, you hear me?
Don't you leave them!
Get the fuck back down there,
you hear me!
Stop!
No.
No!
I'm sorry,
but he was really short.
I know, right!
You want to hear
the latest?
Another proposal?
Now you're just bragging.
Our butcher
came to my father
and offered him my weight
in beef to marry his son.
Whoo!
So, like a dozen patties?
Exactly!
Wait, McDonald's
for the reception?
Get me a Big Mac
and I'll marry your butcher.
Oh!
That's why they call it
a happy meal.
-And for fries?
-For fries, I would--
Taliban.
ISIS.
Out! Out! Out! Out!
Fuck going down!
The roof.
Go, go, go!
Which one is
the whore Durani's daughter?
Which one of you is
the daughter of Camila Durani?
Traitor to her people.
She wasn't here today.
She called in sick.
They're going to
come up here.
Car park.
I can drive.
He's coming. He's coming.
You are the daughter
of the whore
who forces learning on girls
in defiance of the Prophet.
The Taliban
at least read the Quran.
If you are ISIS, you know your founder
couldn't even read his own name.
-So, I am speaking to an educated woman?
-Yes, you are.
Well, I don't need to explain that there
is a price to be paid for arrogance.
You fled here with your cowardly parents.
Look at you.
You could have
made good wives
if her mother
hadn't poisoned you.
No! No! No!
Stop!
No! No!
Stop! No!
Those girls
who may be redeemed will be.
For the daughters
of the American diplomats
and for those
who are beyond redemption,
ten million dollars each
and the release
of Sheik al-Shimali,
a holy man, imprisoned by the
corrupt Taliban government.
Five days.
They're gonna kill us.
No, they won't.
We're worth something.
Unlike my friends.
Weren't you the one who told
them they'd be safe on the roof?
We all heard you.
-How did that work out?
-Leave her alone.
-Okay? That wasn't her fault.
-Really? Then ask her friends.
Halle, you're alive right now
because your father is the ambassador
and our parents
are deputy ministers.
But of course, if you ever got
your nose out of that TikTok,
you'd know that America doesn't
pay ransoms to terrorists.
So maybe wipe
that smug look off your face
and realize that we're all
pretty close to dying.
Or being given
to ISIS fighters.
-What?
-Look around.
They took maybe 50 girls
from the school.
Where do you think
they are right now?
Hmm?
-This being 1106--
-Let's hold that for a second.
Captain, you've been up my ass for
a year and now you have your moment.
But before you humiliate
yourself and the service,
I'm gonna give you one last
chance to withdraw your complaint.
-With all respect, sir--
-Fuck your respect.
Warrant Officer Collins there flew into
hostile territory and saved your life.
A mission that cost the lives of
his fellow pilot and four Rangers,
wounding two others as he was
almost shot out of the air.
And yet, you want him
charged with cowardice.
Perhaps the colonel would understand
if he watched his men be executed,
while Warrant Officer Collins
chose safety over duty.
Safety?
You're right, Captain.
That must have been
a terrible decision to make.
Maybe similar to one you made
just a week before that.
Something some people think you
should have been prosecuted for.
-Extenuating circumstances or not.
-Yes, sir.
But you're willing for all that to come
out again and risk prison yourself.
I'm willing to take
responsibility for my actions.
He should as well.
Fine.
Me, I'm gonna wait
until Monday.
Because I'm not in the mood
to ruin my weekend.
We can go back on the record.
The session
is adjourned at 1108.
Get the fuck out of here.
Tap out.
Tap out, fucker!
You tap out, bitch.
I heard you've been
making friends.
Nice to see
with my own eyes, though.
Fuck you, Travis.
It should be fuck you, sir,
but after that,
I don't think I'll pick a fight.
I lost.
Yeah, he seems
to be savoring his victory.
Hit the showers.
Can't talk to someone
who smells like a horse.
I know why you're here.
-And you're not gonna stop me--
-From blowing your career?
Wouldn't waste my breath.
Shower. Seriously.
When?
I leave for D.C.
in an hour.
Hopefully they know more
than they did last night.
I got you a seat on a C-5 departing
at 1600 hours from Wiesbaden.
You fly commercial
from there.
This has nothing to do
with the big brass' worry
that my testimony is gonna take the shine
off the Army's glistening reputation.
It's a closed hearing.
Whatever you're gonna say is
never gonna leave that room,
and you know it.
The only head on a pike outside
on the gate is gonna be yours.
So you're here
to save me from myself.
I won't say
I could give a fuck,
as we both know
that would be a lie.
But right now,
I care more about them.
This is CIA bullshit.
Send in Delta.
We did, rescue mission
three days ago.
No survivors.
So this CIA bullshit is the only hope
these girls have of seeing next week.
We're going in as an
international relief organization.
Has to be 60% women
to be believable.
There are a lot
of good Rangers.
And you'd be surprised
how many are women.
International.
Some mercenaries
from Kurd-fuckistan?
I'm sure
they're the best of the best.
When you meet these two,
you can ask them how many
kills they had in Ukraine.
Which side?
It's your choice.
I just figured you'd rather
take out all that anger
on the guy
who hacked up your team,
instead of the pilot
who saved your life.
Maybe not.
I think we both know
the only person you want to
see pay for that crime
is sitting across from me.
Canadian passport and ID.
I managed to find
the one photo
where you didn't have a middle
finger in front of your face.
So, you know I'm going?
Seven years and I still know
almost nothing about you, Jake.
This would be the exception.
Jessica Rabbit?
Rabit.
It's a proud,
proud French-Canadian name.
Miss Rabbit?
Rabit, one B.
Where's the car?
-Let me take your bag.
-No. Car.
It would look bad.
It is my job.
Thank you.
I was going to ask you if you
have any relation to this famous--
She's a fucking cartoon.
How would I be related to her?
But they draw
someone, right?
-So maybe your mother--
-Car.
Car.
Sorry for my car.
People drive crazy in Pakistan.
Holy shit!
See? Crazy!
No, no. No need.
I'm celebrating being alive.
You put that
toward a nice coffin.
Thank you.
Jessica. Raquel.
Call me Rocky.
It's Jake.
Listen,
I don't need names.
I won't remember
either of yours
and they're probably just
as real as Jessica Rabit.
So you want what? Numbers?
Functions.
Then mechanic,
which is close enough.
We're this way.
This is someone's idea
of a safe house?
The safest that's left.
I'm afraid Pakistan is no longer
the friendliest of allies.
You American
or Afghan?
Because you want to know
if you can trust me?
I know at least one Afghan I would
trust over Americans any day.
Just one?
One still living.
We emigrated
after my father was executed.
Tends to be the Taliban's
punishment of first resort.
By the CIA.
He either shared information
with the Taliban under torture
or he was a double agent.
Which one was it?
No way to know.
And assumptions
are dangerous.
If I made them, I could assume
you couldn't be trusted.
Unless it isn't true you
killed your own team leader.
No. That is
absolutely true.
Shot him?
Rock. About the size
of a hardball.
I played shortstop in Baltimore.
You're a pitcher?
You never know when a
skill will come in handy.
I'm sure he deserved to die.
It was the last thing
he deserved.
And I assume you shared this
tidbit with the rest of the team?
No. They shared it with me.
When does Travis land?
That's Rocky's chair.
And I bet she's been here
long enough to find another.
Travis?
-In the air.
-Which is our Wi-Fi?
The one
named Secret Secure Network.
We have a long time
to prep, do we?
You read Arabic? Daylight743?
You set this up.
-So you're Tech, right?
-Mm-hmm.
Cher, no relation.
She doesn't need names.
Just functions.
Well, aren't you
a charmer?
Call me Geek.
That's Rachel.
Weapons specialist.
Shooter!
"Shooter" it is.
You already
pissed off Theresa.
Explosives,
which may not have been wise.
-You can call me "The Bomb."
-I like that.
Always wanted someone
to call me that.
You are The Bomb.
Oh, and here's our medic.
Hi. Was just in conference
with our real doctor.
-Conference, right.
-Somebody's jealous.
Girl, bah.
Not at all.
I'm sure the close bond
you've established
over the last, what, seven hours has
been professional and productive.
-Jane.
-She only wants functions.
I thought
we'd be friends.
As you make them so easily.
Oh, and here's Dr. Mike.
We just call him Dr. Mike
because he's the only one
going by his real name.
-Mike.
-Jake.
Nah, nah, nah, nah.
We gonna call you Rabbit.
Because what rabbits
do best is run.
You see, Rabbit here
escaped a hellhole
and left her whole team behind
to be slaughtered.
That was after
she killed her own CO.
Right, Rabbit?
Look, don't take offense,
Rabbit.
Dr. Mike
doesn't like us either.
We're just using him
to get us across the border.
Been waiting a month for
permission from the Pakistanis
to take medicine to Khost.
I agree.
It magically appeared.
Khost, just across the border?
As far as the Taliban
will allow us to go.
Also, where they're
holding the sheik.
Not that we had a chance of
getting him out of that prison.
-That was the plan?
-Not one of our best.
All Americans.
-So who is this?
-Badia Durani.
Mother was the Afghan
Minister of Education.
Meeting her this morning.
We're meeting her?
-That's on Travis.
-Great.
Even mom knows we're here.
So, we cross the border.
Then what?
Drop off the medicine, then discover
we have a cracked distributor cap.
Getting a new one will give us two days.
Maybe three.
Can't take any weapons. Have to
assume they're gonna strip the truck.
Travis's fucking weapon stash
better be there.
-Right.
-All our ID will hold up?
Names are all real staff.
Six women, two men.
You can count me
on their side of the column.
Not wearing a fucking burqa.
Where's the nearest
Internet café?
Salaam.
Who is this?
English.
So you're alone.
Tell me you're calling
from America.
Awina, I need your help.
I'm Taliban
and loyal to my country.
And the only people who hate ISIS more
than the Americans is your Taliban.
I need to know
where the American girls are.
Are you insane?
How would I know?
You know how you know.
Well, I don't.
No one knows.
You have 12 hours
to find out.
Don't come here.
I won't meet you.
You know that's a lie.
And you know where.
What?
How the fuck did you get
here before me and you're still late?
Where?
Anything more complicated,
you go straight to medic.
-Anything life-threatening--
-Got it, Doc.
Can you give us a second?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
Got you a green tea.
I hear you've been
making more friends.
Friends die.
Which is a pretty sure bet
after what I've seen.
So,
we go in, find them based on
questionable satellite data,
and if we find them,
we shoot our way out.
Well, it's a little more
refined than that.
Yeah.
I hear you have
a weapon stash.
-Something for a rainy day.
-You sure it's still there?
They proved pretty good
at finding shit we left.
Under a metal floor
I welded shut.
She's early.
How many people are you
telling about your secret plan?
Nobody.
She found us.
Beautiful.
Minister.
Former. Camila.
You'll forgive us if we
don't introduce ourselves.
I know why you're here.
That's all I need.
Please, sit.
I'm curious
to how you actually do know.
And I wish
I could tell you.
-Coffee?
-This won't take long.
Do you know where
my daughter is being held?
We have good information.
Even better
than the last time?
Minister, we're risking lives
based on that information.
So we're gonna do our darndest
to make sure it's right.
I appreciate it.
But if it turns out your
darndest isn't good enough,
I would ask you to deliver
the ransom they demand.
That's 70 million dollars.
Ten million.
So for just your daughter?
I hope to have it
by tomorrow.
You know we can't do that,
Minister.
I'm giving you the option,
if you need it.
To save my daughter from
being publicly beheaded.
-But just your daughter?
-Mine will be first.
Make a show
of the Afghan girl,
so the Americans use some back
channel to pay for their own.
As they have done
many times.
For you to consider.
I came to help you
cross the border
where you may be
most at risk of discovery.
Arguable.
An old friend named Bashir is
a supervisor at the crossing.
-He'll help you through.
-How do we find him?
Don't ask.
It will draw attention.
He'll be watching for you.
May Allah
watch over you as well.
Thank you.
Bring me back my daughter.
We'll do everything we can.
Miss Rabbit, hello.
Very good to see you.
You have
to be fucking kidding.
Come, come with me,
Miss Rabbit.
Abbas. Not a chance.
Enjoy the ride.
And thanks for the name.
Gotta find pleasure
in my work.
Excuse me.
Miss Rabbit, come.
-Let me help you.
-Rabit.
One B.
Yes, I know.
Like the Bugs Bunny.
Me, Malik.
Drive, Malik.
Mal-eek.
Oh, Miss Rabbit.
Do you have any idea what
time our connection works?
-'Cause this looks like hours.
-Wish I knew.
Looks like
we're waiting it out.
Boss.
I fix. No worries.
Abbas. Abbas!
Thanks.
No worries.
Abbas will fix.
Bad driver, good fixer.
Happy to hear that.
-You like music?
-I like music.
Taliban and ISIS hate music.
Only reason I hate them.
Just their problem with music?
You like The Doors?
I like The Doors.
Steppenwolf?
You have a surprising
musical vocabulary, Malik.
-Ma-leek.
I've learned
from my brother.
He plays in a cover band.
Your brother, Abbas,
plays in a cover band?
His favorite song,
Steppenwolf, "Born To Be Wild."
It's a great song.
Bad driver,
great singer.
You love your brother.
Abbas saved me.
Many times.
I owe him everything.
You know that feeling.
I do.
What did I say?
-Good fixer.
-And singer.
Very good singer.
Bad driver.
Get back inside!
Salaam alaikum.
Go back!
-What are you doing here?
-Go back in line.
You're not listening!
Okay, open the truck.
Everything out! Open it.
Medical supplies!
You break them!
You're breaking them.
You wanna kill
your own people.
-Shut the fuck--
-They are to save your people.
Your own people!
You kill them!
Those are medicines,
for Christ's sake.
-Doc, don't engage.
-Get back in the car.
-I'm not the one--
-How long since you've been back here? Twenty years?
You think the Taliban
don't respect women
but are tolerant
of cross-dressers?
-I'm not a--
-Get in the fucking car!
Stop! Just stop!
Read. "Antibiotics."
Drugs, you poison our people!
Antibiotics,
you fucking muggle!
-Muggle?
-What you call me? What you call me?
I called you a fucking muggle.
You're breaking the very thing that you--
Muggle is
a very serious man.
Don't even believe in wizards.
Look at
the fucking label!
Would you
shut the fuck up?
Are you trying
to never get laid?
There are weapons.
I know there are weapons.
No weapons.
Thinking we tell 'em
we're here to kill ISIS?
At least we'll be
on the same side.
Maybe keep that to yourself.
Apologies.
You may continue on your way.
Bashir?
We appreciate the kindness.
In an emergency only,
call this number.
Can't promise to help.
Hopefully we won't need it.
May Allah be with you.
And with you.
You reach for an insult,
and you pull out Harry Potter.
Magnificent.
Jail.
Yeah. Looks like it.
Cleric.
Sheik al-Shimali. Jail.
So that's where
they're keeping him.
Do not pass go.
Now Monopoly, Malik.
Abbas always beats me.
He cheats.
I cheat too,
but he cheats better.
So many reasons
to look up to him.
I'll do anything you want.
Then have coffee.
-What?
-Sit.
We have had no response from our
offer to release you and your friends.
Other than the American is trying
to kill us, of course.
But, you know, that
didn't work well for them.
-No, that wasn't my fault.
-No, no, no.
None of this
is your fault, I know.
Sip.
I have decided that we need
to show good faith.
-So I'm let you go.
-You what?
I'm letting you go free.
-Me?
-You're surprised.
I understand that.
Based on what your media
is trying to paint us.
You threw my friends
off the roof.
Yes, it was a monstrous act.
But, you know,
we have our cause
and we believe strongly
in that cause.
The American
believe in theirs.
And they killed
so many of us.
Our families, our childrens,
with their drones and bombs.
Since before you were born.
My family as well.
I had two girls.
And a wife.
You know, I'm not going to try
to convince you.
-Should I pick someone else?
-No, no.
No. I'll go.
Good.
I want you
to deliver this note
to the police station.
-The Taliban police?
-Yes.
Tell me.
Can I trust you to do that?
Yes.
You can.
Thank you.
Finish your coffee.
That's okay.
I know.
It's bitter as hell.
They want us all to leave in the other
truck as soon as we are unloaded.
-It's not good.
-No. Abbas will fix.
Okay.
That's what okay looks like?
Yes.
I paid them,
the rest is show.
-That's some show.
-Yeah.
You see behind, boss?
See the humby?
I see the Humvee.
Yes, humby.
Look where it drives.
Where they keep the big guns.
-The armory.
-No, no.
Guns, bombs,
shit goes boom.
Thanks, Abbas.
We got it covered.
No problem, always.
Malik.
Shit goes boom.
Rachel, Theresa, headscarves.
Let's go grab some toys.
It's The Bomb.
What is?
I am.
Shooter.
Aim a gun.
Pull the trigger.
Next time.
Fuck you
for coming back.
for still being here.
I fight for my home.
Just not very well.
Where are they?
Fuck.
So it's under there?
Fuck!
Thought a satellite's
been keeping an eye on it.
Guess a flat roof looks
like a flat roof from outer space.
-Orbit.
-What?
Satellites are in orbit,
not outer space.
Then that explains it.
Fuck!
Got me some wheels.
Steal it?
Borrowed it.
Borrowed it?
Should've stolen
a bulldozer.
Got you this.
Black market. Fifty bucks.
Beauty.
Go!
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I was told to give you this.
"This you get for betraying
your faith and your cause."
What the fuck is that?
About five keys of C-4.
ISIS.
No one in the world seems to
notice there's a civil war here.
Malik. Malik.
Malik will check,
boss.
Miss Rabbit, you okay?
I go check.
Doc, you mind?
It's what I do.
All right. Easy stuff first.
Satellite data
places the hostages here.
And we're still loving
the satellite confirmation?
Farmhouse. Twenty klicks south.
Confirmed by two sources.
They're wrong.
They're at
an abandoned tobacco factory.
Those are the coordinates.
And you know this how?
Source is a midwife.
A small circle here,
and midwives talk.
One of Amir's women
gave birth two days ago.
And your source was there?
She wasn't.
But her friend told her
the American girls were.
Just out in the yard
doing yoga?
In a cage.
One of them
had a bad cut on her arm.
And the midwife was asked
to clean the wound.
And we trust this source?
She's Taliban.
I saved her life.
ISIS was closing in on us.
I got her out.
She would have been beheaded on
the spot for cooperating with us.
Unlike the rest of your unit
that was hacked to pieces.
That's enough.
We stow this shit right now,
we start acting like a team,
or we fucking die.
-You believe her?
-I do.
Yours is a trap.
And she's willing
to come with us.
That says it all to me.
Okay.
So weapons.
The stash?
Sensitive subject.
Abbas,
we're taking your armory.
Smart, boss. Let's do it.
-Seriously?
-We use what's been given to us.
Rocky,
we can't use the NGO car.
I need you to steal me
another one.
So, we're taking the base
with some Molotov cocktails
and a rifle from World War I.
Shooter, Rocky, eyes.
Abbas, Humvee.
Everybody else grab what we need.
Taliban!
Yes!
Stop, go back!
-Sorry, Miss.
-Go back!
We're not leaving him!
Go back!
Can't.
You know what they're
gonna do with the body.
If that was Abbas,
would you leave him?
Would you?
Bring them home.
Fuck you.
You're gonna be fine.
I'm calling that number
in two minutes.
I need you to trace
the location.
What the fuck was that?
We don't leave men behind.
No, you get them killed.
You wanna make up
for abandoning your men?
Do it at
someone else's expense.
Right now,
they don't know who we are.
But if they find an American
with Doc's ID, they will.
And we'll have no way out.
Hey, I'm connected,
and we're online.
That's why
you went back?
No.
Hello?
We need what you offered.
Half the city's on fire.
The police
are searching for you.
-For us?
-I don't know. Some say it was ISIS.
It wasn't.
That doesn't matter now.
They'll find you.
I can't help you.
Bashir, wait. Just listen.
Listen to what?
-We'll see you soon.
-See me?
We're close. Five miles.
Driving in that?
We won't make it a mile.
Geek. Let's go.
You cannot stay here.
You have to go.
But we have no choice.
We need somewhere
to bury our dead.
Miss Rabbit.
Miss Rabbit!
It's deep enough.
This won't take long.
-You called her?
-Of course.
How did you get in
the country?
He tells me
two of your men are dead.
I'm very sorry to hear it.
The news says it was an ISIS attack.
Same as the police station.
One of the girls from
the school was found there.
At least her uniform
and parts of her.
Caucasian.
I was wrong about
who would be first to die.
But I don't think I will
be wrong about the second.
Ten million.
You heard what Travis said.
Travis is dead,
so who's in charge?
Then it's your decision.
All thousands?
Thousand-dollar bills?
I didn't know there were
that many in circulation.
Where'd you find
ten million in thousands?
She didn't.
They're counterfeit.
You want us to pay a ransom
in counterfeit bills?
It's all I could get.
They shouldn't notice.
Took her less than a minute.
Amir is not American.
It will give you time.
This just gets better
and better.
Your rescue failed.
What choice do you have?
Save one girl.
America will pay for the rest.
Then you can escape.
I assume that's why
you're here, to escape?
Do one good thing
before you go.
Do we even have a way out?
I have a number
to call for evacuation.
Black Hawk sitting hot
across the border.
So call it.
All cell phones
on the table.
If the news is fake,
they could be trying to track us.
I'm keeping mine off.
Pull the SIMs.
Smash everything good.
-Fuck you!
-No!
You admire women?
That why you threw them
off the roof?
Where is Halle?
I promised
to let her go.
And I did.
Right.
I hear we are moving.
Americans coming, are they?
The guards like to talk.
If I was afraid
of the American,
I wouldn't make plans
to marry you.
Marry me?
We just need to wait
for the cleric.
You are out of
your fucking mind.
I decided
I need a strong woman
to give me childrens
who are fighters.
Because weak women
make weak childrens.
I would rather die
than marry you.
That's going to be
exact your choice.
But, by marrying me,
you will save
the lives of your friends.
-You'll let them go?
-No.
I will marry them
to my most loyal fighters.
They deserve the reward.
Better than being sold
to slavery,
where they will be
treated differently.
I won't marry you
without your consent.
Car approaching!
You invited guests?
Hello.
I'm Taliban.
Nice to meet you.
The Taliban think it's ISIS.
You mustn't have left
witnesses.
But Amir knows it wasn't.
My friend heard they're moving the girls.
She doesn't know where.
Beautiful. No leader,
no weapons, and no target.
We have weapons, some.
They think ISIS stole the
weapons to attack the prison.
So they're moving the sheik.
-When?
-Soon.
-Where?
-To the only near maximum security prison.
America built it.
What was the stupidest plan
you came up with?
-Nothing could have topped that one.
-What was it? Come on!
Break the sheik
out of prison and trade him.
Amir wants money
and the sheik.
We have the money.
Let's get the sheik.
And make Amir come to us.
I always liked this plan.
He's going to be
very heavily guarded.
Yeah. I need your phone.
I wasn't dumb enough
to bring it.
Burn all our fake ID.
If anyone is caught,
just admit
you're an American soldier.
Won't be pleasant, but
you'll eventually be traded.
Got it?
You weren't.
No. But it's
the best chance we have.
So how will they know?
When they see us.
Well, I hope to God
they're ready.
She's coming.
Get into the car.
-What?
-Go!
I'm sorry, Rocky. I'm sorry.
Tell them
you're an American soldier.
I am.
Fucking right you are.
Tell them.
Abbas.
Open up!
Get in.
Go!
Abbas.
Abbas!
What he did worst,
he loved most.
Singing?
No.
Singing was good.
He loved driving.
That he did.
For you,
freedom is America.
For him,
it was just driving.
You wanna talk about it?
What?
Not really.
You start out pretty early
in life knowing there is a...
a line you won't cross.
Things you'll do,
things you'll never do.
You get into a tough spot,
the line shifts.
You get in the real shit,
it shifts more.
I will never eat a cat.
Wait till you're starving
to death and they serve you
the stray kitty
you've been petting.
But there is still a line.
Thick, dark and straight,
and the line holds.
Till you find yourself in a
place where the line just ends.
Gone.
Every choice is unthinkable.
Frank, our team leader,
he held us together
for months in that hole.
Every single one of us
loved him.
He was about to die
a horrible death. Slow.
His bones breaking rock by
rock, thrown by his own men.
They stood us in a circle.
We all refused.
So Amir sliced the throat
of a village woman.
Let her bleed out,
kicking on the dirt.
We still refused.
He did the same to her kid.
I was his second.
It was on me.
So I picked up
a nice round rock,
weighed it in my hand.
And Frank
looked me right in the eye.
Gave me this little smile.
He'd seen me pitch back at the
base when we played pickup.
He turned his head
so that his temple was to me.
And I wound up and I hurled
the fastest pitch I ever threw.
I swear
I heard his skull crack.
Just took the one rock.
You do something like that,
you never find the line again.
And that smile
haunts me every night.
I thought I'd never
leave anyone else behind.
She's on the TV!
What?
He says she's an abomination,
not man or woman.
Fuck you!
What?
And that she's ISIS.
-They saw us right?
-They saw us.
Because only ISIS would
accept a woman that is so degenerate.
-This is bullshit!
-Come on, Rocky. Speak English.
And that she and others have
killed many brave Taliban soldiers.
Tell them.
Now he's asking if she has
anything to say in her defense.
-She won't.
-She will.
She'll tell them
she's American.
-She promised me.
-She won't give us up.
Our cover's already been blown,
they know it's us. She knows that.
She won't.
Please, Rocky!
Now she's praising Allah
and his kindness.
English.
No!
-Is she dead?
-Unconscious.
What the fuck?
You saved her life.
I only thought I did.
She brought them to us then,
and she's bringing them to us now.
What?
Fuck. She's been
updating them the entire time.
-How long do we have?
-Minutes.
Give me the phone.
Get the cars on the road.
Bring me the money.
-It's in the car.
-Bring it.
Leave it here.
-What about them?
-We leave them.
You're giving them
everything--
Get the fucking cars
on the road!
Hmm.
Oh.
Okay.
-Let's go.
-Go where?
To find my phone.
-I love Find My Phone.
-Where is it?
In the bag of money.
Let's get to them
before they start counting.
Diesel fumes.
-What gear do we have?
-Guns, ammo, no ropes.
There's some in the trunk.
Don't know
how strong they are.
Handguns, grenades,
knives, explosives.
No rifles. Only Shooter.
Time to make your choice.
Shit.
Beautiful.
It is your choice.
Three levels.
The girls locked up
on the second.
Only six of them.
One missing.
Durani's daughter.
No sign of Amir.
Maybe on a lower level.
Yours?
Hers.
The money is not good
and you led them here.
Your first wifely duty,
clean up the blood.
Fuck you.
-Get up! Get up!
-Up, up, up!
-Badia Durani?
-Yes.
Help her get them out.
-Get them to the elevator.
-Where are you going?
Medic.
And don't wait.
Come on, move!
-Come on! Move! Move! Move!
-Come on!
Come on, come on, come on!
Move, move, move!
On the floor!
On the floor! On the floor!
Hey, you okay?
Fuck!
-You gotta go.
-Fuck you!
Get outta here.
I'm fine.
-You're fine!
-Jake!
Jake!
It's okay.
We came here
for them, right?
Get them home.
It's okay.
All clear! All clear!
Move!
Medic team over here!
Go! Go, go, go!
I got you!
Move!
Hey, sergeant, I got you!
Get on!
You going?
I'm not.
Me neither.
What the fuck are you doing?
Abbas mixtape.