Hi.
Hi. I'm Ani.
No? You waiting for someone else?
All right. Are you sure?
Okay.
Hello. Hi.
- How are you?
- Hello.
- Hi. I'm Ani.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Very nice to meet you.
- Yes.
- How you doing?
- I'm doing well.
- Yeah?
- Thank you. Oh, you look quite lovely.
You can sit right there, okay?
Oh, okay.
Do you still... Your family,
do they know you do this?
- They do? They're okay with it?
- Yeah.
I'd be okay.
Does your family know you're here?
- I hope not.
- Yeah?
- Hi. I'm Ani.
- Nice to meet you, Ani.
- Nice to meet you.
- I'm Ricky.
- Ricky?
- Yeah.
Very nice to meet you.
I'll just sit right next
to you, right here.
- Oh, yeah.
- Very cozy, right?
- Pretty serious.
- Yeah.
- A lot of work, but that's why I'm here.
- You're a hard worker.
Chill out and come here, you know?
Yeah, well, we could go
chill out in a private room.
All right, lucky number six.
That's my number.
Thank you.
Yeah.
- Ani?
- Yeah.
When Robert was here the other
night, did he ask you for a dance?
- Yeah.
- And you danced with him?
Yeah.
Okay.
- Okay.
Bitch.
Yeah!
He was really weird.
Super weird.
- Like, serial killer weird?
- Like, he would rub...
Yeah, like, he was like
Indian Jeffrey Dahmer,
- and he kept, like, rubbing my leg...
- Oh, no.
In a circle like that.
What is that? Is that a butterfly?
- Yeah, it's a butterfly.
- You're so classy.
I know.
I got dollar signs like a real ho.
No, but you're
manifesting with those.
He said I looked like
his 18-year-old daughter.
And then he bought
five dances from me.
That's fucking disgusting.
Well, at least he
bought the dances.
Yeah.
- You can touch me. It's okay.
- Yeah?
I'll build you a belt.
Yeah, make me a belt. A money belt?
You don't have cash? Let's go to the
ATM. You want to go to the ATM right now?
- I can't spend too much.
- Yeah, okay. Let's go to the ATM.
Let's go get you some cash.
Seriously, he came out
of the bathroom one time,
and he didn't zip
up his fucking pants.
It's like, if you can't zip up
your fucking pants
after you take a piss,
I don't trust you with the music.
Dude, he's 40. He's
literally geriatric.
- No, I know.
- Ani.
I got a kid who wants
someone who speaks Russian.
You know, Jimmy, the
girls and I have been talking,
and if your cousin doesn't start
showing us some respect,
we're not gonna tip out anymore.
- All right. I'll talk to him.
- Yeah.
Who are you talking about, the DJ?
- All right, seriously?
- He's an asshole.
I shared my playlist with him, and
he was very rude and dismissive.
You're killing me.
Let's go. Come on.
- No. No, I'm eating my food.
- That's why you have Tupperware.
- To keep things fresh.
- She's eating.
He's a spender.
- Come on. Let's go.
- What the fuck?
Time is money,
baby. Get a roll on it.
Without pants, without nothing.
And then some fucking...
- Hey, guys.
- Then... One second, bro.
Guys. Guys. Hello.
This is the beautiful Ani.
She's gonna take care of
everything you need tonight.
Ani, make me proud.
Yeah. I'm... Yeah.
You are beautiful.
I'm, uh... Ivan, and...
but you can call me Vanya.
- Vanya. Okay.
- Yeah.
Nice to meet you, Vanya.
And this is my best friend,
fucking best friend, Tom.
- Hi. I'm Ani.
- What's up?
You're not bad. And, uh...
I heard you speak Russian, right?
No, I don't speak Russian,
but I know Russian.
What do you mean?
I can speak Russian.
I just prefer not to, but you can
go ahead and speak Russian.
I'll understand.
Uh, I not understand.
What the fuck?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Hello, Ivan.
My name is Ani.
This is how I speak Russian.
Do you still want me
to speak Russian?
Fuck, yeah!
No, it's... My Russian is
terrible. I can't even roll my R's.
No, no, you... You
are not bad, really.
You are not bad in Russian.
Your Russian is great, great.
- Really? Okay.
- Yeah.
Well, I disagree, but thank you.
Yeah. And how do you know Russian?
My grandmother never
learned English, so...
Ah. Aha.
- Yeah.
- But enough about me.
You two are from Russia?
Yeah, I'm from Russia,
but he lives here. Yeah.
Oh, so you're on vacation or...?
Yeah, vacation. I guess
you can say that. Yeah.
But I'm speaking, uh...
May I switch to Russian?
- Yeah? Yeah.
- Oh, yeah. Whatever you want.
Yeah, because my
English sounds terrible.
- At all, yeah.
- No, no, no.
- Your English is really good.
- Yeah.
And that's why I
think we should toast
to our fucking bad
accents with a bottle.
Yeah. And you want
to go to VIP, maybe?
Yeah, excellent. I want.
You work in a cool place.
Yeah, it's a cool place.
And the room I'm bringing
you to is really nice.
- Wow.
- Right in there.
You're very good, really.
And one more. Yeah.
Thank you.
Where are you going?
No, I'm not going anywhere.
Can you sit on your hands for me?
- What?
- Sit on your hands.
- Hands under your legs.
- Like...
This is not allowed,
but I like you.
Ooh!
God bless America.
Here's to having a hard
dick and lots of money.
Um, I want to ask. Do
you work outside the club?
Give me your phone.
Yo.
Yo. Yo. Did you pick up milk?
Do you see milk in the fridge?
No.
Then I didn't pick
up the fucking milk.
Wonderful. Thank you.
Hi, um, I'm here for Mr. Zakharov.
- Ivan?
- Yeah. Mm-hm.
Hi. Hello. What's up?
Hi.
Come in. Come in, please.
So welcome to my humble abode.
- Hugs.
- Oh, yes.
Hugs.
I can help you.
Oh, thank you.
Oh. You... You look beautiful.
- Awesome.
- Aw, thank you.
Want something to drink?
Uh, yeah, I'll...
I'll take a water.
Water? Are you sure?
You can take everything you want.
Vodka, tequila,
whiskey, whiskey cola.
Coca-Cola, maybe?
No, a water's good.
Yeah, thank you.
Suit yourself, Ani.
Sparkling or flat water?
Um... Either is good.
Where's the fucking water?
Wow.
Not too shabby.
What is "shabby"?
Oh, I'm... I'm just playing.
I meant your home
is... Is beautiful.
My home is okay, girl.
- Um, sparkling.
- Thank you.
Bedroom's upstairs. Let's go.
Okay.
Oh, sorry. I am waiting for you.
Oh. I'll hurry up.
They didn't make my bed yet.
Fuck. Is it so difficult?
Sorry.
Whoa.
Nice view.
My view is better.
Okay. So, what are you looking for?
Um... sex.
Yeah, I know.
I mean, like, anything special?
Yeah, special sex.
"Special sex." Okay.
So, like, a little
bit of everything?
A little bit of...
Yes. Sounds fucking amazing.
You want to take your clothes off?
Yeah.
Wow, okay.
You want to put this on?
Or do you want me
to put it on for you?
Faster. Faster, faster.
Faster. Faster. Faster.
- Stop. Stop. Stop.
- Okay.
- So you want me to stop?
- Stop, stop, stop!
- I said... Oh, fuck.
- Okay.
Ah. Want you?
- Oh. Uh, sure.
- Sure.
But be careful with
that shit, yeah? Careful.
And that's for you. Tip.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
That's very generous of you.
And I want to say one more thing.
Yes.
It was really amazing.
Oh, oh, oh.
I love these guys. You know them?
No.
Oh. You must know them.
So, um, how old are you?
Twenty-one. How old are you?
Older than you.
How old are you? 25?
No, I'm... I'm 23.
Oh. Wow.
You act like you are 25.
Okay.
You're funny.
Yeah, I know. So... funny? Why?
I don't know.
You're just... You're, like...
You're funny. It's...
Funny cool, right?
- Yeah, of course.
- Yeah.
Really funny cool.
And if you don't mind me asking,
like, what do you
do to get all of this?
What do you think I do?
Well, what do you
think I think you do?
Oh, fucking English.
Okay. I can say, but
it's... It's really big secret.
Okay.
I am really big drug dealer.
Oh, really?
Why you trust...?
No.
But I'm really big gun dealer.
Okay. Come on.
Oh, my gosh.
Wait, so, like, you made
some app or something?
- Is that...?
- Yeah. Yeah. I made.
I do have some cool ideas for apps.
No, but, no, no. I... No.
Okay.
My father...
Yeah?
Uh, long story short,
my dad is Nikolai Zakharov.
- Whoa.
- Sorry. I don't know who that is.
Google him.
- Google?
- Yeah.
Um, wait, what's his name again?
Nikolai Zakharov.
I can spell it for you.
N-I-K-O-lai...
No, I got it.
- Yeah?
- Thank you.
Yeah, let me see.
"Children."
Yeah. Vanya Zakharov.
It's me.
Oh, shit.
"Oh, shit."
No. No way.
- Yes fucking way.
- Bro.
And I'm seeing him
again tonight, so...
Crazy.
I guess he had fun or something.
Yeah, we all know
what fun you are, babe.
You want to mind
your fucking business?
You're making it
our fucking business.
- Calm down, Diamond.
- Chatty bitch.
Gross.
Ginger cunt.
Yeah.
This is genius!
Come on, come on, come on.
That was crazy.
Little bonus because
you're the best.
Okay.
Let's go!
By the way, I'm having a party.
New Year's party.
And you have to come.
It's going to be banging.
I might have to work that night.
Oh, no. You might
not work that night.
Fuck.
- Can I bring someone?
- No.
If it is a boy, no.
I don't want a sausage party.
Fuck.
No, she's not.
Okay. See you here.
Why don't you shoot?
What?
You know, you paid for an hour,
and there's still like 45 minutes
left, if you want to go again.
- No fucking way.
- Yes fucking way.
- I fucking told you.
- Girl.
- Right? I know.
- Girl!
And it's fucking insane inside.
- There's an elevator.
- Oh, my God.
- Fucking elevator.
- Wait.
- Never seen anything like it.
- Are my tits off?
No, your tits look amazing.
- Okay.
- They look perfect.
- Wait, are my tits off?
- No.
- Bro.
I know. I told you.
Didn't I tell you?
- Girl.
- It's crazy,
and upstairs is
even more beautiful.
Yo, yo, yo. What's up? Hi.
- Hi.
- Yeah.
Oh, uh, Lulu, this is Ivan.
Yes, this is Lulu.
Very nice to meet you.
I am so excited that you
are here, and let's go drink.
- Yes? Yeah, go, go, go.
- Yeah.
- Want to get some drinks?
- Hell, yeah.
Are you ready?
And, Ani, your mouth here.
From the titty.
Yo, that's the escort
that's fucking Ivan.
- No way.
- I'm telling you.
She's pretty good, yeah?
Totally.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Get down. This is not jungle gym.
Seventeen! Sixteen! Fifteen!
- Yeah!
- Fourteen! Thirteen!
Twelve! Eleven! Ten!
Nine! Eight! Seven! Six!
Five! Four! Three!
Two! One!
Ani, Ani, Ani, let's go, go, go.
Yeah, yeah.
Fireworks after!
Tell me if you see those Armenians.
I don't see anyone.
By the way, you can't find
blow like this in Moscow.
Your, uh... looks great.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
You were right.
You were right. This is banging.
- Ah, yeah?
- Yeah.
Having fun?
Yes. Are you?
Yeah, yeah. Do exactly that.
I wanted to ask,
are you available tonight?
Maybe.
The fuck? Maybe?
Well, it's New Year's.
Ah. Ah, and what?
I have holiday rates.
Yeah?
Ivan, we're leaving. You good?
Dude, what the fuck? I'm busy.
These fucking guys
don't know their place.
- All good?
- All great.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck.
Good morning.
No. No, dude, not good morning.
It is 5:00 p.m.
Well, then, good evening.
Wait, are you leaving?
Yeah, don't go. Don't go yet.
No, dude, I have to go to
work. I have shit to do, okay?
But text me if you want
to see me again. Yeah?
What? No.
I have one question.
- You have a question?
- Yeah, man.
Okay. One minute.
One minute, one question.
Yeah?
I want to make an offer.
Would you want to
be exclusive with me?
Like, how exclusive?
I don't know. We can
hang out with my boys.
Simply be my
girlfriend for the week.
My horny girlfriend for the week.
Oh.
What about...
10 K of dollars?
Fifteen.
Cash, up front.
Deal.
You know, I would've
done it for 10.
Well, if I were you, I
wouldn't do it for less than 30.
Goodbye.
Goddamn, dude.
She's fucking hot, man.
Yeah, baby.
- Who's the birthday boy?
- This guy right here.
Happy birthday.
Thank y'all for coming
in. Y'all come back.
- Y'all come see us soon.
- Bye!
Come with me.
- Go ahead. Tell him.
- Okay. Thank you.
Tell him because I don't want to.
- I am gonna fucking tell him.
- What's going on?
- You don't even want to know, Jimmy.
- Hi, Jimmy.
- She wants a week off.
- I thought you wanted me to tell him.
You see the shit that
I have to deal with?
I just made the schedule. Now
she wants to pull this bullshit.
Oh. "The schedule."
We just gave you New Year's.
Oh, Jesus Christ, Jimmy,
once you give me health insurance,
workers' comp and a fucking 401(k),
then you can tell me
when I work and not work.
Well, none of that's
gonna happen, so...
- Shocker.
- Bye.
I'll be back on Tuesday.
- Today is Tuesday.
- Correct.
- That's a week.
- No shit.
Thank you.
- You like that?
- No.
You know, Ani, it's the
champagne glass of my mother.
Of my fucking mother.
And it will be your
champagne glass.
And what we are cheering for?
About my new girlfriend.
- Hell, yeah. To Ani.
- Yeah.
To the most amazing chick.
Yeah.
- One more. One more.
- Okay.
Instantly. Instantly.
Fuck.
Klara, maybe you want a hit?
Sorry, Ivan. Not today.
It was really funny when
Klara smoked last time.
My mother caught her
in the cryo chamber.
What?
Nothing. Just keep working.
- You have a cryo chamber?
- Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, but I'm not allowed to drive
them because my parents are dicks.
- What's up?
- How are you?
- I'm good.
- Yeah, what's up, man?
- What's up, Ivan?
- Welcome.
You guys can just eat
whatever the fuck you want.
We got ice cream.
There's, like, whatever the fuck
these are. There's Ring Pops.
Like, literally, I just
fuck around in here.
The boss is old as fuck,
and he's, like, blind and deaf.
He can't even fucking hear us right
now, Helen Keller-ass bitch, like...
- Just fucking go crazy.
- Okay.
- Yep, yep, yep.
- Up.
Want? Oh, yeah, man, finish it off.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Bitch, don't die on the job.
You okay?
How many times you
guys have to be told not...?
No smoking dope in here.
- But we're addicted to the reefer, Billy.
- Come on, man.
We're gonna take our
break. Ten minutes, man.
Ani!
- What the fuck?
- Oh, shit.
What are you doing? Don't do that.
No, come back.
- No, no, no.
- Come back.
- What are you doing?
- It's fucking cold.
- What the fuck?
- What are you doing?
- Come back.
Can you say hi to my Instagram?
Ani.
Are you happy?
Yes. Very happy. Are you happy?
Yeah, I'm always happy.
No, it's really good
lines, but ladies first.
Ladies first.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
that's... Can you...?
Guys, the best
ketamine I ever tried
was in Vegas.
Vegas. It's a great idea.
We are going to fucking Vegas.
Yeah!
Welcome to Vegas!
We're in Vegas, bitch!
Welcome back, Mr. Zakharov.
Your suite is almost ready.
We didn't know you were
coming and the suite was occupied,
but they're out,
and housekeeping
should be done any minute.
What the fuck, man? Are
you fucking kidding me?
You mean, I have to wait?
You mean, we have to
wait right now, bro, yes?
- Yes?
- Tell him, tell him, tell him, Ivan.
- Yeah, go off, Vanya.
- Come on. Come on.
I am fucking with you,
dude. We will stay here.
- It's nice to come back.
- Very good.
Let's go apeshit on
this fucking casino!
Have a great time.
What the fuck are you waiting for?
Yeah!
Can somebody turn on music?
- Tom, Tom.
- Turn on the music!
I got it. I got it.
Try this, try this, try this.
Vanya! I want this one!
- No, no, no. No. No, no, no.
- This one's mine!
- Vanya!
- Go away from my room!
You claim this room,
I claim your sister.
I claim your mom.
If you are ready
now, yeah, we can...
- You ready now?
- Okay, yes, I'm ready now.
You want me to...?
Let's play blackjack, for sure.
"We are going in, all in."
- Yeah? Okay.
- Yeah, say it.
- We are going all in.
- Motherfucker.
Twenty-two, all in.
Whatever. Whatever, guys.
- How much money is that?
- What...?
But do it with a double dose
because we're gonna
go even harder tonight.
Okay?
Thank you.
Tom, give me a cigarette.
One cigarette.
You know what? Fuck you.
Oh!
They fucking do this every day.
I am really happy that we are here,
- and... I don't know.
- Thank you.
Fuck. You're the best, guys.
You are the fucking best.
Vanya. Vanya.
Vanya.
- Vanya, wait, wait, wait.
- What happened?
Well, you know, it could last longer
and be better if you just take it easy.
Like, how?
Here. Let me do it.
Oh.
Mm-hm. Oh, I think
I love you. Fuck.
I hope you had fun this week.
Oh, I did.
- You know, we should do it again sometime.
- Yeah.
For sure.
But...
I have to go back to Russia
because I promised my father
that I would start working
in his fucking company.
Okay, so that's why
you've been splashing out?
No, I am always partying like this.
I love it.
Well, I'm gonna miss you.
- What?
Does that, like, sound weird?
No, no.
And will you miss me
or my money blyat?
Or your money blyat.
- Of course.
- Yeah, I like it.
But if I get married
to an American,
I wouldn't have to
go back to Russia.
Oh, yeah?
Okay.
So who'd you marry?
I don't know. Maybe Crystal.
Or your friend Lulu.
She's so hot.
You.
"You."
It's Vegas.
It's fucking Vegas. Don't
people get married in Vegas?
Don't fuck around.
I am not fucking around.
Okay.
Okay, go.
- Go get married.
- Yes.
- Yes, let's get married.
- Fuck. You asshole.
- Why?
- Don't.
Like, don't fucking tease
me with that shit, okay?
- Stop.
- It ain't cool.
Stop, stop, stop.
- Ani.
- Yeah?
Will you marry me?
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
So you want to get
married to me, Vanya?
You want me to be
your little wifey? Yeah?
Yes.
I just think that we had
great time together, and...
Shit, I'm nervous.
I'll say it in Russian.
I think we would have a great
time, even if I didn't have money.
And I will become American,
and then my parents
will suck my dick.
Are you serious?
I am serious.
And I said it twicely.
Three karats.
What about four or five?
Or six?
Do you promise to love, honor,
and cherish her all
the days of your life?
I do.
And do you, Anora, take this
handsome gentleman standing before you
to be your best friend, your
protector, your husband?
Do you promise to love,
honor and cherish him
all the days of your life?
- Say yes.
- Oh, fuck, yeah, I do.
It is now my great honor
to now pronounce you
as husband and wife.
You may seal your
promises with a kiss!
My wife!
- It's my wife, man.
- We got married!
Sorry sir. It's my
wife. She can do it.
It's my wife, man.
Yeah, we got married
five minutes ago, man.
You're an American, Vanya.
- I'm fucking American!
- We're fucking married!
I am American, bitch!
So this is for real?
Yeah, it's for real.
- What do you mean?
- 'Cause if it is,
I gotta stop letting
the high rollers in.
They're stealing my best girls.
Come here.
You're so lucky.
Oh, my God, I know. Thank you.
Yay!
You hit the lotto, bitch.
Oh, my God. Are you gonna cry?
Stop. You don't...
You'll come over for dinner, right?
You know, I've been
thinking about our honeymoon,
and I think we should
do it at Disney World
because that's been, like, my dream
- since I've been a little girl.
- Stop.
Yeah. You know those suites
where it's, like, the
Disney Princess theme?
- Cinderella.
- Yes, fucking Cinderella.
You know me so fucking well, babe.
Bye, Ani. You
better visit us, bitch.
Oh, of course I will, Jenny.
- Bye, babe.
- Caught your whale?
Seems I did, didn't I?
I give it two weeks, bitch.
Oh, Diamond. Oh, sweetie.
You know, I really hope you
find your happiness one day.
- I really hope...
- I hope you find
a fucking plastic surgeon.
- What the fuck?!
- Okay, Ani. Ani, come on.
Play in my fucking face
again, bitch. See what happens.
- You're a fucking bitch.
- Oh, stay jealous, babe.
Stay jealous, honey.
Jealousy is a disease.
Remember that, Diamond.
I'm just gonna go chill in
my mansion or whatever.
You know, no big deal.
This is impossible.
These are just rumors.
I was with him two weeks ago.
He isn't married.
With all due respect,
Galina Stepanovna,
these are just rumors.
No, but I'm heading there now.
Garnik. Garnik.
Now?
- Yes.
- Now?
Take this.
Grab the Russian
and get over there.
What did he do now?
Die, die, die.
Yeah...
Come on.
Just answer it or shut it off.
Vanya.
What did, uh...? What did
they say when you told them?
I don't want really
talk about them.
Well, you did tell them, right?
Mm. Sure.
I mean...
this is good news, right?
Parents usually want
their kids to get married.
Yeah...
But my parents are dicks, you know.
Whatever.
No matter what, I
hope they like me.
You know...
when we meet.
Uh, by the way, when
will we meet your parents?
Well...
if you want to go to Miami.
My mom lives there with her man.
And you can meet my sister anytime.
Although I'm sure
she'll try to steal you.
She loves Russian guys.
What? Are you making fun of me?
I'm trying here, asshole.
Yeah. No, your Russian
is wonderful. Really.
Every single day, you're
doing better and better.
You're almost like
a native speaker.
Oh, okay.
- You're a liar.
- No, no, no.
Not now. Ani, not now.
I'm playing. I have a mission.
Give me the controller.
I lost.
- Okay.
Arguments and Facts
ran a photo of him
with some chick at an NBA game.
And they are saying
she's a prostitute.
It's not funny, man.
Don't you dare laugh.
If it's true, Toros
and I are fucked.
Well, Toros would be
fucked more than me, but still.
Sounds like tabloid bullshit.
Probably.
But listen, if things get crazy,
don't get rough with Ivan.
Actually, don't even touch
Ivan. Let me deal with him.
I got you. But what do
you need me for then?
In case his boys are there
and they want to play games.
Hey. Is Ivan at the house?
I don't know.
He hasn't left since I've been
here, but I just started my shift.
Do you know if he got married?
Married?
I have no idea. I just got here.
Okay, open the gate.
Drive in and park
on the right side.
Right here.
- Expecting guests?
- No way.
Yo, what do you want?
Ivan, it's Garnik.
I know. What do you want?
Ivan, open the door, please.
I'm busy. No.
We have to talk.
Why do I always have
to repeat myself with you?
I'm busy. I have guests.
- Ivan, it's important. We have to talk.
- No, we're done. Get the fuck out of here.
- Who was that?
- They're my father's monkeys.
Son of a bitch.
What the fuck?
Are you fucking kidding me?
What the fuck are you doing?
You think you can
enter my house like this?
Vanya, what the fuck?
- Slow down, you'll break my leg.
- I don't give a fuck.
- Vanya, should I call 911?
- Ivan, your father sent us.
It's okay. It's okay.
Right, my father sent
you. Are you kidding me?
Well, not us.
Your father sent Toros
and Toros sent us.
So where's Toros?
He's busy.
But he will be very upset
with you if this is true.
If what is true?
That you got married
to some prostitute.
What?
Is that her?
Are you married to her?
Yes.
Did you lose your fucking mind?
Yes, we married and
we're doing fucking great.
- With a signature and paperwork?
- Yes. Now get the fuck out of my house.
You're in big trouble, brother.
You'll be in trouble if you
don't move your fucking leg.
Vanya, what the fuck is going on?
We'll wait, I need to
see the marriage license.
Fuck. Are you serious?
Bro, the faster we do it,
the faster we're out of here.
My parents are fucking crazy.
Okay.
If my parents need
proof, I'll give them proof.
Where is the marriage paper?
- Marriage...
- The marriage license?
- License, yeah.
- It's...
It's in the desk in
the office. Why?
- Okay.
- Should I go with you?
No, no, no. Stay here.
Wait here.
Hi.
Here. Choke on it, dude.
I'm Igor.
You?
Ani.
I'm Vanya's wife.
Congratulations.
What are you doing?
I've been asked to take a
photo of the license, if it exists.
That's insane.
My parents asked for that?
Toros.
Are you fucking kidding me?
No.
What the fuck is going on here?
I have no idea.
It's over, go, go, go.
Wait. Wait.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah, it's okay.
- Yeah? What the fuck is going on?
- Yeah, just time to say goodbye to guys.
Me and my wife need some privacy.
You look tired, Garnik. Go home.
We need to wait to
see what Toros says.
I'm waiting for you and
your fucking Armenian ass
to be out of my house.
Sorry.
So sorry.
I'm so sorry. Excuse me.
I'm waiting for you to be on
your fucking way. Welcome, bro!
Ivan...
It's Toros.
"Stand by."
"Stand by"?
He texted, "Stand
by," so we stand by.
So stand by outside my
mansion, motherfuckers.
- Yeah.
- What's the problem?
So, apparently, it is true.
Yes. I've seen the
marriage license.
Galina Stepanovna,
please don't worry.
Ivan, with all due respect,
your father sent us.
Fucking Toros sent you!
Toros works for me! I pay him!
And you bring some
fucking gopnik into my home.
I promise, I will fix everything.
Galina Stepanovna.
Yes, Galina Stepanovna.
I'm having your ass fired!
You're dead for this!
Bitch!
Okay, look, look. You
work for Ivan's family,
so I'm assuming that means
you work for him, right?
So if he's telling you to take it
outside, fucking take it outside.
Fucking take it outside!
Listen to my wife!
Real talk!
Are you kidding me?
Everybody, so sorry. I have
to go. I have an emergency.
Sorry about that.
He says we have to stay here.
Move, move.
Move. Thank you.
Wait. It's Toros.
Hello, Toros.
Put me on the fucking speaker
so this hooker can hear me too.
He just called me a hooker?
You're already on speaker.
She's fucking erotic
dancer. Hi, Toros.
What did you do,
Ivan? What did you do?
I don't check in on
you for two weeks,
and you go and marry a prostitute.
Fucking hell.
I'm not a fucking prostitute,
you fucking piece of shit.
- Yeah, fucking Armenian piece of shit.
- You Armenian piece of shit!
Do you understand
how shameful this is?
- Toros.
- Your mother was crying. Do you hear me?
- Toros!
- Your mother,
she never cry in her life.
She was crying on the phone.
- Toros!
- Shame on you!
Fuck you! Blyat!
- Ivan.
- Fucking faggot.
And guess what.
Guess what, you little shit.
And what? Surprise me!
You really did it this time.
What?
Your parents are on their way!
Your parents are on the way.
Can you hear me?
To where?
Here. Where else? Here.
Coming to pick you up
like a naughty schoolboy.
You hear me?
We're meeting them
tomorrow at noon.
Vanya, what the fuck is going on?
They're taking you back
to Russia, so start packing.
Ivan, what the fuck?
What does that mean?
Do you understand?
Game over for you. That's it.
Vanya, we are married. They're
gonna have to accept that.
- Yeah, I know!
- Yes.
Accept that?
That's funny. Sure, yeah.
Ivan, listen to me carefully.
I'll be there in ten minutes.
You and your whore
are coming with me.
Whore?
Your mother is a fucking shlyukha.
- Who the fuck is this guy?
- Hey!
I'm gonna be there in
ten minutes, you hear me?
In ten minutes, both of
you are coming with me
down to the city hall.
We're gonna annul this marriage.
Do you hear me? This
marriage is gonna be annulled!
Oh, I am not going
fucking anywhere.
We are not getting a
divorce because you tell us to!
Go fuck yourself!
You go fuck yourself.
How about that?
Me go fuck myself? Me fuck myself?
You go fuck yourself and your
fucking mother, motherfucker!
Shut the fuck up! Shut the fuck up!
You don't even know
who the fuck I am.
Stop, stop, stop. Toros, Toros.
You said my parents are
on their way to America?
Yes, yes. Are you deaf?
They are leaving Russia in an hour.
Tomorrow, noon, we're gonna
go meet them, you hear me?
- What the fuck is going on?
- Come on.
- Come on?
- Come on, come on, come on.
Why do we have to leave the house?
They can't just fucking
come in here like that.
Excuse me. Get the fuck
away from me, please.
Toros will be here in ten minutes.
Garnik, shut that bitch up, please.
- Where are we going, Ivan?
- Ivan, Ivan...
I don't know where are
we going, but we are going.
Where is he going?
Why do we have to leave,
and why are they staying?
- Ivan...
- That doesn't make any sense.
Ivan, where are you going?
We should call the
fucking police or something.
In ten minutes,
Toros will be here...
- Vanya.
- Garnik!
Did he say he's leaving?
- Ivan! We...
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Okay! I need to
get dressed, though!
No, no. Let's do this,
let's wait for Toros.
My fucking clothes
are upstairs. Fuck!
Garnik, get him. Garnik,
don't let him leave.
- Toros will arrive in ten minutes.
- Where the fuck...?
- Vanya, wait. Give me one fucking minute.
- Stop, stop.
- Where are you going? No.
- I have to get dressed.
- I have no fucking pants on.
- Oh, God.
Okay, bye.
- Did he say bye?
- What the fuck?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Keep her here.
- Ivan!
- Oh, my fucking God!
- Garnik!
- Ivan, what the fuck?!
Whoa. Uh...
Get the fuck out of my way.
Ivan!
Get the fuck out of my
fucking way, motherfucker.
- But you...
- Do not fucking touch me!
No. No, no, no.
Stop!
Ivan! Ivan!
- Fucking touch me!
- Relax. Relax.
- It's okay.
- You fucking relax.
What is happening?
Somebody talk to me, please!
Don't you touch me, motherfucker!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
- Relax. Whoa.
- Motherfucker!
- Everything all right?
- What?
Fucking impressive.
- Okay.
- Stay the fuck back!
No, no. What? No, no, no!
Put it. It's... It's bad way.
- Just sit.
- I fucking dare you.
- Take another fucking step, motherfucker.
- No. I don't... I don't touch you.
No, no, no! Don't leave. It's okay.
Just put it... No!
Stop.
Please stop.
Stop, please.
No, no. Stop.
Stop. Stop, please.
Garnik, what are you
doing? Are you killing her?
- Stop it!
- Fuck!
Ivan throwing another
one of his tantrums, huh?
Hold on. It's okay.
If you don't stop,
I will tie you up!
You're not tying me
up, motherfucker!
Get the fuck off me!
You are fucking insane.
Hey. Hey!
Help me! He's attacking me.
- What the fuck are you doing to her, bro?
- Get the fuck off me! Somebody help!
- What do you mean?
- Get him off me!
You wanted me to keep her
here, so I'm keeping her here.
Yes, but why are you tying her up?
But she got fucking crazy.
Started jumping all around.
- What else could I do?
- Help me!
- Why are you just standing there?
- Igor, what the fuck are you doing, man?
She threw the candlestick at me.
Let's tie her legs.
No, no, no! Please,
please, please don't.
We are not doing that. Let her go.
Let me go, you fucking asshole.
- Goddamn fucking bastard.
- She will run, bro. I promise.
Where will she run?
We're two grown men here.
Are you out of your mind?
Okay.
- You crazy motherfucker!
- Hey.
You better stay the
fuck away from me!
Stop, stop. Listen. You
are not going anywhere.
Come back. Please come...
- She will run away.
- Really?
Hey, stop.
Get her!
Get the fuck off me!
Put me down, motherfucker!
Fuck!
- What the fuck, man?
- She's biting, man!
Fucker!
Come on, tie her legs.
What? How?
You motherfucker! Fuck!
What do you mean,
how? Somehow, dude.
Fucking motherfucker.
You fucking asshole.
With fucking what?
Use anything!
- That cord.
- No, no. Don't, don't.
No, no, don't. I don't... I don't
even know what is going on here.
I didn't do anything. Don't tie me.
I'm not gonna run. I promise. I'm
calm. I'm not gonna do anything.
- I'm not gonna run away.
- What?
- You do not need to tie me.
- Are you fucking kidding? Tie her!
No, you motherfucker.
You don't need to tie me.
- Calm down. Listen, listen.
- I am calm. I am calm.
Ivan's father wants
this marriage annulled.
You're staying here
and getting this annulled.
You heard my boss.
Fuck your boss.
I swear to fucking God!
Garnik, you stupid fucking idiot!
Oh, fuck.
I just want to know
what is going on.
Someone fucking tell me what's
going on. I'm not gonna run. Let me go.
Damn, it's broken.
I think she broke my nose.
Yeah. I'm glad I broke
your fucking nose!
You fucking bitch,
you broke my nose!
Yeah? Next time, I'll kick
you in the fucking balls!
- God, let me go!
- Hold her.
Garnik, you fucking
idiot, talk to me!
Fucking untie me, motherfucker!
Hello? Garnik?
Hold on a minute, Toros. Hold on.
You fucking piece of shit.
- Hold on?!
- Fucking psycho.
- Come on, man, hold on. Fuck.
- I am not fighting.
Garnik, I swear, if
you fucked this up...
- Garnik! Motherfucker!
- Untie me.
I am not fighting. I'm not
gonna run. Just fucking untie me.
No.
Don't let her go!
I swear!
Oh, you are so fucked.
You're going to prison.
Where's your ice?
I can't wait until Ivan
sees what you did to me.
Rich people don't have ice?
Ivan did just leave the house.
He did not leave. He
is going to get help.
I don't think so.
Garnik!
You fucking asshole.
Yeah, I bet you like this, huh?
Yeah, you like this, you sick fuck?
I bet you get off on this.
Fucking psycho.
Tor, where are you?
Here, you donkey fucker.
- Open the gate.
- Okay, sir, but Ivan just...
Open the fucking gate!
I am not fighting. Let me go.
No. You are not going anywhere.
Don't let her go, under
any circumstances.
You two are fucking dead for this!
I am Ivan's fucking wife!
Vanya?
Oh, are you the Armenian
fuck I was talking to?
What the fuck is happening?
Is this the big fucking boss?
- What happened here?
- She happened.
Hey, mister. Can you fucking
tell this guy to untie me?
- What?
- Yeah, she did this.
- Hello.
- Where is Ivan?
Ivan run away.
- Why the fuck is no one...?
- Run away?
Excuse me, sir. Hello.
- You didn't stop him?
- I tried,
but then there
was ice on the floor.
- I tried to stop him.
- Hello?
- You tried?
- Hello?!
You tried? You don't try.
You just grab the guy.
What do you mean, you tried?
- What do you mean? I'm not a...
- So he's gone?
I'm not allowed to
touch that motherfucker.
- Excuse me! Hello!
- Shut the fuck up!
No, you fucking let me go.
Tell this guy to fucking let me go.
What were you doing?
Why did you let him leave?
Are you the boss?
You're the fucking boss?
What? He told me
not to touch the guy
- and I was dealing with her.
- Tell him to fucking let me go.
Fucking... Excuse me.
- Fucking motherfuckers.
- Please leave your message...
He doesn't answer.
He doesn't pick up.
Hey, fuck face.
Of course he's not going to answer.
Can you tell this
motherfucker to let me go?
Why is she on top of you, man?
- What's going on?
- I don't know what's going on.
Can you please
tell him to untie me?
- Why is she sitting on you?
- I'm holding her!
Put her down, please.
- No, don't do that.
- Yes, fucking put me down.
No, don't do that.
Tell him to fucking
put me down, please.
Put her down. Why
you holding her like that?
- No, no, no. Be careful, bro.
- Fuck. Fuck!
- Be careful.
- Why...?
Hey, now can you tell
him to fucking untie me?
Why did you...? Why...?
Why did you tie her hands?
- Untie me.
- Look.
- You afraid of this little girl?
- Can you tell him to fucking untie me?
- She's an animal.
- She's a fucking little girl! So she...
- She beat you both up?
- She's not fighting like one.
- I'll get my phone.
- Can you untie her?
- If you untie her, I'm just leaving, bro.
- This is ridiculous, man. Untie her.
- It's embarrassing.
- She will start swinging again.
I can untie her, but you
won't get what you need
because she's out of control.
- Fuck you.
- She's an animal, bro.
- Trust me.
- No, these guys are
- fucking liars.
- Okay, listen to me.
Where is your phone? Can
you please give me your phone?
My phone is in the other room. I
will go get my phone if you untie me.
- I need you to untie me.
- Where?
Which other room?
Over there? Can you...?
Go grab her phone, please.
No, I will get my
phone. I'll get my phone,
- and I'll call Vanya.
- I will untie you.
- Give me a minute.
- No, don't do that!
- I just need your phone to call Ivan.
- I know, and... I will get my phone.
I'm telling you to get
the fucking phone!
Let's just calm
down for one second.
- Careful.
- Calm down for a second.
- Just calm down.
- I am calm.
- I'm not fucking moving.
- Listen to me.
Okay, look, we have
an emergency here.
It's very important.
Okay, I need you to
cooperate. I'm begging you.
Your guys came in here.
They chased Ivan out
of the fucking house.
They fucking tied
me. They attacked me.
That motherfucker was
making me sit on his fucking lap.
Your guys are fucking crazy.
I'm terribly sorry it went
down that way, okay?
I'm terribly sorry.
But now we have to just call
him, okay? Here. Help me, please.
He's on your phone?
Yeah, it's under "husband."
Okay. Yep. "Husband."
Here we go.
- Please leave your message...
- It goes to voicemail.
That's a fucking great
husband you have.
First ditches you, now
doesn't answer your calls.
Real marriage my ass, man.
He's flown the coop.
Fucking little piece of shit.
I don't know what kind of...
fucked-up family
shit is going on here,
but Ivan and I are married, okay?
This is a real marriage,
and I'm not getting a divorce.
This is not a real marriage.
This is a real marriage.
Okay, and we're getting it
annulled, and you have no say in it.
Well, I'm his fucking wife,
so I do think I have a say in it.
Absolutely not. Listen
to what I'm telling you.
You got married illegally,
it's a fraud marriage,
- and we're getting it annulled ASAP.
- A fraud marriage?
No, we are two consenting
adults who got married legally,
and there is nothing you
can fucking do about it.
No, this is Ivan
just fooling around!
- Would you get over it?
- No, it's not.
- You have no fucking idea.
- Oh, yeah?
When'd you guys meet, huh?
- When did you meet him?
- Strip club.
I am telling you, you
do not know this guy.
I do know him.
You do not know this
guy, I'm telling you.
- Oh, I know my husband. I do.
- No, you don't.
It's classic Ivan.
I've been dealing with
his shit since he was...
- He was 6 years old.
- Classic Ivan.
And now his parents
are gonna kill me,
and my fucking family
will never talk to me again.
Little bastard.
And you left the baptism
halfway because of this guy.
- Tell me about it.
- Oh, my God.
I love my husband, and I
plan on being with him forever.
No, don't give me that bullshit.
Do not give me that
bullshit. You don't love him.
You do not love him,
and he doesn't love you.
You understand?
That's in your head.
I can't wait to have
Ivan's children.
In fact, I think I'm
probably already pregnant.
I certainly hope you're lying
'cause we're gonna have
to take care of that too.
- I promise you that.
- Oh, the fuck you will.
- Yes, we will.
- And I would like all of you
to fucking untie me
and leave my home,
- or I will be pressing charges.
- Your home?!
- Yeah, my home.
- This isn't Ivan's home.
This is his father's house.
Everything Ivan has belongs to his
father. You understand? Ivan has nothing.
You know that bedroom
you've been fucking in?
That's his parents' room.
Do you know where is Ivan's room?
It's down the hall with fucking
spaceships on the walls.
Do you know why?
- Do you know why?
- Fucking tell me why.
- You're already gonna tell me, so...
- Because he's a fucking child. That's why.
Fucking kid.
You don't understand.
He's shamed his family
by marrying somebody like you.
If you think for a second
this is gonna be allowed,
you're dead wrong.
In fact, if you don't help me fix
this, I'm gonna have you arrested.
Yeah.
- I'm gonna have you arrested.
- Arrested?
Yeah.
- That's fucking hilarious.
- Yep.
- Arrested for what?
- For what?
- Yeah.
- I'll tell you for what.
- Trespassing.
- "Trespassing."
Fraud, cheating.
- Theft.
- Theft?
- Yes, theft.
- Assault.
And I... Actually, the picture
is very, very clear here.
A scheming prostitute
married Ivan, cheated...
Cheated Ivan to marry her, so
she can steal from his wealthy family.
- That's it.
- Definitely.
And I'm sure you already
have criminal record, so...
For sure happened.
Yeah. One, two,
three, you're in jail.
- Easy.
- Yep.
Ivan proposed to me.
He wanted to get married.
He put a fucking ring on my finger.
- Do you see this shit?
- What ring?
He bought me a
fucking four-karat ring.
Does this look real
to you, motherfucker?
Bet you've never seen one of
these before, have you, huh?
Uh, take that ring off her finger.
- No. No.
- Take it off.
This is my fucking
ring Ivan gave me.
- Give me that fucking ring.
- Why?
I am not giving
you the fucking ring.
Take that fucking ring off!
Touch me and I will scream,
motherfucker. Do not come for me.
Get that fucking ring off of her.
- Be careful.
- Hold the legs.
Careful, bro!
This is Zakharov's property.
- Fuck you! Fuck you!
- Shut up. Shut up.
Rape!
Hey, hey, don't scream.
Hey, what is she saying?
- Rape! Rape!
- Shut up. Shut the fuck up.
Is she saying "rape"? Is
she...? What? What? Shut up!
She bites!
Ouch! Rape? What rape?
- Don't go near to her.
- Rape!
Shut her mouth! Somebody
is going to call the police!
- How?
- You got to shut her up!
How? I need a rag or something!
Motherfucker!
- Rape!
- Shut the fuck up.
Stop screaming.
Please stop screaming!
You get us in front of that
judge first thing in the morning,
or the family cuts
ties with your firm.
Simple as that.
No, no... No trying.
Everything will be okay.
Yeah.
Time to break this bitch. Let's go.
You calm now?
You gonna behave?
Careful.
Trust me, I know.
I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking this
little shit betrayed you.
Well, guess what, he
betrayed me too, okay?
- Me too.
- You see?
He betrayed all of us.
'Cause he's a spoiled brat
that doesn't want to grow up.
Big time.
And now we're in this mess
that we have to fix it together.
You understand?
But I'm gonna help you.
Okay? I'm gonna help you.
The way I see it, this is
a green-card marriage.
Therefore, Ivan owes you
a green-card marriage fee.
It's only fair.
So once this thing is annulled,
I'm gonna make sure you
get $10,000 fee in cash.
I'm gonna bring this down,
but no screaming, okay?
If you scream, this goes
right back in. You understand?
Ten K.
It's as good as you're
gonna get here, honey.
What do you say?
I want to talk to Ivan before
agreeing to any of this.
Sure. Of course.
We all want to talk to Ivan.
We want the same thing.
Okay, so let's fucking find Ivan.
All right, but look at me.
Look at me.
Once we find Ivan... Which we will.
And we get this thing
annulled... Which we will.
You're gonna walk away with 10 K
fee and never, ever contact Ivan again.
Is that understood?
Fine.
Untie her.
You got their marriage
license and passport?
Excuse me, I have to get dressed.
Can I have some privacy, please?
Anora Mikheeva?
Ani. It's Ani.
It says Anora.
I know, but I go by Ani.
- Thank you.
- Okay, get in.
So I'm done?
You're with us until
we find him. Get in.
Wait, why is he getting back here?
I'm not sitting next to
this fucking psychopath.
- Can I sit in the front?
- You are the psychopath.
Yes, get in the front. I don't
want to fucking sit next to you.
I'm not getting
back there with you.
Un-fucking-believable.
Klara, come here.
It's a bit messier than usual today,
so this is for you. No questions.
So you're saying
he's gonna be there?
I have no fucking idea.
He better be. Okay, let's go!
I need to go to the hospital...
No, you're okay.
Don't worry about it.
No, I'm not, bro.
I feel like I have a
concussion or something.
- I'm sorry for what...
- Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Was happening back there.
How could I have imagined...
I don't want your dude
talking to me, okay?
Leave her the fuck alone, man!
My head is pounding,
bro. You can't even...
Shut it, Garnik!
Oh, my God, we're gonna
get into a car accident
with you driving like that.
- Are you suicidal or something?
- Just shut the fuck up.
- You almost hit that old lady.
- What do you know about driving?
- What do you know?
- You shut the fuck up.
Swing by my place and
I will give him something,
so he'll stop whining.
- Give him what?
- What he needs.
You're the biggest
fucking pussy I ever met.
Just don't eat all at once.
What the fuck?
Okay, let's go. It doesn't matter.
Let's go. Let's go.
A little bit faster.
Hurry up.
- Hey, Crystal.
- Hey, Ani.
Hey, have you seen Vanya today?
- No, why? Is everything okay?
- No?
Uh, yeah, everything's fine.
Could you give him
a call for me, please?
Okay. What's going on?
I just need you to call him. Can
you do me a favor and call him?
Um...
Don't ask too many questions.
Just pick up your phone and call him.
Okay. Tom?
- Tom, Ani's here...
- Miss?
- Hey, Tom.
- What's up, Ani?
Have you seen Vanya today?
I have not. No.
Okay, has he, like,
texted or called you at all?
No, not at all. No.
Okay, could you
just call him for me?
- Who are these dudes?
- My friend, can you...?
- It's fine.
- Can you call Ivan, please?
- Is everything okay?
- Wait, what's going on?
- Everything is fine.
- Why would I call?
- Just pick up your phone and call him.
- I'm not gonna call him. Who are you?
- Doesn't matter who I am.
- It does matter.
I'm not gonna give you
my phone to call Ivan.
Ivan is in a lot of trouble.
We need to find him.
One of you better get
Ivan on the line now.
"On the line"?
- "On the line"?
- What the fuck is funny?
- Who the fuck are these guys?
I'm telling you to call Ivan.
What's wrong with that?
Don't complicate your life.
I'll complicate your fucking
life, you motherfucker.
- Why?
- That's not a good idea.
- Get out of here.
- That is not a good idea.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- Tom.
What's up, man?
Tough guy.
What do you plan to do with that?
Break your legs if you
don't get the fuck out.
- I told you it's a fucking bad idea.
- Tom.
- So pick up your phone and call him now.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Fuck off.
Fucking smash everything.
- What the fuck?
- Fuck, fuck, fuck...
Tell him to fucking
stop! What the fuck?
- Oh, no.
- Fucking call Ivan now!
- What the fuck, man?
- Okay, okay. Jesus, fuck!
That's crazy.
- Oh, fuck.
- I am so fucked.
Put it on speaker.
I am so fucked.
Please leave your message...
- Where's your phone?
- Hold on, man.
Just don't break
anything, all right?
- Call him.
- What the fuck?
- Put it on speaker.
- There you go.
Just don't break anything, man.
He's not gonna answer the phone.
- I know. I know it.
- Please leave your message...
He's not gonna fucking answer.
Where's his other friend?
Is he with Aleks?
Aleks is working right now.
- He can't be with Aleks.
- Where is he working?
Tatiana's.
- Fuck.
- Let's go.
No. Oh, no.
What the hell?
- Jesus fucking Christ.
- Where are you going?
- To the car.
- It's five-minute walk.
No, no, no. I'm not
walking down there.
- Let's drive up there.
- It's freezing.
No, I'm not gonna
look for other parking.
- Come on, let's go.
- Why don't we drive?
It's right here. Walk.
Chop-chop. Move.
It's fucking cold, man. Look at me.
Are you doing this on
purpose? What the fuck, bro.
That took way fucking
longer than five minutes.
Hey.
Table for four?
Is Aleks here? Aleks?
Aleks?
He should be working here.
- The assistant cook?
- Yes.
Let's go.
No, wait. Hold on.
- You guys cannot go in there.
- No, you're good.
They know what
they're doing. Relax.
- Oh, my God, Aleks.
- Ani!
- Have you seen Vanya?
- No. What's going on?
We're looking for Vanya.
It's a family emergency.
- Have you seen Ivan?
- What the fuck is going on?
- No.
- I can get fired.
- You're good.
No, you're good. Don't
worry. Don't worry about it.
- Can you call him?
- I haven't seen him.
- Call him? Really?
- Yes, just call him.
Yes, please call him. Call him.
Are you an actress? I
saw you somewhere?
I'm not an actress, no.
No? You look good.
Where are you from?
Give me your phone one second.
We can't find Vanya anywhere.
Have you talked to him today?
No, I haven't saw him.
He's probably at home.
No, he's not at home,
and Tom and Crystal
haven't seen him either.
Can I have my phone
back, please? Thank you.
- I need Ivan's photo.
- Okay.
You gotta have your
husband's photo on your phone.
No, I am not giving you my phone.
I need your phone for one second.
- I just need your phone...
- No, and you know what?
If you touch me again,
I will fucking scream.
Stop. Stop.
Use Instagram.
I don't have Instagram. I'm an adult,
man. What are you talking about?
You're going to cost
me my job here. Please.
I have it. Here.
- Guys.
- Oh, okay.
Ani, what's going on?
We're looking for Vanya.
We don't know where he is.
But it's like, this
nigga's fucking insane.
Okay, thank you. Where...?
Where are you going?
You think that he
would be with Dasha?
Not unless he's in Bahamas
with her and her new fuck boy.
Stop the music one
second. Stop the music.
Excuse me, I'm terribly sorry,
but I need one minute
of your attention.
We are looking for a
missing child, a sick child.
I'm going to show you his photo.
Any information would
be greatly appreciated.
We're the ones fucking
paying and he wants attention?
My apologies, but
the kid is very sick.
Please let us know
if you've seen him.
You didn't see him?
Give me a cigarette.
Are you kidding me?
I'm freezing, and this
guy wants cigarettes.
Toros, seriously.
You'll get cold if you
don't cover your neck.
Why did you bring that?
Why the fuck did you bring that?
Why? So you could
fucking gag me again?
Motherfucker.
Fuck it. Give me the scarf.
No! No! No!
Swear to God!
Hey! Hey! This is my car!
No, no, no.
- No, no, no.
- Man, it's already attached.
- Please.
- It's already attached.
I gotta take it. I
gotta take it in.
- You can't take my car.
- Don't do that.
This is my car.
Hey, listen to me.
Hey! It's your fault!
You were parked in the middle
of the fucking street, okay?
My friend, I was just
parking! There is no sign.
- I'll give you money. How much?
- Listen.
100, 200, 300? Tell me.
Down in the yard, you're
gonna talk to people.
- Okay?
- Take the money.
Fuck you, then. Fuck you.
- What do you mean, fuck me?
- Fuck you.
What the...? I don't give a shit.
- Hey.
- Get the fuck out of my way.
You get out the fucking car!
You fucking asked for this.
I've been on the job
two fucking weeks, bro!
What the fuck are you...?
Are you fucking kidding?
Fucking kidding me!
- Oh, my fucking God.
- Jesus Christ!
Are you fucking...?
It's all because of you.
- Fuck you!
- Get in the car!
- Come on! Come on!
- You are so fucked.
I have your license plate. If you
get in that car, you're all fucked.
No, no, no!
What the fuck are you doing?
Fuck you, Russians!
- You are crazy.
- God. Jesus Christ.
You guys are fucking crazy.
We're going to find this fucker,
even if it takes all fucking night.
I swear on my mother's life.
What the fuck did you just do?
Come on, give me
something. Like, something.
- Where would you...?
- I don't know. I don't know.
Think. Think. Where?
He... Gaming. He likes video games.
Maybe he'll be at an arcade
or something. I don't know.
Hurry up. Stay awake, man.
Guys, anybody see this guy today?
Have you seen Vanya Zakharov?
No, not tonight.
Guys, see this kid today?
Oh! Billiard hall.
There is the billiard hall.
Remember, five years ago, we...
You were teaching
him how to play billiard?
We played here, right
here around the corner.
- You remember?
- Five years ago?
I remember.
Come, come. One second, my friend.
Look at this picture.
Have you seen this guy?
Ivan, Ivan.
- Is that Vanya?
- Yeah.
Have you seen him today?
- No, not today.
- No.
He does the greatest
parties, though.
Yeah, he's really cool.
I hate this bitch so much.
I want to vomit
when I see her face.
Please leave your message...
Guys, have you seen this guy?
He's... He's been missing.
You sure?
Let me ask them.
- Wait, stop.
- Give me a second.
Guys, have you seen this...?
- This guy today?
- No.
He's probably not lost.
Perhaps he is kidnapped.
Yeah, sure, kidnapped. Of course.
Think, think, think.
And can you keep
calling him, please?
What the fuck?!
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, you gotta be
- fucking kidding me!
- Jesus fucking Christ.
You understand that my wife
has to drive this car tomorrow?
Do you?
How am I gonna
get rid of this smell?
It's better you go back to Yerevan.
Fucking get rid of you.
Do you want to blow us up?
- I'm careful.
- Fuck off!
Get the fuck out of here!
You care about Ivan more than me.
Start cleaning!
Who's more important,
Ivan or your dying brother?
Yeah, I'm not
getting back in there.
Fuck Ivan. Fuck that little bitch.
It still fucking stinks in here.
Fuck, I know. Shit!
Which clubs did you go with him?
I don't know. We went to... I don't
know. We went to a lot of them.
Take me to every single one.
Hey, have you seen this guy today?
Yeah, we cut him
off. He was wasted.
When?
Like 20 minutes ago.
He just left.
Have you guys seen this guy today?
No?
Did you ask about Ivan Zakharov?
He left me an $800 bill.
- Where is he now?
- How should I know?
- But somebody has to pay me.
- Okay, bye.
No, wait. But you know him.
I told him my apologies. You
can tell him one more time.
I'm gonna definitely make them up
to you. Or up to them, or up to you.
What can I do? What
do you want me to do?
He's fine.
Tell his mom that
everything is fine.
He's sitting next to me.
Is it a real mink?
I'm telling you, I can't
talk anymore. I have to go.
No.
Please, I'm begging
you. Please stop.
- It looks like real mink.
- Of course I do. Why you...?
I am ashamed as well.
Yeah, it's fucking
real, but it's not mink.
It's fucking Russian sable, okay?
- I'm the godfather of that child.
- Which is worth a lot more than mink.
Of course I'm ashamed.
No, don't... Don't
talk about that baby.
Guys, have you seen this guy today?
- End of the line.
- I just have a question.
Have you seen this kid?
Yeah, he was here 30 minutes ago.
He was too drunk to enter.
- Do you know where he went?
- Who the fuck knows?
Your ID, please.
What a shitty godfather you are.
Instead of protecting
the child, you just left him.
Are you fucking with me?
Maybe he's on a bender.
If you're so competent,
why did you let him leave?
How do you say bender?
Uh, "Bender."
It... It's a bender. Yeah.
Tor, what does that have
to do with competence?
Fuck this shit. I
didn't sign up for this.
I just want to go home
to Armenia. This sucks.
I'm so fucked.
So fucked!
You know, he fucked me
much harder than he fucked you.
- Oh, yeah?
- Hundred percent.
Trust me.
If we haven't found him by
now, we are not finding him.
Did I ask you? Did I ask you?
I'm just saying, man.
Keep your opinion to yourself.
I'm not going to talk
at all from now on.
Ani's fucking billionaire
husband just strolled in,
and he's looking for action.
And I'm gonna give him some.
Vanya?
Vanya.
You know, it's so sad.
That marriage must really
be in the toilet already.
Vanya's here?
'Scuse!
- Have you seen this guy today?
- No.
How about you, sir?
Igor, thank you for the pills.
I want what he had.
I want one of those.
Did you fucking hear me?
I said I want one of those.
No.
No?
What the fuck? Why?
'Cause I don't deal drugs.
A fucking gopnik who can
afford to live in Brightwater
and doesn't deal drugs?
Yeah, right.
It's my grandmother's
apartment and her drugs.
I don't have any more,
and I'm not gopnik.
Yeah, you're right.
You're a faggot-ass
bitch, is what you are.
Hey, guys, have you
seen this guy today?
No.
What does faggot-ass bitch mean?
Fucking faggot.
Yep, what he said.
Go away!
Why are you being rude?
- I'm just asking a question.
- I don't give a shit.
And why am I faggot-ass bitch?
I don't know. They say
you're just born that way.
You know what, I'm so
sick of your generation, man.
I mean, look at you.
No respect for elder, no
respect for authority, no goals.
I mean, the only goal you have
just to buy pair of cool sneakers.
That's all. I mean, honestly. Come
on. What the fuck is wrong with you?
Why don't you just hear me out?
No work ethics.
Lazy, stupid.
I don't understand.
I've been working
since I'm 16 years old.
What is wrong with you?
All you do is TikTok,
Instagram, TikTok, Instagram.
- That's it.
- He's at HQ!
What?
Fucking Headquarters!
Hey. Hello.
- What's the address?
- West 38th Street.
- I fucking love that place.
- You mean, fucking Manhattan?
- Yeah, it's in fucking Manhattan.
- Oh, my fucking God.
- Hurry up!
- Oh, I need cash.
- Toros!
- That's 45 minutes away. Hurry up.
Beautiful.
You're Vanya, right?
Yeah, that's me.
Anora. Anora!
It's not Anora. It's Ani.
Tell your friend to hold
him there at any cost.
Even if they have to physically
hold him. Like, grab him really.
- More? More?
- More, more.
Because you have the
best skin that I ever touch.
- I love you. I love you.
- How do you say it in Russia?
Don't have a heart attack,
but Vanya's upstairs in
a private with Diamond.
Ani, who the hell are these guys?
Vanya?
Where is...? He's in
one of these rooms?
Yeah.
Shit. Sorry.
- Sorry. Sorry, Daisy.
- Hey, Ani.
Vanya? Oh, shit.
Carla, have you seen Diamond?
I think she's in the pole
room. Hey, what's going...?
- Where's pole room?
- Fucking pole room.
- Vanya?
- Oh, what the fuck?
Oh, get the fuck off
my fucking husband.
You fucking mad?
Yeah, I am about to
be fucking mad, bitch.
- Skip out, ho.
- Let's go!
Oh, you want to fucking go?
Yeah, come get some, bitch.
We're running around all night,
and this guy is here
getting his rocks off.
- Nice to see you guys.
- We were looking for you all night!
We've been fucking looking for you.
All night!
I've been texting. I've
been fucking calling you.
Why haven't you answered
any of my fucking calls?
- You little son of a bitch.
- Why'd you fucking leave me, Vanya?
I tried to run after you.
These guys, they
fucking tied my wrists up.
- They took my ring.
- For what, bro?
They fucking assaulted me, Vanya.
Okay, get up. Let's go.
You can talk in the car.
- Get up.
- No, I fucking found him,
so I get to fucking talk to him.
- Okay? That was the deal.
- Vanya, our hour's not over.
Oh, get her the fuck out of here!
Oh, get the fuck out
of my private, bitch!
- Vanya, look at me.
- I am looking at you.
I'm coming back, bitch.
Fuck you, Diamond.
This is very important.
Vanya, look at me. Just
listen to me, baby, listen.
These guys, they want
us to get a divorce, okay?
It's not divorce.
- I told you hundred times.
- Back off. Let me...
It's annulment. Annulment.
Vanya, tell them that we're
not gonna get a divorce, okay?
- Tell them that this is a mistake.
- Are my parents here yet?
Baby, this is very important.
- Listen to me.
- No, no, no. We...
Your parents are coming at 12.
I helped you, so let
me fucking talk to him.
We still need to go
- to the courthouse!
- Vanya, just look at me, okay?
Fucking ignore them. It
doesn't fucking matter about her.
It doesn't matter about
anything, okay? Just...
I need you to tell them...
Vanya, this is not funny.
I know. It's not funny.
Vanya, look at me, baby.
- Let's stay married, okay?
- Yeah.
You know these guys?
Yeah, I love them. I love them.
Jesus, Vanya.
We have to talk about this, okay?
This is very, very important, all right?
- I don't want to talk about it right now.
- Okay, but just...
Look, what...? No, no, no,
Vanya, we can't drink right now.
You need to tell them...
Guys, he's fucking drunk.
We can't talk right... No.
We're not fucking done talking.
- I wanted to talk to him.
- Come on.
Here we go!
Vanya. Vanya.
Vanya, Vanya, we have
to keep talking about this.
Vanya! Do not fucking
touch me! Jesus.
Vanya, we're not...
We have to keep talking.
They're trying to bring us
to get a divorce. We can't...
Do not fucking... Get the
fuck out of my fucking face.
Jimmy, Ani's here with
three guys causing a scene.
Russian Ani?
- I fucking told you.
- Get the fuck out of my fucking face.
Didn't I? Two weeks
on the fucking nose!
Wrong one, bitch.
Guys, there's a fucking fight!
- No way!
- Oh, shit!
Oh, my God, I love it.
I don't recommend that.
Garnik, do something!
Yo, yo, yo. Break it up.
Take it outside.
Take that shit outside.
There's no fighting at HQ.
Okay, calm down.
Man, get the fuck out of here! No.
Get the fuck out of here. Get
back. Get the fuck out of here.
You told me Ani's one of our girls.
- Go. Go.
- In the car.
Fucking found you! We found you!
I can't believe you went
running like a fucking baby.
But it's okay. Your
parents are coming.
You're gone. You're gone, finally.
- Fucking gone.
- Vanya. Vanya.
Do you know what's
happening right now?
Do you fucking know what's
going on right now, Vanya?
Get off me, man.
He's fucking wasted. He...
I need to talk to him
when he's fucking sober.
- I can't talk to him like this.
- Talking is done.
Talking is not done. Of course
he's gonna do anything you say.
- He's fucking plastered.
- Talking is done.
Now we're gonna get this
thing done in three hours.
- No, this wasn't the fucking deal.
- Yes, it was.
- Slow down. I'm gonna get sick.
- We're gonna get this thing done.
You're gonna get your fucking money,
and you're gonna walk away. That's it.
That was the deal.
Fuck.
What? You know, you must...
You must really hate me, man.
I mean, seriously.
And after all I've done for you.
You know, everything.
I mean, I bailed you out
how many times? Huh?
How many times?
And you do this to me?
You know, it makes me upset.
You know, it's... You know how...
How embarrassing that is for me?
Are you even listening
to what I'm saying?
He's passed out, a bit.
Now we wait.
Okay. He's here. Hey.
Wake up. Wake up.
He's here. Let's go.
Vanya.
Wake up, brother. Come out, please.
I want to stay in the car.
- Vanya, Vanya, look at me.
- Do not get a ticket and do not get towed.
We need to talk before
you go in there, okay?
Vanya?
- Keep your phone on.
- Vanya, Vanya.
Don't say anything when
you go in there, okay? Vanya.
Vanya, I'm gonna handle this, okay?
- I got it.
- Handle what?
- Don't talk to him.
- None of your fucking business.
- Let's go.
- Hello, everyone.
- How are you, sir?
- Toros.
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
Whoa, is he all right there?
Does he fucking
look all right to you?
- He is okay.
- He is not fucking all right.
- He can barely stand.
- How are you?
Fine, thanks.
Uh, the judge is being very
kind, and he bumped us up.
- Good.
- Hello, Ivan.
Ivan, it's Michael Sharnov,
your father's attorney.
Remember me?
You don't remember Uncle Michael?
He's a little bit tired.
- It's okay.
- I see.
Tired?
And this is the...
The lucky lady.
- Okay. And who is this?
- Him we're gonna need.
Just holding.
Okay, I don't know what that
means and I don't want to know.
Let's go. Get your IDs ready.
I talked to him and it's
clear he wants this done.
But does he know that
his son is intoxicated?
He's not intoxicated.
He just woke up.
Toros, please. Come on, man.
I'm not gonna risk my
license because you can't...
You want to keep working
for Zakharov family or not?
Mr. Sharnov.
- Consider yourself very fortunate.
- Your Honor.
We have a light
calendar today, so, um...
what's your urgent matter?
Your Honor, we are
here to file a complaint
and request for an
immediate annulment
of a union that took
place under duress.
Ivan Zakharov and
Anora Mikheeva married...
Duress, my fucking ass.
- Okay.
- Whoa.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Your Honor,
but this is bullshit.
- It's bullshit.
- Your Honor, I...
- These men are trying to...
- You gotta stop.
You can't... You
can't talk this way.
Okay. I'm sorry. They're
trying... Do not fucking touch me.
- Who's this man in the camel coat?
- Please get this man away from me.
Who are you, sir?
Mr. Sharnov, is he with you?
Get him away from me.
- Come on, come on.
- Officer, take him...
Your Honor, I apologize.
Thank you, officer.
I appreciate it.
- Okay, have a seat. Have a seat.
- I'm sorry.
And thank you, Your Honor.
- I really appreciate it.
- You're welcome. Keep that tone.
- Okay.
- You're welcome.
Your Honor, clearly, my
husband is intoxicated right now.
He is in no place to be
making any decisions.
Your Honor, objection.
She shouldn't be talking.
Don't listen to her, please.
- Camel coat, sit down.
- My stomach.
- He is clearly intoxicated.
- Why is she talking?
What I have been trying to explain
to you... We got married legally.
Objection, Your Honor.
They're not legally married,
and she shouldn't be talking.
- I shouldn't be talking?
- Camel man, sit down.
- My apologies.
- Your Honor, I apologize.
My client doesn't
know what she's saying.
And they are trying to force
us to get an annulment...
- I am intoxicated.
- Sit quietly or begone.
We got legally married at
a legitimate marriage place
- in Las Vegas, Nevada.
- Miss, please keep it down.
It is real.
- We have a marriage certificate.
- Mr. Sharnov, take charge now.
- We're not gonna be signing...
- They got married in Nevada?
So what?
We can't get it annulled here.
- Mr. Sharnov.
- What?
- We can file for one...
- Mr. Sharnov.
But if you want this
now, you have to go there.
- Last time.
- Do you see what
- I've been dealing with?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- My stomach hurts.
- Folks, get out.
- No, no, no.
- Have a seat.
Officer, get him off the
table before he throws up.
- I need... I need...
- Fuck!
Get him off the table.
- Get him out.
- Fuck!
Everyone out of the court.
Come on.
Clear the court, officer.
- Time to go.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Officer, clear the court, please.
Why did you go to Vegas?
Why not here in New York?
Guys, you don't have to
fucking drag him around.
Why not here in New York?
Can you explain to me?
We got fucking married in Vegas
because that's where he proposed to me.
So now we're gonna
go see your parents.
- Vanya.
- You're gonna explain to them
that you went to Vegas
without my permission.
No, we're not fucking
going anywhere.
- You understand? It wasn't my fault.
- Vanya.
- You too.
- Oh, no, I am not going anywhere.
You're gonna tell them that you took
him to Vegas without my permission.
- No, no, no.
- This is not my fault.
- No, we are...
- Get in the car.
- I'm not getting in the car
'cause we're fucking done here.
And I want my fucking ring now.
You got a ticket?
- Vanya, you don't have to...
- What's going on?
Vanya, get out of the car, okay? You
do not have to listen to these people.
You had one job
and you get a ticket?
You don't have to listen to them
because you're an adult, Vanya. Okay?
I must have dozed off.
You dozed off! But I
told you not to fall asleep!
Yeah, but are we done?
You are an adult.
Let's go.
I just need to talk
with my parents.
Okay.
Okay. All right. We'll
talk to your parents, okay?
We're gonna talk to your parents,
and they're gonna understand
because they love you.
Get in.
What happened?
They got married in Vegas,
that's what happened.
They love you, and they're
gonna understand, okay?
- Vanya, okay? Right?
- What are we going to do now?
- They're gonna understand, right?
- Get in the car.
Get in the car.
This is a never-ending nightmare.
Right, Vanya?
Right?
Get in the car.
I want him clean and
presentable in ten minutes.
And you behave.
Once...
this idiot and his friends
decided to swim in Kool-Aid.
- Do you know what that is?
- Vanya.
It's a juice.
They were stoned
and poured 4 pounds
of Kool-Aid in the pool.
They destroyed the whole system.
$87,000 in damages.
Hello, Galina Stepanovna.
Where is he?
Okay.
Showtime.
Nikolai Ivanovich,
how was your flight?
Face down, ass up.
I have some bad news.
Go on.
- You're not going to be happy.
- I'm already not happy.
What?
Vanya. Vanya.
What's wrong with you? Look at me.
Are you drunk?
Damn. Garnik, he's drunk.
Yes, Galina Stepanovna,
he's not sober,
but it's not our fault.
Mom, I got it. I'm
already embarrassed.
- So you're embarrassed?
- Yes.
So you're embarrassed?
You made our family
a national disgrace.
Galina Zakharova.
I'm Anora.
It's so wonderful
to finally meet you.
It's such an honor
to be Ivan's wife...
and a part of your
beautiful family.
Ivan is not your husband,
and you are not
part of this family.
And your Russian is embarrassing.
- Is this from the new collection?
- Yes, new collection.
Uh, ma'am?
- Ma'am?
- Yes?
Vanya and I, we are in love,
and we would like
you to accept that.
Vanya is not in love
with you. Understand?
- And we will not accept it, okay?
- Galina.
Toros has something to tell you.
Fuck.
You are all idiots.
Vanya, we cannot get on
the fucking plane right now.
Toros, we will discuss
your future in our company.
Vanya, why are you listening
to your fucking parents?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Vanya, we have to talk
right fucking now, okay?
Kolya, hang up the phone already!
Vanya, we have to fucking talk.
No, no, no. Go back to the plane.
I want us refueled and
in the air in ten minutes.
Vanya, fucking look at me. Vanya.
Vanya, be a fucking
man and talk to me!
Is it necessary to take
the night butterfly with us?
Yes, both parties must be present.
What do you want me to say?
Can you understand
that now we must go
in the fucking plane
and fly to fucking Vegas?
Get it?
You get it?
So we're getting a divorce? You...
Of course! Are you stupid?
Ivan, hurry up!
One second.
And thank you...
for making my last
trip to America so fun.
Yeah? You had fun?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Where is she?
I don't know. There.
Board the plane now.
No.
No, I'm not doing that.
You are getting on this plane
and you are getting divorced.
Yeah, we're gonna
get a fucking divorce,
but, uh, first I'm
getting a lawyer.
Then I'm gonna sue Ivan and you,
and I'm gonna walk
away with fucking half
because I didn't sign a prenup.
Do that and you'll lose everything.
Any money you may have...
Although I doubt you have much.
Will be gone.
Do you have a house?
Do you have a car?
All gone.
Your life and the lives
of your family and friends,
everything will be destroyed.
You want to talk about it now?
- Yes.
- Because I don't.
Please show some
respect, I'm hungover.
If we were your age and if
we had everything we wanted...
Listen, you little shit.
Next week, you start working.
Understand, little shit?
Why do you need me there?
Maybe it's not the right
moment, but I just want to say,
I'm very happy to finally
be able to spend time
with your wonderful family.
Thank you so much for
trusting me and Toros.
Stop it, get out of
here. Are you crazy?
I want to say a couple
of nice things to them.
Better you married a man.
Do you think that can't happen?
Then what kind of
freedom can we talk about?
If I can't potentially marry a man?
- Galina Stepanovna, I just...
- Listen.
I'm sorry, I just want
to use this moment
to say thank you...
Don't interfere. We are
having a family discussion.
So you think it's normal?
Everything that happened is normal?
How did you end up in Vegas?
I understand...
and forgive you what you did.
I just bought a ticket and flew
to Vegas. Why can't I do that?
- Who gave you permission?
- Who would forbid me?
Great.
I'm so grateful for
your forgiveness.
You talk about freedom and
then ask why I went to Vegas.
Why can't I just fly to Vegas?
Because you went to study.
Not to party, drink
and get hungover.
Why make a tragedy out of it?
What do you want from me?
Do you want me to apologize?
Just kill me, Mom.
What did I do? I just
spent time with an escort.
I just spent a week with
her. So, what's the big deal?
Why are you making this such a big deal?
This isn't our family's biggest problem.
Sit!
It's not going to be
a fucking problem.
I breastfed you!
I'm fucking glad to be
divorcing your sorry ass.
- You are fucking pathetic, man.
- Are you seriously?
You're a pathetic motherfucker.
Fucking pathetic.
- Blyat, no.
- See?
You hurt your mother so much.
I gave you everything.
Kolya, give me your hand, please.
I'm just going to
need some signatures.
If I could just get
that back from...
Actually, if I could
just hang on to all...
- Could I just...? Thank you.
- Okay, question.
- Okay. Yes, of course.
- What this mean?
We don't need to worry about
that. That's for the judge, so...
- Are you sure?
- Um...
Very sure.
Okay, so we're just gonna
need some signatures here.
So there you go, and
this one will be for...
Come here.
Sorry, I'm gonna
mispronounce your name.
- Sign.
- So, Anora Mikheeva,
I just need your signature as well.
Thank you. Um... Oh.
There you are.
Where the red box is.
Sign, please.
And then... Oh,
sorry, just one more.
Thank you. Great.
Oh. Um...
- May I have my ID?
- You can.
All right. Let's go. Come on.
This may be out of line,
but I think it'd be
appropriate if Ivan apologizes.
Don't pay any attention
to him. He is tired.
He also drank on an
empty stomach on the plane.
He helped us all night.
Listen here.
My son won't apologize
to anyone. Is that clear?
Of course.
'Cause your son is a fucking pussy.
What?
What? What?
What? Did you not hear what I said?
I said it's 'cause your
son's a fucking pussy.
That's enough.
Let's go.
And you are a disgusting hooker.
And your son hates you so much,
he married one to piss you off.
That's enough.
Yeah.
Yeah, your family is fucking trash.
Is this my scarf?
Yeah, you want...?
There. Go get your
little scarf, sweetie.
- That's enough. Let's go.
- Oh, I'm leaving.
- I'm leaving. You know what?
- Okay. Let's go.
What are you laughing at?
Why don't you take
your fucking coat too.
That's enough. Let's go.
- Thank you so much, ma'am.
- You're very welcome.
- Goodbye, America.
- Okay.
It's for you.
- Present.
- Sorry. Oh, gosh.
No, I couldn't. Thank
you so... Wait, is this real?
Take them to McCarran
Airport, domestic.
Igor is gonna take you back.
You can stay in the house tonight,
but you gotta be out
of there in the morning.
And he'll pay you when
the bank opens. Go.
And thank you.
And it is starting
to stick, as well.
We'll show you a live look
at the roads in a little bit,
but officials that we've talked
with today say they are ready
for whatever Mother Nature
brings the next few days.
We got thousands
of sanitation brothers and sisters
coming in, doing overtime tonight.
If it accumulates, we'll be clearing
snow and ice from the street.
Every highway, every
bike lane in the city.
We'll be out starting a
midnight shift tonight.
On Long Island, the salt trucks...
Happy birthday to me.
Was today your birthday?
January is National
Blood Donor Month...
No.
Is urging people to donate.
Advocates say the winter
months are a crucial time...
Yesterday was my birthday.
The senior vice
president and chief of staff
at New York Blood
Center, Clarissa Heyward...
Yesterday was your
fucking birthday?
I was 30.
Mm. Happy fucking
birthday, I guess.
Thank you.
I like Anora.
I mean, I like Anora more than Ani.
Okay.
Says the fuckhead named Igor.
Fucking Igor.
Stupid name.
No, it's a good name.
It means "varrior."
Warrior.
Yeah?
Igor means "hunchback
weirdo," you fucking piece of shit.
Can you shut the fuck up, please?
"Toosh."
- "Toosh"?
- "Toosh."
Touché?
Touché, motherfucker?
You know, you really
should try learning English
before attempting French.
Okay. Touché.
Yeah.
And your name is better?
No.
But what does it mean?
In America, we don't
care about that kind of stuff.
We don't give meaning to names.
It's... It's not a thing.
So it means...
"pomegranate fruit."
"Light."
Yeah, I'm not interested
in conversation, dude.
And "bright."
It's good that you're
not part of this family.
Did I ask for your fucking opinion?
- No.
- No. Exactly.
I just tried to support you.
Support me?
Dude, you fucking assaulted me.
You... Fucking support?
- You... No, you...
- What?
No. I didn't assault you.
You didn't... You
don't call that assault?
- No?
- No.
No, you're right, it's fucking
battery, as well as kidnapping
and fucking a million
other felonies, I'm sure.
Fuck you, dude.
But I didn't assault you.
I was trying to calm you
down so you didn't hurt yourself.
You fucking pinned
me to the ground.
You tied my fucking
hands behind my back.
You... You fucking gagged me.
Have you seen the fucking bruises
on my legs and my fucking arms?
You fucking assaulted
me, you psychopath.
First, it's because
you have sensitive skin.
No, it's not. It's because
you're fucking crazy.
And second, because
you're too crazy.
I mean "crazy too."
But I can say you're too crazy too.
It's not funny, yeah.
Touché.
"Toosh"?
But anyway, you were not in danger
of injury or harm, right?
You know, if Garnik wasn't there,
you'd have raped me, guaranteed.
Raped?
No doubt.
Why...? Why would I have raped you?
You have rape eyes.
- Raped eyes?
- Rape eyes.
You heard me.
You sick motherfucker
would've raped me.
Okay, uh, but I didn't
want to raped you.
Oh, yeah?
Why?
What?
What "why?"
Why wouldn't you have raped me?
Because I'm...
not a rapist.
Nope, 'cause you're
a faggot-ass bitch.
Here.
Good night.
Hey.
Don't tell Toros.
This car is very you.
Do you like it?
No.
It's my grandmother's.