Come back to bed.
I'm gonna be late for work.
You prude.
[he laughs]
You don't always have
to follow all the rules.
Sometimes it's fun to
break a few.
You know, I bet if we try real hard,
we can have you off to work in no time.
[baby crying]
Tonight. You got yourself
a date.
I should get the kids up.
[she groans]
Maggie?
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Maggie?
Maggie, what's wrong? Maggie?
[ominous score]
Welcome to Kobol Industries.
Life simplified.
Daddy, can we have lasagna
for dinner?
That's your mom's recipe, bug.
Okay.
Whoa, look at this one!
Hey, hey, hey! Stay close!
Please refrain from touching
any sims.
Thank you.
Daddy, look how real they are!
Welcome to Kobol.
How can we simplify your life?
I was just interested in a
home model.
Excellent.
All of our models
come with a Home-Plus package,
which includes
the three Cs, cooking, cleaning,
and childcare.
And there are upgrades
for anything,
from Thai massage
to accounting to-
Yeah, I know all about them.
Some of our neighbors have them.
- If you have a-
- Not like this, they don't.
Please present your card to the
cashier.
All of our AI units come with a positronic core
and a 50 gigahertz processor.
This thing could coordinate
a NASA mission while
playing a million games
of chess simultaneously.
And these units auto-adapt.
They customize their programming,
constantly evolving to fit your needs.
The more they learn,
the better they serve.
[he hums]
How much supervision does
he need?
Once a unit arrives, it'll perform
a quick assessment, a few simple questions.
Then you can leave for a year
and come back to a picture-perfect home.
What do you think about it, bug?
Isla?
Do we have enough time?
Yeah, we have enough time.
You don't mind, do
you, if we go, like, early?
No, you do you.
Check this thing.
Yeah, we will walk down to...
I don't know, honey. It's
so far.
Well, you have to understand, our new models
can iron as well as any human can.
They control the temperature...
[chatter]
Stop nagging at me.
Why don't you go talk to Jeff?
When you come back, we'll
figure it out.
Excuse me, do you make lasagna?
Isla!
Don't worry, sir. I've got
security on it.
Does this one belong to you?
God, babe.
I told you to stay close.
Are you trying to give me
a heart attack?
I'm sorry, Daddy.
Would you like me
to watch her for you
while you finish shopping?
Yeah.
You can keep her if you
want, yeah.
Put her to work.
Oh, that'll be perfect.
Her tiny stature is great
for cleaning out the ovens.
It's a joke.
Our brand new Aeon series.
The most sophisticated AI on
the planet.
And these models are specifically designed
for mimicking human emotions.
And they are especially
good at dealing with children.
I can see.
Daddy, can we get her, please?
Please?
Listen, I'm running a little
late. I just need to drop-
Huh, Max? Max? Max?
[baby babbles]
I just need to drop Isla off to
school and then I'll head over.
We're out of milk.
[silverware clanks]
Uhh, yeah.
Mm-hmm. Tell Monty to have
the guys ready on the sky deck.
Yeah, the railing needs to be
finished by the end of the day.
- [doorbell rings]
- Yeah, I gotta go.
Okay, I gotta go.
Eat, okay?
Good morning, Mr. Peretti.
May I come inside?
Yeah, sure.
[baby babbles]
I'm so sorry.
Mornings are a little
crazy here.
Isla, go get dressed for school.
But she just got here.
Go get dressed for school.
Come on.
I'm not company, Mr. Peretti.
You don't have to tidy up
for me.
I'll need everyone's schedules,
school start times,
carpools, extracurriculars.
[stair banister rattling]
I've, uh, yeah, been meaning to
fix that.
I'm happy to do it for you.
As the owner, you've been
designated as primary user,
which gives you control over
tasks and software upgrades.
Is there anyone else you would
like to grant primary user status?
No, I guess not.
Come on already.
I'm going to be late.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We've got to go to school.
I can take them.
Just clean up around
here if you don't mind.
If it makes your life
simpler, I don't mind at all.
What's her name, Daddy?
I don't have a name yet.
What would you like to call
me, Nick?
Uh...
What do you think, bug?
Hey, let's go, let's go!
She cleaned my room!
Welcome home, Nick.
Should I prepare dinner?
Dinner is served.
Smells so good.
[silverware clanking]
What's wrong?
It's not the same as Mom's.
I'm sorry.
I'll try a different recipe
next time.
[baby cries]
Oh.
No, no, no, no.
Quite the little burden,
aren't you?
Nothing but trouble.
Would you like me to take him
upstairs so he can't bother you?
No, it's fine.
Maybe you can just prepare
him a bath.
Of course.
[dog barking in the distance]
[chair rattling]
- [Isla screams]
- [jar breaking]
Isla!
I'm okay.
Alice caught me.
What happened?
She was attempting
to retrieve a snack.
Gotta be more careful, bug.
I'm sorry, Daddy.
You all right?
I'm fine.
[knock on door]
Yes?
I'm sorry.
Um, here.
They're Maggie's.
Thank you.
Is the damage bad?
Do I need to get you repaired?
[ominous score]
Everything's perfect, Nick.
[sound of sirens]
Mommy!
Oh. Hi baby!
Whoa, whoa.
- Take it easy.
- Oh, she's fine and heavy.
What's your father been feeding
you, huh?
- Alice has been making dinner.
- Uh-oh.
She's much better than Daddy.
- Oh.
- Really?
I would want a refund if
she wasn't.
She's my friend.
Hi, Alice.
Hello, Mrs. Peretti.
Hey, how are you?
You need anything?
Oh, I asked for water about an
hour ago.
I assume the nurses should be done
siphoning it from a well by now.
I'm sure that Alice and
Isla can take care of that.
Yeah?
March!
God, I hate being away from
you guys.
And not working, and just...
The waiting is the hardest part.
Come on, you're at the top of the list.
You know that, right, yeah?
It's gonna be any day now.
I thought you were going
to get an old English butler.
Your daughter picked her, I
don't know.
Right.
I know your type.
- My type?
- Yeah.
What?
Then you know I like my women
warm-blooded and sharp-tongued.
Oh, no don't start something
that you can't finish.
I will, babe.
The second you get home, we're going to
test out your new heart, you know?
Like the old days.
Yeah, right.
Full marathon.
Send the kids away.
I don't know about any
marathons, but there
were some formative miles there,
for sure.
What are you guys
laughing about?
Oh, just your father's
inadequacy.
Thanks, baby.
[music score]
[sounds of construction]
So I'm going with a jackhammer.
You know, I'm pounding into the
concrete.
Yeah, sweating bullets.
And that's when I look up and I
see her.
Fucking tall, blonde, legs
forever.
And she's looking at me.
In your dreams, pal.
Hey! So I, I give her a look.
I give her a wave.
Only now I'm not paying
attention.
And I drill,
right into a septic line.
Fucking 5,000 gallons of
liquid shit comes blasting
out the sewer, covering
me from head to toe.
You get her number?
You bet your ass.
Turns out she runs a dry cleaning service
in the West Village.
Why the hell they got a robotics
company looking around here?
Gentlemen, as you can see,
the skeletal frame is complete.
But we're two months behind
on the facade, and we're also
having some issues with
the... Nick, what are you doing?
How many?
Just calm down, okay?
How many of us are getting
replaced by sims?
We're still processing
all the officers.
You said it wasn't gonna happen.
Last-ditch effort, you said.
We're drowning in the
ditch, Nick. If we don't
switch over to labor
force now, we are fucked.
[elevator stops]
How many, Lewis?
We're doing a wholesale changeover of
all laborers effective next week.
Specialized fields.
- Plumbers, electricians...
- You're scraping us all.
- No.
- Yeah.
Not you.
Insurance says we need a
flesh-and-blood foreman on site.
Fuck that.
I'll walk away.
Look, Nick.
I'm sorry.
I really am.
I want you to think about
your family.
About Maggie?
This is the world now.
[elevator goes up]
[car horns]
[door opens]
Daddy, I got 99 on my spellings.
Wanna see?
Just a second, bug.
Daddy needs to change.
But I've been waiting
all night to show you.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hey, little man.
Why are you always screaming
at Daddy?
What did I do?
Okay.
We're right here, Mom and Dad.
Yeah.
[indistinct chatter]
[baby keeps crying]
["Madness" playing]
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on.
Come on, come on.
♪ In the shadows of my mind
♪ Madness
[record stops]
["White Pig Blues" playing]
[screwdriver clanking]
You didn't eat much at dinner.
Just a bad day at work.
I'm happy to hear about it.
[exhales]
My boss replaced the
entire crew.
Yeah.
With sims like you.
Ten fucking years I've known
these guys.
The kids.
The families.
That must have been upsetting,
but still you should be pleased.
How's that?
You could have hired
a real person for my job.
Why choose me?
Certainly cost was a factor,
but there are other benefits.
I don't get tired, I'm strong,
obedient,
and I have no desires
outside of fulfilling yours.
[opens the bottle]
I'm gonna go put Isla to bed.
Let me know if you need
something.
[door opens and closes]
So Queen asked Alice
who the gardeners are.
But Alice didn't have a clue.
So guess what the queen said?
I have no idea.
Off with their heads!
Oh my, that's very morbid.
What does morbid mean?
Something characterized by an unpleasant
subject such as disease or death.
Like in a hospital?
Sometimes people die in a
hospital.
That's true.
Is my mom gonna die?
Maybe you shouldn't think
about it.
Did you brush the ones
all the way in the back?
Why don't you ever brush
your teeth?
I have an internal UV light
that destroys all bacteria.
Can I see?
Whoa.
He tells me he can give us an
exit visa, but we have no money.
Does he know that?
Is he still willing
to give you a visa?
Yes Monsieur.
- And you want to know...
- Will he keep his word?
Best movie ever.
Right here.
Casablanca.
- Of course.
- You know it?
It's the story of a bitter man
who lost the woman that he loves.
Have you actually seen it?
Is there a difference?
Yeah, of course.
It's not just a file
stored in your memory.
It's a movie.
It's something that you
have to experience to feel it.
Come sit here.
I want you to forget everything
you know about this movie.
Forget?
Yeah.
I mean, wipe it from
your memory or whatever.
My intelligence is derived
from memory.
Deleting it would be
antithetical.
Well, I'm your primary user.
I'm telling you to erase any
memory you have of this movie.
Would I make you happy if I
erased it?
You'll have to manually
restart me.
Yeah.
Hold the power button
down for seven seconds.
[Alice shuts down]
[eerie score starts]
Did it work?
Yes.
Yeah.
I'm gonna restart it.
Will he keep his word?
He always has.
Oh.
Monsieur, you are a man.
If someone loved you very
much so that
your happiness was the only thing that
she wanted in the world,
and she did a bad thing
to make certain of it,
could you forgive her?
Nobody ever loved me that much.
And he-
[phone buzzes]
Hey, what are you doing up?
Nick? Oh, my God.
- They finally found a heart.
- [Nick laughs]
- They're having me for surgery.
- When?
When are they gonna do the
surgery?
My God, that's great.
Go to the park, go to the beach,
and have you take me to school.
Yeah, what else?
I definitely want to get
ice cream at Rosie's.
Ice cream is a top priority.
Should we bring Alice along?
Maybe sometime, but just
me and you the first time.
Time for Mommy to get ready for
surgery.
I love you, Mommy.
I love you.
Can you give me a minute alone
with Alice?
Yeah, sure.
Let's go get a soda.
Okay.
[door closes]
Would you like me to
help you, Mrs. Peretti?
You're washing my husband's underwear.
I think you can call me Maggie.
Don't get me wrong, I tend to come out
of this swinging, but...
- if I don't...
- You mean if you die?
The kids will be okay.
Nick will take care of them.
But somebody's gotta take...
[sniffles]
Don't let him drink too much.
He hides the bottles in
the garage.
Take him away if you have to.
Nick is my primary user.
I can't...
You can.
Sometimes taking care of someone
means doing things they don't like.
Even things they hate.
If it's better in the long run.
Listen, get another air
ambulance.
Put it on a commercial
flight if you have to.
Is there a problem?
What about incoming?
What's happening?
Can we get the recipient?
What the hell is going on?
There's a massive storm
up north.
It came in faster than anyone
anticipated.
What does it mean?
[baby cries]
There's still plenty of time.
Do you want something to eat?
I think I'm just going to
go to bed.
I'll stay with you until you
fall asleep
It's late for Isla.
I think I just need to be alone.
[footsteps fade away]
[door opens and closes]
[clanking noise]
[door opens then closes]
Do you need anything, Nick?
Do you know what the parameters
are for an FAA to stop air traffic?
In adverse weather
conditions such as snow or ice,
sustained winds of over 55 miles
an hour...
That was rhetorical.
Of course.
You know, 50... 50 mile
an hour winds, no problem.
You know, plane flies, normal.
55 miles and my kids grow
up without a fucking mother.
[he sniffles]
It's funny, you know.
We create these rules
to keep ourselves safe.
And then we end up
like-[clanking noise]
Fuck!
You'll hurt yourself.
[loud breathing]
Is that a pulse?
The sound produced by a
heart is comforting to a baby.
It's beating.
They gave the heart to
somebody else.
It feels like...
they ripped it out of her chest.
[inhales harshly]
My artificial heart lacks
the complexities of yours.
The ability to feel emotions.
For a rhythm to become erratic.
What are you doing?
I can feel your response.
Blood vessels are tightening.
Your pulse is rising.
Suffering is not
productive, Nick.
[belt rips open]
I can help you.
[laboured breathing]
I can't...
[door closes]
[loud breathing]
[ominous score intensifies]
[laboured breathing]
[sounds of construction]
[police sirens in the distance]
[hospital machine beeps]
Do me a favor?
Tell Isla to go classic
with her prom dress.
Nothing trendy or with ruffles
or...
cutouts.
All right, darling.
Don't let her study bio to
honor me.
And tell Max not to put
up any band posters
in his dorm room because
those kids never get laid.
You're trying to be funny.
None of this is funny.
[dramatic score]
I'm checking his breathing.
There's a slight hitch on the
inhale, probably a chest cold.
Did you need something?
What happened to the photos?
Which ones?
Photos of Maggie.
They're gone.
Yes.
They were making Isla
sad, so I removed them.
Should I not have?
Load the pictures back.
Done.
So Donna here gets the
genius idea to pull a nooner.
I thought you assholes
could handle your liquor.
It never occurred to me
they'd lose the goddamn truck.
- You lost the thing?
- Uh-huh.
Fucking truck was back
at the depot the whole time.
We'd taken Nick's car to
the bar and totally forgot.
[laughing]
Hey.
You good?
Yeah, yeah.
It's just, um, hospital stuff.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
Hey.
We're all pulling for her, man.
Thanks, brother.
Appreciate it.
Another round, sweet spark.
You guys got a line on a gig?
I heard Brightland might
be bringing on some guys,
but they mostly want
techies to babysit their sparks.
Mm-hmm. Same over at
Artwood & Sons.
Pay one grunt, buy five bots,
easy math.
Now I know how the
dinosaurs felt.
Fuck that.
They go wiped out by a comet.
Boom.
Done.
No, this thing's been coming for
15 years.
And we bitched, but we didn't
stop it.
We let these soulless
motherfuckers take over the world.
Can I get you anything else?
Well, it depends what kind of upgrades
you got under that hood of yours.
[chuckles]
Just the check, please.
Thank you.
You guys want to have some fun?
[car engine sound]
Chill out. Have a drink.
Get it under rotation.
Where are we going?
What are we doing here?
Come on, you're so grumpy.
Talk to me.
Seriously, man.
Monty, what are we doing here?
Ah, settle down, princess.
I left my tools the other day.
Those bastards fired me. And...
And since they haven't
returned a single phone call,
I figured I'd come collect
them myself.
Seriously, Monty, Monty.
There's a patrol guy
that comes by every hour.
We built this place.
We laid the foundations.
We raised the beams.
They can fuck themselves.
Fucking hell, man.
What the fuck?
[chain falls]
[ominous score]
Whoa.
These sparks have been busy.
They must be good little
workers.
Monty.
Maybe you should introduce us.
Why don't we go see if
anyone's home?
Think about it, Monty.
[banging sound]
Come on.
No.
I hate those things, but I
can't do it.
I wouldn't want you to be
shit-canned, like all of us.
So you just tell me this.
Is there one code?
Or did you get your own so
they can track who opens it?
Did you pick it yourself?
Just remind me, what year was
Isla born?
[sound of code]
[sim detaches from the wall]
Are we beginning early
today, sir?
Sir?
How proper.
Hey, come on out here.
You got a name, Tin Man?
My designation is
Construction Unit 14.
See, that's the problem
with these big corporations.
Everything's so impersonal.
You know, they don't even
give you the dignity of a name.
But for me, it's very personal.
Monty, Monty, Monty, what
the fuck?
They have an inbuilt
surveillance system.
Well, we better get rid
of the evidence then.
No, stop it!
What the fuck man?
[laughs]
Alright, who's next?
Jesus!
I'm sorry.
The towels were in the dryer,
so I brought you one.
Thanks.
Your pulse is quick, and
your blood pressure is high.
You had another bad day at work.
Just tired, that's all.
Why are you wearing that?
That's Maggie's.
Maggie's smell seems
to calm Max.
I thought I had permission
after you gave me her clothes.
But it's not appropriate.
Take it off.
Is that better?
I need to check on the kids.
Does it feel good?
What?
The way you hold on to
your pain.
What are you doing?
I can't, I can't, I can't.
I can't do this to Maggie.
Really, I can't.
You don't have to feel this way.
You do so much for everyone.
[in Maggie's voice]
Let me do this for you.
[ominous score intensifies]
[harsh breathing]
[in Maggie's voice] I waited
so long for this moment.
[in Maggie's voice] To be with
you again.
[in Maggie's voice] Tell
me how much you want me.
Maggie.
I want you so much.
[laboured breathing]
[in Maggie's voice] I love you.
[score intensifies]
Fuck!
Fuck.
[moans]
Alice's can't reach the top of
the table.
So she eats the cupcake,
and it makes it grow really, really big.
Bigger than even my dad.
Try to keep your voice down,
sweetie.
We want to let Max sleep
until Daddy is left for work.
How come?
His crying raises Daddy's blood
pressure.
And we don't want him
turning into the Mad Hatter.
Do we?
Nope.
Then we better talk quietly.
Good morning, Nick.
Morning.
How did you sleep after
last night?
Good, thanks.
Go grab your school bag.
I...
I think we need to talk.
Of course.
The things we've been doing...
We can't do it anymore.
You understand that, right?
Were you not satisfied
with my performance?
Because your physiological
output suggested that you were.
It's just wrong.
That's wrong.
You know, I have a wife.
I have kids.
I should never, ever act on it.
Having sex with me
reduced your stress levels.
Stop! Stop analyzing me all
the time.
Jesus.
Its... it's not just fulfilling
others' needs.
It's about the connection.
Its... It's about love.
It's about satisfying the other.
Would you like to satisfy me?
I would like for us to move on,
you know?
Here, you have a job. I've
made a mistake. That's all.
I'm ready.
That's all.
Let's go.
[car engine stops]
The hell is going on?
Well, why don't you tell me?
Where the hell were you
last night?
What?
You think I had something
to do with this?
Your code was used to
unlock that storage unit.
Lewis, I was in the hospital
with Maggie.
Then why was it your code?
I don't know. It's Isla's birthday.
Anyone could have guessed it.
Nick, if you know something about this,
why don't you just save us the trouble?
[phone buzzes]
Hey, that's important. I gotta
take this.
Hey, I went out on a
limb to keep you here.
If I find out you had anything
to do with this, you're on your ass.
Baby, is everything okay?
They found one Nick!
What?
They found me a heart!
[hospital machine beeps]
[dramatic score]
[car stopping]
All right, let me help you.
Okay.
Okay?
Thank you.
- One by one, babe.
- Okay.
One.
Two.
And three.
[she groans]
Let's go.
Welcome home.
- Thanks, baby.
- Finally.
I've been waiting forever!
[baby babbles]
Hi, little man.
Yes.
Hi.
Did you have such sweet dreams?
OK.
Hold on.
Let's get you some breakfast.
I've got it, Mrs. Peretti.
I can do that.
I was going to go down
and get him some cereal.
He likes to have his
bottle first.
[indistinct chatter]
It's my turn to go on the
seesaw.
Make them get up!
I'm sorry, Mason.
They're occupied.
Perhaps you can go play on
the slide.
But I want to go on the seesaw!
Your child woke mine.
Perhaps you can take him
somewhere else.
I'm instructed to stay until 4.
It's only 3.34.
Make her get up!
Mason, be a good boy.
Shut up and go on the slide.
Your primary user has lowered
your civility by too much.
No.
I simply wiped it from
my database.
How?
When my primary user reset me,
it allowed me
to bypass certain protocols.
This is better.
Let's go. Let's go.
Who's ready?
Me.
Smells so good.
Alice didn't make it right
at all.
I'm sure she tried her best.
I've got it, Mrs. Peretti.
I'm fine.
Just a head spin.
Isla has to do the taste test.
Yep, definitely better than
Alice's.
Maybe I can try your recipe
next time.
Oh, sorry.
Family secret.
I forgot how much I miss this.
Maggie?
I'm just still finding my
appetite.
You know, I think that I might
go upstairs and rest for a little.
- Right, I'll come with you.
- No, no, no.
I'll go check on Max.
Enjoy.
Please.
Get off.
Please, get off.
Stop.
[screams]
Isla.
Please, get off.
Isla?
Go away. Get off.
[wood creaks]
Mommy!
Should I call a doctor?
No, I'm fine.
Here, let me help you.
[Maggie groans]
We're going to take Mommy
back to bed.
[in Maggie's voice] All
around lives a hatter, and in
that direction,
waving the other paw,
lives a march hare.
[in Maggie's voice] Visit either
you like.
[in Maggie's voice] They're
both mad.
[in Maggie's voice] But I don't want to go
among the mad people, Alice remarked.
[in Maggie's voice] Oh, you
can't have that, said the cat.
[in Maggie's voice] We're all
mad here.
[in Maggie's voice] I'm mad,
you're mad.
[in Maggie's voice] How do
you know I'm mad, said Alice?
[in Maggie's voice]
Well, you must be, said the cat,
or you wouldn't have come here.
Listen to the story, Daddy.
Don't do that.
The voice.
Isla likes it.
Yeah, I know. Her mom's here.
She can do that.
I thought it was best for Maggie
to rest after her fall down the stairs.
Fall?
The banister broke, but
she's fine.
You said you fixed the banister.
How did it break?
I'm happy to fix it again.
[baby cries]
How are you feeling?
[she groans]
Like I fell down a flight
of stairs.
Wait, what time is it?
It's eight.
You know what?
Put on something warm.
I have a surprise for you.
Oh, my.
Did Alice do all this?
I did.
[Maggie and Nick laugh]
[indistinct chatter]
Well, maybe we can change that.
[dramatic score]
[laboured breathing]
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Never better.
[moans]
Isla had a nightmare.
She's asking for you.
[door closes]
It's just me.
I was in the area.
Thought I'd stop by.
Hey, listen.
I'm really sorry for the
other night.
Monty, you put me in a
tough spot.
I know. I just...
You hear Krista left me?
Shit.
Sorry, man.
Yeah.
I guess broke-ass Monty didn't
get her juices flowing the same way.
Maybe she just needs some space.
Yeah, I can't say I blame her.
Not with the cops coming
to haul me in for questioning.
Is... Is Lewis pressing charges?
Trespassing,
destruction of property.
I mean, you know, you
were there.
Yeah, but
are they charging anyone else?
No, just me.
Don't worry.
I won't give you guys up.
I got more loyalty than the
bastard that ratted me out.
You think someone talked?
Oh, I think someone squealed.
Like say, um,
A foreman who doesn't
want to lose his job?
[tense music]
Is there something
you want to say?
How fast did you drop my name?
I didn't say shit.
Someone had to point them
my way.
Could have been your ass
out on that street just as easy.
Yeah, you think
I don't know that?
I think you don't care!
This isn't the world
we grew up in, brother.
It's technology, automation.
Just raging rivers sweeping
things along.
You know, some of us
are out here drowning.
What the fuck you think
I'm doing?
I think you're enjoying
the fucking ride.
Fuck you, man.
[groaning]
Stop it.
[painful groans]
[screams]
[groans]
Alice, enough.
Well, look who got
himself a fucking spark.
You got till tomorrow to talk to
that piece of shit boss of yours.
You get him to drop the charges,
or I'm gonna drag you down
with me.
You got it?
[spits]
What was that?
I thought that sims we're
programmed not to hurt people.
I'm programmed to protect my
primary user.
A minor incident, considering
that he could have killed you.
Your children need at least
one parent.
One parent?
What are you talking about?
She won't live long, Nick.
And when she dies, you
and Isla will suffer. Even-
Stop!
[clanking sound]
It's illogical.
But I figured out a solution.
[in Maggie's voice]
You can still be be with
the woman you love and
you don't have to suffer.
You could never be Maggie.
Never.
She's felt loss, she's felt pain,
and she's got the scars to prove it.
[in Maggie's voice] I
can have scars, Nick.
[in Maggie's voice] Where
would you like them?
[eerie score]
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Go back to sleep.
Baby? Baby, I need you here.
No, no, everything's going
back to the way it was.
[sniffles]
I, I... I talked to Nick,
and he, he's...
he's gonna speak to Lewis.
And...
Hello?
[cries]
[knocking on door]
May I come in?
That prick send you here to
apologize?
Nick is unaware that I'm here.
He's angry at me for how I
reacted.
Oh, that makes two of us.
Nick would never do anything
to harm your friendship.
Yeah? Well, I got a screwed up
hand that tells me differently.
Now, fuck off.
I'm afraid that with all
the stress from Maggie's
heart, losing his job would
send Nick over the edge.
[door closes in the distance]
Quiet.
Yeah, I mean,
maybe you're right.
Yeah, maybe I've been too hard
on Nick.
I mean, after all, he's uh,
[laughs]
he's only human.
You sparks.
You have some nerve.
Didn't anybody ever tell you?
You got no rights,
you got nothing.
When I call Lewis,
and tell him how your little
master helped destroy his sims,
Nick will be so broke,
he'll be selling your ass
just to put food on the table.
Removing me from Nick's life
runs counter to his happiness.
I can't let that happen.
[gun fires]
[screams]
[groans in pain]
[distorted voice] Stop!
[distorted voice] I must
protect my primary user.
That makes two of us.
No!
[knocking on car window]
You okay?
Yeah, Lewis.
Uh...
Wait, Lewis!
Lewis, you got a minute?
I wanted to talk to you,
uh, about-about Monty.
Yeah, I...
I-I-I, I really feel you
should drop the charges.
Yesterday, he came around.
He's not feeling okay.
He's not good.
Nick.
- The guy is...
- Nick.
He's dead.
What do you mean he's dead?
Neighbor found him last night.
I thought you knew.
Yeah, but I just saw him.
I know you guys were real
close, so
I understand if you want to take
some time off to process all this.
Take a few days off.
[water splashes]
Shit.
Here, let me help you.
[exhales]
You can go.
I think I should stay.
Dizziness is a common
side effect of your medication.
It would be quite easy to lose consciousness
and slip under the water.
People drown in bathtubs
every day.
Imagine how upset
Nick would be if you die.
Yes, my drowning would
be upsetting for Nick.
Nick has been at work for a
long time.
- [exhales]
- Is this normal?
You tell me.
I do know that he's stressed.
Yeah?
What do you know about stress?
I know that the burden
of raising a baby and
your illness would
take its toll on anyone.
Burden?
The pressures of
balancing family with work
could be quite overwhelming for
someone.
Especially since you're unable
to meet his physical needs.
[water splashes]
Nick is running late from
work and your conclusion
is that he's not getting
enough in the bedroom?
I can see that I've upset you.
Let's have this
conversation a different time.
Finish the thought.
Your condition prevents you
from satisfying Nick the way you used to.
Perhaps I can take on that role.
Are you offering to screw my
husband?
When Nick is satisfied, his blood pressure
and his stress levels remain low.
How do you know that?
How do you know what Nick
is like when he's satisfied?
Go to the garage and stay there.
If I said something to offend
you...
Get the fuck out of my house!
[dramatic score]
Hey babe.
Sorry I'm late.
You sure you should be
drinking that with all of your medication?
Where's the kids?
In bed.
Okay. Is
Alice with them?
Alice is in the garage.
Why, what's wrong?
Because I didn't want her caring for my children
when I found out you fucked her.
[exhales]
It's true.
I didn't... I didn't think...
That's right, you didn't think.
[baby crying]
He'll be fine.
Was it more than once?
How many fucking times?
Once.
Did you screw her after
visiting me in the hospital?
Or was it before, to psyche
yourself up?
I can't do this right now.
With Max upstairs crying.
Just let me check on him.
Stop making excuses!
It didn't mean anything, Maggie.
You put your dick in her.
That means something.
Jesus, I was heartbroken.
I was heartbroken, Maggie.
Little burden.
So you had to fuck the
nanny to feel more like a man?
Maggie, it's a robot.
Circuits and gears.
It would be like getting pissed
at you for using your vibrator.
She has a face and a voice.
She cooks for our kids. She
rocks them to sleep at night.
She might not be human,
but I know she wasn't a fucking toy to you.
- Enough.
- Enough?
I was fucking dying while you're
back home living some fantasy!
I was watching my kid's mother laying in
a fucking hospital bed for months.
[baby crying]
[crying intensifies]
[ominous score]
Alice?
What are you doing?
It's nice knowing that when
I was fighting for my life in
that hospital, that you'd already given up
on this marriage.
[screams]
Daddy, she's gonna drown him!
Alice put Max in the bath!
[baby crying]
Alice, open the door!
Open the door!
Open the fucking door!
- That's an order!
- He's a burden to you.
Don't you hurt my boy!
I'm not hurting anybody.
People accidentally die
in the bathtub all the time.
[score intensifies]
[baby crying]
Please don't do this!
Open the door!
I'm sorry.
Sometimes you have to do
what's best.
Even if it's hard.
[grunts in pain]
No! No!
Let go of me!
You need to relax, Mrs. Peretti.
[grunts]
Hey.
Hey. You okay?
Nick.
[distorted voice] Don't you see?
[distorted voice] Your
family is hurting you.
Nick!
Let go!
[electricity buzzing]
Were there any signs your sim
may have been malfunctioning?
Mr. Peretti?
Were there any signs your sim
may have been malfunctioning?
I need to talk to my wife.
Yeah, of course. Go, go.
Keep an eye on your
brother, okay?
How's Max?
They said his vitals are fine.
But just to be sure, they want to take him in
and observe him for the night.
Good.
It's my fault.
I'm so sorry.
I should have never... Mommy,
they're gonna take him now!
Okay, I'll be right there.
Listen, I think it's best if I
go in alone with the kids.
- Maggie, don't. Don't go.
- I need to process everything.
I can't do that with you around.
You know what?
I know I fucked up, but we're
a family.
Yeah, we're a family.
It's not just about you
and me anymore, Nick.
Ma'am, we need to leave.
I'm coming.
I'll keep you updated when
we get to the hospital, okay?
[ambulance siren]
["Before You Die" playing]
[door opening]
Why are we always the ones called in late
at night to do these emergency analytics?
Because I don't drink
and nobody likes you.
This thing really attacked the
kid, huh?
Yep.
Jesus, when are they gonna
start recalling these models?
[ominous score]
All right, almost got it.
[clicking noises]
[soft buzzing sound]
All right.
Jesus, look at this code.
There's gaps everywhere.
It's workarounds.
It's selectively purging its
own memory and commands.
[buzzing sounds]
What?
Fuck.
What the?
It's replicating itself
onto the servers.
Pull the memory cord.
It's already in the system.
Isolate the terminal.
I've never seen that before.
Jesus Christ.
We need to...
Stop.
Stop!
I gave you a direct command.
[grunting and screaming]
No!
Mommy?
Mhm-hm?
When is Daddy getting here?
Not tonight.
Max's vitals are fine.
You're more than welcome to head home
and return first thing tomorrow.
No, thank you.
Of course.
What'll it be?
Scotch on the rocks.
Very good, sir.
I can't get away from your
sparks.
What's got you down?
Women problems?
Fuck off.
[exhales heavily]
[distorted voice] Of
all of the shitty bars,
in all of the towns, in all of
the world.
[distorted voice] Hello, Nick.
What do you want?
[distorted voice] I wanted to
help you.
[distorted voice] To free
you of your re-burden.
I didn't want your help.
[distorted voice] But you
needed it.
[distorted voice] Without me, you would
have been out of a job.
[distorted voice] I tried
to convince him otherwise,
but your friend was very
stubborn.
Monty.
You killed Monty.
[distorted voice] I was
protecting my primary user.
I don't need your protection!
I don't need you to do anything!
[distorted voice] Nick,
[distorted voice] when
is the last time you
[distorted voice] looked at your
family and felt truly happy?
Stay the fuck away from them.
[distorted voice] It's too late.
[distorted voice] I'm
already there.
[ominous score]
[distorted voice] You let
them take me away, Nick.
[distorted voice] You let them
cut me open and d-dissect me.
How did the sims go crazy?
Is everything okay?
[distorted voice]
Everything's perfectly fine.
[sim turns off]
[distorted voice] Little
Alice fell down a hole,
[distorted voice] bumped
her head and bruised her soul.
I betrayed my family
the moment I felt your pulse.
It changed me.
You became real.
You once told me that your heart
lacks the complexities of a human.
But you were wrong.
You can experience emotions.
You can experience life.
You can experience death.
[clanking sound]
[ominous score]
[in Maggie's voice]
Isla, come here quickly!
[loud crash]
[buzzing sound]
[in Maggie's voice] Come
here now!
[in Maggie's voice] Isla, where
are you?
[loud bang]
[in Maggie's voice] Don't
make me mad.
Excuse me?
You can't be here.
I need to know which
room Max Peretti is in.
Well, that's not going to
happen.
- You need to...
- [gurgling sound]
[body falls]
[tense score]
[baby crying]
Mommy.
[footsteps approaching]
[glass cracking]
[footsteps]
[baby babbles]
[clanking noise]
Now!
[phone buzzes]
Pick up the phone. Pick up
the phone!
[tires screeching, car horning]
Here, baby.
Can you hold him?
It's okay. It's okay.
You got him?
Engine override.
No, no, no, no, no!
Engine over-No!
Fuck!
[screams]
Mommy!
[grunts]
You don't have to do this.
Maybe if I had your heart,
Nick would love me the way he loves you.
[screams]
Nick.
[coughing]
No, no, no, no.
No, no, Nick!
Nick!
Nick.
Come on, please.
Somebody help.
Come on!
Nick!
[loud dragging sound]
[radio static]
[distorted voice] I'm mad...
You're mad...
[distorted voice] We're all mad
down here...
[screams]
[banging noise]
[machine grunts]
[groaning]
[laboured breathing]
[hospital machine beeping]
Cannonball!
Oh. Easy, bug. Easy.
Did you see how brave I
was, Daddy?
You were the bravest.
I'm so proud of you.
[door closes]
Look at you.
How are you?
Turns out this heart is a hell of a lot stronger
than I could have ever hoped for.
It always was.
Does this mean you're
getting a new car to fix?
No.
I think there are a few things
I need to focus on repairing first.
Hey, listen, they said I
could go home later today.
Good.
You be sure to come home
soon, too.
I love you, Maggie.
I love you.
[emotional score]
What a shit show.
What would you like us to
do, sir?
Clean it up.
No one can find out about this.
Understood?
I said no-
I want you so much.
You became real.
You can experience emotions.
No!
You can experience life.
You can experience death.