Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Hey. Come here. I got you.
- I'm so sorry.
- Hey, you're gonna be okay.
I'm so sorry
you couldn't be here, honey.
I don't know what we're gonna do.
What are we gonna do?
Okay.
Oh, God. We have to pick flowers.
We do, yeah.
I can't believe we're picking flowers
for your father's funeral.
I know. I know.
I don't know why you moved.
I don't understand it.
I mean, if I had
that job that you had--
Oh, boy,
I would've killed for that job.
I appreciate your support
and enthusiasm, Mom. I really do.
I love you.
I'm gonna go set my stuff down.
Okay.
- It's lilies.
- What?
The flowers for a funeral.
They're--
Oh, lilies.
I'm so...
I'm so glad you're home.
Me too.
He really loved you.
Who?
Your father.
I know. I...
Yeah, I know.
How's the eulogy coming, hon?
It is one of the most
beautiful things I've never written.
Just say five things
you loved about your father.
Mama, it's... it's not a grocery list.
Just five... five things.
Simple.
From the heart.
You're gonna be great.
It's gonna be great.
We're here to honour
the prestigious,
generous Andrew Bloom.
Deeply beloved mayor
of this fair town.
Husband of the highly adored
Jenny Bloom.
And father to
the wonderful and sweet Lily.
Lily, come on up
to the stage, darling.
Hello.
Thank you all for joining us.
In honour of my father's life,
I would like to share with you
the... the five things that
I love most about him.
He...
I'm sorry.
It's a strong chair.
Is it?
I'm... I'm sorry.
It's... It's been a day.
Will you please
get down from there?
I'm... I'm good. Thanks.
It's making me nervous
sitting so close to the edge.
Please?
Cherry on top?
I'm okay.
You gotta be--
I once read that
maraschino cherries
stay in your stomach
for, like, seven years.
Or cause cancer. I forget which.
I didn't know that
about maraschino cherries.
Yeah, I may have made that up,
but they're pretty gross.
Yeah, they're definitely gross.
So, what happened?
Sorry?
What was that over--
I didn't mean to, but...
Was it a woman?
Or man? I--
It was a chair, wasn't it?
Yes.
So, what floor you live on?
You first.
Top floor, right next to
my sister and her husband.
What do you do for a living?
Neurosurgeon.
Is that funny?
- Jesus. You're serious.
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Wow.
Oh, my God.
Please. I'm so sorry.
No, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
You've spent way too--
I'm sorry.
You've spent way too much time in school
to have me laughing like this.
I'm terrible. I'm sorry.
I... I thought you were a crypto bro.
- You thought I was a crypto bro?
- No, no, no.
Yeah, no, well, I don't know,
or like
a really expensive prostitute.
Well, I am expensive.
You can forget about
kissing on the mouth.
Why haven't I seen you before?
Well, mostly because I've never
required brain surgery.
But also
'cause I don't live here, so...
So, you just
broke into my building?
You have a really nice view.
I do.
What's your name?
Lily.
- You?
- Ryle.
Ryle what?
Kincaid.
You just made that up just now.
Why would I make up
my last name?
- Well, I mean-- Fine.
- What's your last name?
It's fine. We don't need to...
We don't need to do this.
- I'm just asking your last name.
- It was really nice meeting you.
- Thank you. Just be careful.
- Okay.
It would be courteous
to give me back your last name.
I'm not gonna stalk you.
No, it's just really--
It's sort of embarrassing.
What is it?
Bloom.
- Your name is Lily Bloom?
- Yes.
It... It actually gets worse.
- Yeah. Yeah, no. It... It does.
- No way. Not possible.
Than Lily Bloom?
I don't wanna talk about it,
'cause it's really
kind of embarrassing.
I'm obsessed with flowers. I--
And I'm about to open
my first flower shop.
Flower shop?
Yeah, it's a lifelong dream,
so...
Stop. I told you.
No, Lily Bloom the florist.
No, doesn't sound
made up at all.
Hey, you could always use your middle name
if it doesn't work out.
- No, Violet.
- Trust me.
- Petunia.
- No, stop.
Of the valley.
- Toadflax.
- Blossom.
Goddamn, your parents hate you.
Well, I mean,
we may never know for sure,
'cause my dad
died on Monday, so...
Yeah, that's actually
why I came up here,
to have a good cry and,
hopefully,
meet a wealthy neurosurgeon.
So...
I'm sorry.
I could've made it back,
you know,
to see him before he died,
but I...
I didn't.
Damn.
Yeah.
Well, you know, naked truths
aren't always pretty.
I watched
a little boy die tonight.
He was only six years old.
His brother found a gun
in his parents' bedroom,
and it went off by accident.
Tried everything.
No one should have to--
I can't imagine
what that's gonna do
to that little boy who lived.
Destroy him for life.
That's what it'll do.
All right, give me another one.
Naked truth. I like that.
- Go on.
- Okay.
I... I don't know...
The first guy
I had sex with was homeless.
Stop it.
Yeah, no, really.
In high school, yeah.
Tell me more.
I actually think we're supposed to say
"temporarily un-homed," or "displaced."
I shouldn't have said--
Now you're
avoiding the question.
I'm not.
There's nothing to tell.
I want the good stuff.
Okay, I was friends with
this boy named Atlas.
And he was
kind and incredibly capable
and, you know,
he just got a shit hand.
You're making me jealous
of a homeless man.
Oh, my.
Okay, that's enough. That's--
Your turn.
Oh, no, I think I'm done.
Can't top that.
That was
both sexy and disturbing.
Okay, just shock me. Say--
I mean, you can say anything.
I wanna have sex with you.
- What? I mean--
- You said to shock you.
What?
How many-- I'm sorry.
How many women
has this worked on?
I'm not a relationship person.
- Yeah, I gathered that.
- Never been good at them.
But how do you know
if you've never tried
having a relationship or carbs?
How do you know
it doesn't work for you?
Carbs? I never said I didn't eat carbs.
Come on, you don't look
like a reckless snacker.
Well, thank you.
Love isn't for me.
Lust is nice though.
- I feel like you're missing out.
- Am I?
You haven't
answered my question.
Forgot what the question was.
How many women
has this worked on?
All of them.
Well, I...
I can't-- I'm...
I'm gonna have
to break your record.
I'm the kind of girl
you take home to mama.
How far would you go?
I'm not sure.
I'm an unreliable narrator.
You could try me.
Too far?
No.
This?
Depends what happens next.
Shit.
Yeah.
No, I'm not supposed to--
Okay, prep the OR. Tell Tom he's cutting.
I'm gonna supervise.
All right, I'll be there in ten.
- Holy shit.
- I know. I'm sorry.
No, I mean, holy shit.
I... I... I just now realised
you're actually a neurosurgeon.
- I tried to warn you.
- No, congratulations.
- That's... That's amazing.
- Yeah.
I-- This is-- You know, I--
I'll see you around.
Will you?
No.
It was nice meeting you, Lily Blossom Bloom.
It was nice meeting you,
Ryle Siegfried Kincaid.
I like that.
Oh, shit.
Thank you.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
So, why are you at that house?
My mom kicked me out.
Why?
Because...
she likes dating guys
who beat the shit out of her.
What happened to your hand?
God, I can smell him from here.
It got in the way.
Look, my parents don't get
home from work till around 5:00,
so if you wanna shower or...
I don't know, wash clothes or--
- I don't mind.
- Yeah.
Sure.
Your enthusiasm's contagious.
Did you feel the earthquake
this weekend?
Yeah!
- You did?
- Yeah!
Hey.
Thanks for the clothes.
Yeah, of course.
My dad won't even
know they're gone.
He doesn't usually
wear jeans much, so...
My parents aren't gonna
be home for an hour or so,
if you wanna watch TV
or something.
So, what do you wanna do
after you graduate?
I'm... signed up to go to
basic training in May.
Basic training. What is--
In the Marines.
Wow.
I'm sorry. I'm--
I'm sorry.
It's just the... the clothes--
My dad's clothes,
they make you kind of
look like Ned Flanders a little.
Your clothes kind of
make you look like a carrot.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah.
- Mom...
- If it doesn't work out--
Mom, you do know a challenge
only excites me.
I... I... I said, "If."
"A flower sales statistic that
shocks many new store owners..."
Mom, what makes you think
it's not gonna work out?
"...a whopping 45%
of all flowers die..."
Mom.
Mom, are you reading this
from Google?
Of course I am.
How would I know that?
I'm worried about you.
Google is worried about you.
Well, you're both too late.
I'm picking up the keys now.
Okay, okay. Okay.
- I love you. You can do this.
- Wait. Sir! Sir! Hi.
- Make it bold and brave.
- Okay, Mom.
You sound crazy.
I'll talk to you later. Bye.
Hi. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
- I... I just moved here.
- Okay, sweetheart. Good luck.
Thank you.
Hi.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Sorry. Hi. Yeah. I'm sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
I can't--
- Oh, wait.
- I can't hear you. Hi.
Hi. Can I help you?
Can I help you?
Excuse me?
The "help wanted" sign
out front?
You have a "help wanted" sign
out front.
Oh, God. I'm so sorry.
Yeah, I didn't... I didn't put that out there.
- I just, yeah, got this place.
- I figured. It's pretty old.
And I walk by this place
every day,
and I'm just obsessed with it.
I've always wanted
to see inside,
and I was wondering, like,
"Who's gonna come along?"
- And it's you, yeah?
- No, it's me. Yeah, hi.
- Are you the owner?
- Yeah, I'm... I'm Lily.
- Allysa.
- Nice to meet you.
Sorry. Disgusting.
Hi. Nice to meet you. Yeah.
Well, yeah,
are you looking for any help?
Well, I'm not hiring just yet.
I just... I just got the keys
a few days ago,
and I'm still sort of, you know,
figuring out
what I'm doing, so--
May I just ask,
what is this place going to be?
A flower shop.
I'm so sorry.
I have an issue with--
My face says it all.
I just hate flowers.
You hate flowers?
- I do.
- Okay.
Like, why don't you just
give me something that's living
rather than something
that's on its way to dying?
And then it's gonna create
more work for me,
and I'm gonna
have to deal with that,
but again,
it's a solo perspective.
It's-- I find flower shops
depressing. It's just me.
I do wish you luck.
I'm so sorry.
I agree. I find them depressing.
Because I feel like...
I don't know, it's like
the beauty of what a flower is--
This is ridiculous.
The beauty of what a flower is
has been lost, right? It's... It's...
It's like we order them
like takeout now-- It's... It's...
- Yes.
- Right?
It's what you're talking about.
It's highlighting the pain
and the tension and the--
You know,
the fact that it's fleeting
and it's storytelling and--
I don't know,
that's actually what I find
beautiful about it, and--
That's what I'm
trying to do here, so--
That's absolutely beautiful. I'm--
If that's what you're doing,
yeah, sign me up. Wonderful.
Thanks, thanks.
Well...
Yeah, I really do
wish you the best...
Thank you.
...and I'll just be lurking
around in the neighbourhood.
Hopefully, I made
my first customer.
- Yeah. Yeah. Great. It's so gorgeous.
- Hope to see you--
Yeah. Bye.
Hey, I...
I don't know, this--
I do need help.
Do you want a job?
This is exactly what I wanted
to happen to me
when I walked in here.
- Yes.
- Oh, God. Okay.
- Wonderful. Great.
- Okay.
I have to be out
by 5:00 p.m. tonight.
I do have a dinner.
- Tonight?
- Yeah.
I just started working here.
- Okay, perfect.
- Great.
I'm gonna just need to wipe off
a surface for this girl.
Here. There you go.
- That's--
- Thank you so much.
It's a real Ghostbusters
situation in here, huh?
Hey. Frame it.
Did you see that?
Oh, my God. It's still attached.
Oh, God, I can't watch.
Yeah. Yeah.
You're like Dr Frankenstein,
but with flowers.
Okay. No, no, no.
We got it. We got it. We got it.
I don't have it. Hold on.
- Okay, here. Here we go.
- Hold on. My husband's calling.
Can I ask him to help us?
- Yes. No, please. Genius.
- Or is that weak?
- You got it?
- Nope.
- Babe.
- Not at all.
- Babe, the game's over. Where you at?
- Hi, honey. Sweetheart.
- Where are you?
- I'm at the shop with my boss.
And we need some help
hanging something up.
I don't like
when you say "boss."
- Babe.
- You should be the boss.
Let's buy the place
and make you the boss.
Honey, you're on speaker.
- Yeah. Just--
- Hi.
- Just--
I want you to know that they're
gonna be wearing onesies.
Because the bar gives free beer
to the people...
I can see you.
...who wear onesies
to the Bruins game,
but they don't always wear that.
- I'm across the street.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God,
babe, you are stunning.
Can you bring my brother in too?
Okay, I can't take responsibility
for either of the people
who are about to come in here,
just so you know.
- Hi.
You look great.
- This is Lily.
- Hi. Lily. Hi. Nice to meet you.
- This is my husband, Marshall.
- I didn't mean the boss thing.
That's my brother Ryle.
Hi. Hi.
- Hi.
- Lily.
Lily Bloom.
Yes. Yes.
- You guys know each other?
- No.
- A little bit.
- No, we--
We met a few months ago.
We shared each other's
naked truths.
- That's-- Okay.
- No, that's--
We're adults.
- That was a bad choice of words.
- You said it.
You said "naked truths" first.
- No, we just talked.
- You're lying.
That's what we're calling it
these days, "We talked"?
- 'Cause we talk all the time.
- Great.
We talk, like...
We talk, like, three to five times a week.
Wonderful.
Can I show you
the work that I've done here?
We should talk?
We can talk tonight.
No, we could hang this.
No, let me take you over here.
Let me talk to your sister
over here.
- Okay.
- I mean, it is really good.
We meet again.
It's good to see you.
So, this is the flower shop
that my sister works at
'cause she's bored, huh?
We like to say "inspired" here,
but, yeah, this is--
You know, I-- Yeah.
Yeah.
Looks like we will be seeing
a little more of
each other then.
Is that so?
Babe, these are incredible.
Thank you very much.
You're even more terrifying
in the daytime.
Same.
Okay, guys, idea.
Let's go have
some dumb fun today.
I've gone up
to the roof a few times.
Hoping you might be up there.
I wanna see you again.
Well, now you see me.
You know what I mean.
Okay. Let's go, let's go.
But that's a bad idea, right?
Because of my sister,
because of your business.
Go, Lily!
Yeah, that's a bad idea.
Yep. Of course.
This is you right here, babe.
No. Hey.
She's off-limits.
No, she's mine.
I see you.
- Hey.
- It's true.
So, we'll just be friends then?
I like it.
Yeah, friends.
- To friendship.
- Yeah.
It's the weekend somewhere.
Let's go.
Oh, no. Please don't leave, sir.
Our Uber's about to leave.
I love you.
I'm gonna head home, honey.
No. no, no. It's brunch in Singapore.
Come on, Lily.
- Let me walk you home.
- No, it's fine.
- I... I live around the corner.
- It's on the way.
- You live where we live.
- Semantics.
Okay, fine, but only 'cause
you'd feel really bad
if I got murdered.
Okay, don't fish
where I swim, Ryle.
I love you.
See you tomorrow, Lil.
I appreciate you walking me,
but you really didn't--
I can't stop thinking about you.
I'm right here.
Well, that's the problem.
I thought we agreed
to be friends.
We did.
But that was, like, hours ago.
Can I just kiss you?
- Oh, my God. You are pushy.
- Just once. Just once.
That's all I need
to get you out of my system.
- That's it? That'll do it?
- One kiss.
Okay, well, good luck with that.
Is that a yes?
Just once?
Just once.
Okay.
Did that get me
out of your system?
I'm gonna walk
myself home, okay?
Bye, friend.
- Is this enough over here?
- Yeah.
Can you grab, like,
a little right there?
Okay.
You're just protecting the roots,
you know, from the snow
or in case it freezes over or anything.
I mean, the roots are the most
important part of the plant.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I didn't know that about roots.
That's cool.
Here, you want some?
Thank you. Yeah, I'll take that.
What made you wanna
start growing things?
When I take really good care
of these plants,
they reward me
with flowers and vegetables.
And when I don't,
they just shrivel up and die.
Kinda like us.
What about that oak tree?
It doesn't need anybody to grow.
Because it's capable
of taking care of itself.
No matter what,
it will keep standing.
Strong and sturdy...
and yeah, it survives
because it's a goddamn oak tree.
You embarrassed me.
- You like the attention.
- Lily's asleep upstairs.
Honey, please. Please, don't!
I heard what happened
last night...
with your dad and your mom.
I don't-- Okay, yeah.
Does that happen a lot?
I'm sorry.
Hey, Lily.
Do you wanna do the honours?
No. You go ahead.
I wanna take it in from here.
I was hoping you'd say that.
Okay.
Hold on!
Oh, my God.
- This is insane.
- Congratulations.
I couldn't have
done it without you.
Oh, my gosh.
I don't know what
I was thinking. Thank God.
It's incredible.
It's perfect. It's you.
It's perfect. It's great.
What if we don't
get any customers?
No, don't do that.
Your mom's coming.
Oh, my mom.
She's flying in
to be a customer.
Yeah, I mean-- Yeah, but how
depressing would that be
if the only customer
we have is my mom?
Well, Marshall's coming
this afternoon.
So that's two, so you're good.
Okay, here we go.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
This doesn't even look like
the same shop. Congratulations.
How's it going so far?
I mean, we literally
just opened, but--
So, that means your brother's
the first official customer?
You have to buy something
to be considered a customer.
Right now you're just loitering.
Good morning, Lily.
Good morning.
All right. I'll take these.
Do you deliver?
- Is that for a girl?
- It is.
She might send them back,
knowing her.
Right. Okay.
That little card, fill out
the message on the front
and then the back you put the
person's name and the address.
Okay.
So, are you bringing
this mystery girl
to my birthday party on Friday?
'Cause I kind of, like, need to
plan for that sort of thing.
I don't know.
Are you going, Lily?
Yeah, of course.
- Yeah.
She has to go.
She's my best friend.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- What do I owe you?
- Fifty-one even.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- This is a big moment.
- Sure is.
Thank you so much
for your service-- business.
Thank you. Yeah.
Hey, congrats.
Get out. Thank you.
- Good to see you.
- Bye.
Goodbye.
Oh, my God. He's such a dumbass.
He put the name of our shop
as the delivery address.
Weird first customer.
Lily.
- Hello. Happy birthday.
- Oh, my goodness.
- You came. You look great.
- I missed something important.
- What is everything?
- This is my-- It's a long story.
Welcome to our casa.
You guys, this-- I mean, your house--
This is...
- I can't believe this is your house.
- This is our humble abode.
I just wanted to do something low-key
for baby girl over here.
Oh, my God.
And to think I did not even
marry him for the money.
- You're not in it for the money.
- I'm not.
- You're my ride or die.
- Yeah.
When we first met I was dead broke,
and I was driving a Toyota Camry.
You still drive a Toyota Camry though.
Right?
- The greatest automobile on earth.
- Yes, he does. Also...
Can't convince me otherwise.
He thinks it makes him relatable.
- It really does.
- I'm a man of the people, okay?
Happy birthday. I'm gonna go grab a drink.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay, thank you. Okay.
Yeah, you are a man of the people.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
You didn't like the flowers?
Stop flirting with me.
Hi, may I have a scotch please? Thank you.
I can't do that.
I thought we were friends.
We are friends.
Okay.
Excuse me. You're on my hand. Thank you.
- Hi.
- Come on.
- What?
- What are you doing?
Nothing.
You gotta... You gotta stop.
You have to stop this.
- Please.
- What?
Just the, you know, staring at me
like that and the--
I'm just looking at you.
Okay. You're just looking at me.
Stop showing up at my flower shop
- and sending me flowers.
- My sister works there.
Stop walking through this party,
following me around.
- You're making me feel like--
- Can you just shut up for one second?
Okay.
I like you.
What, are you five?
I'm trying here.
Go on.
Do you wanna go somewhere more private?
To talk?
To talk.
Okay.
No. No, no, no, stop.
You want me to stop?
No.
But yes. I don't wanna have sex.
Not tonight.
I know, I know.
But I don't do casual,
and I know that's how you do it,
but I won't change my mind.
And I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
You okay? What are you doing?
Getting ready for bed.
We're going to sleep.
Sorry, we're what?
Going to sleep.
My God.
Do you mind?
Well, do you have something I can wear?
I don't think you've
ever done this before.
It was sexier in my head.
Pants?
You've got it.
Smart-ass.
Good night, Lily Bloom.
Ryle, I'm very nice,
so I brought you coffee.
- Hi.
- No.
Oh, no.
I understand. It's not as bad as it looks.
- It looks pretty bad.
- It kind of is.
Okay. None of my business. Okay.
What-- I'm... I'm gonna go.
Let me just say one thing.
This man runs through women like candy.
- This is different.
- Is it? Wonderful.
Well, just in case it obviously is not,
let me say that if you're looking for
nothing from him, that's a great option.
Okay.
But if you're looking for romance
and you want a relationship,
this is not the person,
and it's not about you.
And I love you.
- Yeah.
- But let me just say--
Date me.
What?
I've-- I don't--
What... What does that mean? I--
Okay, no. I'm gonna leave.
And I'm so sorry,
but I was just bringing coffee,
and now, I'm so embarrassed.
You can't have any of that.
That's for you.
I'm outta here.
A normal person would just leave
and go to therapy.
What are you talking about?
I wanna try.
Come on. You think you can do this?
I have no idea.
But I definitely wanna kiss you again.
Well, that I can do.
Okay.
But don't make me regret this.
Hey.
Good morning.
You've already brushed your teeth.
That's not fair.
So sorry. I gotta go in early.
Am I gonna see you tonight?
No. Not tonight. My mom's in town.
She's obsessed with trying
this new restaurant, Root.
It's her dying wish to take me there.
Your mom's in town?
Yeah. Yeah, no, she's not actually dying.
- It's-- I was just saying that.
- It's just, you didn't...
You didn't tell me that.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think you'd wanna know.
Is there room for one more?
What?
Wait, you wanna meet my mom?
Is that a problem?
I mean, I don't think it's a good idea.
- Ouch.
- No.
No. I mean--
It's not because of you.
It is because of her. This woman--
I just wanna meet the mother
of the woman I love.
Hey!
Hey. Sorry, you forgot this. Bye.
Wait, wait, this isn't mine.
I know.
I happen to love you too.
You're gonna be late.
Get over me, my gosh!
I'm taken!
Did you make this?
Yeah.
Carved it from a branch
from your old oak tree.
In case you forget.
Strong and sturdy.
Thank you.
Gross. I bet she has rabies now.
Get up.
- Get up. Get up. Get up.
- Stop. No, no.
Come on.
Do you like to cook?
Yeah. I love it.
Necessity is the mother of invention.
Smells great. What is it?
Hot chocolate cookies.
Dark chocolate with burnt marshmallows.
That's good.
My mom would splurge on
Swiss Miss for us at Christmas.
That was her favourite.
So, did you... did you kiss me earlier
because you really wanted to,
or was it mostly just to
get back at Katie?
I just--
I really need some clarity here.
I wanted to.
That's my dad.
- That is my dad. You have to go.
- What?
- You... You have to go right now.
- Don't forget the cookies.
Okay. Okay. I got it. You gotta go right now.
- Out the back door. Please, go.
- Twelve minutes, okay?
- Go, go, go.
- Okay.
- Hey!
- Hi!
- How are you, honey?
- Good.
- You all right? How was your day? Good?
- Yeah.
Yeah, great.
Good. Busy?
Yeah...
Busy's good.
I made cookies.
Yep.
- Yeah, I'm starting to--
- Wow.
Pigs are flying.
Yeah.
Wish I didn't love you so much.
Yeah, same.
Okay. You gonna save me some?
- Yeah, of course.
- You promise?
Yeah, I promise you.
- My goodness.
- Yeah, it's amazing.
- Hi. We're just meeting her.
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah. I am sorry in advance.
- No.
Yeah, no, no. Prepare yourself.
Hi! Hi, Mama!
- I love this place!
- It's beautiful, right?
Oh, my God! It looks beautiful.
- Let's order cocktails.
- Let's. Yes. Yeah.
- Hi.
Mom, this is... this is my friend, Ryle,
yeah, who I now sleep with. So--
- Ryle Kincaid. Nice to meet you, ma'am.
- It's so nice to meet you.
- You know you said that out loud?
- I do know I said that out loud.
Allysa, you know, who I work with?
This is her brother.
- Yes! Now I see a resemblance, sure.
- Yeah.
- Well, we both favour our mother.
- Here it goes.
That's what everybody says
about me and Lily.
You know, I see it.
Yes.
The apple does not fall far from the tree.
- How lucky are you, Lily?
- The luckiest.
How lucky am I?
Oh, my God.
Would you excuse me? I have a thing.
I like to wash my hands a lot and--
- Give me one--
- Get out of here.
- I will. All right. All right. Bye-bye.
- Leave us be.
- Oh, my God.
- Mom, you know, we don't need to do that.
You never told me you were dating
the most beautiful man.
He's got a good personality
to make up for it, though, so--
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Who is he? Where's he work?
- Don't do that. Don't.
- What does he do? Don't do what?
Hey, I am-- I'm your mother.
Boston Grace Hospital.
- Oh, no.
- Stop.
- Welcome to Root.
- No, please, don't.
- Can I get you something to drink?
- God. Please. Thank you. I need alcohol.
I would like to try a negroni.
I hear they're delicious.
- They are. I'll get you a negroni.
- Thank you.
And what can I get you?
I'll-- Surprise me.
So, what'd I miss?
Are you by any chance a doctor?
I am. I'm actually gonna be performing
a once-in-a-lifetime operation soon.
Oh, my Lord. Is it dangerous?
It's a risky surgery.
It's amazing though. He's amazing.
They're five years old.
Thank you so much.
So tell me about Boston.
They were the best years of my life.
- The food is really amazing there...
- Yeah?
...and the harbour.
My uncle would take me
fishing there sometimes.
Sounds like you miss it.
Yeah.
I'm gonna move there after the Marines.
Everything's better in Boston.
Except the girls.
Boston doesn't have you.
I'm gonna miss you.
Same.
I don't know how you did it.
But somehow,
you became my favourite person.
Same.
Hey.
What?
Are you sure?
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't have a condom.
- I have one.
- You do?
It's health class.
I've... I've never done this before.
- It's okay. I'm no expert.
- Okay.
- I've only done it once.
I've been studying them since they
were born, since I've been a resident--
I'm gonna use the bathroom real quick.
- Okay, honey. Okay.
- Yeah.
You get to know each other.
I'll be right back.
Lily Bloom.
Atlas.
You look--
Yeah, you-- You... You...
God, thank you.
I mean, my mom didn't recognise you, so--
- It's probably for the best.
- God, right? Yeah.
What have you been up to?
Just working. Living.
Yeah, same.
Yeah. Did you go to the military or what--
Yeah, yeah. No, I did... I did eight--
Yeah, eight years.
- Wow.
- Yeah. I got out and moved to Boston.
What are--
What are...
What are you doing in... in Boston?
Are you... You visiting here, or--
I live here.
Yeah. Where everything's better.
Is that your-- your guy?
Yeah, that's... That's Ryle.
He's, yeah, he's... he's really special.
I think you'd really like him.
- I'm so happy for you.
- Yeah, thank you.
Do you have anyone, or are you married?
Or do you have a girlfriend
or, you know, anything?
- Yeah. I got Cassie.
- Yeah?
Yeah, she's great.
That's so good.
You look so well.
I... I don't wanna get you in trouble
or anything.
Well, how do I find you?
If I wanted to find you.
I... I mean, I... I opened my flower shop.
Lily Bloom's.
- Of course you did.
- Yeah. Over in... in Back Bay.
So, you know,
you can look me up sometime, or...
- Yeah. Well, I... I gotta-- Well, you know.
- Yeah.
- I'm working, so...
- Okay. Get out of here.
- Yeah, I'm gonna go. All right.
- Okay.
- ...once-in-a-lifetime operation.
- Lily?
What are you drinking?
I'll have wine, please.
You are not getting wine.
You're in a onesie.
- You don't get free wine with a onesie.
- Fair point.
- Whatever you're having, I'll have it.
- Bingo!
Three beers and a water for my ladylove.
Wait, did you just say "water"?
Okay, yeah.
We didn't plan on telling you here--
Stop it.
You know.
I'm gonna be a dad!
- And I'm gonna be the mom.
- Yes!
I'm gonna be a dad!
- I knew it.
- No, no.
This is fucking crazy! I know!
- I'm so happy for you. I'm so happy.
- Yeah.
- I'm a papa.
- I'm just so happy for you.
You're gonna be the best mama.
Oh, my God.
To Allysa,
who's 11 months younger than me,
and you still teach me every day
what being a grown-up looks like.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Eleven months? You guys,
I didn't know you were so close in age.
Oh, yeah. Three kids in three years.
Makes you feel bad for our mom.
Three? You guys have a sibling?
Yeah. Yeah, we had an older brother, Emerson.
And he died when we were younger.
I'm so sorry.
- Let's go. Goal!
- Yeah!
Good morning.
You like frittata?
What is happening?
No, no, I feel like I'm in a porno.
What... What is this?
I did not know you could cook.
I can't.
Well, good, 'cause I was
starting to get a little intimidated.
It was, you know,
a little too good to be true.
- That's for you. Yeah.
- That's mine. Thank you.
I like a little hair of the dog.
Don't be shy.
It's actually--
This is just to celebrate my big surgery tomorrow.
Oh, my God, I'm--
- I'm so sorry.
- No, no, no.
- I don't know what I was thinking. I--
- It's fine.
It's not fine. I'm sorry.
- Hey. I am sorry.
- Hey, what's that mean? The heart.
Oh, God, it's nothing. I just--
You know, one of those
silly things you do.
No, it's not nothing.
Every tattoo means something.
I know. No, no.
This is just like one of those
silly things you do in high school,
and I don't know why I still have it.
No.
It's one of my favourite parts of you.
Okay. Baby?
I have to tell you something.
Your frittata's burning.
It's gonna be perfect.
Okay.
Well, what are some of your
other favourite parts about me?
Your glabella.
- Your flagina.
- Oh, no! Stop!
- Oh, shit!
- I told you. I'm sorry. I did tell you.
- No, no. Baby, you need a potholder.
- Oh, my God! Shit!
You're gonna stick your hand in there?
Hey, baby.
- Hey, hey. You're okay.
- What was that?
What was that? No, no.
- Can you give me a second, please?
- Hey. Hey.
- Just give me a second.
- Oh, shit!
Are you okay? I'm sorry.
- Oh, my God. Your hand.
- No, don't worry about my hand.
Baby, your surgery.
You okay?
I think so. I don't know.
Let me see it.
- Shit, I'm--
- I know. I'm hurt.
I knew we'd make a mess.
- I'm so sorry.
- It was an accident.
No. I didn't... I didn't... I didn't...
- What did we do?
- It was an accident.
I'm okay.
- God, I'm so sorry.
- Hey.
- Thank you for coming. Sorry I'm late.
- Stop.
- I'm a disaster.
- No, here. I think I got everything.
Yeah, no, no, thank you. Okay.
How was the wedding?
- Also a disaster.
- No.
- It's fine. It's fine. It was a little, just--
- How's a wedding a disaster?
Well, I mean, their marriage is
probably the disaster, but they're fine.
- They're lovely. They deserve each other.
- But the flowers were beautiful?
Yes, the flowers were off the char--
I'm so sorry. How was your--
How was your surgery?
How did your sweet hand hold up?
- It was awesome.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah. There was this moment--
Allysa and Marshall messed up.
We're going to Root.
The place we went to with your mom.
- There was this moment, and I--
- Well, hold-- Why? Why?
I don't know.
I know, but I was dying
to try the new place...
- Yeah, but they heard...
- ...and we've already been there.
- ...how we talked about it and--
- Yeah, but we could just call them.
- No. They're already there.
- No, I know.
- They ordered 14 appetisers.
- I really wanted to...
- You know my sister.
- ...try the new place. I know. I'm sorry.
- I will take you there next week.
- You know I love food. That's all.
- You know I'm a creature of habit.
- That's all it is.
- I'll get the same thing I got last time.
- Okay.
Yeah, I mean, it's perfect.
The food... The food is so good, so--
Hey. Hey.
What?
- Hi.
I'm sorry. It's been a...
It's been a week.
I don't need to be complaining to you.
You've been through it.
Yeah.
Tell me. I wanna hear everything.
- Okay.
- Hi. Sorry.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Hey.
- Hi!
- What's up?
- I'm so sorry we're late.
Just sit down. Don't worry about it.
- Can I have this?
- Yeah. Of course.
- We've ordered so much food.
- We're so sorry.
- Yeah, it's... it's my fault.
- Oh, baby.
I didn't--
Ryle told me something happened,
but he didn't tell me
it was looking like this.
Look at you, honey.
- It's fine. It doesn't even...
- Yeah.
It doesn't even hurt.
It was a mess. You should have seen her.
Yeah. I mean, his hand.
And he got hurt too.
- So we're-- Yeah. We are.
- Yeah. No, I'm fine.
- I feel bad. It was... It was a beautiful mess.
- Yeah.
Wait, so, dude,
what happened with the surgery?
Probably the greatest day of my life.
Twenty-seven hours.
- Twenty-seven hours?
- Yeah.
The only thing I've done for 27 hours
is day-trade and play Call of Duty.
Do you guys have baby names?
- Sorry, I didn't mean to interrupt.
- And go on a DraftKings bender.
- Baby names?
- Yeah, sorry. I was, yeah, thinking.
We're thinking something strong.
- We're gonna do big-time authors.
- This riff...
R. L. Stine.
Judy Blume.
That is going to be
the demise of our marriage.
- How we doing, folks?
- Hi.
- How are you liking your appetisers?
- Wonderful.
I've had one bite of one thing and this is
already my favourite restaurant.
- What'd you go for?
- The Brussels sprouts.
Brussels sprouts.
What about you? What do you like?
I'm-- Impossible to choose.
My regards to the chef.
Thank you. Appreciate it.
It's actually my mother's recipe.
That's very beautiful.
- It's my first restaurant. Yeah.
- Love that.
And I love the creativity,
dude, seriously.
- So...
- I'm an entrepreneur as well, so I get it.
What's... What's your...
What's your deal? What's your thing?
Right now we're looking to allocate
capital in local Boston businesses,
and a place like this
would just be amazing.
Not to be too forward,
but what are margins right now?
I mean, the place is jumping.
Thirteen, 14, 15 percent?
But I love the story about your mom.
You do a Series A and scale this thing up.
- Honey.
- Did I offend him?
No, just keep saying "allocating capital."
- The chef was the asshole.
- I have been holding it for so long.
I'm gonna go pee really quick.
I'll be right back.
- Do you want me to come?
- No, I'm good. I'm good.
- Are you--
- No, no, you... You guys keep talking.
I'll be right back.
- Come on.
- What happened?
Come on, tell me. What happened?
Nothing. I-- We... I...
He burned his hand, and I fell.
I know. I know.
It's... It was an accident, though. It was--
- That was an accident?
- Yes.
Leave him.
- God.
- You gotta leave him.
- I am not your mother, Atlas.
- Leave him. Come on.
Are you turning into yours?
- Let me out of here.
- Lily.
- Let me out now.
Stop.
Wait, what is this?
Atlas! Stop.
Touch her again, I'll cut your hand off
and shove it down your throat,
- you piece of shit.
- Atlas, stop! Stop.
Stop.
So this is Atlas.
- Baby, hey.
- The homeless boy...
- Come on. Stop.
- ...you wasted your virginity on?
Guys, stop it! Stop it!
- Please! Please stop it. Stop!
- Hey! Break it up.
- No! Please.
- Come on.
- Please, stop. No!
- Get out of my restaurant!
- Stop! Let's get out of here.
- Stop, please, please. Let's go.
- Come on.
- Get out!
- Stop it, now!
Ryle?
Excuse me. Ryle.
Ryle. Ryle, wait.
- Ryle, please, wait.
- What was he doing in the bathroom, Lily?
What was he doing in the bathroom?
He saw my eye,
and I think he saw your hand.
And he knows it was an accident.
And I told him it was an accident. He...
Lily.
What?
I don't--
I don't know him.
I mean, we... we... We were kids.
- I don't know him now.
- Anyone but him.
Anyone but him.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- I know you. Anyone but him.
Promise me.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
I've never been here before.
- You have me. You have all of me.
- I know. I know. I know.
- So, if I'm not what you want, you just--
- No, no, no. You're fine.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
Stop. Stop.
- Stop.
- I love you, Lily.
I know. I know. I know. I know.
I know.
I love you, Lily.
I love you, too.
No, please stop. No, please, please.
Lily! Open the door.
- You gotta leave right now.
- Lily!
- I'm coming!
- Open the door!
- Leave right now. Put your clothes on.
- Who's in there?
- He's coming. Come on.
- Hey! Open--
- Thank you. Enjoy.
- Thank you for coming by.
We appreciate it.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
Thanks so much for stopping in.
- It's busy.
- Yeah.
I think that's the last of it.
How you doing, mama?
I'm doing.
- I'm doing.
- You in that little dress.
Do you mind if I--
- If I see the baby for a moment?
- Oh, yeah. Have a visit.
Hi, bubba. How you doing? You getting big.
Hey, question.
If we're not allowed
to go back to that restaurant...
Yeah.
...why is he allowed to
come to this store?
- I don't--
- Coffee.
- Okay.
- I'm getting coffee. Would you like some?
No, I'm good. Thank you.
- Excuse me. Hi. Hey. Excuse me.
- Hi.
Thank you.
- Nice to see you.
- Yeah.
Hi.
This is incredible.
Yeah, thanks.
Kind of exactly how I imagined it.
Yeah, yours too.
Thanks.
Look at us.
So, look, I...
I came by the next day after the fight,
but he was here. And I... I just didn't think
that was a good idea.
I just... I just wanted to say I'm really sorry.
- I was out of my mind...
- Yeah.
...and... and acted like a jackass and...
I just feel really bad and I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah. No, it's all good. It's...
Yeah. It was a misunderstanding. So--
Well, I don't... I don't know. I mean, no, it wasn't.
I don't think it was.
Why are you here now?
I gave you my address months ago.
What are you... What are you doing?
I came the next day.
I drive this street a lot.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Are you happy?
Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I couldn't be happier.
Are you?
No.
Sorry.
That your phone?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
That's my number. In case you need it.
Okay, well, I won't, so...
But thank you.
I hope you don't.
Hey, that--
That thing that he said about that--
You know, with us. It wasn't--
It wasn't wasted.
I know.
I was there.
Hi.
- Hey.
That smells good.
Thank you.
Are you happy?
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm just--
I'm just curious.
I wasn't.
Lily, you make me happy.
Are you happy?
I mean, I don't think anyone's
happy all the time, but...
I don't know if I like the sound of that.
No, no. It's just, you know--
Of course I deal with, you know, my stuff
and, you know, life, and ticking clock
- and, you know, all those decisions that--
- Right.
that women have to worry about.
But, I think I'm an innately happy person.
It's probably just a coping mechanism
I learned from my mom. So...
Your mom?
My dad used to hit her.
Shit, I'm so sorry.
You never told me that.
That's not something people talk about.
Did he ever hurt you?
No. He nearly killed Atlas though.
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
Oh, God.
I'm so embarrassed. I--
That mess at the restaurant.
I didn't know.
That must have been so hard on you.
Yeah.
Baby, all I wanna do in my life
is protect you.
You know that, right?
When you hurt yourself by accident,
when you stub your toe, I blame myself.
It's like it's my fault
that the wall was there.
Stop.
I'm the luckiest goddamn man
on this planet.
And I could clean up. Trust me.
Okay. I'm not trying to hear about that.
- You don't wanna hear about that? Just a little bit?
- No. No.
Yeah, I'm a ripped neurosurgeon
for Christ's sake.
When was the last time
you saw someone who looked like me
that wasn't on a daytime soap?
I mean, come to think of it,
yeah, I-- No, I haven't.
- Yeah.
- And I'm rich.
And humble.
We can work on that.
God, I love you.
I know. I love you too.
That's the problem.
It's a big problem.
It's a really big problem.
Stop.
Look at her. She's like a little alien.
Yeah, she's perfect.
Do you want to hold her?
- Yeah.
- I knew it.
Here you go.
Okay.
- Hi.
- There we go. Right there.
- You're so beautiful. Hi.
- Wow.
You're a mama.
Yeah.
My sister's a mama.
And you're an uncle.
Wow. You did it.
This is just hormones. Don't look at me.
Do you guys want kids? Well--
- No pressure. We're not...
- I'm putting you on the spot right now.
I mean, it would be great
for childcare and stuff like that.
I'm not gonna make her
put on a white dress
and have my babies.
Unless she wants to.
Then I would marry her tonight.
- Oh, shit. He's serious.
- Oh, my gosh.
Ryle, you are--
You're drunk on baby smell.
No, no, no. I am serious as an aneurysm.
Oh, God. Please don't do
neurosurgeon humour when you're propos--
I mean, if you are.
Is that-- Is this--
- He's going around.
- I mean, if that's what you--
- Give me the baby.
- This is out of it--
- Please stop.
- Yeah. Wait.
No, no. No, no, stop.
- He's doing it?
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Okay. Okay. What--
Can we just--
Can you get the baby? We have a baby.
- We can take that. That's ours.
- Give me.
- Here you go.
- Here you go, baby.
You get back down there.
You get back down there right this second.
Will you marry me, Lily Blossom Bloom?
Yeah?
Okay.
- This is just-- I'm just--
- He did it.
This is a miracle.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, my God.
- But we'll do a proper wedding one day.
- You got married without me.
And I continue to be very sorry,
but at some point
you're gonna have to forgive me.
I will wear you down.
- My wife will wear you down.
- Not possible.
I don't think you should ever forgive her.
Just saying.
Okay. That's enough of that.
Hold on, can you charge my phone?
I haven't been dreaming about
your wedding day your whole life,
I've been dreaming about it my whole life.
And I'm sorry, I just feel cheated.
Yeah, okay. Got it. Thanks, Mom.
Okay, we're gonna find a way to move on.
If I don't get to watch you
walk down the aisle,
I will not be denied watching you squirm.
- You wanna make it up to me?
- Yes, please.
Make me a grandbaby. No, three. Three.
Make it triplets.
All right, can you just-- Can we move past
this conversation, please?
You okay?
What happened?
- Mom, I'll call you right back, okay?
- Okay.
Yeah, no, hang up.
Hey, what happened?
Hey, you okay?
I dropped your phone,
and the case fell off.
And I found this.
I called the number...
- It wasn't--
- You promised me.
- I know.
- I would never lie to you.
I know. It's nothing.
- It's nothing?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- It's nothing?
- Yes. Yes, I promise.
Yeah.
Okay?
It's nothing.
- Okay.
Ryle.
Ryle, baby, I promise
I didn't mean to see him.
- I promise. Please.
- Stop! No, no, no.
- No. I promise, please.
- Lily, stop!
No, it's-- Please, just listen to me.
- Please. I didn't know he was coming.
- You promised me, Lily. Stop.
- Just talk to me. Please. Just--
- Stop!
- You stop. Please. Don't--
Hey. Just try to be still.
Just try to be still.
It's all done. I'm here.
- Stop.
- I'm here.
Hey.
What-- What happened?
You fell down the stairs.
No, no, no. Don't... Don't touch it.
Yeah, you tripped and--
And I... I... I tried to catch you.
- No, Ryle, no.
- You're... You're okay. You're okay.
- Don't.
- It hurts.
I know it hurts. You're okay.
- Okay.
- You're okay.
Do you know who you are?
Lily Bloom.
Okay. Where are you?
- Our apartment.
- Okay. Who am I?
My husband.
And what am I doing right now?
Helping me.
How many fingers am I holding up?
- Five.
- And now? Okay.
- Two.
Tell me it's nothing.
It's nothing.
Yeah, come.
Thank you.
Am I okay?
You're okay. You're okay.
Okay.
Lily! Oh, my God.
Did you see it? Did you see the magazine?
You did it! Look at this!
Top ten. We're in the top ten!
- We're in the top-- You did it.
- Wait, where is it?
Where's the genius? Right there.
Look, look, look.
- Right there. There's you!
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. I'm gonna call Ryle
and then tell him
to get, like, 50 copies of this thing.
Hey.
You saw?
- Congratulations.
- Yeah, thank you.
I didn't know it was a big deal,
"Best in Boston."
Best in Boston.
Hello.
Okay.
I love this tattoo.
Hey, remind me what that means again.
What?
I told you.
Really doesn't mean anything?
Did you read it yet?
Yeah, did you?
Will you read it to me?
- I don't like that kinda stuff.
- Please.
No. Baby, I made dinner,
and it's gonna get cold.
- Read it.
- And I don't love this kinda stuff, okay?
"Number seven, Lily Bloom's.
- An avant-garde floral shop--" What?
- No, no. Skip to number one.
Our favourite restaurant.
Look, baby, I--
Read it.
"The top pick should
come as no surprise--"
No, go to the end.
"The owner, Atlas Corrigan,
spoke to the sweet origin story behind
his farm-to-table hot spot, Root.
When I was a kid, I carved a..."
- Carved what?
- Baby, I don't wanna read--
Keep reading.
"...small hollow heart
from an oak tree for a girl.
So the name was meant to represent
something she said to me,
which I'm gonna keep between us.
But there was no other name for Root.
It was...
always for her."
Baby--
Just go to this last paragraph.
It gets better.
- I don't wanna--
- Read it.
"When asked if he had seen the girl
since they were kids,
- Corrigan replied--"
-"...Corrigan replied...
'Yes. Next question.'"
Do you love him?
I did.
Do you love him now?
I love you.
That wasn't my question.
I don't know.
Thank you.
Sorry, baby.
- Come on. Let's have dinner.
- No.
Okay. Please.
Hey, no, no, no. Not now. Please. Just--
Please. Hey. Stop, please.
Baby, stop. Stop.
- You want me to stop?
- Not now. Hey, stop it.
Stop it.
- Hey.
- Stop!
- Stop, please. Please, stop.
Hey!
- Hey.
- Stop.
Stop it.
Stop! Stop. Hey!
Don't. Stop. Stop. Hey.
- What are you doing? Stop. Stop.
- Hey.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
- Baby. Hey.
- Stop. Stop.
Hey.
I love you.
I don't think I've shown you
how much I love you.
You have.
- You have.
- No.
You have.
- Baby...
- Please.
You have, baby. You have.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
- I love you so much.
- I love you, baby.
- I love you.
- I love you so much.
Baby. Baby, please stop.
Please stop.
Please. Hey. Hey, stop. Stop.
Hey. Stop. Look at me.
- I love you so much.
- Look at me. No, no. Look at me.
And I want you to know
that I love you enough.
- You have. Hey. Hey.
- No.
Look at me. Look at me. I love you.
Baby, look at me. Please look at me.
- Please look at me.
- That tattoo.
Please look at me.
Please look at me. Please.
Please. Please. I love you.
I love you. I love you. Please.
Please, don't do this.
Please. Please. Please.
Stop! Stop!
I don't think I'm showing you
how much I love you.
- Yes, you have.
- No.
No, I haven't.
- Hands.
- Yes, chef.
I was never gonna become her.
You're not becoming her.
Don't even think about that.
Okay?
- Yeah.
- You're not.
Is that what I think it is?
Yeah.
I wanna tell you something.
I don't know if it's the right time--
Sorry for the delay.
Been really busy tonight.
So, we have a certain examination
for these situations.
It's called the SANE exam.
It's completely optional, of course--
He didn't--
No, I wasn't-- It's--
Did he try?
I don't need the exam. Thank you. Yeah.
May I?
Oh, yeah. Of course.
Does this hurt?
This?
No, it's just the skin. Yeah.
So, usually,
I'd give you an X-ray on this collarbone
to make sure that it isn't fractured,
but, given your situation,
we're gonna clean it up,
and the nurse is gonna come in
and give you a tetanus shot.
I-- I don't understand.
We don't give X-rays to pregnant women
unless it's vital.
Okay?
Yeah.
- Right. I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Okay.
There's no Cassie, is there?
No.
No, there isn't.
It's--
It's the place.
Kitchen, living room.
Hey, let me grab you some clothes.
Thank you.
My dad won't even notice they're gone.
Bedroom's all yours.
- No, I'm not gonna take your bedroom.
- No. Please.
I have to get up early
for work anyway, so...
I love that couch. It's a good couch.
So, stay as long as you want.
Thank you.
Okay. Now, get some rest.
See you tomorrow.
Hey.
Hi.
I wasn't sure if you were hungry,
so I went with a few fan favourites.
What song do you want at your funeral?
If you had to pick one.
Have you not thought about this?
What song you're gonna play at my funeral?
Yeah.
At my funeral,
I'm thinking Creed, "With Arms Wide Open".
- You know, "With arms wide..."
- Yeah.
...as the casket's being lowered.
You're gonna be okay.
It doesn't feel like it.
I know.
But you are.
I think it's a little different this time.
If I can't even take care of myself,
then how am I, you know,
supposed to take care of a baby?
That night I went
to that old abandoned house,
I didn't go there because
I needed a place to stay,
I went there to kill myself.
And I was sitting
on the living room floor,
and I saw you in your bedroom window.
The light came on,
and you poked your head
through that curtain,
and as soon as I saw your face,
I couldn't do it.
The next day, you brought me food,
you fed me...
I mean, you saved--
You saved my life
is what I'm trying to say.
That's who you are.
And if you decide to keep it,
you are going to be an amazing mother.
And that baby is so lucky.
You've got this.
Lily.
If you ever find yourself in the position
to love somebody again,
just fall in love with me.
Yeah. Okay.
I'm so sorry.
I've been watching him my entire life,
and I've seen...
how afraid he is
of opening his heart to anyone,
ever since he was a kid.
And I think I felt
that he was dying inside.
Just dying inside, little by little,
until he met you.
And I'm not making any excuses...
I never--
I never thought he was capable of this.
Would it... Would it be okay
if I asked what happened to Emerson?
Of course.
You deserve to know, and it's our family.
My father had a gun.
Ryle and Emerson were
playing in the house,
you know, pretending to be cowboys,
and they found it.
And Ryle was six years old.
He was a six-year-old boy.
He didn't even know
that it was a real gun.
He thought that it was pretend
until it was too late.
- Emerson was our brother...
- I'm so sorry.
...his best friend.
He's never been the same since.
Yeah.
To be at that funeral...
I really did used to love flowers.
Listen to me.
As his sister,
I wish more than anything
that you could find a way to forgive him.
But, as your best friend,
Lily, if you take him back,
I will never speak to you again.
I'm so sorry.
You're the best friend I ever had.
I'll be an even better aunty.
Sweetheart.
- This side?
- That side.
Yeah, if I hold it in like this,
I think it'll be a little easier.
- Righty tighty, I think.
- Yep. Come on.
I'm sorry.
No, no. You got it.
Your dad always did this stuff.
I'm sure you built a thing or two
in your life.
No. No, no. That was always his domain.
It doesn't wanna go in there.
Why did you stay with him?
It would've been harder to leave.
And I loved him.
Yeah, me too.
I think I got it.
And that's the heartbeat.
Look at that. Do you wanna know?
- You can tell already?
- I can.
Okay.
Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah?
Okay.
Can you see that?
That's her little head.
Hi.
Hi, baby girl.
"Her," huh?
Hi.
Hi, my baby girl.
It's always--
Thank you.
Is she kicking?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
All right.
Sturdy.
- Here you go. Grab this side.
- All right.
Thank you.
I can clean all this up, so...
Okay.
Do you wanna feel, before you go?
If you want?
Is she kicking now?
Always. Yeah.
Yes.
Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, go ahead. Yeah.
Here. Here.
There she is.
Yeah.
Big old noggin. You feel that?
That's her little heel. You feel that?
She's kinda stretching. Yeah.
Come home.
Look, I won't--
It will never happen again.
I promise. I will... I will get help.
Please come home.
- I'm s--
- You're gonna be late for work.
Come. You wanna join us?
Got room for one more.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I know. I got you. I got you.
- Hey.
- Wanna hold her?
Yeah.
- Here you go. Like that.
- Hey. Hi.
Mommy's got you.
- Yeah.
- Mommy's got you.
Still here.
I know, I know.
I know. It's okay.
Keep her cosy.
- Hi.
- There we go.
- Hi, beautiful.
I'm your daddy.
Yeah. Yes, you are.
Yeah.
What should we call her?
I was thinking we could name her
after your brother.
- Emerson.
- Yeah. Emerson.
That way, we can call her Emmy.
What do you think?
I think that's the nicest thing
anyone's ever done for me.
Thank you.
It's okay. It's okay. Daddy's got you.
Daddy's got you, Emmy.
Hi.
Hi, beautiful. I'm your daddy.
I'm gonna keep you safe, Emmy.
I'm gonna keep you safe.
I want a divorce.
Hey. Let's not.
Hey, yes.
Yeah.
It's not for you or me. It's for her.
Yeah, you know.
Look at her.
What if, one day, she came to you
and said, "My boyfriend hit me"?
What would you...
What would you say to her?
Or if she said, "Daddy, my husband
pushed me down the stairs,
but he said it was an accident,
so it's fine."
Or if she said her husband held her down
and she begged him to stop,
but he swore he'd never do it again?
What would you tell her?
If the person she loved...
was--
was hurting her,
what would you say to her?
I would beg her to leave him.
Yeah.
And I'd beg her never to go back.
Wanna go to your mama?
You have such a good mama.
Here.
I got you, bug. I got you. Yes, my love.
Okay. I'm gonna--
Yeah.
There you go, bug. Mama's got you.
Mama's got you.
Yeah.
Stops right here, bubba, with you and me.
It ends with us.
Okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Thank you.
Mama, I love you.
I'm so proud of you.
- Okay. Okay.
- Okay.
- Be right back.
Let's go meet your grandpa.
Okay.
Goodbye, Pops.
That's enough of that.
Come on.
Yeah. You got it.
- Hi.
How've you--
Was that your daughter?
Yeah, that's Emmy.
I saw you guys before.
I just-- I didn't--
Yeah.
She's beautiful.
Thanks.
Are you still with...
No.
No, no, it's... it's just us.
Wow.
- Are you with anyone?
- How's the store?
No.
Not yet.