I love you.
Love you.
How does Daddy use you?
- Any way he pleases.
- Louder.
Any way he pleases.
What do you do for his cum?
Anything he wants me to do.
Back up here.
Come here.
Do you like this kind of sex?
Request subtitles via my email:
ramin.nekouei@gmail.com
In e-commerce, due to an increase in
e-commerce and fast shipping expectations…
and in the face of real estate
and labor shortages.
Due to an increase in e-commerce
and fast shipping expectations…
An increase in e-commerce.
We need to understand
what it means to be good.
We need to learn what it
means to protect and nurture.
- Who's Ed?
- The homeless woman downstairs.
I don't need them.
I'm a dancer not a hiker.
Yeah, but we go hiking all
the time, so you do need them.
Why do you keep wearing
that apron? It's so weird.
- No, no. Not you. Sorry.
- You don't like it?
- If you don't have your shoes…
- No, no, to my wife.
…you can't come with us.
You'll be left behind.
Did you say that you gave your
shoes away to a homeless person?
- Yes.
- To Ed.
- They made me look weird.
- Well, did they fit him?
- Her.
Mom, can Mary sleep over?
Uh-uh.
Why?
Because your mom is busy
with her company right now.
We need peace and quiet.
These are scary times.
No, it's not scary. It's exciting.
Listen, I made some
small changes over this.
Come on, eat your breakfast.
- Oh.
- You're gonna be fine.
- Hmm.
- Oh.
Hey!
Hey, what the fuck? Hey, get off me!
- Hey, get off me!
- Someone help him!
- Oh, my God!
- Ow!
Stop! No, no, no, no,
no! Stop, stop, stop!
Please!
No, no, no, watch out!
Come here.
Oh, my God. Jesus Christ!
Good girl. Good girl.
Good girl.
Is this your dog?
Thank you so, so much. I'm so sorry.
Here you go.
Great. Oh, I was texting you.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Good. All right.
- Do it.
- We're not late.
Amit Ray said…
"As more and more artificial
intelligence is entering into the world…
more and more emotional
intelligence must enter into leadership."
We engineer accountability
into our products…
and they are changing
the way we live every day.
I am delighted to introduce to you…
the newest asset to our fleet…
Harvest.
- Yeah?
- Hey.
Their response was great I hear.
Yeah. The quote about emotional
intelligence was very good.
Jacob's idea.
Uh, is now a good time
for me to introduce the interns?
- Uh, now is good.
- Okay.
- It's their first day, so…
- Yeah.
Come in.
This is our CEO, Romy Mathis.
Hello. Welcome.
Don't be nervous.
We are so happy to have you here.
And if you have any questions,
please just let us know.
I have a question. Um…
Do you really think automation
can provide a path to sustainability…
or is that just something people
say to make you like robots?
Okay. Uh, let's... Uh, let's go.
Uh, Mrs. Mathis is very busy
today. So, let's please go.
Go. You. Out.
It's her company.
I am so sorry about that.
Do you want me to…
Uh…
Ah.
- Hold on.
- Okay.
Yes. Yes. We were very happy.
How did you feel?
I think it was an excellent day.
Yeah, if that's what you want…
but I think it was
a very successful beginning.
Um, I'm sorry. Excuse me.
Um, who can apply?
- For what?
- Oh, uh…
Everyone. It's a company-wide program.
You'll receive a list of names
by email at the end of the day.
I highly recommend it.
A mentor makes a huge difference…
in how you get
to experience the company.
And you're all invited to
the holiday party this Friday.
Yes! There will be a DJ…
so, you know, make sure you
bring your best dancing shoes.
Good morning, Mrs. Mathis.
Morning, Ari.
He's a problem and we don't need him.
It's just investor appetite
is huge and he can just...
Right.
Yeah. Uh…
Yeah, okay. Well, whatever you decide.
I'll play along.
Um, hey, can you get me
a cup of coffee?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
Safe navigation. Flexibility.
And? Tell him.
I mean, technology alone
can't handle everything, can it?
Anyway, I have to go. All
right. All right. I've got to go. Bye.
Um.
Hey, how'd you get that dog
to calm down?
I gave it a cookie.
You always have cookies on you?
Yeah.
Why? Do you want one?
No.
You shouldn't drink coffee after lunch.
How many do you drink a day?
None of your business. Seven.
Yeah?
All right. Tell him yes.
Hey. Hey.
Hmm?
I want to see you.
Hey, hey. Look at me. Hey.
Oh!
Hey.
I want to watch porn
while you have sex with me.
What?
I want to.
Okay.
Feels weird.
No, like this. Touch me. I prefer this.
You touch me.
Yes, do it.
Come on.
- You do it.
- I can't like this.
- Why?
- It makes me feel like a villain.
Okay. Okay.
Being a CEO means being
a collaborator and a nurturer.
I mean, I see myself as a strategy
expert, but also a human expert.
At the same time, one-day shipping…
has dramatically upped
the stakes for all of us.
And there's huge demand
for what we do.
And everyone is just waiting for
us to buckle under the pressure…
but I say, "Look up. Smile.
And never show your weakness."
Oh, don't use "weakness"
to describe yourself.
It's a positive to be
vulnerable, not a negative.
Got it.
Hey! How are you?
Oh, look at you.
You wore this for me?
- Yeah. Of course.
- Beautiful.
Come on. How did you get
her to... You did it for me?
- Come on.
- You guys want a drink or anything?
Romy, I got you a drink.
No, thanks.
You know, I love your name.
- You do?
- Yeah. Where does it come from?
Is it Polish?
I was named by a guru.
Seriously?
- I grew up in communes and cults.
- No!
Huh.
Oh, my God. You know,
I would never have guessed that.
I mean, I thought that you were raised
by soldiers or something. Or robots.
Or something.
I'm joking, of course.
Do you have a lighter?
Can I borrow your lighter?
Thanks.
I don't like Christmas. Do you?
- I mean, I don't really have any...
- I was reading some... Oh.
- Sorry, go ahead.
- No, no. You.
- No, no. Go ahead.
- No.
Go.
Oh.
I chose you as my mentor.
What?
I'm not a part of that program, so…
Oh, you are.
No, I'm not.
Oh, no, you are. You're on
the list. You're on the, um…
I got an email
and I clicked on your name.
You're on the list.
Thanks for the light.
Come on. Yeah!
When was the last time we danced?
- I don't know.
- A long time ago.
- I can't dance with you right now.
- But they know we are married.
Scarlett doesn't understand
Hedda Gabler at all.
She thinks it's about desire. It's
not about desire. It's about suicide.
Mm-hmm.
Hedda's life is over
even before the play begins.
Before it begins. Yeah.
That makes sense. I think I…
What are you mumbling about?
You're not making any sense.
Are you having a seizure or something?
You're so rude.
And who are you texting the whole time?
I'm not texting. I'm emailing.
- As if that is a good excuse.
- Yes!
- That is the whole problem.
- It is...
- Come here, please. Come here.
- Okay.
- Romy.
- What?
Am I relevant to you as a director?
We are all irrelevant.
We have to pay more attention
to the avalanche…
that is gonna cover us all very soon.
We were a little cautious.
We were leery about markets.
And financials are clearly
higher beta stocks.
Uh, but those who are more optimistic…
and those who are gonna make
plans, who are gonna act upon a dip…
we would point out big
financials, big banks, big insurance…
big asset managers, uh,
big brokers, big exchanges.
The results that are coming out
these companies are good.
Capital markets activity is good…
and, uh, has potential to,
you know, speed up even more.
But I think "big" is the key
theme when it comes to financials.
These big institutions
have the deposit base…
they've got the confidence of
those who buy their securities…
and they are the ones in the
position to continue to invest…
You're sure you don't
want numbing cream?
No. I'll be fine.
This might bruise a little bit.
Five, four…
three…
two…
one.
What are you noticing now?
What?
- What are you seeing?
- Nothing.
Okay.
No feelings in your body?
Come on, Isabel. Please.
- Come on.
- Oh my God.
Okay. Well, we got that.
So, let's have a look here, Emily.
Thank you. Good.
Do you want to go get
changed now, please, Isabel?
Come on. Let her wear
what she wants. It's fine.
Come on, honey.
You look really weird.
Like a dead fish.
- Hey, baby.
- You're just, like, you know, the...
No, come on. Enough. Enough.
- I'm sorry, Dad. It looks awful!
- Enough! Come on!
Go and get changed, please, Isabel.
Why do you do that to yourself?
- Come on, come on.
- All right.
Oh, fuck off.
Will you change too, baby?
Sure.
Good. All right, Emily, how
about one of just the two of us…
- while we're waiting for her to change.
- Yeah. Yeah, let's go. Okay.
Wait. Hold the door.
Hey.
Oh, um, I'm looking forward to Tuesday.
Tuesday? Why?
I got an email saying they
scheduled the first meeting.
The what?
The ten-minute introduction meeting.
I don't know who sent that email, but I…
I definitely don't have time for that.
It's just ten minutes.
What's that? What is that?
What's what?
There's no need for the...
It looks good on you.
Who decided to make me a part
of that mentor program, by the way?
Hazel thought it'd be good for you…
to take part in some
extra activities internally.
They say there's a talent war…
so, I don't know…
I guess it's important to make
new talent feel involved.
Show you're an approachable leader.
A talent war.
Think we could talk
about my promotion soon?
Of course.
- Hey.
- Hi.
How are you?
You have seven minutes.
Ten. I think.
Thanks for making the time.
I was forced.
What?
Um… What?
I didn't say anything.
Why did you want to meet here?
You don't like this room?
No, no, no, I like the room.
It's a nice room. It's very...
It's got a nice vibe. I think...
It's sound-proof, which is good.
- If I were you I'd hurry up.
- Yeah. Of course. Sorry.
How… did…
it… start?
What?
The warehouse automation dream?
That is your question?
Yeah.
Google it.
No, I just wanted to hear it from you.
- Why?
- Because the internet's not reliable.
I graduated Yale cum laude. I
was recruited by an investment firm.
The selection process was grueling.
There were six rooms, they
took me into six different rooms.
I had to answer certain
questions in each room…
and solve math formulas.
One of the questions was
how many ping pong balls…
would fit in that specific room.
Huh, what is... How many
would fit in here, do you think?
At the end, they wanted me
to solve a hypothetical case…
of a company that was in deep trouble.
I spent a week trying
to solve it. I couldn't.
So I went back in and I told them
they could go fuck themselves.
Did you? What did they say?
They hired me.
Because you were bold?
I guess because they were
looking for certain personalities.
What kind?
After five years,
I started my own company.
I wanted to automate repetitive tasks…
and give people their time back
by limiting...
Power hungry personalities?
You think that's what I am?
No. No.
I think the opposite.
You think I don't like power?
No, I think you like to be told what to do.
Sorry. I didn't mean to...
Sorry, that was inappropriate.
That was incredibly inappropriate. I'm…
I just want to see if I can…
Just let me write this out.
Okay.
Your seven minutes is up.
Oh, this stupid pen.
But we can definitely
have another session if…
I mean, if that's…
Yeah.
…what you were hoping for.
I have your number already so, um…
1,824,000 is the answer.
That's how many ping pong balls
fit in the room.
I was just working it out.
Wait, wait. Just wait a second. Wait.
- I have to go. I...
- Just wait.
Close the door a second.
Just close the door a second.
No. No, no.
- No?
- I'm so sorry.
That shouldn't have happened.
- It's okay.
- It's not okay. I'm so sorry.
It's fine. It's okay. It's okay.
Shit. Um, great. Thank you.
Okay. Thank you.
Mom!
- Can you do that?
- Mm.
Watch out.
- Ew.
- Oh, God.
Do you like the girl from next door?
What are you talking about?
How old is she? 17?
I thought you were in love with Mary.
I am in love with Mary.
I was just having fun with Ophelia.
At Tensile, we care
about the safety and well-being…
of everyone on our team,
because a respectful workplace…
"A respectful workplace
is an efficient workplace."
If you experience harassment…
the most effective
and efficient way to address it…
is to report it immediately
using our internal complaint...
Oh, wait.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Can I ask you something?
Sorry. Why didn't you respond?
Um, to what?
We're supposed to meet weekly,
but you didn't respond to the email.
They sent an email.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
I have an appointment.
No, no. It's really...
It's very, very simple.
There's a... There should
have been a link in your email…
you click on it and select the date
and time for the second appointment.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
If you don't want to be my
mentor, I understand, but…
but I do want one because it makes…
- Hello, Mrs. Mathis.
- A big difference.
And so there's lots of
other people I can ask.
You know what I mean? So it just...
Are you done?
With?
Do you understand your behavior
is totally out of line?
Is it?
Yes.
Well, we're supposed to meet weekly.
I didn't make the rules on that.
You know?
Okay, sure. I'll think about it.
- Okay.
- Good.
Perfect. Thank you.
Appreciate that.
Wait. Wait.
That's what comes of sneaking in
by the back way.
Are you out of your senses?
I'm shooting at you, Judge Brack!
No! No! Do not shoot at me!
Did I happen to hit you? Whoops.
I wish you would leave
these pranks alone.
You're not really happy.
That's what's at the bottom of it.
Hey!
I know of no reason
why I shouldn't be happy.
It's amazing!
- Uh, uh…
- Perhaps you can give me one?
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
Watching you in your natural habitat.
Oh, good.
Wow.
Last time you did that was…
1997, when you thought
I was having an affair…
with a lighting technician.
- What's going on?
- I'm coming!
Don't you have to be at work?
Mm…
Okay, let's do this thing again.
This thing with the gun.
It's almost like a...
- Hi.
Your party's right there.
- I'm Natalie.
- Natalie.
We here?
- You finally came! Hi.
- I did.
You know, we have been begging her…
to come get a drink with us
for over a year.
Really?
- Hazel.
- Yes.
There is something
I wanted to run past you.
I don't know, I was thinking
wouldn't it be…
amazing to focus more
on recruiting women?
We are. And we do.
- No, I know. I know.
- Listen to her.
But, I don't know, wouldn't it be cool…
if there was some sort
of program within the company…
to, I don't know,
help young female employees…
- find their way to the top easier?
- Got you.
You know what, let me tell
you this, write a proposal for me.
Of course! Sorry. It's all right.
I know you didn't, but...
But just put it in an email
and we'll figure it out.
- Okay.
- See?
- Email me. You have my email.
- Okay. Okay.
- She's the best. I'm telling you.
- I understand.
She is adorable.
She's enthusiastic.
I don't have enough going on right now...
- I...
- You really don't, okay?
We can go toe-to-toe.
What is this?
Did you order this?
Uh, no, I did not.
I'll get him to take it away.
- No, it's...
- Excuse me.
Are you gonna drink that?
Don't drink that.
Should we all do one?
I'm impressed.
Thank you.
Good girl.
And what will I do in the evenings?
Oh, I dare say
Judge Brack will be so kind…
as to look in now and then.
Happily. We'll have a ball.
Oh, yes, you'd love that,
wouldn't you, Judge Brack?
To be the only cock in my run.
Oh, now she's playing
with those pistols again.
- It was so good.
- Thank you.
Congratulations.
You should be so happy.
Romy! Hey!
Hi, Stephen. You were wonderful!
Thank you. Thank you. So
how's things in the robot business?
Do you have a phone addiction?
You know, that's a thing.
No, Stephen I have a job.
- I loved it. I just loved it.
- You did? Good.
- Huge success.
- Say hello to her.
- Hi, how are you?
- Yes. You were amazing.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Amazing. You made me cry.
I have to go because
I have this work emergency.
Hold on, hold on. It's the one
night that I need you by my side.
- I know. I'm so sorry.
- Baby. Baby.
I have to go.
Uh, it was wonderful, everyone!
I loved it. Absolutely loved it.
Bye. So good to see you.
Hello?
Oh, you're here.
Sit down.
We need to have
a conversation about this…
This is… It's…
What you're doing is wrong.
Your behavior is unacceptable.
- What behavior?
- That's all I have to say.
That's the only reason I'm here.
To stop this and your wild behavior.
What are you talking about?
What am I talking about?
Leaving me notes. Texting me.
Calling me. Sending me milk.
- Are you fucking insane?
- You drank it all.
Keeping me waiting
in this disgusting hotel.
- I mean, I don't wait for anything.
- Sorry, no.
- And that may not be what you mean.
- I'm confused though…
because you want me to...
I don't really know how to...
What do you want from me
because… you show up here...
You don't know me, I'm a
stranger... Dressed like this.
You expect me to just look
at you and not do anything?
I'm not some thing you can
just pick up and play with.
Shut the fuck up. Just shut up.
- Get on your knees.
- No! What?
Get on your knees now.
No!
I don't know how to... I'm just...
Is that what you want? I
don't know. Is that... Be honest.
I don't know.
You're very young.
I don't want to hurt you.
Hurt me?
I think I have power over you…
because I could make one call
and you lose everything.
What? Does that turn you on
when I say that?
Get on your knees.
No, I have to go.
This is unacceptable.
- Unacceptable?
- I have to go. Yes.
Oh…
No. I don't like that. Not like that.
- Not like that.
- What?
Not like that. I don't want it like that.
Stop!
Open your eyes. Please.
Here. Get up.
Hold my hand.
Maybe take your clothes off.
Can you do that?
Uh-uh.
- I don't want to.
- Why?
I don't know. I don't want to.
That's okay.
It's fine.
Just, maybe, come sit here?
Come sit here.
Yeah, that's it.
Maybe could you, um…
get on all fours?
Why?
Can you just try it and stop asking why?
Can you just try, maybe,
for the sake of what we're…
Go back.
- Mm-hmm.
Spit it out.
All right.
- No, I can't. I can't. I can't.
- No. No. No. It's okay.
- No, I can't. I can't.
- Just wait. Hold on.
Just a second.
I'm gonna pee. I don't want to pee.
I can't let…
I can't.
Hey, good morning.
Whoop! Ah!
Sorry.
- You wanted to see me?
- Yes. Just for a minute.
Can you close the door?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, Samuel!
Okay, um, Havest is
surpassing all of our expectations.
We're super excited about it.
I want you.
Why don't you clean that up?
It was so rude.
Oh, my God. She's dancing.
It's where I get it from.
- I can't dance.
- Too much.
- You're incredible.
- All right, everyone, bon appetit.
She was helping. She's never done that.
I know. Yeah, I know.
They seem so happy together.
It's wonderful.
- Yes.
- I like Mary, too.
I think she's a great girl. Good for her.
- Yes.
- Nice.
Where'd you go to school?
- What's your favorite color?
- Purple.
- Yes, me too!
- Yeah?
Yeah! What does your mom do?
She was a teacher.
And your dad's in, like, security?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, he was a fighter first.
Like a professional fighter.
And then he became
like private security for VIPs…
and political leaders, things like that.
Yeah, he did that for a while.
Worked for some pretty
high-profile people.
And then, um, yeah…
he retrained, became a
philosophy teacher, up in Illinois.
So I used to go visit him quite a lot.
But, uh…
yeah, he was a really smart man.
You know?
Really complicated, incredibly tough.
You know, he was impressive. He
used to write these beautiful poems.
Hey.
Oh, hey. You forgot
your laptop at the office.
Esme told me to bring it to you.
Oh, she couldn't organize a messenger?
We thought better in person
because of sensitive information.
I took the train.
Is that a new dress? You look hot.
- Ew! Hot? That's disgusting, Dad.
- Do you work with the robots?
No, no. Not directly. I'm
only an intern. I'm not allowed.
Do you get paid?
Yeah, yeah. Of course I do.
And I work at a bar.
- What bar?
- The Nines.
I'm a dancer. Do you want to
see me dance the tarantella? Yay!
No, no. Come on. We've got
plans now. Sit. Nora, please.
- You should come hiking with us.
- No, no, that's okay.
- No, I'll leave you guys to it.
- No, no. He needs to leave.
- No, no, you're gonna love the property.
- It's fun.
Save me! Help!
You are never safe!
I really like your family. They're so nice.
That's something I want later.
Don't ever show up at my house
like that again.
Huh?
I was just doing my job.
My family is everything to me.
Don't you ever, ever do that again.
- Wait. Wait, wait. Just wait.
- Will you unlock the car?
- Would you just wait, please?
- Please just unlock the car.
- Okay. I need you to listen to me.
- Let me out. I want to get out.
We just have to calm down.
And we have to talk about this…
because I feel like I wasn't
expecting you to show up at my house.
And I don't think we can…
I don't think we can see each
other outside of work anymore.
Get off me. Don't touch me.
Romy, you know I don't want a…
I don't want a girlfriend…
if that's what you're afraid of.
- No.
- Okay?
Because you look like a mother…
- and I'm not interested in that.
- Thank you.
Well, it's true,
so I'm not interested in that.
I thought what we were doing,
was like, you know, in my mind…
I see it as this thing where we're like…
you know, we're two children
playing and that's natural.
Come on, you're not a fucking child.
- Oh, whatever. Let me out the car.
- No.
- Unlock the car.
Unlock the fucking car!
- Okay, it's okay.
- Now you're making me mad.
All right. Shh!
I don't want to feel like this.
- Okay, shh!
- Why are you making me like this?
- Okay, listen.
- No, you make...
Yeah. It's confusing.
- Yeah. Yeah, it is.
- Yeah.
For you. For me.
Whatever this is, I don't know.
So, you're very young.
- No, I'm not.
- You are.
No, I'm not.
I'm not gonna…
I mean, I'm not gonna fire you.
But we have to keep it professional.
What the fuck does that mean?
I'm just trying to take care of you here.
- You're taking care of me?
- Yeah.
No.
Oh.
Welcome back in arguably
one of the most exciting…
developments in warehouse robotics.
Tensile Automation is reporting
an overwhelmingly positive response…
to their newest product Harvest.
- Good morning.
- Hey, good morning.
- Thank you so much. I appreciate it.
- Oh, thank you.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Look at this. I didn't even
ask for it. Very bright kid.
Anyway, I want to talk to you…
about the tapes that Hazel sent us.
Um, you... you can relax a little.
You don't have
to be scared of their questions.
Yes. Yes, I was a little tense.
I get that. Um…
No need. No need.
You've done it a million times before.
Uh, excuse me. I am gonna
have to take this, Sebastian.
Hey.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- What's wrong?
- I'm fine.
I just, um…
I don't feel comfortable
working for you anymore.
I'm gonna talk to someone.
Ask to be transferred
to a different department.
- You can't do that.
- I can.
You can't. They'll ask questions.
They'll investigate. They can't...
You can't do that. They could fire me.
It's for the best. For both of us.
What? What? Come on. Wait! Wait!
Shit.
You want to play a little bit?
Yeah.
Just a little bit.
Get out.
Why did you do that?
I have never had an orgasm with you.
What?
What? Baby.
Don't fucking touch me.
I can't.
I can't come with you.
Are you all right? Hey.
No.
Hey.
Josh. Come here a second.
Okay.
I think it's time to leave.
I need to talk to him.
I'm sorry, but he says you need to leave.
- He said that?
- Yes. Right now.
Did you order the headphones
for Isabel's birthday?
Mm-hmm.
Good.
Did you, uh…
Did you mean
what you said about never…
I was just taking it out on you.
I didn't know what I was saying.
I was stressed.
Of course I didn't mean it.
It's been 19 years.
It's just normally women,
you know that…
I'm not normal. I'm not other women.
Look at me. I'm not normal.
No, you're not.
All right. Hi.
I have seven minutes.
Oh.
Yeah.
Did you talk to them already?
You're sweating.
Oh, sorry. Shit.
- Do you want to lose everything?
- What?
You give that impression.
What do you mean?
The way you look at me. As if
you're expecting me to do that.
To take it all away.
Oh…
No.
- Are you using me to do that?
- No, of course not.
- Because that scares the shit out of me.
- No. I'm not doing that. I…
I just think because you're
young and I'm older than you…
I want to be protective
and I don't want to hurt you.
You keep saying that. But I'm…
I'm... I'm okay.
I think you're the one that's hurting.
You don't have to
worry about it. It's not...
It's...
What we do is...
If we continue to do this, it's normal.
As long as it's consensual.
What does that mean?
Well, it's about giving
and taking power, no?
Come on. What did you do?
Go to a library, look that up?
Oh, no. It's…
I'm just saying it has nothing
to do with your business…
or your family. It's between us.
I'm sorry. I'm…
I'm nervous.
- You're nervous?
- Yes.
Yeah. You look nervous.
You're all... You're acting all...
Why are you nervous?
Why are you so nervous?
Just to be safe, if we're going to
do this, we need to set some rules…
that you and I both agree on.
I think. Um…
Like, I don't know, starting with…
I tell you what to do and you do it.
- Oh, come on. Jesus Christ! Okay.
- Oh, look, this is what I mean.
- This is what I'm talking about.
- No, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, no, no. Wait.
Come on. Sit down.
Come on. It's okay.
Sit back down. Please.
You have to be the one to say
it out loud. That's how it works.
- How what works? I don't...
- This. The dynamic. It's about trust.
I thought you said
it had to be consensual.
Yeah, that's what consent
is, Romy. That's what it is.
That's what consent is. You
have to agree to it. You have to...
Both parties have to agree
to it. That's what consent is.
- And if I don't?
- Then I'll go talk to someone.
No, don't do that. Please.
Oh, come on. Just admit
that this is what you want.
Be honest.
You don't look comfortable at
all. I think you should sit there.
Sit on the table.
On the edge. Right there.
Okay, you need to say it…
otherwise I'm gonna have to go talk to
someone and asked to be transferred.
- No, wait. Wait.
- I'll go talk to...
No. What are the words? What are the words?
- You know the words.
- I don't.
- I don't know them.
- You do.
- Just say it.
- Okay. What? I'll say it.
- I need you to just say it.
- Okay.
What do you want me to say?
- I will do…
whatever you tell me to do.
Whatever you tell me…
to do. I will do whatever
you tell me to do.
- Say it again.
- I'll do whatever you tell me to do.
Good.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Oh, hey, there's
a whole living room in here.
Nope. Stay.
Take your panties off.
Okay.
Open your legs.
Take your hands away.
- How does that make you feel?
- Um, scared.
Really?
Okay, you want to take your
dress off for me now so I can see?
Mm-mm.
But you're gonna do it anyway.
Yes.
Yes, what?
Yeah, I'll take my dress off.
You're so beautiful.
- No, I'm not.
- You are.
No.
You are.
No, I'm not.
- Yeah.
- I'm not.
You are.
You're my babygirl.
Go ahead.
What's the safe word?
Hmm?
Shouldn't we have a safe word?
Um…
Jacob.
Your husband's name?
Okay.
Will you do your, um…
your therapy on me?
- No.
- Why?
I'm not... Because
I'm not a therapist and…
You're afraid of what might come up?
You think I'm a bad person?
No, I think you're a lovely person.
And I think you know things.
You sense things…
about people.
What they want. What they need.
Sometimes I scare myself.
I'm not scared of you.
No.
What star sign are you?
I don't believe in that shit.
Can you hold me?
Your mother's gonna cut the cake.
I'm gonna cut it for you.
You wanna do the first one?
- Oh, come on.
You wanna do it. You wanna do it.
Yes! Good! Don't touch the bottom.
- Go for it! Go for it!
- Don't touch...
- That's okay.
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
No. No. I couldn't recognize
you. For Christ sake.
Yeah. Wait there.
Oh, hey.
- Hi.
- Hi. Come in.
Oh…
- For Isabel, of course.
- Hey.
- How are you?
- Yes. You brought her a gift.
Come through.
You don't mind, do you?
Um, no.
There she is.
There's the girl of the moment.
- Isabel, look who's here! Say hi.
- Hi, gorgeous.
What?
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
Why are you here?
You're with her?
We see each other.
What does that mean? What?
Well, what did you want me
to say? "No, I can't come…"
Are you dating her?
Isn't that man in there your husband?
I don't want you seeing other women.
I don't want... You're mine. You're mine.
Hey.
Everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah. I was just seeing
if I could help with anything.
Yes, please. Can you clean that up?
I think, um… this needs a sweep.
Uh, it's a lovely party.
- It is a lovely party.
- It is. Isn't it?
She's having such a great time.
Such a nice party.
Yeah, it's lovely.
- Really nice. You need anything?
- No, I'm good.
Come in.
Hi. You wanted to see me?
Mm-hmm.
- Sit down.
- Okay.
Yeah, I just wanted to check in.
How are you?
Uh, I'm well. Thank you.
Mm.
How's Samuel?
Um…
What?
I thought we were gonna talk...
Mm-hmm.
But I just wanted to see
if you're okay because, um…
we're gonna be talking
about your future soon.
No, yeah. No, I know. That's...
And you have to be careful, Esme.
He's an intern.
I don't want to dramatize this, but, uh…
you're in a position of power over him.
Is this because of the party?
Because I... I genuinely…
didn't think that
it would be a problem and…
Sorry. I guess I just hadn't…
thought about it in that way before.
It's all good. I just want
to protect you, that's all.
It never stops.
Uh, this is Isabel, I just have to...
Hey, um…
- Hey.
- I want to see you tonight.
I'm gonna have to, uh, work late.
No, you don't have to wait up.
Would you tell Isabel that, um,
she has soccer tomorrow?
And Nora is doing dance, right?
She can sleep in. I'll wake her up.
Okay. Well, I'll just sneak in.
Bye.
Love you.
You know that cuckoo birds,
they lay eggs in others birds' nests?
What?
The cuckoo chicks,
they grow up thinking…
they're in a different place.
And they create chaos. Total chaos.
- You're not a bird.
- I am.
Do you do with her,
what you do with me?
No.
She's not like that.
That's why I like her differently from you.
That's why I like myself
differently when I'm with her.
Hey.
You're still up.
I'm worried about you.
Oh, I'm fine. I'm fine.
It's just been very busy
the past few weeks.
But it's done.
We've accomplished a lot.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Yeah.
- How's Mary?
- Good.
She's good.
Oh.
Bedtime.
Here. Did you want some more?
Come on.
Finish the bacon, would you?
I got it.
- I'll get it.
- No, no. No. It's fine.
You know we never win.
It's also just practice today.
Who is it?
Esme.
Hi.
All right, ladies. We are late.
- Hey.
- Come on.
Um…
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
Bye-bye, baby. Hey, nice to see you.
- Yeah, you too.
- Bye.
Yeah.
Are you all right?
Romy, uh…
I... I genuinely…
believed that…
women with power
would behave differently.
What does that mean?
I just... I…
I tried so many times to talk to you…
about my future at the company and…
Yes. Of course. I'm sorry.
Oh…
I mean, we can discuss it now.
It's been a very hard time, Esme...
Romy, I... I don't want you
to make any promises…
because you're afraid of me.
Why would I be afraid of you?
I know what's going on
between you and Samuel.
And I only want what I deserve.
Okay? Not what's given to me
to silence me.
That's... that's...
And it's how it might have worked
when you were younger, but…
What are you talking about?
You will never see Samuel again.
You will be a good leader.
You will create more opportunities
for women within this company.
And you will be a good example
and role model to us all.
You're confusing ambition with
morality. They're very different.
I have no interest in taking you down.
Okay? Fuck, you're one of the few
women who actually made it to the top.
My interest is in keeping you there.
Not as you are now, but…
as a version of you that I can look up to.
- Okay?
- Okay. Thank you.
Hey. Here you are.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
I need to, um…
Tell me. Tell me.
Ever since I was, um…
Ever since I was very little…
Ever… little…
like, since I can remember…
I've had these specific thoughts
in my head.
What thoughts?
Um…
Dark. Dark thoughts.
Dark ideas. Disgusting.
And I would do anything
to be able to get rid of them.
Because I see myself
as this smart woman.
This very smart, strong woman who...
Getting things done. In control.
- I'm very loving…
- I know.
…and caring, and responsible,
and I... I want to…
I want to…
I want to work on myself
and be a good person.
I want to be... But I'm…
I'm not. I'm not.
- What are you trying to say?
- I'm just saying... I'm saying every…
I've tried. I've tried everything.
I've tried all this therapy.
I thought it was connected
to my childhood.
My fucking childhood and all the...
- But it's not. I was born... I was...
- What do you mean?
I was born like this.
What do you mean?
I wanted you to do, maybe, something…
but you're not into it.
I know you're...
- Into what exactly, Romy?
- I just want to be normal.
I want to be normal.
- Hey. Come on.
- You. I want to be what you like.
I want to be the woman you like.
- This is all very confusing.
- I know.
- Can you be a little bit more specific?
- Yes.
I've never experienced any
of these fantasies in my head…
in real life.
I haven't because I... I...
Until I…
I met this…
You met…
Who? Who did you meet?
Uh… I...
- Do I know this person?
- No.
- No, you don't.
- It's no one at your…
No. It was just a man.
Uh, just...
Just a stranger.
- How many times?
- Just once.
Are you in love with him?
No, I'm not. It's just…
Oh, this is so…
Uh…
It's not about a safe word, or
a safe place, or consent, or…
or the kink, kind of.
It's not that. It has to be...
There has to be danger.
Like, things have to be at stake.
Really at stake and it's obscene.
And it's as if this monster
is just sort of there.
- So what did he do to you?
- That will destroy us, and me...
- What did he do to you?
- It's over now. That's what I'm saying.
I don't even know what his
name is because it's not about us.
It's not. It is not me.
- This is not about our family.
- It has everything to do with you, Romy.
- It's a good thing.
- You know that it's not excuse for this.
- Not your mom. Not your childhood.
- It's out of my system.
- You just fucking lied to me.
- I've done it. No.
- To us.
- Jacob, you're not listening to me.
- I love you. Only you.
- "Something has to be at stake"?
For Christ's sake! What the fuck, Romy!
You know what?
I don't give a shit about your...
your pathetic…
banal sexual fantasies
because it's not about that!
You jeopardized
the most important thing.
Our children!
For what?
I love you.
You know all of this is...
is making me sick.
I want you…
I want you out of this house.
Out! Now!
Fuck that!
You have to go!
What?
You have to leave.
Help me out then.
I could drown you right here.
You should.
No one would even know it was me.
Did I mess with your head?
Yeah.
Yeah, you did, but, um…
but I messed with yours too,
so we're equally responsible.
No.
I mean… that doesn't make it okay.
I think we're okay. We're even.
But it's not okay what I've done.
Just, just... No, just...
Leave me alone with
him a second. No, no, no!
Just give me five minutes, please.
Calm down. You need to calm down.
- And step outside with me.
- Don't do that! Please don't do that.
- I'm asking you for five minutes.
- Just come with me.
- I want you to step outside...
- Jacob. Jacob.
No, no! Stop! Stop it!
- You motherfucker! Stay back!
- Please! Okay!
God, no, no!
Please! Don't!
Stop! No!
No, no, no. Please.
No, no. Please.
I felt sorry for you, motherfucker!
No!
Thanks.
No, no, no. Sit down. Sit down. Sit down.
Sit down, please.
Yeah.
What did you do to him?
She used you.
She abused you. You know that, right?
Humiliation, submission,
domination, whatever you want to call it.
It's just neurotic, right?
Female masochism
is nothing but a male fantasy.
- It's a male construct...
- No. No, you're wrong.
It's, uh…
That's a dated idea.
A dated idea?
Yeah, it's a dated idea of sexuality.
I'm sorry, but you don't understand.
Are you okay?
Oh, shit.
- Jacob.
- No. No. Not you.
Here. Drink some water. Come on.
What's happening? You can't breathe?
Drink some water. Come on.
What is it? Are you having
a panic attack right now?
You need to breathe. You're
not breathing properly. Come here.
Hey, hey, it's all right.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey. No, no, no.
I'm really sorry.
Okay, I'm really sorry.
It is such a huge honor…
to have been guided
by a woman like Romy Mathis.
She understands the importance
of being a voice for your peers…
and an advocate
for women around the world…
who might not have the same
opportunities that us, sitting here, have.
So to be lifted up by a hero like her…
makes this experience
so much more exceptional.
Who are we, as women?
Modern leaders aren't afraid
to take chances…
embrace change, and usher
a team into the unknown.
Sincerity, vulnerability,
and radical self-honesty…
will create a work environment
of shared learning, compassion…
and true connection.
Now, how do we do that?
By making changes from top
to bottom to support women…
at every level across the company.
If we dare to let go of expectations…
and move towards what scares us…
we can often find unexpected strengths.
Today, we celebrate genuine authenticity…
and true uniqueness in every
individual that works at Tensile.
We invite each other to show
the world who we really are…
regardless of people's
assumptions and without fear.
Hmm?
Oh, hey.
You okay?
You look like Grandma.
How did you get here?
I got a car.
You did?
That's expensive.
Mom…
you have to come home.
Dad needs you.
He won't leave the theatre.
He won't eat, and he's reading the Bible.
He'll forgive you, Mom.
What did he tell you?
Nothing.
Mary forgave me.
It's okay, Mom.
It's okay.
God.
Okay.
Please come home.
It's all my fault.
I told you that I was
someone else and I got angry…
because you didn't know
who I really was.
And I'm so sorry. It's my
problem. It's my problem.
Hey. What a great way
to start the year, huh?
Um…
Whatever happened to that intern?
The one who bought me the coffee?
I heard he took a job
at Kawasaki? In Tokyo?
Mm-hmm.
Good for him.
Good for you, too.
You didn't have anything
to do with that, did you?
Why don't you come over
next week for drinks?
I've got the house to myself.
We can talk about it.
Why don't you fuck off, Sebastian?
Hey, careful, Romy.
I'm not afraid of you, whatever
the fuck you're capable of.
Of what you know, of what
you don't know. I don't give a shit.
Just don't ever talk to me like that again.
If I want to be humiliated,
I'm gonna pay someone to do it.
Now get the fuck out of my office.
Five…
four…
three…
two…
one…
Mm-hmm.
Request subtitles via my email:
ramin.nekouei@gmail.com