[looped distorted dialogue]
[gasping sound]
[breathing heavily]
[engine revving]
[sniffs]
- Hey, what the fuck? Hey, hey.
- Easy. Don't move.
[speaks Russian]
[in English] You're making
big mistake, you know that?
Shut the fuck up.
- Let's go.
- Fuck.
[speaks indistinctly]
—[Joel] Get the door. Shut the fuck up.
- Watch the fucking jacket, man. It's new.
- [Joel] Shut the fuck up!
[high-pitched beeping]
[beeping stops]
Listen to me.
You alert your brother and I shoot you in
the back of the head, you understand me?
Okay. You're the boss.
Slow.
[brother] Yo, yo, yo!
You remember my pumpkin frappé, huh?
[Joel] Don't! Don't.
Touch it and he's fucking dead. Hands up!
Jesus Christ, you dumb motherfucker.
Do you know who we are?
Yeah, I know who you fucking are.
Last January, the two of you shot
an innocent mother and a kid.
Killed 'em. In Newark.
[chuckles] Oh, yeah? Says who?
Who the fuck are you, huh?
I brought something to give you.
[brother] Uh-huh?
But you have to watch what I'm doing.
You watching?
- [brother] Oh! No!
- [groaning]
No! No!
[Joel groans]
[brother groans, coughs]
Oh, shit. No, no, no.
No, no, no. Fuck!
- [coughing]
- Fuck, fuck, fuck.
- No, don't die. Don't die, don't die!
- [chokes]
Fuck! Fuck. Look at me.
Look at me, you motherfucker,
you can't die! You can't die!
It needs somebody to fucking pass to.
If you die, it won't
fucking work. Look at me!
Stay alive, you piece of shit.
Stay alive, you piece of shit!
- [gasps]
- [breathing heavily]
[chokes, gurgles]
Oh, G... No.
Oh, no.
Oh, no. [grunting]
Fuck. Fuck.
Fuck!
Now it has no one to pass to, fuck!
[bottles clattering]
Fuck. Fuck.
No, no, no!
- Who the fuck are you?
- No one.
Who the fuck are you?
I'm Lewis. I'm no one. I'm no one.
I'm literally no one.
- What the fuck you doing here?
- Don't shoot me.
Answer me!
What the fuck are you doing here?
I just buy from them, okay?
I fucking hate those guys.
I hate them, too!
I fucking hate them, especially him!
Please, don't shoot me.
I didn't know anybody else was here.
Okay, fuck it.
I didn't fucking know
anybody else was here!
I fucked this whole thing up.
I fucked this whole thing up
and I'm sorry.
This wasn't meant for you.
What?
What wasn't meant for me?
I'm sorry.
What? What are you... Fuck.
What are you sorry for?
Fuck.
- I'm sorry.
- What?
Yo,
who the fuck is that?
Oh, shit.
Ah!
- Fuck!
- [pounding on door]
[gang member] Who has the goddamned key?
Come on! Fuck!
[straining]
[door clatters]
- [Lewis] No, no, no, no, don't shoot!
- Shit.
[gang member] Fuck!
- Alexi and Yev are fucking dead!
- Oh, fuck.
[gang member] Get that piece of shit!
Open it!
Break the fucking door down!
Break it! Break it!
[banging]
Go! Go!
- Move! Move!
- [grunting, panting]
Shoot the motherfucker!
[gunshots]
[car horn honks]
[screeching, crashing]
[gang member laughs] Problem solved.
[dogs barking in distance]
[electricity crackling]
[singer] ♪ I already grieved you ♪
♪ So say What you want, but ♪
♪ This time
I don't believe you ♪
♪ While you been
Talking circles ♪
♪ Every time you got caught ♪
♪ I already grieved you
Grieved you ♪
[applause]
Thank you, everybody.
Now, nearly one year ago,
singer/songwriter
and pop superstar Skye Riley
was fighting for her life
after being injured in a car accident.
An accident that also
tragically took the life
of actor Paul Hudson.
Today, for her first public interview
since the accident,
ladies and gentlemen,
the one and only Skye Riley.
[cheering, applause]
[Skye] Oh, my God, Drew!
Thank you so much for having me.
So happy to be doing this with you.
I mean, I have got to say
that you look incredible in person.
- [Skye] Oh, my gosh. As do you.
- Your hair... I'm obsessed.
Oh, my God. My hair.
I was just trying something new.
- I'm not sure if I'm pulling it off.
- Um, I... What do we think?
- [cheering, applause]
- [Skye] Oh, my God.
[Drew] Well, I think you have your answer.
- Now you've announced new tour dates...
- Yes.
Actually kicking off
right here in New York City next week.
Is this an emotional comeback?
Yes, a lot of different emotions,
you know, with this one.
- A year ago, you had just won a Grammy.
- Mm-hmm.
You were in the middle
of a big world tour.
- Mmm.
- And then you hit this rough patch.
"Rough patch" might be generous.
[chuckles]
I was wondering
if you could share anything
from that period of your life.
I was dealing with a lot of stress
and pressure from the demands of the tour.
And I should have asked for help,
but instead I drowned it all out with...
drugs and alcohol
and a lot of bad decisions.
And I let myself get
completely out of control.
And actually,
I want to take this opportunity
to apologize to my fans,
my loved ones, urn, my team.
Everyone who was counting on me
and supporting me.
I let you all down and...
I promise
that will never happen again.
- [cheering, applause]
- So, thank you.
You were in the hospital.
When you got out,
what has the time been like
between then and now?
[sobbing]
I spent a lot of time looking inward.
Relearning how to appreciate life sober.
And I'm...
I'm just so grateful
for this second chance,
and I don't want to waste it.
Car's waiting right outside by the curb.
There's a bit of a crowd.
[muffled screaming, cheering]
Skye!
[no audible dialogue]
- [muffled] My name is Ashley.
- [muffled] So nice to meet you.
[screams]
That went really well.
- You were perfectly graceful.
- Yeah.
Skye, you've got Instagram and TikTok
- seriously blowing up right now.
- [Skye singing on earphones]
[fading]
You're trending number two on Twitter.
I mean, you should really be so proud...
[Skye on earphones]
♪ There's no medicine to change me ♪
♪ I'm goin' crazy! ♪
♪ Doctor, I need a new brain ♪
♪ Lost in a spiral ♪
♪ Keep making old mistakes again ♪
♪ Uh-oh, gimme a new brain ♪
♪ Stuck in a cycle ♪
♪ If I don't stop
I'll end up dead .I'
♪ Can you change my thoughts?
Can you make 'em clean? ♪
♪ Can you clear my head?
Can you fix my dreams? ♪
♪ Doctor, I'm goin' insane ♪
♪ I've got a bad mind ♪
♪ Give me a new brain ♪
♪ I've got a sweet tooth
For bad decisions ♪
♪ My mind is Wired wrong ♪
Good.
♪ It won't take long
Till I'm the villain ♪
♪ Put me under
Anything you can uncover ♪
♪ Make me forget my wonders
Make me forget... ♪
Eyes up!
♪ Do you think
Someone could save me? ♪
♪ Curious, can you erase me? ♪
♪ There's no medicine
To change me ♪
♪ I'm goin' crazy! ♪
♪ Doctor, I need a new brain ♪
- ♪ Lost in a spiral ♪
- [Skye grunts]
[music stops]
Are you okay?
What happened?
Are you hurt?
Yep, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I think I just took a weird step.
Let's take a break, everyone.
Can we get some ice?
Anton, I'm fine. I'm fine.
- Skye.
- Can we... Can we please just go again?
- I want to get it right, okay?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's go again.
- [Anton] Line up!
- Rewind it.
- Yep.
- Back to one.
Music.
[Skye on speakers]
♪ Give me a new brain ♪
♪ I've got a sweet tooth ♪
[knocking]
Shit!
One second!
Yeah, come in.
- Hey.
- [Skye sighs]
You okay?
- You ready to go?
- Yeah, Mom.
I just need a minute.
You should feel really good about today.
I know.
I do.
Good.
We're ready whenever you are.
[thump]
Final rehearsal is
confirmed for Wednesday.
So we'll be at the venue
first thing in the morning.
You have a fitting, photo shoot,
then stage walk-throughs,
then a fan meet-and-greet.
Please go straight to bed
when you get home.
It's going to be a long day.
Oh, and reminder: Darius gets in tomorrow.
He's gonna be here for opening.
I want him to feel the love, please.
The label is advancing
a lot of money on this tour.
Have I ever not been good with Darius?
Darius adores you, obviously.
Just want you to remember
who's paying the bill.
[phone chimes]
Hey, straight to bed, Skye.
Good night.
Miss Riley.
- [pedestrians chattering]
- [sirens wailing]
[sighs]
Hey.
[breathes shakily, grunts]
- [grunting]
- What the fuck, Lewis?
- What do you want from me?
- Vicodin! Just Vicodin.
Just for pain, same as last time.
Fuck that! Skye Riley isn't just gonna
suddenly show up here.
Your text said to come over.
- What?
- What? What?
[both breathing shakily]
I don't... I don't remember texting that.
How come I don't remember texting that?
- Oh, fuck.
- I don't know.
Just get the fuck off me.
Get the fuck off me!
Oh. Oh, shit.
Holy shit, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I am having the worst week.
[chuckling, groans]
[sighs]
[sniffs]
The worst!
Lewis... what was with the sword?
Uh, what? What sword?
Oh, that sword. [chuckles]
I feel... I'm so sorry about that.
I cannot be too careful right now. Okay?
I am in the middle
of some genuinely fucking freaky shit.
Okay? I'm talking like fucking scary,
fucking haunted-house shit, you know?
Yo...
do you believe in, like, weird stuff?
Yeah, I'm gonna go.
What? No, no, no!
No, please stay. Please stay.
What am I doing? What am I doing?
Skye fucking Riley's here and Lewis
is being fucking crazy? [chuckles]
I am so stoked to see you.
I am pumped. Come on. Come in.
I will chill. Be my guest.
Please take a seat.
Make yourself at home.
I'm sorry about the mess.
You said you, uh, wanted... what was it?
You want Vicodin? Right?
- Yeah.
- I got you. I got you.
Want anything else? I got banger ketamine.
I got really good fucking Molly.
I got some...
- I don't know what this is.
- No, dude, just the Vicodin for my back.
Oh, right, your back.
Ouch. That sucks. I hate that.
Okay, well, you chill,
and I'll be right back.
You chill and I'll be right back, okay?
[chuckles]
I'll be right back. Mmm. [sniffs deeply]
- Oh, my God.
- You smell good.
I missed you! Skye fuckin' Riley, dude!
Vicodin. Vicodin.
What the fuck are you thinking?
[weatherperson 1] ...could still have
some freezing or subfreezing temps...
What the fuck?
Ah, shit.
[sighs]
[weatherperson 1] Here's how we see
everything coming together.
The cold air stays in place.
North of the area...
[weatherperson 2 laughs]
Freddy. It's some snow.
I mean, this is not a huge storm.
It's not, you know,
an ultra-dangerous situation out there.
It's our first snow of the season.
[anchor 1] Over in pop culture news,
singer/songwriter Skye Riley is back,
nearly one year after
she was hospitalized in a car crash
that tragically killed actor Paul Hudson.
Hudson had been driving the vehicle
after the high-profile couple
had left a private party
where both
were reportedly seen intoxicated.
[anchor 2] Yeah, you know,
that accident occurred
while Riley was in the middle
of a blockbuster tour,
and at the time, there was speculation
surrounding Riley's substance abuse.
Especially after candid photos
of the singer went viral
just two weeks before the ace...
Hey, uh, Lewis, I kind of have
a really early morning tomorrow, so...
Lewis!
[sighs] This fucking guy.
Lewis, what the fuck, man?
Lewis!
Swear to God,
if you're fucking with me, dude...
[screaming]
Jesus!
- Skye!
- What the fuck is wrong with you, Lewis?
- Where the fuck did you come from?
- What?
Oh! No!
- No! No!
- What? What is it?
Get the fuck away from me!
- Get the fuck away from me!
- What the fuck is happening?
No! No!
[choking]
Oh, shit.
Lewis? Lewis? Fuck!
What do I do, Lewis,
do I call an ambulance? Fuck. Shit.
Lewis, Lewis! Lewis? What the fuck?
- [choking stops]
- Lewis?
Fuck. Shit!
Shit. You fuckin' OD'ing, man'?
Shit! Fuck!
Lewis?
[breathing shakily]
[gasps]
[dripping]
[squelching, dripping]
[breathing shakily]
[weight clatters]
[gagging] Okay.
[gasping]
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
[breathing shakily]
[tears]
[squelching, dripping]
[breathing heavily]
[distorted dialogue]
[distorted] What do you think, Skye?
Skye?
Hey! Are you paying attention?
[normal] What?
Yeah.
This stuff is important.
- I'm listening.
- Are you okay?
- [sighs] You look exhausted.
- Wow, thanks, Morn.
It's really important for you
to stay on top of your sleep schedule.
- Joshua, grab her a water.
- I'm fine.
I want you to have someone around
to help out with things again.
Have you talked to Gemma
about coming on tour?
Gemma is not gonna want
to hear from me, Mom.
- Have you reached out?
- No, not exactly.
She's your best friend.
I'm sure she'd be willing to forgive
whatever it was that happened
between the two of you.
You're a completely different person
than you were a year ago.
Can you please leave it alone?
All I'm saying is real friends
are hard to come by.
And it was really good for you
when Gemma was around.
You know, I'd be more than happy
to help out with any personal stuff
Skye might need.
- Do you want...
- I don't want that.
You need to stay hydrated.
Will you just stop?
Okay.
No, sorry, not you.
- [knocking on door]
- [Skye's mom] Come in!
- [Skye's mom gasps]
- Hi, Darius!
Just wanted to say hi
to my favorite rock star.
I'd get up and hug you but I'm...
I'm trapped.
- All good. I'll come to you.
- Look at you.
- Hey, Elizabeth.
- Hi.
- [chuckles] Hey, Darius.
- Hey, man.
Starting to get exciting around here.
Oh, my God. I am so excited.
I, uh, have a little favor to ask of you.
Sure.
Tomorrow night, there's a fundraising
dinner for Music Inspires Hope.
It's a foundation
for underprivileged youth.
Interscope Records has done
a lot of work with the foundation.
- Wow.
- I know this is super last-minute,
but I was hoping you'd be willing
to be a special presenter.
- Oh!
- I know you've got a lot on your plate,
but there's no arrival carpet, no press.
None of that annoying stuff.
It's purely about the kids.
—[mouthing] Yes.
Your remarks will be prewritten.
All you have to do is smile
and read from the teleprompter.
How could I say no?
[crew member] Number three.
[photographer] Let's start with a 70.
[camera shutter clicking]
All right, Skye.
Loving this.
Can you give me more?
Even more.
More.
[no audible dialogue]
"Hey..."
- [squelching, dripping]
- [gasps]
[gasps]
[screaming]
[exhales shakily]
[inhales shakily]
What the fuck?
Fuck this guy, man.
Come on. [clears throat]
[softly] Get your shit together.
Get your shit together.
Jesus!
Can you knock?
We were knocking. You weren't answering.
Why were you screaming?
I-I saw a spider.
Sorry, there's a...
There's a spider in here?
Tanya says there's some wardrobe issue
that you needed me to look at.
Yeah, I'm not wearing this one.
I love it. What... What's wrong with it?
Can you show her, please?
The lighting's gonna show
right through this onstage.
And?
I'm not trying to show everyone
how fucking disgusting I am.
I think you're overreacting a little bit.
Yeah, Skye, you know what?
I think your scar is badass.
- [Elizabeth] It is badass.
- Seriously.
This is honestly one of your best looks.
I'm not wearing it.
[no audible dialogue]
There you go.
Thank you, thank you!
All right, let's grab that photo, yeah?
- [exhales sharply]
- [chuckles]
Can we do matching poses?
Of course. What are you thinking?
Um, like...
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
- [camera shutter clicks]
- Twinsies. Super cute.
Thank you. Thanks for coming out.
- Thank you.
- Who's next?
"Too Much For One Heart" got me through
literally the worst breakup of my life.
I feel like you're my spirit animal and...
Oh, my gosh, can I give you a hug?
Oh, my gosh, yes! Aw.
[camera shutter clicks]
- Skye, you got to check out my SoundCloud.
- Oh.
[chuckles] Like, who does your production?
All right, dawg,
let's grab that photo now.
- [Joshua] Nice.
- Oh, can we do one more vertical?
♪ Doctor, I need a new brain ♪
- Oh, my God, that's...
- [panting]
- That was amazing.
- [gasps]
[breathing heavily]
Could you sign, "For Alfredo..."
Alfredo...
"love...
Skye."
[whispering] Yeah.
There you go.
[Joshua] All right. Let's take that photo.
I'm a really big fan.
Oh, thanks for coming out.
I can see you're sad on the inside.
- Sorry, what?
- I could make you happy.
- We would be so happy together.
- Okay, I think we got it.
And you're so beautiful.
You have the most amazing... skin!
- Dude, get the fuck off me!
- Amazing skin!
Skye, I love you!
I love you, Skye! Skye!
- [gasps]
- Skye, I love you!
- [man grunting in distance]
- [exhales]
Hey, folks, just give us, like...
one quick sec.
[breathes heavily]
[exhales] You okay?
- You need to take a break?
- [sighs]
- You sure'?
- [sighs] Let's just get through this.
Hey, Skye.
- Everything gravy?
- Yeah, fine.
All right, who's next?
Hi. What's your name?
That's... That's a pretty
cool shirt you got.
You want me to sign it?
[Joshua] Okay. How about a photo?
Yeah. So sweet.
All right, one, two...
Cheese.
- [camera shutter clicks]
- [chuckles] All right.
Now that's a good one. [chuckles]
[breathing heavily]
[tears]
- [line ringing]
- [breathing heavily]
[Gemma] It's Gemma. Leave it.
—[voicemail beeps]
Hi!
Hi, it's me. Um...
I was just thinking about you and, uh...
how much...
how much I want to apologize
about everything.
[inhales deeply]
Anyway, I don't know
if you want to talk to me. Urn...
Will you call me? Please?
I miss you.
Shit.
[breathes heavily]
[phone ringing]
[gasps]
- Hey!
- [Gemma] Hey.
[stammers] How have you been?
Pretty good, I guess.
Surprised to hear from you.
I know.
Sorry I just called out of the blue.
No, it's okay.
It's cool.
Actually, um...
I kind of feel... [chuckles]
really, uh, overwhelmed at the moment.
I know it's not...
I know it's not your problem
and it's probably really...
shitty of me to even
be calling you. But, uh...
I don't really have anyone
I can talk to right now.
What's going on?
- Any chance you'd want to come over?
- What, like right now?
Yeah, unless you're, you know,
busy or something.
No, I...
Yeah, no, I can come over.
Yeah. Give me, like, 45.
- Perfect.
- Okay, cool. See you soon.
See you then. Bye.
[exhales]
[sighs]
[switch clicks]
♪ Got thick skin ♪
♪ I got thick skin
But I'm hollow ♪
♪ Made up of broken parts ♪
♪ Got a body
But it's borrowed ♪
♪ With a shadow for a heart ♪
♪ Is this how my story's told? ♪
♪ I get higher till... ♪
- [glass shatters]
- [gasps]
[breathes shakily]
Hello?
[lock clicks]
[door creaks]
[switch clicks]
[breathes shakily]
[breathing shakily]
[switch clicks]
- [Skye screams]
- Jesus, fuck!
- What is happening right now?
- [shushes]
[Skye panting]
Is someone else here?
[Skye breathes heavily]
[door closes]
- Skye, what's going on?
- [gasps]
What the fuck?
Right. So...
I'm confused.
Oh. Hi to you, too.
- How did you get here so fast?
- Wait.
Why? What do you mean?
You called me like an hour ago.
An hour?
[stammers]
How you doing, Skye?
I, um... [clears throat]
didn't sleep last night, and I...
think I had some sort of crazy
lucid-nightmare-fever-dream,
and it scared the... [inhales sharply]
scared the crap out of me.
Um... thirsty?
[breathes heavily, groans]
This therapist from my recovery program,
she suggested that
anytime I feel overwhelmed
by the urge to use or get drunk
that I should stop whatever I'm doing
and drink a full glass of water.
It's supposed to be some
sort of form of acknowledgment
for what I can and can't control.
Well, it's good to see you.
[scoffs] Jesus, Gemma.
I'm so sorry.
I was a ginormous fucking asshole.
- I owe you such a huge apology.
- You really do.
I don't know why it's taken you
like a year to tell me that.
I know. I'm sorry. I...
I did want to call sooner.
I just didn't know if you would...
forgive me or if you hated me
and never wanted to hear from me again.
Okay, apology accepted.
Oh, God.
Fucking love you. You know that, right?
- Okay.
- Seriously. You're my ride or die.
Okay! Before we start
sucking each other's dicks,
what's going on'?
Why are you being so weird?
I don't know.
[sighs]
I'm such a mess.
[Skye sighs]
Just how messy are we talking?
Something really bad happened.
[breathes heavily]
You remember Lewis Fregoli?
Lewis Fregoli from high school?
He died in front of me yesterday.
- What?
- I went to his apartment to buy Vicodin.
- Skye, what the fuck?
- Just for pain, I swear.
Gemma, I haven't touched alcohol
or coke in a year, I promise.
But my back is still fucked.
Since I have a history of substance abuse,
no one will prescribe me
anything stronger than Tylenol.
You think that maybe
there's a reason for that?
Well, I don't know what else to do.
Everyone's counting on me.
Okay, just wait. All right. Go back.
What happened to Lewis?
When I showed up,
there was something off about him.
Like he was scared of something.
He started... freaking out and screaming,
like screaming screaming.
And then he...
grabbed this metal gym weight
from like a bench press...
and then he like...
just smashed his whole face in with it.
What?
- Ew. Oh, my God. What?
- I didn't know what to do.
I just freaked and ran out, and...
Gemma, I just left him there.
Does anyone else know about this?
No. Should I... Should I tell the police?
No! Skye, no, listen to me.
If anyone connects you
to a drug dealer's death,
the story will take over your life
and fuck up everything.
And it's not your fault.
I keep seeing his face everywhere.
I just feel so fucked up!
Yeah, no wonder.
I can't imagine
how scary that must have been.
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry I'm laying all of this
on you. I just...
I don't know, I just don't really
have anyone to talk to.
You want me to spend the night?
Really? Would you?
I mean, I'm already here.
Oh, God, I missed you, bitch.
[groans]
[grunts]
[gasping, coughs]
[gasps, groans]
[sobbing]
[gasping]
[crying]
[sobbing]
Help me!
Please someone help!
[sobbing]
- [gasps, breathing heavily]
- [rain sounds playing on headphones]
[sighs]
[breathing heavily]
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah.
[exhales]
[breathes heavily]
Gemma, I'm so sorry about everything.
[softly] I know, it's okay.
I already forgave you.
I don't know why I destroy everything.
I feel like my brain is...
this really fucked-up place,
full of all this
chaos and noise.
And I'm trapped there
all alone... [inhales deeply]
in this darkness.
And I just want to quiet the noise,
but I don't know how.
[Gemma] It's because
you're a horrible person.
What did you say?
Gemma?
[breathing shakily]
- [car horn blares]
- [screams]
- [Gemma] Oh, hey, you're up!
- [gasps]
What the fuck is happening?
What do you mean? I made matcha.
Matcha? What?
Wait, it's... it's morning?
What-What time is it?
Fuck! Fuck, I'm so late!
Why didn't you wake me?
I'm sorry, I didn't know.
I don't have your schedule.
My mom is gonna fucking kill me! Oh, shit.
- Can I help you or something?
- Will you come on tour?
- What?
- Come to rehearsal with me today.
Today? I can't.
I have a friend's thing later on.
What? What... What friend?
Do you have to go?
Well, yeah, I made a commitment.
Fuck. Well, then can you start tomorrow?
I mean, I don't know.
I sort of feel like this is like a thing
we should have a conversation about first.
[door opens, closes]
- Are you kidding me?
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
There are a hundred people
waiting for just you.
I know! I know!
Hey, Elizabeth.
[crew member 1] Look, talent's here.
[crew member 2] Okay, talent's pulling in.
- [Darius] Thought we said 8:30.
- I'm so sorry. It's my fault.
But I'm ready. I'm ready, let's do this.
Sorry, everyone. I'm here. I'm so sorry.
Sorry.
- [breathing deeply]
- [Skye vocalizing]
[vocalizing continues]
I need some water for my daughter.
For my daughter, I need some water.
I need a waiter with some water.
[inhales deeply]
[exhaling sharply]
[cracking]
["Blood on White Satin" playing]
♪ I've got a secret to tell you
I think you already know ♪
♪ There's something wrong with me
Bet you can see it's starting to show ♪
♪ I'm feeling different in my skin ♪
♪ I feel that something is changing ♪
♪ Is it just me or are the colors
Melting off of the painting? ♪
♪ Might be a tragedy ♪
♪ Devastation right in front of me ♪
♪ Am I a future disaster
That's waiting to happen? ♪
♪ That's waiting to happen ♪
♪ Like blood on White ♪
♪ Pan' the sea
You should get out of my way ♪
♪ I'm holding glass in my hand
And it could break ♪
♪ Something so physical ♪
♪ Made me a cynical disaster
Waiting to happen ♪
♪ Like blood on white satin ♪
♪ It's like the switch of an engine ♪
♪ I think I broke all the brakes ♪
♪ Am I defective? Cuz I'm dying
To make stupid mistakes ♪
♪ Oh, might be a tragedy ♪
[snaps]
Oh, fuck!
God!
Oh, my God! Fuck!
Oh, fuck, fuck!
- [screams] Fuck!
- [music stops]
[groans]
Oh, God. Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Are you okay?
My leg!
What happened? What's wrong?
My...
Who was that?
One of you was out of place
and knocked me over!
Who was it?
Skye, I don't think that's what happened.
Do not tell me
what I just experienced, Anton!
I'm not.
I'm just saying
that from where I was watching,
I didn't see anyone out of place.
Skye!
[breathes shakily]
[breathing shakily]
[tears]
[grunts]
- What happened?
- Where is Joshua?
Christ, what did you do?
Hey. Everything okay?
Can I get you anything?
What the fuck is your problem, man?
[chuckles]
- Sorry, what?
- Are you fucking with me?
I have no idea what you're talking about,
I swear.
He trashed my dressing room!
- What? Wha... No, I didn't!
- I fucking saw you, Joshua!
Skye! I... Skye. I would never,
ever do something like that to you, okay?
Like, come on. What reason would I have?
- Fuck you. Fuck you!
- Okay.
Fuck you! Fuck you, Joshua!
- Fuck you!
- All right. That's enough.
Mom, you need to believe me. He did this!
- He fucking did this!
- You need to cool off.
You're not actually taking his side?
- I am on your side, okay? Always.
- [scoffs]
But Joshua has been with me
the entire day.
What? What are you even talking about?
I don't even care what happened
in here, we'll get it fixed.
I just need you to...
[scoffs] ...tell me the truth.
- I'm gonna ask you something...
- [glass breaking]
and I want you to be honest with me.
Skye? Are you using again?
What?
Nobody has to know.
You just have to tell me the truth.
Oh, my God, no! I am not using again, Mom.
You want me to take a drug test?
Okay.
I believe you. Um...
What's going on?
I don't know! I don't know! I just...
Fuck, I feel crazy all the time.
Everything's going wrong.
Nobody will fucking listen to me
and everyone fucking hates me.
Oh, come on, do you hear yourself?
Everybody loves you.
We're all here for you.
We're here because we believe in you.
We believe in this tour.
I think doing this tour
was a huge mistake. It's...
It's too much.
I'm not... I'm not ready for it.
Okay, you know what? We're gonna, urn,
look at the book tonight,
look at the dates,
carve out some time for you
to decompress before opening.
But right now you need to pull it together
and get back out there.
Because we need to be on time
for Darius's foundation event.
Fuck, no.
Mom, please don't make me do that.
I can't get out on stage
in front of a bunch of people tonight.
Skye.
—Mom, you're not...
Fuck, you're not listening to me!
I am not in the headspace
to put on a fucking dress
and play dancing monkey
in front of a room full of strangers!
Darius is counting on you
to be there, okay?
- You gave him your word.
- [stammers]
You are a woman who keeps her word.
You are not gonna cancel on a commitment
to underprivileged youth
right before launching a tour.
[host] Music Inspires Hope
was founded on the idea
that no dream could be too big.
[fly buzzing]
With the help and support
of everyone in this room
and from all of our donors
across the country,
the foundation has been able
to reach more families this year
than ever before.
[fly buzzing]
[host] Thanks to you,
more and more children every day
are able to make
their wildest dreams a reality.
And now without further ado,
it is my great pleasure
- to introduce...
- Ten seconds.
A wonderful young artist.
Ladies and gentlemen,
- please put your hands together...
- I'll take that.
[host] ...for Skye Riley.
[applause]
[cheering]
[Skye] Wow.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm Skye Riley,
and I'm here tonight to...
Uh...
[crowd whispering indistinctly]
I'm here tonight to...
Uh...
That's, uh...
[clears throat]
[sighs]
So, how's everyone doing tonight?
- [applauds]
- Hope you're all enjoying the party.
Uh. Don't worry, though.
I'm sober. [chuckles]
So... [sucks teeth]
Um...
What can I say about
how music inspires hope?
Well,
music gave me everything I ever wanted.
Then again, music did almost kill me,
so there's that.
[chuckles] Uh...
Well, I... I guess that's not fair.
Music didn't put
all those drugs up my nose,
I did.
[whispering indistinctly]
Um...
I... I think I'm supposed to be up here
offering words of inspiration and advice.
Well, when I think about
what I wish someone would have told me
when I was younger
and first getting started,
I suppose I'd say
this business is really hard.
And, uh, you'll spend years of your life
chasing success
you know, thinking that when it comes,
it will magically fix,
you know, everything that's...
bad and wrong about you.
And then you achieve success,
and you realize that it can't fix
the deeply broken person
that you have always been.
And now you can't escape
the miserable thing that you've become,
and one day,
you realize how badly you wish
you could just trade it all just
for one fucking moment of happiness!
[clears throat]
Ooh. [chuckles]
Sorry about that. Uh...
[inhales sharply]
What I meant to say is:
I hope the next generation
of young artists
finds themselves truly inspired tonight.
I know I sure am.
And without any further ado,
I'd like to introduce our next guest,
a very special person
who surely needs no introduction:
Paul Huds...
[murmuring]
What?
Why does it say that? That's not...
This... No. Why did 3...
This... Why did...
- What?
- [murmuring continues]
No.
No, stay away from me.
Stay away from me!
Paul's dead!
You're not Paul!
Stop smiling at me!
No, no.
[groaning]
I can hold it. No, no, stop.
[stammers]
[screams]
- [screams]
- [clamoring]
[no audible dialogue]
[phone chimes]
Okay.
[Lewis breathing shakily]
[door creaks]
[continues breathing shakily]
[whispers] Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
[sniffing, breathing shakily]
[whispering] Do you see it?
It just stares at me,
smiling.
- Skye!
- [screams]
[elevator dings]
[phone ringing]
- [rock music playing]
- [indistinct chatter]
Thank you for agreeing to see...
Wait, what are you doing?
Sending a photo of you to my friend
in case you're some kind of creep.
What? I'm not a creep.
Yeah, that's what every creep says.
Look, I realize you're super famous,
and I invaded your privacy. I apologize.
This is also very weird for me.
- How do you know Lewis?
- I don't.
I... I didn't. [clears throat]
I was trying to contact Lewis to warn him.
Tracked down his address
and went to his apartment.
The front door was unlocked,
and he was already dead inside.
I checked his phone, and you were
the last person he texted with.
W-What were you trying to warn him about?
Look, I'm aware that what I'm about to say
is going to sound completely insane,
but Lewis didn't kill himself.
He was systematically infected,
possessed and then murdered
by some kind of metaphysical being.
What the fuck are you talking about?
If it helps, you might call it
a... a spirit or a demon.
Maybe. I have no clue what this thing is!
But it disguises itself
to look like people.
Like... smiling people.
But only the person that's
been infected by it can see it.
No, that's... that's not real.
That's some supernatural bullshit.
But you've seen it, haven't you?
That's why you're still sitting here.
[phone buzzing]
I don't know.
I don't know what's happening.
I feel like I'm losing my goddamn mind!
That's precisely
what this thing does to you.
It's what it did to Lewis
while it was latched onto him.
It's like a parasite
that infects the host through their mind.
In less than a week,
it drives the host insane.
It's like it feeds off
all the bad shit in their head,
and then once it's done feeding,
it forces the host to kill
themself in front of a witness.
And then that witness
becomes the new host.
That's how you got it from Lewis.
It was passed to Lewis by a cop in Jersey.
That cop was the first one
I tried to contact,
but I guess he went off the grid.
That cop caught it from some doctor,
who got it from a patient,
who got it from a college professor.
And the chain keeps going back.
I've documented all of this.
I can show you.
Why do you even know all of this?
Because it killed my brother.
My brother was a host
eight people before you.
He tried to tell me
what was happening to him.
But he made it hard to trust him,
and the stuff he was saying
sounded certifiably crazy.
He begged me for help.
But I didn't listen.
And then a few days later...
[inhales sharply]
I got a call informing me
that he tore his own jaw off
with a crowbar.
- Well, have you gone to the police?
- [chuckling] And say what?
My brother's suicide was actually caused
by some cosmic evil being
that no one else can see?
The police can't stop this thing anyway.
So I'm just supposed to wait
until this thing kills me?
- No, I want you to help me destroy it.
- [phone buzzing]
How?
From what I can tell,
the chain stops when
an infected host dies in some other way
outside of the being's control.
My guess is that,
just like other parasites,
without a living host
it has no way to survive.
It ceases to exist.
So it only stops if...
If I die before it kills me?
Exactly. We need to kill you first.
What?
Only technically. Look.
There are ways
that we can very safely stop your heart.
That'll deprive it of a living host.
Once it goes,
I can resuscitate your heart
and bring you back.
Are you out of your fucking mind?
I know it seems extreme.
- "Extreme"? You're asking to kill me!
- Whoa, hey. Just keep it down.
I don't even know you.
I don't even know you!
My name is Morris.
I'm an ER nurse, and if we don't do this,
it's gonna kill you like it killed Lewis
and infect another victim.
Look, I've already got
everything prepared.
We should just go now
and get rid of this thing tonight.
I can't. I can't do this.
You're nearly out of time!
This thing has been feeding
on you for three days already!
It's already taking control of your brain,
and pretty soon you won't even realize
the ways it's manipulating you,
and then it'll be too late to stop it.
We have to go right now.
-[onlooker] Is that Skye Riley?
—[drunk person 1] Holy shit. Dude.
- That's Skye?
- [onlooker 2] It's Skye Riley!
Would you do a quick TikTok with us?
—Skye Riley!
I watched that video where you knocked
down that old lady like fifty times!
That shit was so fucking funny.
[grunts, laughs]
—[people in bar clamoring]
[drunk person 3] Skye!
Skye, can I get your autograph?
[yells]
Fuck!
[grunts]
- [tears]
- [grunts]
Fuck!
[screams]
[gasping, wheezing]
[grunting]
[breathing shakily]
[swallows]
[light bulb shatters]
[screams]
No! No!
Don't! No!
[grunting]
No! No! No!
No!
- [grunts]
- [piano rings]
Get off!
[grunting, shrieking]
- [screaming]
- [tearing]
[gagging, choking]
[bones cracking]
[clears throat]
[Paul] What?
What?
- [Paul] What?
- What?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Are you crying right now?
I'm... I'm not crying. [sniffs]
- [laughs]
- Are you crying?
[sniffs]
- Hmm? Huh?
- [clears throat]
Hey! Hey, I'm fucking talking to you!
["Boss" playing loudly on radio]
Are you fucking kidding me?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
—[radio switches off]
What the fuck is wrong with me?
What the fuck is wrong with you, huh?
I don't know! I don't know!
I don't know, Paul.
Why don't you tell me,
since I can't do anything right?
Jesus Christ! I swear...
I swear to fucking God, you are so...
- What? What? What?
- [car revving]
I'm so fucking what?
Say it. Say it. What am I?
[clapping] Tell me, I am so fucking...
You're fucking psycho!
- Oh, yay!
- Yeah!
Psycho!
- It's out of the bag!
- You're fucking crazy!
- [cheers]
I'll show you crazy!
- You want to fucking see crazy?
- Stop it! Stop it!
- What are you doing?
- Is that crazy enough for you?
- Is that fucked up? Huh?
- Stop it!
- Is that crazy enough for you?
- Yes, that is crazy,
you fucking psycho!
Jesus fucking Christ! I'm fucking driving.
[grunts] Fucking hate you!
Good! Good!
'Cause I fucking hate you, too.
I fucking... [sighs]
You crazy bitch.
[cackling]
Ah, you psycho bitch!
[mock crying] Oh, you're gonna cry.
Are you gonna cry now?
Is that your thing? "Oh, God!"
Oh, you look so fucking ugly
when you cry. It's horrible.
I can't... Ew, I can't... [mock gags]
"Oh, help me, God!"
[mock sobbing]
- [screams]
- What the fuck are you doing?
What are you doing?
- [horn blares]
- [Paul] Jesus!
Oh, my God!
- [metal crunches]
- [gasps]
It's okay, it's okay.
Everything's fine. Hey, hey.
You're okay.
You have a mild concussion.
Where am I? Where am I?
Harvest Moon.
It's a private wellness clinic.
You fainted and hit your head.
We found you lying
on your living room floor, unconscious.
The doctor said you were sleep deprived
and extremely dehydrated.
No, no, no, that's not...
That's not... That's not what happened.
Joshua, could you go find Dr. Fowler
and let him know Skye's awake?
Of course, yeah.
I hope you're feeling better, Skye.
I, uh... I brought a sweatshirt
for you, just in case you...
you get cold.
[Elizabeth] We can cover that with makeup.
And the team's already working
on a fill piece for your hair.
Don't worry, you won't be able
to tell the difference.
And I've cleared your schedule.
So today you can just have a whole day
of rest and recuperation.
[Skye whimpering] Where's my phone?
- I need my phone.
- It's right here.
I got it.
- I need it. Give it to me.
- Maybe later.
Right now,
we're just gonna focus on relaxing.
[whispering] Mom. Please, please.
Something really crazy is happening to me.
I need to get out of here right now.
No.
We are gonna stay here together
until we head to the venue tomorrow
for the preshow.
That way we can make sure
you're a hundred percent
and ready to perform.
No, no. I can't. I...
Can't what?
[breathes shakily]
I can't do the show.
If you... cancel the show,
then you will be
checking yourself into a recovery program.
- That's the only explanation...
- Mom...
as to why Skye Riley
is canceling another tour
the night before it starts.
You will have to explain to the label
who've invested millions of dollars.
And you're putting the workers...
—Mom, you don't understand!
No! You don't understand, Skye.
There are no more second chances.
If you cancel, this is it.
The media will rake you over the coals.
We'll be sued by the label for millions.
It will be the end
of everything we've built.
[sobbing] Oh, my God, Mom.
Why is that all you care about, Morn?
You treat me like
I'm some fucking windup toy.
You don't give a shit about me
- other than the business I bring in!
- How dare you talk to me like that?
You arrogant little asshole!
I have given up everything for you!
Every second of my time.
Years of my life.
My career.
And here I am, sacrificing every fiber
of my being to support you.
But you're too selfish to even see it.
You put everyone through absolute hell,
and still we support you.
But you want to go
and throw it away? Fine!
Do it! Throw it away! I don't care!
That's what everyone expects
of you anyway.
I wish you could feel what it's like
having to live inside my head.
[in demonic voice] I've tasted
what's inside your head!
[sobbing] No, no, please, no!
Please, no.
No.
No, no, no! Please!
No!
[grunting]
Oh, no, no!
[breathes heavily]
[grunting]
Look what you're doing
to your poor mother.
[Skye crying]
No, God!
[groans]
[breathes shakily]
[gasps]
[Elizabeth choking]
[whispering] Oh, God, that's not real.
It's not real. It's not real.
It's not real.
No, no.
[screams] No!
It's not real, it's not real,
it's not real. [inhales deeply]
[gasping]
[shakily] Oh...
Oh!
[gasps, sobs]
- [knocking on door]
- [gasps]
It's Joshua!
- [door opening]
- I need a second!
- I'm changing.
- [Joshua] Oh! Sorry! Uh...
You know what? I'll wait out here.
Also, the doctor said he's gonna
come and see you in a few minutes.
Actually, I...
I... I feel kind of thirsty. I need a...
Do you think you could go
find me something to drink?
Oh. Uh, I brought some bottles of water.
Put them in the little refrigerator.
I feel like soda.
Could you get me a soda, please?
Sure. Yeah, no problem.
What kind?
Any kind, just... surprise me.
You got it.
You know what? I'll be right back
with one, uh... surprising soda.
[breathing heavily]
[shakily] Fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck. Oh, fuck!
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Shit.
[exhales shakily]
[indistinct chatter]
[chattering]
[Joshua] Skye?
Are you...
Oh, my God! Is that...
blood?
No.
[shakily] Hey, uh...
We need a doctor over here!
[whispering] Shut the fuck up!
Yeah, could we please
get some help, somebody?
Just shut the fuck up!
Are you hurt?
[Joshua] Somebody please help!
We need a doctor.
Oh, my God, Skye.
Hey... you, you, you!
Please help me!
[guard] Whoa, whoa, easy! I got you.
Get away from me!
[all gasping]
Hey... just take it easy.
[all screaming]
I said get the fuck away from me!
[breathes heavily]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Skye?
Skye? What are you doing?
Think about the tour.
Fuck the tour!
[indistinct chatter]
[person 1] Is that Skye Riley?
- [bystanders chattering]
- [train passing]
- [glass breaks]
- Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck! Oh, God.
[Gemma] Skye?
What are you doing out here?
- Gemma, what are you doing here?
- Your morn called me. Are you bleeding?
- Is your car here?
- No, your mom's driver drove me, why?
- Where is he?
- He just dropped me off over there.
What's going on?
[bystander] Skye! Skye Riley. That's her!
What happened? Skye!
[bystander 1] Hey, that's Skye Riley!
[bystander 2] Totally off her rocker.
Hey, get out! I need your car!
Ms. Riley, what...
Get the fuck out of the car!
[bystander 3] She's got a gun!
[Gemma] What the fuck are you doing?
Gemma, I love you, but if I don't leave
right now, I'm gonna fucking die!
Fuck it! I'm coming with you. Move over.
- No, Gemma, no!
- You don't know how to drive. Move over!
- Fuck!
- [bystanders clamoring]
- [horns honking]
- [bystanders] Whoa!
[siren wailing]
Dude, where are we going?
What am I doing? Where am I going?
Where am I going? Skye!
I don't know yet. Just keep driving.
No, I need you to explain
what the hell is going on.
[phone chimes]
I need to get to Staten Island.
What? Gross. Why? Oh, shit.
Fuck!
[groans]
Jesus Christ!
You need to go to a hospital!
No! I need to go to Staten Island.
What the fuck is going on?
Why are we going to Staten Island?
[groaning]
- [groans]
- Skye.
- Gemma, pull over, please.
- What?
You just told me to go to Staten Island!
Gemma, just fucking pull over, please!
All I've ever done is make your life hell.
I don't deserve you.
So please, just pull over
and get away from me
so I don't fuck up your life, too.
No, fuck that noise.
Ride or die, bitch!
[shakily] I need to...
I need to tell you something.
-What?
—[phone rings]
Skye?
[ringing continues]
Hello?
[Gemma] Hey, it's me.
I got your voicemail.
Sorry it's taken me a few days
to get back to you.
But, honestly, I wasn't even sure
if I was gonna call you back.
Did you spend the night at my place?
What? I haven't been
to your place in like a year.
Since you said
I was a "stupid opportunistic cunt,"
remember?
Also, what's up with these
weird-ass fuckin' text messages
you've been sending me?
Hello?
[in demonic voice] Gemma hates you, Skye.
No, please. Please, Gemma, no.
Please, Gemma, no. Not you, please.
No, no!
No! No! No!
Fuck you!
Fuck you, fuck you!
Let me the fuck out!
- Let me go!
- No one cares about you.
This is not real.
You're not driving, you're not driving.
You're not driving, this isn't happening.
You're in my head, you're in my head.
You're in my head! You're in my head!
You're in my head!
You're not in control. I am!
You're not in control. I am.
[whispering] I'm in control,
I'm in control, I'm in control.
I'm in control, I'm in control,
I'm in control.
[gasps]
[horns honking]
[breathes heavily]
[honking continues]
I'm in control.
[driver] Fuck you! Learn to fucking drive!
[car horn honks]
[car horns honking]
- [horns honking]
- [tires screech]
[Morris] Jesus Christ!
Christ, are you okay?
Where are your shoes?
- I don't have any. Here, take this.
- Why do you have a gun?
Just take it! Hey!
If this theory of yours doesn't work
or you see me change and start smiling,
- shoot me in the head.
- Whoa, whoa, hold on!
Hey! You need to stop it, no matter what.
We're going to.
- Promise me!
- All right!
All right, I promise I'll shoot you.
How do we stop my heart?
[Morris] Sorry I haven't
done anything about the lights.
[door closes]
Is this a Pizza Hut?
It's the only thing I could find
for lease on short notice
that had a large enough freezer.
Why do we need a freezer?
[Morris] For your brain.
Fuck.
Once we stop your heart,
your brain stops receiving oxygen.
Normally, necrosis sets in immediately.
You'd have two minutes maybe
before permanent brain damage occurs,
but if we bring your body temperature
down far enough, we can delay the process,
giving us up to nine minutes
before permanent damage.
We need to make sure this thing
isn't able to hang around. And...
[strains] ...I like our odds
with nine minutes better than two.
[door creaks]
[Morris grunts]
[breathing heavily, grunting]
[door creaks]
[door thuds]
- The freezer door latch is broken.
If it closes all the way,
it can't be opened from the inside.
[shivers]
Here. Change into this.
[breathes heavily]
Jesus, that's a lot of blood!
Are... Are the cops
gonna be looking for you?
I don't know. [sighs] Let's just do this.
Once your body temperature
drops low enough,
I will inject you with a drug
that will cause your heart
to start slowing down until it stops.
How long will it take?
It's critical you reach
flatline as fast as possible.
So I'll need to inject it
directly into your internal jugular.
After 30 seconds... you'll be dead.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Jugular, like in my neck?
[breathes shakily]
Let me see the needle.
[needle clatters]
What the fuck, man?
I know. Sorry.
Lie down here.
[breathes shakily]
[grunts, exhales sharply]
[shivering]
Oh, my God, I'm so fucking cold.
That's the idea.
I'll be monitoring your heart rate.
The moment you flatline,
I'll start a timer for eight minutes.
Once the timer's up,
I will inject a dose of
adrenaline into your heart
- and start CPR resuscitation.
- [shivers]
I can't believe I might die
in the freezer of a fucking Pizza Hut.
I promise I'm gonna bring you back.
[breath shudders]
Morris?
I'm sorry about your brother.
I know that's why you're doing this.
Thank you for helping me.
Can I ask what made you change your mind?
[shivers] Every good thing in my life...
ends up broken because of me.
I hurt everything and everyone I touch.
It doesn't matter
what happens to me anymore.
But I will not let this fucking thing...
use me to hurt anyone else.
[gulps, sniffles]
Put this in your mouth.
Don't move.
I just have to get something.
Wait. Where... Where are you going?
- [door creaks open]
- Shit.
[grunts]
Wait.
[grunts] Morris?
[grunts]
[breathes shakily]
[shivering]
Hey!
Don't leave me alone here!
Please.
Mor... Morris?
[grunts, shivers]
[breathing shakily]
[dripping]
[person sobbing]
[shivering]
[sobbing continues]
[wailing]
[shivers, gasps]
No! [wailing]
[shivering]
[wailing]
No! No!
[screams, grunts]
[grunts, breathes heavily]
[breathes heavily]
[screams]
[grunts]
I've been waiting for you
for such a long time.
Mor... [breathing shakily]
Morris! Morris, it's in here!
Morris can't help you anymore.
It's just you and me.
[grunts]
I like wearing your skin.
[grunts, coughs]
[grunts, wheezes]
You can't get away from me, Skye.
[echoing]
[wheezes]
[flesh squelching]
[breathing heavily, wheezing]
[flesh squelches]
[breath shudders]
You'll never escape who you truly are
on the inside. [echoing]
[whimpers]
[in demonic voice] Look at me!
[gasps]
- [groaning]
- [bones cracking]
[Other Skye screeching]
[bones cracking]
[both groaning]
Fuck... you!
- [Skye grunts]
- Skye!
[grunts]
[Other Skye screeching] Skye!
Skye!
[distorted, echoing] Skye!
Skye! Skye!
[breathing heavily]
[breathing heavily, gasping]
[Other Skye chuckling]
This isn't real, Skye. [chuckles]
[chuckling continues]
No! No!
No.
[Skye breathes heavily, wheezes]
No. No!
Please, no!
You're not in control, Skye.
No!
I am.
[breathes heavily, wheezes]
Break a leg out there.
[Skye breathing heavily]
- [machinery whirring]
- [Skye breathing heavily]
[Skye] No. No.
[breathes heavily, gulps]
[crowd cheering]
[gulps, breathing shakily]
[crowd cheering, whistling]
[fan 1] Skye, I love you!
[fan 2] Skye!
[fan 3] Whoo! Skye!
[fan 2] Skye, you're the best!
[fan 1] Skye!
[fan 3] I love you, Skye!
Skye, you look beautiful!
[breath shudders]
[fan 1] I love you, Skye!
[fan 4] All right, Skye!
- [fan 3] Skye!
- [fan 2] Skye!
[Elizabeth] Whoo!
[cheering]
- Yeah!
- [fan 2] Skye!
[fan 4] Whoo!
[breath shudders]
[fan 5] I love you, Skye!
Smile.
[breathes shakily, sniffles]
[breath shudders, whimpers]
[sobbing] No.
No!
[microphone feedback squeals]
[Skye gagging, coughing]
[fan 6] Somebody help her!
[murmuring, gasping]
- [Skye continues gagging]
- [fan 7] My God. Do something!
[fan 6] I love you!
[fan 1] Get up, Skye!
[fan 6] Yeah! There you go, Skye!
[fan 7] Whoo! We love you, Skye!
[fan 6] All right, Skye!
- [crowd cheering, whistling]
- [fan 7] Skye, we love you!
[fan 1] Yeah, Skye! You got this!
[fan 2] Whoo! Yeah, Skye!
[cheering, applauding]
[microphone feedback]
- [microphone thuds, feeds back]
- [squelches]
[thudding, squelching continues]
[crowd screaming]
[microphone thuds, squelches]
[body thuds]
["Death of Me" playing]