Why does everyone work so hard?
Study.
Club activities.
Romance.
Win and lose.
They need validation from others.
The privilege of youth.
Special people.
I don't understand, and I don't
ever really thought about it.
HAKUHO ACADEMY
Dreams for the future?
What a hassle.
I just want to relax
and play "video games".
Oh?
Oh, shit.
It will be destroyed.
Huh.
I don't think I'm dead.
Wait, wait. You're great!
Are you a member of the soccer team?
Ah, I'm dead.
Who are you?
Want to play soccer with me?
Oh, you're the rich kid.
Can I have some money?
Huh?
I don't want to play football,
and I never exercise.
I just want to relax and without
do anything for the rest of my life.
Can I have some money?
But wait, the trap in that game just now...
You definitely have talent!
Come play football with me.
I hate things that require hard work.
I don't want to work.
I like you!
You don't need to change.
What makes it so enthusiastic?
Let's play football!
Is that me?
BLUE LOCK
BLUE LOCK THE MOVIE
NAGI EPISODE
Good morning, Choki.
Ouch.
Ah, that woke me up.
Why do humans feel hungry?
If not, I don't need to eat.
If I don't need to eat,
I don't need to brush my teeth.
If there is no school,
I can keep playing video games.
Life is such a hassle.
Okay, Choki.
I'll go first. Greetings.
HAKUHO HIGH SCHOOL
Nagi!
Hi, Nagi.
This is Grandma, my nanny.
MIKAGE COMPANY SERVANTS
Pleased to meet you.
Come on. Starting today,
we play football together.
Why?
We promised the other day, remember?
Oh, eh, really?
I'm the type of person who can
get whatever I want.
And you will be my partner.
Wait.
Hey, Nagi!
Take this, you idiot.
Just die.
Huh?
Finally found you.
Let's play football.
Wow, you are so persistent.
You have to be the one
best in the world with me.
That is our destiny.
Be proud because you have
I found it.
What a hassle.
I mean,
why do you want to play football?
Because of Mikage Reo's life...
I'm bored.
This is not fun.
...really boring.
I can get anything what I want.
But there's nothing I want.
I want a treasure that is only
be mine only...
I want the treasure that
just be mine...
There he is.
I want this.
Impossible.
Just forget it.
You are my successor.
He's right, Reo.
I tell you this
for your own good.
But...
When I found you...
...my dream begins.
What a hassle.
You watch too much anime.
I don't even know what it's like
football rules.
Everything will be fine.
You just need to do what I said.
Come on. Let's practice so we can do it.
become national champion.
I hope we can work together
with you, Nagi. Call me "boss".
But, Reo, you're not even
member of the soccer team, right?
Thank you for your hard work!
HAKUHO FOOTBALL TEAM CHANGING ROOM
Welcome, Captain Reo!
Wow.
But how?
Connection, my friend.
I make the most of what I have.
So, if we make it to the national level,
we can party with the idols, yeah?
And if we are crowned champions,
We can date with
an actress at an amusement park, huh?
Oh, I see what you mean.
Unleash the power of bloodline
Mikage Corporation, huh?
Correct.
Why not?
At the moment, at most we are only successful
reached the quarter-finals of the qualifying round, but...
Now I'm here, competing
in the national championship is really important!
Yes!
Hey, we have a problem!
We just got an offer
for sparring...
What?
Have you got an offer yet?
Good.
From where?
Yes, actually...
HIGH SCHOOL FOOTBALL TOURNAMENT REGIONAL CHAMPIONS
That's from a really great school
who always appears at the national level,
Dadada High School.
Huh?
Why is the school so famous...
Did you do this, Captain Reo?
Uh, no.
Your father did it.
Wow.
He sent this message,
"Because you are my son, winning
This game should be easy, right?"
"This is a gift to help you achieve your dreams.
your dream." That's what he said.
What kind of prize?
That's absolutely ridiculous.
He wants to destroy my spirit,
so I gave up.
This is the debut match
that we dream of.
Nagi, give me your talent.
Reo.
You hurt me.
So, what do you think?
It's not about that.
Why should we play
against a weak team?
CAPTAIN DADADA
I'm ready to destroy dreams
rich kid to pieces.
Nice to meet you, Prince.
Shut up, you're just a muscle man
who likes football.
Don't assume you can understand me.
with your brain as small as that.
What?
You haven't seen what it's like
a true genius.
Nice to see the little boy's self-esteem
those grown in greenhouses are thriving!
I will destroy you with
to the best of my ability, Mr. "Genius".
FIRST KICK
Is he really a genius?
What are you doing?
Stop that know-it-all brat!
Push him and take it!
Huh?
I don't even know what it's like
football rules.
Everything will be fine.
You just need to do what I said.
I will prove that
you are the best in the world.
So Nagi, you need to...
...Playing soccer
and trust me!
Yes, boss.
Keep going, genius.
Take it!
Do not be arrogant!
You can't shoot if
you lost your balance.
You're finished.
Huh?
What is he talking about?
I can kick it without any problem.
Huh?
Scorpion kick?
Then do roulette volleyball?
Impossible.
What is this creature?
Nagi!
Nice kick!
Take it!
- That's the first goal!
- Interim report.
I came to Dadada High School to
watching their practice matches,
and I found two players
extraordinary on the opposing team.
Ego...
I will invite
they both went to Blue Lock.
HAKUHO HIGH SCHOOL CLASS 2
Let's do this, Nagi! Come on!
we are the best in the world!
HAKUHO HIGH SCHOOL CLASS 2
Wow, that sounds like a hassle.
NEW STAR DUO AT HAKUHO HIGH SCHOOL
Pay close attention.
Hey, I'm going to die.
HAKUHO HIGH SCHOOL ACHIEVES VICTORY
CONSECUTIVE.
HAKUHO HIGH SCHOOL DEFEAT
OTHER POWERS
You want?
No, chew it.
too much trouble.
RACE ON THE ROAD TOWARDS
UNBEATABLE SERENE
Hey, teach me how to play
this thing.
Ah, this gentle breeze feels
pleasant.
DUO STARS DESTROY
THE CHOSEN CHAMPION!
O.
I'm tired, Reo.
Let us go home.
Okay, okay.
I understand.
But let me do it
ten more times, Nagi.
Huh?
But I'm hungry.
Good job today, Mr Reo.
Hi, Grandma. How are you?
TO MIKAGE REO
FROM JAPAN FOOTBALL ASSOCIATION
There is a letter for you
from the Japan Football Association.
Huh?
Oh, that.
Yes, I got that letter too.
SELECTED AS DESIGNED PLAYER
I was selected as a certified athlete?
Wait, is this a training camp?
to enter the Japanese team?
Ah, Friend.
I don't want to practice.
I just want to play
video games and naps.
What are you talking about?
This is our big chance!
Showing off our skills there
is the fastest path to the national team.
Let's practice, Nagi.
Hey, my leg is broken.
My cells are dying.
My heart stopped beating.
Are you a zombie?
Nagi the Dead Man.
Geez, what should I do with you?
Ah, this is fun.
Reo Limousine.
Okay, you do the job.
well today.
Reo, you're weird.
What do you mean?
You're the weird one.
You're weird because you don't feel
disturbed to be around me.
It's completely within my reach.
Besides, you're a nice person.
to be invited to socialize.
How about you?
Are you having fun?
I don't like football, but with you
no hassle, so that's good.
Just think of it as fun!
JAPAN FOOTBALL ASSOCIATION
Okay.
Is this a job interview?
I'm curious, what kind of player?
which will be here.
I am very excited because
can destroy it with you.
But what if there is
a better player than me?
Wouldn't it be better if
do you work with them?
Huh. I will never
do such a cruel thing.
Well, I don't mind.
If you do that.
Wow.
So many people.
They all look like high school students
which is very famous.
Crazy.
What will happen now?
Wow...
Oh, wow!
This is the "jewel of Japanese football" that
reportedly has been called up to the U-18 team,
Guess Ryosuke!
Hm? I think he looks like
ordinary short person.
Not a black-haired man.
The tall and handsome one.
Happy, a diamond in the rough.
You are 300 years old
18 years and under who have been selected...
...according to my decision
which is arbitrary and biased.
I am Ego Jinpachi, who was hired to
ensure Japan wins the World Cup.
Who is this person?
Simply put,
there is one thing needed...
...in Japanese football
to be the best in the world.
The birth of a revolutionary striker.
Here I will do an experiment
For...
...changing one of 300 people
become the world's best striker.
And that is what this facility was created for.
Blue Lock.
Starting today,
you will live together here...
...and undergo special training
that I have designed.
You will not be allowed to go home,
and you will say goodbye to...
...any football life
that you have been living all this time.
But I promise this to you guys.
If you manage to survive and
beat 299 other people here...
...to be the last man standing,
you will be the greatest striker in the world.
That's all.
Nice to meet you guys.
BLUE LOCK
Huh, crazy.
World Cup.
The best in the world, Nagi.
Hey...
I think I'll go home.
Sounds like a tough workout,
and I'm not motivated enough.
Hey, hey.
Wait a moment!
We both can do it.
Let's sign up and see what...
Both of us?
What are you talking about, Reo?
The man said the last person
the one who survives. Single.
Huh?
You can't be
best striker in the world...
...unless you are a person
most selfish in the world.
Just imagine.
You are in the World Cup final.
Eighty thousand people in the stands.
You are standing in the field.
The score is 0-0.
This is the second half
extra time.
This is the final game.
With a pass from a teammate,
you managed to get past the defense.
You're up against the goalkeeper.
Six meters to your right
is your teammate.
If you pass,
you are guaranteed to score.
At a time when all the hopes of the nation
and the championship depends on you,
only a crazy selfish person can
took the kick without hesitation.
If that describes you,
go through this door.
Ignore all common sense.
On the field, you are the star.
No one can give you happiness
more than your own goals.
Live only for that moment.
Doesn't that mean
become a striker?
That short guy...
Is it okay?
I will face your stupid game,
you bastard!
Me too!
What is it?
Only the two of you are left.
I'm coming in!
Come on, Nagi!
No, thank you.
That sounds like a hassle.
Hey, come on.
We've come this far.
I don't think I'm cut out for Blue Lock,
and I'm sure I will
soon get bored and want to go home.
Oh? What am I talking about?
make you bored?
Yes.
Because...
...I can easily imagine
scored the winning goal in the World Cup.
You don't know what your ego is yet.
There are so many people who
called a "genius" like you in this world.
I'm not attracted to narcissistic people
who want to grow old without getting hurt.
Go and live a comfortable life
then rot.
Lock it up.
Okay.
That's bullshit!
Nagi is not a fake genius
that you can find anywhere.
What?
We both...
We can do it!
You two?
There can't be two
the "best" in the world.
So, I will make him
as the best striker in the world.
That's my ego!
Wait, Reo.
I said I don't want to...
Up to you.
You shut up!
Trust me, Nagi.
I will show you
more interesting life...
...rather than taking a nap
or playing video games.
I won't let you get bored.
Okay, then promise me one thing.
GAME OVER
Stay with me till the end.
What does it mean?
Is that your ego?
That's a promise, Reo.
Yes, Nagi.
I promise.
Let's start?
There is no place in the world where
the football is more intense than...
...at Blue Lock.
BLUE LOCK
They took my phone.
You should stop playing video games.
for the time being, Nagi.
Oh, hi.
Isn't that the genius duo.
I lost to you that time,
but that was because I was careless.
Let's finish it here forever.
Who's he?
I don't really remember.
I am a star player from
great team that miraculously...
...you guys beat
in your debut match!
How could you forget?
I'm ready to destroy dreams
rich kid to pieces.
Oh yes.
I remember quite well.
Hey, Nagi!
There's something strange here.
There's a weirdo here!
Wow!
Ghost with upside down feet!
Someone, help me.
I'm going to suffocate!
You realize this is the bottom, right?
Oh, he's right.
Of course.
I know it.
That was a nice refresher.
It was a pre-release.
TSURUGI ZANTETSU
You are absolutely lying.
Your English is also a mess.
Hello. It's finished changing,
uncut diamond?
People who share a room
with you is your roommate...
...and the competitors that will
help you grow.
Your abilities have been measured
and I have rated it...
...according to my decision
which is arbitrary and biased.
That is what is symbolized by
the numbers on your uniforms.
Huh. That's pretty low.
Highest ranked player
in this room is...
Two-four-one.
...that person.
Your ranking may change based on
your training or match results.
And the top five players will get
unconditional playing opportunity...
...in the tournament held
the next six months.
They will be registered as
striker for the U-20 World Cup.
Are you serious?
Besides that,
whoever loses in Blue Lock...
...will never play
for Japan.
What you need to get here
is ego.
Now I will test you to measure.
So, it's time to play tag.
You have 136 seconds.
Whoever gets hit by the ball
is "he".
Whoever is "him"
when time runs out it will be locked.
Besides that,
don't use your hands.
BLUE LOCK RANKING
NAMEOKA RYO
I am "he"?
This is amazing.
If you make it into the top five,
You're in the U-20 squad?
This is an opportunity
once in a lifetime.
Geez.
You talk like the main character.
What an idiot.
You two will lose to me
and go straight home!
Oh, damn!
I'll kick one of you
come out and destroy that "genius duo"!
Give your best effort!
Hey, Reo. Is that okay?
If you deliberately give in?
Against these people?
That must be more difficult.
Yes, you died.
Throughout Heaven and Earth,
only "I am the Foremost"!
Huh?
What? And you mean by that
"Dear."
He has explosive acceleration.
Sorry, but I win, audience.
What are you actually doing?
Who "masters" it,
he is the loser!
What?
Is it true?
Uh, yeah, that's right.
I know it.
He doesn't understand the rules.
Idiot! What a natural idiot!
So he's a know-it-all and
like to talk big?
Yes, he is stupid.
Those who call
other people are idiots...
They are the real idiots!
Wow, he's so upset.
The most dangerous bow...
...the one that slides the lowest!
I think you mean is a "branch".
I'm aiming at it.
BLUE LOCK RANKING
NAGI SEISHIRO
Nice shot!
That idiot hit the nail on the head!
Hey!
Don't call me an idiot!
You're not bad, Tsurugi Zantetsu.
So I'm the "him", huh?
Wow, what a hassle.
Nagi?
So, you finally start getting ready.
Don't call me an idiot again.
I can choose anyone, right, Reo?
In that case,
I won't do anything.
I will lose and go home.
What's wrong with this guy?
He had forgotten about it.
This kid is giving me a headache.
BLUE LOCK RANKING
MIKAGE REO
Yeah, I knew you would, Reo.
You take care of the rest.
I don't have time to relax here.
- Run!
- Hey, don't crowd together!
Spread out, you idiots!
- Of course!
- He was starting to get desperate.
Scream as much as you want.
- You guys gathered as planned.
- Hey, move!
- You're blocking my way.
From that reflection, I will
aiming in the direction they were running,
then, hit one!
It's from Reo for you.
Very good.
Yes!
BLUE LOCK RANKING
TSURUGI ZANTETSU
You again, idiot!
Oh, I see.
So, if I win...
...you are all idiots!
Oh no, you won't win!
Hurry up!
Fake kick?
Huh?
But it's a wall.
Here he is...
...random kicks,
"about anyone"!
Unlucky.
It's about me.
No, I can't let it go.
If Reo comes home, I'm in trouble.
You promised, remember?
That you will stay with me.
He avoided her...
BLUE LOCK RANKING
NAMEOKA RYO
Wow, that means
I can't go home yet.
Nagi, damn it. I know you're trying.
looking for an excuse to go home.
Oh, you can tell, huh?
If he refuses, I can go home.
while pretending to have tried it.
What a lazy person.
Nonetheless...
Thank you, Nagi.
Huh?
What for?
That's enough.
That's amazing.
Especially the trio Nagi Seishiro, Mikage Reo,
Tsurugi Zantetsu,
which may be the level
above high school students.
This is just the beginning.
Just an entrance exam.
The real test for
survival starts now.
Compete with each other,
like a diamond in the mud.
FIRST SELECTION
Five.
The first selection will involve
five teams in a round robin.
The top two teams will
advance to the second selection,
while the rest will be disqualified.
Exceptions are made for goal scorers
the most of each team will also advance.
An exception is made for printers
The team with the most goals will also advance.
In addition, you will receive
special bonus points for each goal.
Oh, I see.
So we have to print
10 goals to get...
...permission "One day outside Blue Lock"
to get out of this place.
No, idiot. You misunderstood.
That means we have to
win the match...
...five team round robin
with this team.
It was a pleasure working with you, Team V.
Huh.
Hello, uncut diamond.
Your match against
Team Y is about to start.
You will prioritize your own goals
or team victory?
A striker's karma is tested
on this first option.
This is a fight about
creating football from scratch.
BL RANK = 255
BL RANK = 254
Are you ready for action, Nagi?
How can I being lazy?
FIRST KICK
The legend begins.
I will show you
Mikage Reo specifications.
No matter what strategy
they use, I can directly...
I'll take it!
What are you doing?
We are on the same side!
The rules say
The highest scorer will advance.
Who cares whether the team wins or not?
Best striker...
That's me!
Unlucky.
I get what you mean.
By destroying each other
the ego of the strikers,
they test individual strength.
That's the gist of this first option.
Now it gets interesting, Blue Lock.
Thanks for the ball.
I'm not a fan of the style
the wrestling fighting game.
He deliberately defended and waited for the ball
just get out without a fight?
The boy with bangs was superior.
But...
I'm more than that because I hunted him.
Thanks for the ball.
No, thank you!
Damn it.
Zantetsu, you idiot!
You still call me that,
Mikage Reo?
He is really very fast.
And complete it with a pose that
looks cool and smart.
Hey, listen.
Want me to be a goalkeeper?
Huh?
Damn it.
That was my hat trick.
I win.
Hey, why are you so relaxed, Nagi?
Look, it's like a hammock.
Very comfortable.
I mean,
our team will win, right?
Congratulations, Reo.
Of course,
but it's not completely...
Oh, I know. Hey, Nagi.
Do you want your phone back?
Hmm? Of course.
I want to play my game.
So, score three goals.
With your goal bonus points
can get it back.
Huh?
Can you do that?
In that case...
That's it, Nagi.
I'll leave the rest to you, genius.
Here he is.
I will stop you.
I'm the one who will score the goal!
Mobile.
Video games.
Three more goals...
Good.
I've stopped you.
Are you afraid, lazy?
A hammock, please.
Huh?
Bicycle kick?
What the hell...
How could he react?
like that?
He's like a trickster character.
So, he's the genius Nagi Seishiro?
An unreasonable egoist,
cruel, and lazy.
Mobile.
Video games.
Two more goals.
PUBLIC BATHROOM, BUILDING 5
How to clean your body without any hassle
Nagi Seishiro style.
Wet your whole body.
Rinse everything at once.
Finished.
DON'T RUN
OR JUMP IN THE BATH
I got my phone back,
so I don't have to try hard anymore.
Good grief!
Don't brush your teeth in the bathtub.
That's dirty.
Oh, sorry.
That's our family motto.
Even if you forget the ceremonial event,
don't forget to brush your teeth.
That's a stupid sounding saying.
My parents are dentists.
Wow.
You have intelligent blood.
Yes, they are all smart,
except me.
So you're like the mutants that are often called
idiot by your family growing up?
No.
My family is very kind to me.
Good-hearted smart people who don't
calling a stupid person an idiot.
Another saying that sounds stupid.
Those are my words.
As you said, people
around me always make fun of me.
What an idiot!
But when I realized that
I am a fast runner,
I decided to make
the world of sports as my home.
Become a great soccer player.
Become a professional player.
Becoming a striker
best in the world.
And become an idiot
the most respected in the world.
That's my dream.
Huh.
You're pretty cool.
Nagi Seishiro,
why do you play football?
Hmm...
I just followed Reo here.
So I don't have any big dreams
like you.
You just "go along"?
What's so great about that person?
Who knows.
Maybe because he was the first person
who is interested in a man like me,
who considers everything bother.
You're a weirdo.
Yeah, I hear that a lot.
But you're not a bad person.
Thank You.
If you think this is not your expertise,
why don't you just do it
what does Reo say for now?
He is very smart.
If this person believes in him,
maybe I will try it.
No, as long as I'm here!
Alright, Mikage Reo.
Show me what you've got!
Here, huh?
End the game
here and now, Zantetsu!
Just do it, Dentist.
Maybe the days when I was teased...
...and do nothing
unless running is not a waste of time.
There was a man who
think I'm cool.
And a man who understands how
make the most of me.
Blue Lock...
...very pleasant!
Ah.
They panicked.
Unlucky!
Fed to me?
Wow, you look so excited.
Anyway,
Blue Lock is indeed troublesome.
TEAM V WINS
GOAL DIFFERENCE
POINTS
NEXT GAME
Easy win.
Team X is not threatening at all.
Let's score a goal, Nagi.
Yes, yes.
Oh.
Sorry, Nagi!
I'm so complacent!
Okay, give it back...
King Barou.
TEAM X: BAROU SHOUEI
I think what you mean is,
"Please return it."
You are a slave
who is waiting for orders.
A slave?
Zantetsu, let's surround him!
Okay.
We'll lock it down!
Damn. He's aiming for the place we're at.
leave it as we move?
That's a blind spot that
only you can go...
...if you have strong insight
and a high soccer IQ.
He's not just a selfish player!
Is it still easy to win, Donkey?
I'm not a slave.
I'm Reo's partner.
Correct.
We are the best partner!
Are you satisfied with the goal?
something as boring as that?
Up to you.
A goal is still a goal.
I don't care whether
it's boring or not.
As expected
from the lower class, you are trash.
What does it mean?
Your goal is a slave's goal,
controlled by
that purple haired master.
You are a parasite that cannot
survive alone.
Listen, puppet slave.
A striker
who rose to the top of the world...
He will be alone until he died.
I'd rather die than
submit to others.
A slave?
I?
Don't mind him.
Even if one person disappears in this world,
the tyrannical system will collapse.
Now, let's score one more goal.
and end this game.
Hi, Nagi!
What do you want?
This slave is ready.
Okay, okay.
Amaze them, genius.
This person...
Controlling it with his heel
just to show off?
Is this...
...still boring?
I will kill you.
Hey, that's a violation!
Penalty!
Geez.
Dropped by a slave?
Your reign as king has ended.
Full time of the match
eighth Building five Blue Lock.
Team V wins, 5-2!
Hi, Nagi.
It was a very difficult goal for
someone who doesn't want to bother.
Is that for me too?
Huh?
Not really.
Good work.
"Can't be bothered"?
Seriously.
He is very selfish.
Next time we meet, I will make it
you as my slave, punk!
BUILDING FIVE CANTEEN
I'm Kuon Wataru. I'm going to play.
with you in the next game.
Do you want to make a deal?
Wow, I'm tired.
Seriously, why am I even trying?
so loud today?
Up to you.
Just thinking about it is troublesome.
Simply put, I'm giving you the info.
about your next opponent, Team Z,
and you can't give up
and win the match.
Or rather...
What's wrong with this guy?
He looked very determined.
So what do you think?
Why not work with me?
I refuse.
That sounds like a hassle.
It's so boring.
Whatever, Reo. I don't want to
bother with this deal.
I mean, chewing becomes tiring.
Let's go back now.
Carry me.
Nagi. I invited you here.
because you said you were hungry.
Excuse me.
Too much trouble.
You're going to let this steak
wasted?
Hm. But eating the rest makes me
looks like a fool, doesn't it?
Wait!
What should I do?
Hey, Reo.
Why is that person so insistent?
He wants to win.
Mm, very tasty.
Huh. So you can't win.
unless you try your hardest?
Being weak sounds bother.
I'd better stop playing.
Hey, Reo.
Is football really fun?
to do even if you lose?
Hey, wait a minute.
Who are you?
Don't underestimate football!
TEAM Z: ISAGI YOICHI
The man from earlier.
I said, who are you?
I'm Isagi Yoichi from Team Z.
I am the one who will defeat you!
CHANGING ROOM BUILDING FIVE
TIME UNTIL MATCH:
Let's go, Nagi.
Yes.
Since I came to Blue Lock,
something feels strange.
Why am I trying so hard?
Because with Reo,
I'm being underestimated?
Because that person annoys me?
This is the final match.
We have not experienced a single defeat
in the round robin stage, so we're already through,
But Team Z's survival
depends on this match.
But of course, we will try
do your best to win.
Okay. "Don't say hello until
you came out of the womb." Okay?
It means "Don't say hello until
you came out of the log."
Wow, this is bothering me.
Okay, this is the last match.
from the first selection!
Don't say hello until you get out
from the womb! Don't say hello!
What a hassle.
So the weakest team tries
beat us, the strongest team?
Okay,
give your best effort, Team Z.
Hey, wait.
There are only ten of you?
I See Mr. Traitor
sitting in the corner there.
If we win, he's the scorer
their most goals scored so far,
so only he will survive.
I think he'll just sit here.
FIRST KICK
So, Team Z, let's see what
owned by the bottom ranked team.
Go ahead, Zantetsu.
Show them your weapons.
My weapon.
I will cook you on my stove!
But if they interfere...
To Nagi!
But, my friend, I'm sure everyone
here likes to play football.
Igaguri!
Yes!
Get the ball, Isagi!
Look how insistent they are.
Thank you!
Of course!
Let's do it!
What does football mean to these people?
Is this a dream?
Is this life for them?
Just kick it, Gagamaru.
Unlucky!
So close!
Once again!
Wow!
This is so interesting!
Hey, Nagi!
Let's try that move!
Huh?
That sounds like a hassle.
What does football mean to me?
Just accompanying Reo?
Activities to pass the time?
I don't know.
That is easy.
I don't know,
why can't you do that.
Great goal, Nagi!
Just as I imagined!
Reo, can I relax now?
Not yet.
Five more goals and you can relax.
Ah. How about four?
It was just one goal.
It's time for us
to attack! Namusan!
We have to do this.
- Kunigami!
- Yes.
You're still not in
shooting range, right...
Kunigami Gains?
Stand!
I won't let you!
Ready for another goal, Nagi?
Same drama as before?
Stop him, Raichi and Igaguri!
I'll press it!
That trick won't work
for the second time!
What is a striker?
What is a goal?
Is winning really that important?
It's troublesome to think like this,
but I can't help myself.
Are you serious?
What the heck is that?
That's not a joke.
I really feel a little bit
not feeling well at the moment.
This is bad.
The score is already 2-0!
Our plan will not work Now!
Go, Chigiri!
Yes!
Wing side!
Get the ball!
Well done, Zantetsu!
I will be there!
He will pass the ball to Nagi!
Damn it!
I will also step down!
If this is the case...
Come on, Zantetsu.
This is your territory, right?
Step back, Naruhaya!
Yes, this is my territory.
Reo...
What does "territory" actually mean?
Wearing fake glasses
won't make you smart, you know.
Stupid Zantetsu.
We can still do this.
But ami ...bow...
Okay, done.
In the end, whoever
we face it, the result is the same.
So, in the end,
they are no different.
Damn. I still haven't found it.
the answer.
I like it.
This is getting more fun.
TEAM Z: BACHIRA TEACHER
What's wrong with that guy?
Who knows.
Bachira, what are you talking about?
Huh? I mean,
isn't that trio amazing?
I'm so excited!
Huh? We lost 3-0!
At this rate, we'll never...
Wait, Isagi.
Don't tell me you're scared.
Of course, their goal was very special.
But the solution is clear.
We need to...
...become very special too!
What...
If weapons and formulas don't work at the moment
we use it to the maximum,
then if we manage to score a goal
against them,
it will happen when we have
beyond our limits, right?
The monster inside me said,
we should be happy, not afraid,
when we are in a desperate situation.
You are attractive.
Let's do it, Bachira Meguru!
Okay!
I'll run past you!
Super fast steps?
Pretend to the left,
but you're moving to the right, right?
Some kind of roulette?
Zantetsu!
Oh no, Blunt Bangs!
Speeding up specifications!
If so...
A lob kick?
If we both do it,
I will benefit.
Outside.
So he went left.
- Please wait?
- Zoom in!
An elastic air?
Wow, it worked!
Wow, my inspiration is endless!
Wow, this guy is crazy.
Excuse me!
There's a madman coming in!
Only three more and I will
score a goal!
You three, block him!
I like this.
We are here to be
the best striker in the world.
If I can't beat you, that means
my level is just an ordinary striker.
Three more.
Two...
One...
Boom!
Damn it!
Don't mess with...
Ah, yes, Bachira!
Rabona kick?
Very cool!
Did you see my super special goal?
Look?
Now it's starting to get fun, right?
Exciting?
I never felt like playing
Football is a fun thing.
They seem to have feelings,
uh..."complacent"?
The word you want is
"friendship."
Silly Zantetsu.
He's attractive.
We must destroy him fully.
Wow, that sounds like a hassle.
Come on, let's print another one!
Yes!
Just look at them,
everything is exaggerated like that.
They bowed their heads
when I came out a minute ago.
Hmm?
Are you angry, Reo?
Not really.
It's just that, ever since Nagi and I started
played football six months ago,
our record is unblemished,
and I don't want any stains there.
Raichi, block Reo!
What?
Why should I do it?!
With your physicality,
we can corner him!
I can't play
my sexy football in this position.
Okay, I'll do it, punk!
But if we lose, I will curse
your descendants until the end of time!
The vengeful type is unpopular
among women, Shark Teeth.
Is it possible!
I can't let my career go
my football is over...
...with me being a defender
in a match like this!
Could these people be
have the answer?
Zantetsu!
Leave it to me.
The answer to what's been bothering me.
The bait missed!
The answer to why I can't
restrain yourself from wanting to relax.
Igaguri?
I stopped him, damn it!
BL RANK = 268
Tch.
Stop him!
Don't let him be
within shooting range!
Give it to me, Kunigami!
Don't be afraid, Kunigami.
Just do it!
You're going to be a superhero, right?
Take it!
FINAL MATCH
BUILDING FIVE
And head straight to Gagamaru!
What are you doing?
You suck!
Return!
Forgive me!
I want to know...
Don't underestimate football!
...about the ego of the workers who
gather at this Blue Lock.
The match went according to plan
with your prediction, Ego.
Yeah, it was intense.
Win or lose.
Life or death.
Every time that line is crossed,
a striker is forced to wake up.
This is what I want to see.
Anri, do you know what
what does it mean to wake up?
Huh? Um, does that mean changed?
from ordinary to extraordinary,
like Super Sai...
Well, that's it?
Yup, you are very wrong.
That's a ridiculous analogy people make.
who have never tasted success.
Threshold...
Waking up is like
solve the puzzle...
...with thought and
accumulated experience.
You are faced with an extreme situation
to get victory,
and after a lot trial and error,
that's when all the things are needed
to achieve success becomes clear,
and a new ego blossoms.
In short, when you wake up is
when you know who you really are.
You are really useless.
You are so arrogant,
so why don't you kick?
You are so inefficient.
But I mean,
why don't you just give up?
Why are you still here?
come to us?
So, tell me.
What motivates you so much?
Shut up, genius.
I will be there soon
to the good part!
Oh, I got yelled at.
What's wrong with that creature?
Come on, Miss!
Do whatever you want!
TEAM Z: CHIGIRI HYOMA
Just try it, Miss.
I'm faster.
Don't call me "Miss".
You want to compete with me?
What? Zantetsu reaches speed
highest and still lose?
Get out of my way, you slow-witted bastard.
Wow, of course!
We caught up!
What are you guys actually doing?
Aren't you ashamed because
defeated by ten people?
Shut up, you jerk!
Reo is annoyed.
I can't lose here.
Nagi and I should be the best.
Are you that afraid of losing?
You're such a protected human!
I'll give you a little bit of an idea.
your first defeat!
TEAM Z: RAICHI JINGO
This punk again!
Am I...
Did Nagi and I... lose?
I didn't know Reo could
showing a face like that.
Give it to me, Reo.
Nagi?
Huh?
Am I trying too hard again?
Because I thought we were going to lose
for the first time?
Because of the people I consider
That sucks but it looks cool?
I thought I wouldn't be bothered...
Reo.
I will try it.
Nagi?
What happened?
Dribble is one of the weapons?
Before my brain could react,
my body is already moving.
It's to divert attention so that
can he break through my legs?
Imamura, block!
Okay, I do!
And my heart started beating faster
before my body could move.
He didn't look at me.
I wonder what it is
I want to know this.
Shots are coming!
Jump there!
Block the kick!
With football...
...I want to challenge myself!
What do I do?
I'm getting excited, aren't I?
Nagi!
You...
Hi, Reo...
Football is quite fun.
How many more goals will
we want?
Are you idiots?
If we don't rise up and win
in the next 15 minutes,
our story is over!
Keep attacking until you die!
Do your best, idiot!
You guys are strikers, right?
I don't think they're dead yet.
One more goal, Nagi.
One more goal and we can win it.
Okay, boss.
I'll take this one now, Miss.
Not this time, Mr. Genius.
If you want it,
you should be here!
There's something about him
that has changed.
Come on, Chigiri.
Oh my, Isagi.
I'll pat your head later.
Wow, that's great!
It hit the pole?
Okay, I'll take it.
Damn it.
You bastard!
We're not done yet.
I will destroy you all!
Attack in waves?
Exactly as I imagined!
Yes!
This is the fire of those who fight
with everything they have.
This is football.
If I score in the middle
This madness, it feels really great.
Go ahead, Zantetsu.
Against.
I will stop you!
What a pity,
Little Miss Red Hair.
Today, we have a genius
who just woke up!
Good job, Zantetsu.
Nice eyes.
This is it, right?
This guy again?
The weakest point on the pitch at the moment.
We often meet.
You won't be able to escape from me!
He will survive based on
my first touch on the ball.
Right foot?
Or left?
Wow, what should I do?
Improvise.
React.
Using his back?
Good grief.
I did it.
Unlucky!
Stop him!
Wow, see that?
I didn't know I could do that.
It feels so amazing...
Violation by Team Z.
Rejecting a goal scoring opportunity
which is clearly visible.
Red card for Kuon Wataru.
He's out.
Kuon, what are you doing?
Oh, damn.
Now you can continue fighting.
What have you done, you rascal?
Take it easy, Reo!
Are you okay, Nagi?
Reo, I'm fine.
Listen carefully, Bastard.
You have to win.
I will be the attacker
best in the world.
Shut your mouth, Kuon.
That's obvious.
We will win it!
I won't let it happen ends here!
But, Friends,
I was pretty good back then, right?
Seriously, pictures of me
doing something...
...that I didn't even imagine
previously continued to appear without stopping.
It feels strange, but fun.
Football makes me excited.
I can feel myself changing.
Which version of me is this?
what awaits me ahead?
I want to know the answer.
Nagi, are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Three more minutes.
Hey, Reo. You want us to survive.
In what way?
Let us tell you
and count the time.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
- Huh?
Our only choice is destroy them.
A draw against a team like this
is the same as losing.
One more goal.
FREE KICK
Don't get caught doing it
violation, understand?
Protect the goal with your life!
Here, Reo.
Pass it to me.
Please pass it to me.
Huh?
He kicked it himself?
Well, that's how it is.
It seems Reo too secure himself.
There he is!
This is my territory!
Where did you come from, actually?
From the wall.
- Get the ball!
- If I could get it first...
Here he is.
One more goal.
We won.
Not finished yet!
I can see it.
This is our last chance.
Unlucky.
Seriously, what is wrong with these people?
Bachira, come here!
Beat them all
with those feet of yours, Chigiri!
We need more people!
Let's do it!
Chigiri!
Block one or two!
He's going to come down to the middle?
Is he...
Come on!
That's the most dangerous place.
No shots fired
mid-range for you!
If the ball goes out,
our story is over!
I told you to score a goal, right?
I will kill you!
Go away, you idiot!
And he's the craziest person.
Come on!
Give it to me!
Be careful in the middle!
Don't let him kick!
Stop him!
Is that the place, selfish?
Perfect, Bachira.
We meet often, don't we?
Right now, you are the most important person
dangerous in this field.
He will get the ball first.
But he always takes the ball
before shooting,
to put it in position
what he wants.
So, I'm going to steal it.
at the time.
Then, I will launch
counterattack again...
...and win
this match with my goal.
Give it to me, Isagi Yoichi.
I will swallow your football
with fire and everything.
You can't beat me.
No!
I want to...
Direct shot?
I know what I see at the time.
It's light.
Yes!
It was a moment of rebirth.
Reo!
We still have time.
If we score two more goals,
we can still...
Nagi...
Time has run out.
Team Z won, 5-4.
Okay!
Oh, damn.
It disappeared.
These are stressful times
It is over.
I could be reborn here.
The reason I'm so excited,
my goal, my intensity,
all of that...
Isagi Yoichi stole it from me.
Hi, Reo.
This is what it feels like to lose after
serious fight, right?
It's hard to accept.
First selection at this time
has been completed in all buildings.
For those who have graduated,
put on your training gear,
and immediately come to the basement area
in the center of your building.
We will start the second selection.
This is getting interesting.
It seems the "genius"
has raised his ego.
SECOND SELECTION, STAGE ONE
FORM OF A TEAM CONSISTING OF
FROM THREE PEOPLE AND DO
Oh.
Hey, good job, Nagi.
You made it through
the first stage too, huh?
Good work!
The second stage requires
a team of three people.
Who else should we choose?
Okay, that's better.
I wait until...
...someone who wants to
work with me appears.
Hmm? Okay, okay.
Are you talking about Zantetsu?
Well, um...
Will he be angry?
If I tell him?
I'll tell you when he's here.
Oh, hi, Isagi here.
Thank you!
Good grief!
United again!
Good work.
Congratulations on having
clearing the stage.
Uh, Nagi?
Hi, Isagi Yoichi.
Want to join our team?
Huh?
Come join our team.
Hey, Nagi. Is this the person you want?
you invite to cooperate?
Yes.
In the match against his team,
he looked most impressive.
I want to play football
with him.
Okay, you heard it.
Now what?
Do you accept the offer?
Of course not.
I will work with you, Bachira.
Sorry, Nagi.
But I can't accompany you alone.
There he is.
Oh, I see...
So...
I will join Isagi's team.
What?
Huh?
That solves the problem, right?
What...
What are you talking about, Nagi?
You have to cooperate with me.
It's a must.
What do you think?
What about me?
Don't make that face.
Reo, You taught me football.
You and I will be
the best in the world.
That is for sure.
But we lost.
We are not the strongest.
I really enjoy socializing
with you, Reo.
You are not a bother and
I can be myself around you.
Plus, it's fun.
But the dream you showed
to me about being...
...the best in the world ends
at the time.
To understand the feeling of frustration
which I experienced for the first time,
I want to play football
with him.
So that I can dream one more time
be the best in the world with you.
I really want to give
everything.
Are you serious?
Do what you want.
What do you think, Isagi?
Come on.
Choose me, selfish.
Join us, Nagi.
FORM OF A TEAM CONSISTING OF
FROM THREE PEOPLE AND DO
ISAGI YOICHI, BACHIRA TEACHER,
NAGI SEISHIRO
PROCEED TO THE THIRD STAGE OF ISAGI
YOICHI, BACHIRA MEGURU, NAGI SEISHIRO
See you later, Reo.
I will wait for you on the other side.
I'm looking forward to it, Nagicchi!
Yeah, me too.
He looked a little sad.
Are you actually a cold person?
Huh? I guess I'd be lying if I said that.
I said I didn't lose him.
But I know,
I will meet him again.
But I'm more excited to
join you two.
Shouldn't it be
I follow that aspect of my ego?
That's where the Blue Lock comes in.
Who we both are now
is not good enough.
Nagi, let's work together.
Yes, let's do it.
We will change, become stronger,
and meet again.
All my life,
all my life...
I always get whatever
what I want.
So he...
The genius is...
...the first thing that can't be done
I have had it since I was born.
Damn it.
But you know, Nagi...
To be honest,
I could tell at that moment.
That you are fascinated by football
and get excited.
That you have realized
your own talent.
And watching you learn the meaning of frustration
After losing to Isagi, I...
It's hard to accept.
I'm actually happy.
But it wasn't me who changed you.
And if I'm honest with myself,
I feel like I can't be by your side anymore.
So I closed my eyes to my excitement
alone and hide it.
I want to play football with him.
With your sparkling eyes
like a child,
you try to change and move forward.
And I can't just say...
Of course, Nagi.
You just continue.
Let's meet on the other side of the dream.
I thought you would never come back
to me if I may say so.
I thought our dreams would disappear
just like that.
I was scared, alone, and weak.
I wish I never knew...
...how painful it is
seeing someone change.
STAGE THREE
SECOND CHOICE
This person...
...really very strong.
ITOSHI RIN
Nagi!
Stop him!
Come on, you cheating monster.
MATCH
Like I said, it's all over,
half-baked amateur base.
Dribbling the ball. Kicking.
Intelligence in playing football.
In each parameter,
he is 200 out of 100.
He's not human, right?
In the third stage,
Three-on-three Competition Fight,
The Red Team won, 5-2.
We lost.
Very interesting.
What do you want to do,
Tokimitsu Rin?
The rules state we can
steal one if we win.
I don't care. It won't.
make any difference.
Even though I work with Isagi,
I lose...
Um, Aryu,
I think we should choose it.
It is such a coincidence.
I want it too.
Join us...
Bachira Meguru.
Let's move.
Don't fall asleep, Bob Cut.
Your future is in my hands.
Wow, I want to be on Isagi's team
until the end.
Bachira.
That's a promise, Reo.
Yes, Nagi.
I promise.
I think I'll go.
That's the rule.
But I won't wait for you, Isagi.
If you want me,
come and meet me.
Hey, Reo, listen.
There are much better players
from me and Isagi.
The situation couldn't get any worse,
and if we lose, our history is over.
And for some reason,
I think I'm having fun.
I can feel myself changing.
I don't want to go home yet.
I want to play more football.
I want to win.
I want to be stronger.
If I don't come to Blue Lock,
I will never know
I can be like this.
If I hadn't met you,
I will never
finding this new me.
Hi, Reo.
When we meet again...
...there are so many who want to
I tell you.
I didn't know that change could...
...very interesting.
SECOND STAGE,
COMPETITION MATCH: 2 VS 2.
TIME UNTIL MATCH:
Of course, we are playing you.
That's why I work together
with them, you know.
Hey, listen, Reo.
You and me now
is the enemy, Nagi.
You didn't choose me,
so I will destroy you.
NEW BL RANK = 10
FIRST TEAM
RIN, ANTOU, TOKIMITSU, HARAKU, KIYOSHI
SECOND TEAM
NAGI, MAROU, CHIGIRI, KENJOU, Seira
THIRD TEAM
FOURTH TEAM
FIFTH TEAM
SIXTH TEAM
SEVENTH TEAM
RANKING TEN
MIKAGE REO
NEW BL RANK = 111
Well, let's just say
many things have happened,
and plans have changed.
It seems that Japanese football officials
want to close Blue Lock and immediately.
So I decided to challenge them.
In that way, the next selection will be
done in three weeks...
...and the future of Blue Lock
depend on it.
This is going to be a special big match
between the Japan U-20 team and the Blue Lock XI.
And if you win the game,
we will hijack the Japanese U-20 team.
A genius can't be a genius
with his own abilities.
A genius can only be recognized when
there are people who find their genius.
JAPAN U-20 NATIONAL TEAM VS BLUE LOCK XI
Listen carefully,
a diamond in the rough.
The world doesn't know you yet.
Change your destiny in the next 90 minutes.
Carve your ego into the world today.
Of course!
Understand.
Yes, Sir.
So true!
Come on, Nagi.
I'll be there soon.
Nagi.
Show us what
that you have, genius.
Yes.
Just wait.
This is the world's stage.
Challenging our fate.
This is our new beginning.
Pay attention to me, Reo.
The fire inside me.
My ego.
Nice to meet you, Japan.
I...
Nagi Seishiro.
NAGI EPISODE
BLUE LOCK THE MOVIE
Blue Lock. Extra time.
EXTRA TIME
GAME OVER
Yeah... it's been a long time since I spoke.
with anyone.
That's not good, right?
But humans are annoying,
so I'm going to look for a pet.
WELCOME!
Excuse me,
give me the least troublesome one.
Huh...?
Okay. Let's get started.
Hmm, I'll call you, hmm...
Let's choose "Choki".
Good evening, Choki.
Did you see that?
That's a perfect header shot, right?
I want to go.
Greetings of peace.
This is my cactus, Choki.
If I don't come back for a while
some time, please just water it.
Mrs. Ba-ya.
Okay.
Huh! I don't know
You take care of plants, Nagi!
Yes, I want to have someone
who can be talked to at home.
Oh, don't flush too much water.
It's good to water it once
every two or three weeks.
You can let it be
just like that.
Is that so... "Be careful, don't let it happen
like it too much."
Is it the same as you, Mr. Seishiro?
Sorry, I don't follow...
Don't mind it.
Now, please,
take good care of Mr. Reo.
Okay, I'll do my best.
See you. Peace be upon you.
Hey! Come on, Nagi!