Stop right there!
Stop!
Huajun, there're Hun soldiers!
Lady, stand behind me.
Fight no more and come back with us.
Brother.
What is going on?
Let's talk after we survive this.
Look out!
Watch it!
It's over now.
Lady, what was it about?
I run out of arrows.
What to do?
Go get her.
Stop chasing!
Brother, the Huns will be here soon.
Lady, back to you.
You'd better leave.
What about you?
No need to worry about us.
Take my horse.
He runs fast.
His name is Lei Zhen.
Be careful.
Take care.
Why holding a dandelion?
My knight,
thank you for rescuing me.
Mengyun is grateful.
Do you like dandelions?
Beautiful.
For you.
Professor.
Check it out.
Here is the genetic report
of the war horse.
It was a warm-blooded horse.
No wonder.
The size of the horse is so big.
Wang Jing.
What have you got?
Professor.
Part of the war horse
has been excavated.
According to the bridle nose piece
and the saddle,
my assumption is
a mount of a cavalry general
of the Western Han Dynasty.
Strange.
The totem and relief carving of
the mask on this jade pendant
were common in Hunnic culture.
How did such a precious
Hunnic jade pendant
end up on the horse
of the Han people?
Could it be part of the spoils?
It's possible.
Either this jade pendant
was seized by the Han army,
or this war horse
was seized by Huns.
How about...
Look so much alike.
What look alike?
Just now I saw in my dream
a very handsome guy,
but you are not manly like he.
I also dreamed of
a very beautiful woman.
That had to be me.
Don't fool yourself.
Didn't you have something for him?
Go get it.
Hurry up. We don't have time.
Go.
Professor.
Keep working
on the remains of the horse.
I will take this back to the office.
No problem, professor.
Oh yes.
Professor.
Xinran in order to buy you this gift
spent eight hours travelling
back and forth to town downhill.
You wasted that much working time.
Just give it to me.
I'll transfer the money back to you.
If you hadn't overworked
yourself so much,
would I bother to get this for you?
Xinran, I have something
for you too.
What is it?
Take it.
Professor, lunch is on the table
in the lab.
Don't forget to eat it!
I know.
What did he give you?
What else
but lab test list.
One way love is hard.
He really doesn't
care about me, right?
It's easy for a woman
to chase after a man.
How easy?
Look at you.
You wear the same
set of clothes everyday.
Why don't you dress up a little?
Why should I dress up
in an excavation site?
Besides,
I don't think he is that shallow.
Oh yes.
Don't buy me facial masks anymore.
When I put it on my face, it's so
sticky that makes me feel terrible.
Hydration is good for the skin.
Also, Wang Jing's friend
invites us to dinner tonight.
This jade pendant
is a symbol of the sanctuary.
The greatest value of the sanctuary
is not the treasure in it.
Rather, it guards the world's
purest and most virtuous land
that holds our ancesters' and gods'
blessings.
It will bestow blessing upon you.
Thank you, my Great Shaman.
I hope you will become my successor.
These are for the benediction
of father's wellness.
My Great Shaman, please bring
them back to the sanctuary.
Dear crown prince, consider it done.
Move on.
Move.
Quickly.
Go.
One by one.
Dear father.
Big brother.
I...
raided the Han people
and took their gold and silk.
I slaughtered everyone in the city.
I also beheaded
the general guarding the fort
and brought it back
as a gift for father.
You rendered outstanding service
this time.
As your father,
how should I reward you?
Father,
I want nothing,
but only wish father would
allow Mengyun
to become my wife.
Mengyun?
Father.
Father has already
granted her to your brother.
How about...
all the Han women you took back...
Father.
Grants them all to you.
What do you think?
Yes.
I will do what father says.
Good.
Father is not well.
You should get some rest now.
Now I will excuse myself.
You get some rest.
Big brother.
You always massacre
the people you subdued.
It is too ruthless.
I'm afraid the Han people
will retaliate.
It will bring disasters
to our people.
I thank the crown prince
for his guidance.
Mother, wait for me
at the agreed place.
I will come and join you.
Let's leave now together.
I must avenge my father.
Let me do it.
Go now.
Be careful.
My daughter.
You killed my father.
I feel deep remorse
for what happened in the past,
but what I did afterwards
was out of love
for you and your mother.
My time
is running out.
Go ahead and do it.
Leave now.
I can still intercede for you.
Think of your mother.
Help.
Father.
Please forgive me.
Big brother.
Father.
What's wrong with father?
Big brother.
This is the crown prince
of your choice.
Let him go.
For you,
I fought battles and risked my life.
But he...
Bit the dust just like that.
You monster.
My son.
Back then the Great Shaman
made a prophecy of divination,
saying I could never become king.
But my dear father,
how come you believe in a prophecy
rather than believe in me?
I'm sorry, father.
I am not being a good son.
Yet
I do this
for our tribes.
Assassin.
Bring Mengyun back.
Professor.
He is my friend, Lei Zhen.
He organizes tonight's party.
Thank you.
The least I can do.
Your huge discovery
is definitely worth celebrating.
My company has developed a new game
called "The Legend of Han and Hun".
Interesting.
When I was in Beijing,
I went to your lecture
on "Wars between Han and Hun".
It inspired me to develop the game.
You are my mentor.
Professor Fang.
Director Wang, how are you?
Please let me introduce.
This is the boy
who discovered the jade pendant,
Baitula, our young friend.
- So pleased to know you.
- Professor, how are you?
Because of you,
we discovered
the horse of an officer
under Western Han dynasty
general Huo Qubing.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
He and his family
handed the jade pendant
to the government.
It's a truly commendable act.
I will give you many 'likes'.
By the way, professor,
your application to continue
research on this artifact
has already been approved.
Please sign here.
Thanks.
And we will put part of the artifact
at the museum for public exhibition.
Professor, please come at the time.
Yes, for sure.
Professor,
I especially want to
join your team to learn more.
I also want to hire you
as history advisor for our game.
Well...
This is something
I specially arranged
for everyone to enjoy.
Xinran?
Lady, your dancing with the sword
was really breathtaking.
I wonder if my bow
can be wielded the same way.
Probably not.
Why are you here?
My mother and I
planned to meet here,
but she hasn't shown up yet.
Please pardon me.
Greetings to Great Shaman.
Rise.
Huduna captured your mother.
He uses her as his leverage
to get you into marrying him.
The last thing your mother wants
is for you to repeat her tragedy.
She is my mother.
I must go back and save her.
It seems that
I chose the right heir.
You alright?
Dear knights,
Mengyun still has matters
to attend to.
I will bid farewell now.
Your kindness
will always be remembered
by Mengyun.
You can really sleep.
Everyone's gone.
Professor, I had a dream.
I dreamed of a young man
who looked a lot like you.
I also dreamed of
a very beautiful woman.
The beauty in real life
was so mad at you that she left.
Leave alone that beauty
in your dream.
She dressed up and danced for you,
but you fell asleep.
Go now to see her.
OK, I go now.
Your coat. It's cold up there.
OK, thank you, professor.
Xinran, here you are.
You finally woke up.
It's so cold up here.
Xinran, I didn't realize
you could dance so well.
Well, you watched?
I was watching.
Surely, with a loud snoring?
Xinran.
Actually without glasses
and in a skirt,
you look really good.
You are so shallow.
Did you use the facial masks
I bought you?
Oh, those were facial masks?
Did you look at the other things?
Work has been busy lately.
So...
I forgot.
I often wonder
other than work in your mind
could you think of anything else?
Such as?
Such as
caring about the people around you.
OK, I'll pay more attention to it
in the future.
Since the Qin Dynasty,
the Huns had repeatedly invaded
China's mainland.
During the reign of
Emperor Wu of Han Dynasty,
Shandan Military Horse Farm
was established.
Since then we had the cavalry force
to fight against the Huns.
Shandan Military Horse Farm
was founded by Huo Qubing, right?
Correct.
What you all see now
is a specimen model
of a Celestial Horse.
I still think only a white horse
is fit for a prince.
Who named you Lei Zhen?
My mother.
What?
Could've been Lei Zhenzi.
Did you know how the word "champion"
becomes widely known?
Please tell us.
Let's hear it from professor.
Seventeen-year-old Huo Qubing
followed his uncle Wei Qing
to fight the Huns
for the first time.
Wei Qing only gave him 800 horsemen.
He went deep
into the enemy territory
straight to the rear of the Huns...
The Huns,
they took my daughter.
Take good care of him.
General,
the Hunnic tribe was found
near the river valley.
March through the night.
We must bring our people back home!
Help!
Please let me go.
Let me go.
Zhao Zhan, Huajun.
You each bring your men.
We will raid them
from three directions
to get them off-guard.
Command received.
Lei Zhen?
What about my mother?
You promised to let her go.
Let's go.
Lei Zhen.
Over there.
Kill them all.
Enemy is here.
Free the people.
Tell me where the sanctuary is.
Only the Great Shaman knows.
The Hans are here.
Guard the king.
Block him.
Lei Zhen.
Hold it.
General's order.
Spare women, children,
elderly and infants.
Those who surrender will live.
Got it.
Come with us.
- Mother.
- My daughter.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Mother.
My daughter.
You must go back to Han land.
Do your best
to live your life.
Mother.
Whoever
surrenders himself to Han Courts
will be treated with mercy.
My father was a Hun general
who pledged allegiance to Han.
King Tudie invaded the city
under his guard
and massacred everyone
including my father.
To ensure my safety,
my mother gave herself
to King Tudie.
She just wanted me to live well.
The best time of my life
was when we two
looked for dandelions.
But now she's gone.
Mengyun,
will you go back
to the garrison with me
and help us train
the horses for battles?
Will you be there?
I will.
Mother.
I can finally go back to Han land.
Zhao Zhan, Hua Jun.
You two went through hardships
and brought back all these stallion
will greatly strengthen our cavalry.
You have done great service
for Han Dynasty.
Your efforts are appreciated.
We only did what we should do.
What a nice Ferghana horse!
Height is good.
Limbs are slender.
Skin is thin.
Face is small and neck is high.
Good horse!
Big brother.
I got a letter from home.
My father found a job for me
at the prime minister's bureau.
When this battle is over,
I will go work there.
You might as well.
Three generations in your family
have held office
in the imperial court.
You are the only son in the family.
People say one should not travel
far from parents' side.
Big brother, ever thought
of starting a family?
Family?
I know not what a family is
since small.
I was born at the frontier.
The Huns
destroyed my family.
As long as the Hun
military threat exists,
there is no talk of
starting a family.
Indeed.
To extinguish such threats
is top priority.
The general is here.
General.
The general has bred excellent
war horses for the country.
We now also have
our own cavalry regiments.
The Huns repeatedly invaded
our Han territory.
We are Han soldiers.
Hun's
repeated offences
must be eliminated.
I believe that in the future
in this land of China,
there will be peace and prosperity.
People will live and work
in peace with contentment.
Huo Qubing built his fame
in this battle
with military achievement
beyond compare.
Emperor Wu named him
"Duke of Champion"
This is how the word "champion"
becomes widely known
Although Huo Qubing
lived a short life
he repeatedly inflicted
heavy losses on the Huns.
For Han Dynasty,
he formed
a superior army of cavalry.
Later, the Han Dynasty
was able to
open up the Hexi Corridor,
and established
the Western Regions Protectorate
to consolidate ruling
over the Xinjiang region.
Huo laid the foundation
for all those to happen.
Professor.
The general on the white horse
doesn't he look like Wang Jing?
Look like Wang Jing?
Not really.
You have only Wang Jing
on your mind.
- Professor.
- No, I...
This is really something.
So many different shapes
of gold nuggets.
This is Horseshoe gold nugget.
You tell me
with all those gold
contributed from Han,
where could the Huns
have stored them?
It is recorded that
Huo Qubing once seized
Hun's golden statue
for worship of Heaven.
Would it be possible
that the gold and treasures
were sent to
Hun's sanctuary for worship?
Up till now, no Hun's sanctuary
has ever been discovered.
However,
since you develop games,
feel free to use your creativity.
Surely I wanted
the treasure hunting element added.
If only you could lead us
to find Hun's sanctuary,
that would be so cool.
Too difficult.
It's so beautiful.
You have good taste.
For this bracelet,
we copy the exact design
and size of the original
to make gold replica souvenir.
Definitely great value for money.
It's perfect for me, isn't it?
Price of gold has risen
so much lately.
Professor.
I have a good friend
who is a shamanic scholar.
It so happens that
he is recently back to China.
He knows shamanic culture
and the history of Hun very well.
He invited us to visit him.
We can talk about the totem
on the jade pendant.
We can surely compare notes.
I will arrange a time.
OK, go ahead.
OK.
What to do next?
- Let's have tea.
- Great.
- Let's go for tea.
- After you.
Gold is expensive.
Forget it.
Let's go.
Yes, too expensive.
What's the fuss?
Professor.
This mask is ok.
Xinran taught me how to use it.
The tacky wet feeling
is uncomfortable.
Professor, can I take it off?
Hydrate your skin is good.
It's gppd for you.
What do you want from me
at this early hour?
I drew a picture
with artificial intelligence.
This is the woman in my dream.
She looks so much like...
Like who?
The one I saw in my dream.
Professor, how can it be possible?
The same person
appeared in our dreams.
Maybe we've been working
on the jade pendant.
We did the same research work,
so we had the same dream.
Professor.
Why do I feel like they are
my memories
of another time and space?
Dreams
are more than the working
of brain's memory system
in our dormant condition.
In fact,
the brain's ability to create
is also functioning.
That's why dreams are also
both fantasy and reality.
A dream is not reality.
We still have to come back
to the real world.
Okay, professor, I'm back.
I have things to do.
Where are you going?
I'll go find Xinran.
Man
should take the initiative.
OK.
Your mask.
Professor, I'll just put it here.
No need to clean up, thank you.
I'm Wang Jing.
What's up?
I have something for you.
No way.
Just a minute.
I will be over right away.
I have something for you.
What?
Here.
It's not a lab test item list
this time?
The price of gold
has risen a lot recently.
I invested some money.
Is it for me?
I'll go now.
Wait.
I...
made coffee.
Do you want some?
No, I already had some
in the morning.
Thanks.
I also have tea.
Black tea, green tea and Oolong tea.
I have all of them.
Tea is bad for sleep at night.
Fruit.
Soft drink.
Biscuits.
Prisoner taken.
Take it.
Let me add some seasoning.
It smells so good.
Mengyun.
I've got something to show you.
What is it?
It's so beautiful.
Do you like it?
This is my family heirloom.
I want to give it to you
before I go to battle.
I can't take something so valuable.
You should give it to the person
you value most.
Can you hold on to it for me?
When I come back from victory,
you give it back to me.
A thing this valuable
must not fall into
the hands of the enemy.
General.
Thank you
for saving my child's life.
Huajun.
Come eat.
We will head out soon.
Let's drink.
- Drink.
- Eat one first.
The wind is blowing.
The clouds are moving.
The wind blows and clouds move.
We conquer and return triumphant.
Where to find warriors
to defend our land.
The wind blows.
The clouds move.
We conquer and return triumphant.
The wind blows.
The clouds move.
We conquer and return triumphant.
Where to find warriors
to defend our land.
The wind blows.
The clouds move.
We conquer and return triumphant.
Where to find warriors
to defend our land.
Professor, we have arrived.
Hello.
Hi.
- Please come in.
- Thank you.
Please wait here.
Mr. Herbert.
The guests are here.
Please sit.
Mr. Herbert.
Archaeologist, Professor Fang.
Wang Jing and Xinran.
Hello, Mr. Herbert.
In our excavation site,
we found this jade pendant.
I was told you were
an expert in shamanism.
I hope you can tell me
more about it.
Thank you.
In shamanic culture,
this is the oldest
seven-star god totem.
Since this jade pendant
was unearthed,
every night the professor and I
dream of the one same person.
But not me.
Besides...
There are objects
that allow us to communicate
with the deceased,
even with the gods.
This shamanic scepter
is an antiquity that I collected
a few years back in Europe.
The crystal on it
also brought me
the same experience like yours.
Similarily,
jade is a medium of communication
with the gods.
All things have spirits.
When life ends,
the spirit is still there.
Jade carries the spirit of the dead.
It uses dreams as a medium
to establish a connection
with the living.
Professor.
Let's meditate together.
Maybe you'll be able to find
the answer you're looking for.
Professor.
Meditate.
Feel the flow of energy
in your brain.
Break the limitations of
time and space.
Expand the realm of your thoughts.
Elevate spiritual wisdom.
Fall asleep already?
General.
We have conquered five Hun tribes
in six days.
Our wounded soldiers
need a few days' time to recover
before they can go on.
General.
You take a rest.
Yes.
Briefing.
General.
Huduna joins forces
with Xiutu and Zhelan tribes.
Near Gaolan Mountain ahead of us
large number of troops have amassed.
How many troops are there?
Tens of thousands.
General.
We are outnumbered.
It's better to avoid
direct confrontation
and take a detour.
General.
We are thousands of miles away
from Han land.
We must pass through
Gaolan Mountain.
If we go around it,
there is Qilian Mountain
on the south.
If we go north,
we will end up in Hun's territory.
When one walks
in the valley of death,
he will have nothing more to lose.
Spread the order.
We regroup ourselves here
Soldiers and horses
must rest and eat well.
Reinforcement must be carried on
day and night.
Orders taken.
We already know
the Huns are not ashamed to flee
or to retreat when suffer losses.
We use the ring pommel
sword regiment
to break up their formation
and inflict as many casualties
as possible.
This is our best tactic to win.
Zhao Zhan.
The ring pommel sword regiment
will be under your command.
Remember.
Huduna must be taken down.
Order taken.
Soldiers.
Whoever is the only son
in the family,
come forward.
Whoever has wife and child,
The rest of you
will become a part of my
ring pommel sword regiment.
In this battle,
the ring pommel sword regiment
under me
will take the lead in the charge.
We are facing our deadly enemy.
The life and death moment
for our Han army has arrived.
I want to join
the ring pommel sword regiment.
We are soldiers
to defend our homeland.
We fight in the battlefield.
We fear not death
and will follow general
to our death.
Follow general to our death.
Let's head out.
This jade pendant
was given to me by the Great Shaman
to keep me safe.
I want to give it to the general.
I am a soldier
for greater part of my life.
To protect our country
and our people
is my only wish.
Please keep this jade pendant
close to you.
Hope it will protect you.
General's wish
will surely be fulfilled.
This jade is like my pure heart.
I just hope it will cast out
all evil for general.
The general's safety
is Mengyun's wish.
Come back safely.
Soldiers.
We are outnumbered in this battle.
Death is hovering over us.
We would rather die in glory
than live in shame.
In this battle,
we shall demonstrate
Han army's majestic power,
so that our enemy
dare not to oppress our people
or invade our land any more.
Gaolan Mountain
will be Han soldiers'
burial ground.
The peace of our country and home
is forged by heroes.
Forged by heroes.
Charge!
Ring pommel sword regiment.
Get around and outflank them.
Attack from both sides.
Shoot arrows.
Shoot.
Move back.
Huduna is defeated.
My lord, should we advance?
Kill them all.
Retreat.
Let's go.
Get into position.
General.
Go get them.
Let's go.
Medic.
General.
Hurry.
Quickly.
General, are you okay?
I am fine.
Medic, hurry up.
Let me take a look.
He is poisoned.
Untie his armor.
The cut is deep.
I have to bandage
your wound right away.
I am fine.
I will go get the herbs and powder.
Hang on.
I will suck the poison out.
This is a special poison
made by the Huns.
Only the Great Shaman
has the antidote.
I can only halt
the spread of poison.
I will immediately go to find
the Great Shaman.
The pendant
you take it.
Let it
keep you safe.
I am counting on you.
General.
Don't move or your wound will open.
I got it.
Big brother.
I can hardly hold out any longer.
You stay with her to protect her.
Sorry to trouble you.
Big brother, say no more.
I will do my best to protect her
and bring the antidote back
to heal you.
Lei Zhen.
Can you still go thru this with me?
I will go with you.
Behind the woods
will be the sanctuary.
Outsiders are not allowed to enter.
Please wait here.
I will come back soon.
Lei Zhen.
You have fulfilled your duty well.
My Great Shaman,
please grant me the antidote!
Child.
Stay here with me.
You two are not meant
for each other in this life.
My only wish is for him to live.
The antidote is only enough
to save one person.
How do you feel?
I've just taken the antidote.
I will be all right soon.
You go back now
to give the antidote to the general.
What about you?
The Great Shaman needs me here.
Huajun.
I return this bracelet to you.
I cannot keep it for you anymore.
Thank you for being kind to me.
You must help me
bring it to the general
to save his life.
Do you understand?
You must get there before sunrise.
Farewell.
Because of him,
you give up your own life.
Is it worth it?
I know you're here
to find the Great Shaman
for an antidote.
Tell me.
Where the sanctuary is?
Today I have to avenge my mother.
Get her.
Mengyun.
You can't die for another man.
If you want to die,
you can only die in my hands.
Sanctuary.
Where the hell is it?
Huajun.
Give the antidote
to the general quickly.
Yes.
Go now.
Come save the general.
Big brother.
I will surely bring
the antidote back to save you.
Mengyun.
I keep my promise to you.
The peace of our country and home
is forged by heroes.
General.
Huajun.
Mr. Herbert.
Is there a glacier up ahead?
Yes.
There is indeed
a ten-thousand-year-old glacier.
Professor.
I think I dreamed about
that place just now.
Can we go there to have a look?
If you want to go,
I can arrange for some local guides
to take you there.
Maybe
you can find the answers
you are looking for.
Thank you, Mr. Herbert.
Let's go.
Professor.
Lei Zhen.
I also had a dream.
I dreamed about Wang Jing and I
surfing on Sanya beach.
- I was wearing a bikini.
- Let's go.
I also...
Wang Jing.
Why are we leaving?
My legs are numb.
Did you dream about anything?
Just when I fell asleep,
you woke me up.
Was I in your dream?
No.
Was I in Wang Jing's dream?
Professor, a very big cave up ahead.
Let's go over there.
Come over, get prepared.
Wang Jing said
you looked good in a skirt,
but this is really too much.
I'm not cold.
Besides, there are
no organs in the legs.
Let's take a look inside.
The cave is so big.
Will there be dangers?
Come on.
These subglacial bubbles
are all methane.
They are highly flammable.
Pay attention to naked flame.
Okay.
Wait for me.
Everyone, be careful.
Professor.
Can we take a break?
This is dead end.
Let's head back.
Wang Jing, get up quickly.
Give me a hand.
Are you OK?
My waist.
My waist hurts.
What is this place?
We strike gold...
It's so beautiful.
- Wang Jing, hurry.
- I'm coming.
Come here.
So, ancient Hun
did in fact have a sanctuary.
Professor.
Look at that.
The seven-star god totem
on the jade pendant.
Professor.
There must be
a secret vault somewhere
or hidden mechanism
for you to discover.
Games have gotten into you.
You really think if you
push a button on the wall,
the top and bottom piece
will open up.
Your right and left will rumble.
Professor.
What are you mumble-jumbling about?
Let's leave.
We talk more when we are back.
Professor.
Do I look familiar?
Mr. Herbert.
You were quite handsome
when young, right?
The reason why I am here
is to get back the treasure
that was mine.
You cannot step on it.
Don't step on it.
Scripture on the wall
should be able to help, right?
Humans, driven by greed
plunder resources.
They kill one another.
Human civilization is constantly
destroyed and rebuilt.
Destroyed and again rebuilt.
People who loved peace and freedom
constructed beneath
the surface of the earth
a peaceful and equal
utopia of mutual respect
where only the kind-hearted
can enter.
Those who force their entry by greed
will definitely be punished.
A professor indeed
who makes a bullshit
sound so serious.
However, professor,
I want to be punished.
How to get in?
Boss.
Take a look.
There's a huge space
behind this wall.
Thank you, professor.
We finally find it.
Vincent, TNT.
Yes, sir
What?
Mr. Herbert.
Is it really necessary to blast it?
Shut up if you want
the rest of the money.
He is a mole.
Lei Zhen, you...
Wait.
Don't bomb it.
Thousand-year-old civilization
cannot be blown away.
Cannot use bombs.
Boss.
I also feel
it is not right to use bombs.
This is a confined space.
With an explosion, we...
Don't bomb it.
Hibiscus tree?
This one?
It should be
Bronze Sacred Tree.
This golden tree,
what is its purpose?
For worships.
It's a stairway for ancient people
to reach out to gods and universe.
Golden statue for worship of Heaven.
I've finally found you.
It doesn't belong to you.
It belongs to all mankind.
Do you know
theft of national
first-class cultural relics
is punishable by life imprisonment?
Even if you flee to another country,
you will still be repatriated.
Can you live up to your folks?
Herbert.
I don't want
any more money from you.
I can give you back
what you paid me.
I am done with this.
Tie them up.
- What is this?
- Come on.
- Hands up.
- I am pulling out, OK?
Calm down.
Go.
Over there.
Come on.
- Take it easy.
- Come on.
Go.
- Go.
Don't push them.
I'm OK.
Are you OK?
Move.
Take it.
Find a chance to get out.
Hand.
Give me your hands.
Bro, don't tie them so tight.
Let's go over there and have a look.
Alright.
Boys.
TNT.
On those 6 pillars.
Yes, sir.
Boss,
a vast hollow below.
Look.
Seems there are some buildings.
Let's first blast down
the golden statue.
Professor.
Shut up.
We can't let them
destroy the artifacts.
I'll find a way
to stop the explosion.
You three get out of here quickly.
We're all tied up.
How can we?
I am not.
Xinran.
Get ready to take the knife.
Take it.
Kick him.
Don't kick me. Kick him.
Not me.
- Leave now.
- Okay.
When I count to 3...
So quick.
Lei Zhen.
If you're my bro,
quickly take Xinran to leave here
- and call the police.
- What about you?
I have to help the professor.
No, I am staying with you.
We stick with each other.
Take it.
When all these are over,
I will be your man.
What did he say?
He will be my man.
Stop being so lovey-dovey.
- Let's get out of here.
- Wang Jing, I'll wait for you.
Professor.
Why are you back?
To help you.
Stay behind me.
I'll be waiting for you.
Don't look. Get down.
Lei Zhen.
- Lei Zhen.
- No more bullets.
- What to do?
Go over there.
Kill them all.
Copy that.
Zhou Bin.
Boss.
We cannot blow up these artifacts.
My baby has just been born.
I don't want to go to prison
for the rest of my life...
Let me see.
Gently.
Press it tightly with your hand.
Luckily there are no organs
in the legs.
Herbert.
Do you think there is
only golden statue here?
The treasures of the Hun
are also here.
Where?
The answer is in the writing
on the wall outside.
The writing on the wall?
You have my attention now.
Tell me.
Xinran.
Is Lei Zhen OK?
He is fine.
He only got shot twice.
Professor.
I'm waiting.
You let them go first,
then I tell you.
Why should I trust you?
That's it.
Professor.
Give it up.
Right.
Let the gas out.
Don't hack me.
Stay away from me.
Don't come any closer.
Professor.
Take them out of here
and call the police.
OK.
Hurry.
- Xinran.
- Wang Jing.
Lei Zhen lost lots of blood,
and must get him to hospital.
- I can't get him up.
- I'll help you.
Okay.
No one can leave.
Wang Jing.
Why did you block the arrow for me?
I saw you were in danger.
Then I...
It hurts? Where?
Where does it hurt?
Nowhere in particular.
My bag!
My leg!
You lost so much blood.
Why didn't you say
that your leg hurts?
Call the police.
Professor.
Are you okay?
No one can defy fate.
What is mine
shall be mine.
Hang in there.
Here.
Drink some water.
Brother-in-law, let's head back.
It's so cold.
Are you cold?
I think it's not that bad.
Here it comes.
You see?
Perseverence will pay off.
This fish is big.
It's a big fish.
Keep going!
Come on!
A big one.
It weighs at least 50-80 catties.
It got off my hook.
Not really.
The fish is still here.
I've never seen
this kind of fish lips.
Don't move.
It has teeth.
Help.
It speaks human language?
I think it said help.
Help.
Pal, how did you get in?
Where are you swimming to?
- Why are you chatting with him?
- Get him out.
Right.
Help.
Brother-in-law, hurry up.
Hang in there.
There is still no signal.
Xinran.
If you're my girlfriend,
you take Lei Zhen out of here now.
What about you?
I'll go find the professor.
Cannot leave him there
all by himself.
Wang Jing.
We agreed we would stick together.
Help.
Hurry up, get the quilt.
Quickly.
Over here, please.
Wang Jing, you're so handsome.
Professor Fang.
In your story "A Legend",
the tragic romance
echoes in one's heart.
Simply splendid.
I develop games.
Can I buy the game rights
to your book?
We have developed the game.
We need nothing
but funding.
That's easy. I have money.
Wonderful!
Let's talk over there.
- Can you walk?
- I can.
- Good.
- Let's go.
Xinran, his book.
Sir, your book.
Professor Fang.
Hello.
Mr. Wang Jing.
The story of Zhao Zhan and Mengyun
has such a sad ending.
I feel awful.
Actually,
the professor has
another version of the ending.
Professor.
Take a look.
Professor Fang.
Do you really have a better ending?
I have another ending
Mengyun would rather
sacrifice herself
to save your life.
I asked her before she died.
Knowing that you two
were not meant together,
why she insisted on doing that?
The day when we first met
he did not know me,
but he risked his life
to protect me.
General's sincere kindness,
Mengyun can never forget.
If I can just help him
to fulfill his wish in protecting
the country and people,
Mengyun dies with no regrets.
"The moon in the sky
changes its appearance"
"The autumn leaves fall unnoticed"
"The time travel seems
imaginary and yet so real"
"And you are as happy as
a good dream"
"The winter snow
stumbles its way here"
"Fragmentary memories
of many centuries"
"Devotion to be part of you
becomes lovesick"
"No one can separate you from me"
"This love is you, me,
mountains and the sea"
"It lasts to the present
and never falls apart"
"This love is you and me"
"my desire in this life"
"is to give it all for you"
"This love is what gives us"
"something from nothing
and our bonding"
"I will spend my life"
"waiting for you"