It's embarrassing how much you're resisting.
Perhaps I was wrong.
A clever trick. That's so unlike you. Still weak, though!
That's because I didn't put my back into it that time!
United States of Smash!
All Might wins!
He's saved us yet again!
Bravo! Bravissimo!
Here is a titan who manages to overcome every hurdle,
always pushing forward, fighting to create a perfect world.
No doubt All Might's the best hero that's ever been.
Now.
It's your turn.
I hear you loud and clear. You needn't worry, All Might.
I will succeed you and become the Symbol of Peace.
What's with this weirdo?
He's looking for a missing girl.
Wearing a three-piece suit?
If he was smart, he'd give up.
Got that right. The country's in shambles.
She's probably gone for good.
Warning. Multiple villains are currently active
in and around the West District.
Citizens are urged to seek refuge in designated safe zones
until heroes are able to contain the situation and restore order.
Who are they kidding? There are no safe places now.
Drop it and get lost.
You wanna die? Didn't think so!
Outta the way!
Talk about a killer haul!
With this much food, we can stuff our faces for months!
I'm detecting multiple explosions.
There's a truck that sounds like it's racing from the scene.
- How far out?
- Two klicks.
You should be able to catch up to them. No sweat.
Yep!
Opening back hatch.
Seventh. Float.
Plus Air Force!
We got incoming.
Looks like a green costume.
Oh, crap. Is it him? The Jailbreaker hunter!
Blackwhip!
St. Louis Smash!
See ya!
Twirling Tail Dance!
Jailbreakers secured!
Leave some action for the rest of us next time, Midoriya!
Nice! Three more villains off the street!
In record time. That's the power of One For All.
Man, that Quirk of yours rocks.
We'll let you take it from here.
Thank you, heroes.
This is Class A, Team Three.
We brought three villains to the police.
Ha! Only three of 'em?
My team just dropped off four of those losers.
Team Two reporting.
We've now secured six Jailbreakers.
Hey! No one likes a bragger!
Great Explosion Murder God Dynamight, numbers don't matter.
This is not a competition!
He's gotta have the longest hero name in history.
It's so immature. Just use "Bakugo."
Go tape your mouth shut!
We've got another villain spotted at the West Harbor.
Based on initial reports, we believe it's a prison escapee
named Ginji Kurau. Villain Name, Ginji.
His Quirk is Mad Gluttony, which allows him to attack
with the mouth in his stomach.
Take caution when approaching.
The West Harbor isn't far from here.
We can handle him.
C'mon, let's go!
We're gonna beat you there!
Team Two, here. We're already en route to the site.
I outsmarted those morons and made off with the prize.
Nobody's gonna be able to stop me while I've got you, girly.
You liar! You said you were going to free me!
Nah, I don't remember that. You must've heard wrong.
It's a UA truck. That means heroes.
The Jailbreaker changed his course!
Oh, no! He's headed straight for a shelter.
- I'll head him off.
- Huh?
-Let me go!
-Stop your whining!
Damn, they're still on me?
He didn't look like that in his file photo.
A hostage!
-Take my hand!
-No, don't!
Flowers?
What's this stabbing pain?
Was it because of those flowers?
Gotta get up. Have to save her!
A villain! Run!
That's not gonna work on me!
Know what I could use? Another hostage.
What?
I've got you.
That's what you think, kid!
This guy is powerful.
Evacuate! Now! Get out!
I'm gonna make this hurt!
What the...
-A gunshot?
-Who's there?
They might hit the hostage.
Someone tailed me.
No!
I won't make it!
What the hell?
Huh?
Apologies, my dear. That was a close call.
Are you doing this?
Is he able to freeze objects in place?
No, that's not it. He's just making things move in slow motion!
Stop shooting!
Danger Sense isn't reacting.
Who is he?
Normal speed. What now?
-Deku!
-Where is he?
It's kind of complicated.
Um, guys. Look up!
Is that a ship?
Yeah, it is. A ship that can fly!
You're safe now, Anna.
Fear not!
Hope has arrived.
'Cause I am here!
Wait, what?
Is that All Might?
No.
He may have All Might's appearance,
but that definitely isn't him.
And Danger Sense went insane the second he showed up!
Who the heck is this guy?
Gollini.
Please. Put me down! I don't...
You must've been so frightened
when that traitor stole you away.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for saving me. I was very scared. You're so brave.
You'll never leave my sight again.
I'll keep you safe.
It's such a relief to have the girl returned, Paulo.
We're lucky Bruno cleaned up your mess.
This won't happen again.
I'll bring them aboard.
You have to let me go.
-Why should I?
-Because this might be my last chance to make things right.
Can someone please tell me what's going on?
I'm not sure. But what happened
to that Ginji guy we were chasing?
Quick! He's getting away.
Not good!
Get outta here!
I've got the building!
Hurry! Evacuate!
Follow my lead!
Being a hero sure seems tough.
Him again. What a pain.
You're so popular. How sweet.
Damn it. If I still had the girl, I'd be getting off scot-free.
Hey, hey! Where do you think you're going?
You bastard!
I thought that you might be compatible with her,
but I didn't expect you to betray me.
I must say, I'm disappointed.
I'm gonna have to teach you a lesson!
Is everybody okay?
Hello there, young man! You look like you want to be a hero.
I'm sure you found that inspiring.
Have this chocolate bar on me.
You're the one who did this?
Hmm. Yes, it was yours truly. But no need to thank me.
He deserved that punch.
Traitors always get what's coming to them.
To think he'd betray the next Symbol of Peace.
Hold on. Who's the symbol?
That would be me, All Might.
Are you crazy? Who are...
Maybe my noble cause and unshakable
sense of justice are just too much
for the layman to fully understand.
Allow me explain
in a way that even an incompetent child
like you might be able to comprehend.
Tomorrow's temperatur—
Who's that?
You're seeing this too, right?
Who's this freak supposed to be?
He looks like All Might.
Citizens of Japan, it's an honor.
I stand here before you as the new All Might.
A bold symbol representing a bright future!
The new All Might? Did I get hit in the head?
Let me ask you this.
Why was All Might hailed as your undisputed Symbol of Peace?
The answer is a simple one. He was the most powerful.
Villains stood no chance against his god-like strength.
He inspired the weak, who looked at him
with both envy and admiration.
We were in awe of the number-one hero.
He provided the entire world with hope.
Unfortunately, that shining beacon is gone.
Just look around if you don't believe me.
Your country has been torn apart by criminals. Wrecked.
Meanwhile, nations across the globe have
abandoned you in your time of greatest need.
Why has this happened?
Because All Might, your symbol, lost his power,
leaving amateurs to protect you.
But have no fear.
Because today, in the birthplace
of the former number-one hero,
I pledge to take up his mantle.
Join me, and we will fly into a glorious future together!
I will not just surpass All Might, I'll go beyond!
Yes!
From now on, it's my turn!
Now. It's your turn.
I am your new symbol, the embodiment of justice!
- You call this justice?
- Huh?
You fought using unnecessary violence,
and in the process got a bunch of innocent people hurt.
All Might would never act so carelessly.
It sounds like Young Midoriya is on the scene.
You're a fraud. And you're nothing like the real All Might!
Not impressed? Well, keep your eyes open.
As soon as you get a glimpse of what I can do,
you'll be eating your words, kid.
Citizens!
This is what your new symbol can do.
Behold unmatched power!
What kind of Quirk is this?
Help!
I'm on my way!
No matter what, I'll save everyone!
-What is that?
-Huh?
The light is growing. And fast.
Come in, UA. Are you seeing this?
The light seems to be coming from
the West Harbor shelter! It shows no sign of stopping.
What is he doing? Is it some kind of attack?
He said he's made of tougher fabric than All Might,
but I have difficulty believing that.
Any word from the evacuees and heroes at the source?
It appears they were blanketed by this ever-expanding light.
We don't know what's happened to them.
This can't be real.
Uh, you guys? Any idea how to slow this thing down?
I'll stop it.
Great! Let's quickly rescue those inside.
Strike that! Retreat!
Why are we running away? Turn this van around, damn it!
- Don't be stupid, human!
- What did you say?
- It's catching up!
- We can't outrun it!
Some sort of enormous object has appeared,
and the light continues to spread further every second!
It's huge. Could he have single-handedly created that?
All Might, quick. You need to take a look at this.
I knew I'd seen some of his entourage before.
So we already have files on these people?
It's the Gollini Family.
As if things weren't bad enough.
That infamous "Family" is made up of villains.
They're the largest criminal organization in Europe.
Deku! Hey, wake up!
Uraraka?
You're not hurt, are you, Midoriya?
I feel okay.
Where are we? That bright light absorbed us.
How did we end up in a jungle?
No idea.
Yeah. We have no clue how we got here.
Maybe this terrain got sucked up from somewhere else.
Hmm?
The tree's hollow. It's fake. An imitation!
Which probably means...
this whole jungle is a manufactured illusion.
Maybe he has a power like Yaoyorozu's
and can produce inorganic matter?
But how could one man create something this expansive?
Anything?
No signal. We're on our own for now.
And I don't hear anything outside the immediate area.
Okay, so what's our next move?
First off, we find the others.
We have to make sure that everybody the light took is safe.
And after that, we find the nearest exit.
What the crap?
Where the hell are we?
- An amusement park.
- I can see that much!
- Aw, look!
- Huh?
The carousel works.
Stop playing around!
I didn't expect us to stumble on an entire city.
There's no reasonable explanation for it.
This isn't even the strangest thing we've seen today.
Everyone. Take a look at the statue.
I don't need special eyes to recognize that pose.
Jeez, someone around here's got
a seriously weird All Might obsession.
There's definitely something fishy going on.
Yeah. Let's check it out.
So, what do you think of the place, Anna?
I hope you like it. After all, you did inspire the design.
Yes. It's exquisite. Thank you.
You know, I had a feeling that's what you were going to say.
He's made contact.
The video call just came through, All Might.
Your imposter is on the line.
And apparently, you're the only person he'll agree to talk to.
Connect me. Big screen.
Ah, if it isn't my retired predecessor.
I wasn't sure you'd be at UA, but I guess it was my lucky night.
What have you done? Is everyone
who got caught up in your light safe?
Oh, them? Yes, all of the specimens are unharmed.
Specimens?
So, listen. The reason I reached out directly
is because I want to swear an oath to you, All Might.
Now that you've lost your power,
I pledge to uphold your will and unify this fractured country.
Everything you tried to do,
I will complete and exceed in your name.
I'll tell you exactly what you can do.
Release every person you took hostage immediately.
Are you willing to cooperate with us?
Hmm. I'm sorry, but no. I need them all.
They're necessary components in my plan
to surpass your ideal and find unrivaled success.
You're doing whatever you like, not what I want.
Know this. I would never deem you as my successor.
The only thing you care about is looking powerful
and fulfilling your own desires.
You sound heroic, but your heart is full of darkness!
Wow, I didn't expect to be called out.
Well, then. I suppose instead of "All Might,"
I should be called "Dark Might." Yes! That's good!
Got a certain panache to it. All hail Dark Might!
I never imagined someone would twist
everything I've stood for so radically.
You're my opposite. A villain.
I'd never entrust you with protecting this country!
I've already chosen a successor.
And I know exactly who will lead the next generation.
The heroes who're no doubt closing in on you at this moment!
You think so? I guarantee those
children will be kneeling before me soon.
Devoting themselves to the new symbol, Dark Might.
Heroes. It's the dawn of a new era.
Tell the world that it can rest easy now. 'Cause I am here.
That was a lot of fun!
Hmm.
If I heard All Might correctly,
it sounds as though he's chosen one of
these pesky kids as his successor.
What exciting information.
The man with the bike. He's the guy
who was taking shots at Anna back there.
I feel as though I've seen him before.
Boss, send me. I'll make him pay for what he's done.
No need for that. The punk's a nobody.
Don't waste your time with him.
But I want to make up for my failure.
I let that Compatible make off with Anna.
If you must. Fine. But this is your final chance, Paulo.
And I don't want anyone calling me "boss" anymore.
From now on it's Dark Might, capiche?
Yes, sir!
Finally, the moment is here.
A new icon has emerged. My story has begun.
Dark Might is not merely a man, but a legend!
What now?
An earthquake?
Feel that? Whatever this place is, it's not stationary.
We're being moved somewhere!
It's gonna crush us!
Mommy, help me!
The enormous structure's on the move!
Reports say the northwest shelter was attacked.
That floating fortress is sucking up every evacuee in its path.
And for some reason he's referring
to the hostages as "specimens."
What could he be up to in there?
Are you all right?
It's a wall.
Oh. A giant mural.
Guess this is as far as we go.
Look over here! There's, like, a manhole cover!
Can't see anything. It's too dark inside.
A creepy chute doesn't sound fun, but it might be our way out.
We need to see where this leads.
No problem. The two of us should explore it together.
Zero Gravity!
Seventh. Float!
This could be a trick.
Stay behind me and make sure you
keep plenty of distance, Uraraka.
Roger that!
Be careful down there!
This goes on forever. No end in sight.
Erasure Spot!
What? Suddenly I can't use One For All.
Everything good, Deku?
Uraraka! Don't come any closer to me!
Something happened, and now my Quirks have disappeared.
Disappeared?
Go back up and ask Sero to shoot down a bunch of Tape.
I'll be right back.
Someone might have a power like Mr. Aizawa's
that can nullify another person's Quirk. But how's it activated?
No. No, no, no. I'm going down crotch first!
You're saying Midoriya's Quirk vanished?
I'm not sure how, but there must've been some kinda trap.
No way.
Better hurry up and regroup.
As long as I use enough Tape, we won't need our powers.
Might be a long climb, though.
Right. Let's give it a try!
I thought I was going to die.
First the jungle, now a mountain range?
And I still can't access my powers.
I need to rejoin the others, fast.
Hey! Are you all right?
It's you.
Great. You're the one who got in my
way earlier. The naive child hero.
What'd he call me?
I'd be grateful if you showed me where the exit is.
I don't know where we are.
I just dropped out of the sky a few minutes ago.
My apologies. I didn't know your Quirk was ignorance.
I've never been insulted so politely.
I have nothing more to say. Kindly take your leave
and die in a different location.
Earlier.
You were trying to assassinate that hostage, weren't you?
Why would you do that?
My actions are none of your business.
-Did you just—
-Merely shock bullets.
They're not even gonna talk to us before shooting?
Isn't this when a hero should swoop into action?
Unfortunately, I can't seem to use my Quirk right now.
Perfect. I'm stuck taking cover with the utterly helpless.
You're far more useful as a distraction.
He's gonna get me killed.
Where is Miss Anna? You have
two seconds to give me an answer.
Anna?
How am I supposed to know?
The better question is
why we'd tell a scumbag like you anything.
Loyalty is admirable. I appreciate your honesty.
So courteous, yet so cruel!
I'm still pretty strong, even without my power.
What's going on?
They must be the citizens who got captured with us.
It looks as though something terrible's happened to them.
Hey. There!
Those two don't look like evacuees.
I finally found you.
I was afraid I'd never see your
beautiful face again. But you're safe!
She incapacitated him.
We're going in!
My, what brave heroes.
Poor dears.
Grape Juice and Chargebolt! Come join us!
Sure! Whatever you say, ladies!
- Little bro!
- Huh?
You wanna play soccer with us?
Toya! Let's go!
Throw the ball over here!
All yours!
Pass it back to me!
A perfectly brewed cup of tea. Ah. The scent is heavenly!
The Ingenium brothers. On patrol!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit. Ribbit, ribbit!
Ribbit, ribbit. Ribbit, ribbit.
Yes. Soba sounds good.
I'll let you enjoy your daydreams for a while.
We'll examine you more closely in due time.
It's such a shame that it's been so difficult to find Compatibles.
I shouldn't be surprised, though.
There were only eight of them among
the twenty thousand members of our revered Family.
For too long, you've fought your
way through devastated streets.
But a brighter tomorrow is here, young heroes!
You'll regret impersonating All Might!
The name is Dark Might, boy.
Do you like it? I came up with it myself. Stylish, no?
Why'd you bring us to this messed-up place? Explain yourself!
Have you ever stopped to wonder
why All Might was respected the world over?
Why everyone adopted him as the Symbol of Peace?
People are attracted to strength, you see.
Power provides entertainment!
This facility, the Symbol of Paradise,
is a landmark dedicated to peace!
Let's see if any among you are worthy
of being dubbed protectors of my palace.
If you pass the test, you can become my knight!
We'll celebrate my official rebirth as a legendary figure.
Together, we'll make history.
Raise your hand if you understand. Aha!
One question. Do you have any idea how stupid you sound?
You brats.
None of you get what I'm trying to do!
At least put on a good show!
Some kinda basement level?
Looks like we're in a dungeon crawler.
Why do I get the feeling we're the new entertainment?
That creep's almost as crazy as his outfit.
Yikes! Are those monsters?
So to pass his test, we gotta conquer this dungeon?
Whatever. Let's just get out of here.
This shouldn't take very long.
Dark Shadow!
Blast 'em to pieces.
Acid Shot!
What vigor. I wonder if any of them will survive this.
I really appreciate you giving me a lift.
It's for my own benefit. I'm practical.
Right now, you're serving as my human shield.
By the way, do you know where you're going?
I borrowed this from one of those trigger-happy henchmen.
If your Quirk is sealed away in this area,
we'll look for a door nearby that will lead us somewhere else.
Well, that was easier than I expected.
Why would they swoop in and start attacking us?
They were likely shooting at me, not "us."
Huh?
Perhaps they figured out how I ended up at the scene.
Why I'm seeking Miss Anna's death.
I'd like to know why.
A missile?
Fire.
Wait. Come back!
That one's using a Quirk.
The last guys didn't. They had to stick to guns.
Tell me, assassin. Why are you trying to kill the girl?
Because I made Miss Anna a promise.
"Miss," huh? I see. You must be Scervino's pawn.
Scervino?
I implore you to please not make
Miss Anna use her Quirk anymore.
Whatever your plan is, you have no idea
how her ability actually works.
We'll use her as we see fit.
In fact, she's going to play an essential role in the boss's ascent.
I understand. A pity. We could
have handled this without violence.
They're standing in one place. That's strange.
Unless... Is he erasing my powers? Then, maybe...
Can you keep them distracted?
-What if I do?
-I'll defeat them.
My trusty partner will be of use.
Huh?
Damn it.
And, I'm back!
I was right. He creates a field that erases Quirks.
But he also forms a buffer inside so his allies can still use theirs.
A zone within a zone.
Got you now!
Manchester Smash!
It feels like my powers are back to normal.
Thanks for the help—
We meet again, amateur hero.
And if I'm to believe my eyes,
it would appear you're able to wield multiple Quirks.
All Might mentioned that he'd decided on a successor
when we had our little chat.
Don't tell me he picked you!
Oh, you kids. I thought heroes
were supposed to keep a cool head.
Why have you imprisoned us in this fake world?
Tell me what your endgame is.
I already did. I'm going to take my place as the new symbol.
The great Dark Might. The whole world will know my name.
You're not serious.
I'll accomplish more than All Might ever could.
Bologna Smash!
Holy whoa. He's strong!
Boss. Please.
Paulo. Oh, Paulo! You've no idea how much this pains my heart.
No, boss. Wait. I'm begging! Just one more chance!
I believed in you.
That's why I gave you so many opportunities
to prove yourself a worthy comrade.
But tell me, Paulo. What have you given me in return?
Utter laziness. Sloth! That's a deadly sin!
I won't let any more bumbling idiots disgrace
the Gollini Family name!
We must be infallible, like All Might was
when he fought in his prime.
I'll never lose or disappoint you again, I swear!
Please, boss, you've got to believe me.
Hmm.
Granting mercy to one who's wronged me would be
a way to demonstrate peace.
I'll be sure to remember
that if our paths ever cross in your next life.
Give the boy a message whenever he comes to.
He will accept that I'm the future eventually.
Until he submits, I welcome his challenges.
In fact, I look forward to them.
Hmm?
How dare he put a mark on this flawless face.
That boy's in need of a strict re-education.
Out of the jungle and into the mountains.
At least our Quirks still work. That could've been awkward.
Maybe Midoriya took care of the issue.
He can tell us, but we've gotta find him first.
Huh?
What is this?
Where the heck are we now?
Huh?
Hello, children.
I guess none of those kids are
going to make it to my inner sanctum.
And here I was looking forward to showing off my costume.
Are you the final boss, here?
You made a shortcut? You think you can break
the rules and ruin my game?
This is disgraceful player behavior!
I'm a walking cheat code.
Bravo, children!
But that was just the first act of the show.
Do your worst, extras.
You're finally awake.
Wow, you must've saved my life back there. I... Thanks a lot.
Oh, yeah. I'm Izuku Midoriya. But my hero name is Deku.
Giulio. Giulio Gandini.
Great to meet you, Giulio. Thanks again.
I didn't save you out of good will.
I sensed that you could be useful to me.
Still happy to be alive.
Deku? That's an unusual name.
Yeah, but I like it.
Am I seeing things? There's an entire city here?
-Curious.
-Huh?
No. What happened?
Uraraka! Talk to me!
Did something knock her out?
Everyone? Who did this?
They were incompatible with my lady's Quirk.
The feedback caused them to pass out.
What are you talking about?
Anna. That was her name?
Yes. Miss Anna Scervino.
What does her Quirk have to do with this?
Well—
-Ojiro!
-Miss Anna!
Lovely. I didn't expect fresh specimens.
Specimens?
Those compatible with Miss Anna's Quirk
are turned into soldiers
against their will.
Yes. It's a great honor to serve
under Dark Might, the new symbol.
He has a place for everybody.
Even those who flail before Anna can still be of use to him.
My Quirk will see to that.
I take it you're using your ability to brainwash Miss Anna?
It's not brainwashing. She's simply watching
a pleasant dream play out.
Under normal circumstances,
I can transfix one person at a time.
But since I'm compatible with our little flower here,
I can make large groups of people
have beautiful dreams simultaneously.
Don't worry. I'm not going to leave the two of you out.
See for yourself. Welcome to my world.
All Might!
More All Might! And even more All Might!
He's everywhere I look! Yay!
I've heard your wish, future hero, and now it's coming true!
Because I am here!
It's the real All Might! Best day ever!
Let's start hero-ing, Young Midoriya.
No. "Deku!"
Together, we will save the world!
Yeah!
Stop.
What you're seeing is not reality. Don't forget yourself.
Huh? Where am I?
You're dreaming. Stuck in some sort of twisted fantasy realm.
These are the spirits of those
who are currently being affected by the villain's Quirk.
Even if you try to wake up, you won't be able to escape.
You must find another way out.
Another way out? Okay, how?
Is that...
Giulio. Sit down and join me. Have a cup.
Me? No. That wouldn't be proper, Miss.
Why are you always so mean to me?
I'm right here.
Giulio. I'm sorry.
My Quirk brings torment. I hate that you suffer.
You can't even leave the mansion.
I don't mind. I know my duty, and I'm happy to do it.
You can take my power away.
Make me feel like a normal person.
I owe so much to you, but I fear
I don't know what I would do without you.
I'll always be here.
You mean it?
Of course, Miss. It's my job to serve you.
So. That's what this is about.
Your motivations are quite admirable.
But I suspect you could become a problem.
Miss Anna. Stop this. Why are you—
Giulio! This is a fantasy! It isn't real!
C'mon, you have to snap out of it!
What are you saying?
I still have my right arm?
Yes. I see. The boy is right.
This is all because of you!
You pest.
How did you escape me? It shouldn't be possible.
Giulio?
Hello, Miss Anna.
It's really you!
Put that away!
Promise me, Giulio.
If anything bad happens, before
I lose control of myself, please kill me!
Step aside.
Let go!
I won't stand here and watch you shoot her.
Do you understand me?
- We'll find a way—
- Damn it!
Why would you interfere?
You're no hero. You're a nuisance.
You meddle around in other people's problems
when you have no idea what's going on. Fool!
This may have been my last chance to stop Miss Anna!
I couldn't let you hurt her.
Because when you aimed your gun,
it looked like you were in agony.
From what I can tell,
deep down, what you really want is to help her, not kill her.
Obviously! The only reason I'm here is to help her.
But it's too late now.
Killing her is the only option I have.
I don't get why you'd have to do something so drastic!
Because she told me it's what she wants.
Miss Anna's Quirk is Overmodification.
It's a power that's constantly activated.
When she touches someone, she transforms their Quirk Factor.
It allows that person to temporarily
enhance or alter their power.
They get a boost.
However, if she touches someone
who's incompatible with her ability,
pain shoots through their body instead.
She never said it, but I think she was
afraid of human contact her whole life.
The first time I met her, she was confined to her room.
Secluded and alone, like a princess in some fairy tale.
She showed no emotion. Never smiled. Never cried.
The bigger problem is that
if she doesn't release a certain amount of her Quirk,
it turns against her body.
She's racked with painful seizures.
That's why I was hired. To help her.
My Quirk is Neutralization.
When I touch someone with my right hand,
I can nullify their Quirk.
I was able to take away her pain.
Come on. You're walking so slowly!
Anna can finally live something close to a normal life.
I'm thrilled.
This wouldn't have been possible without your aid.
We're all so grateful to you.
Think nothing of it.
I should really be thanking you
for taking in a lost soul with no family of his own.
You gave my life purpose.
But Giulio, this job means you're confined
to our mansion and can't leave Anna's side.
My current life is far better than the one I previously led.
I'm well fed, and my compensation is more than adequate.
I can't imagine complaining about these circumstances.
Every year that passes, Anna's Quirk grows stronger.
There may come a day when you can't
subdue her power with your own.
I'll help her. Even if it costs me my life.
Please. Swear to me.
If I... If I ever lose control of my power and you can't stop me...
I want you...
I want you to take my life.
Miss Anna, no.
It's getting worse. My mind gets
hazy every time I have a seizure.
I'm scared.
If I lose control of my Quirk, I won't be the person I am now.
Promise me, Giulio.
If anything bad happens, before
I lose control of myself, please kill me!
Before that could happen,
the Gollini Family somehow found out
about Miss Anna's ability.
They attacked the mansion
and killed Mr. Scervino.
Giulio. Don't let them take me!
Be strong, Miss Anna. I swear I'll find you!
They took her. Used her.
And so I'm here to fulfill my promise.
But why kill Anna when there's a possibility you can save her?
Your Quirk!
Have you looked at me?
I can't use my power anymore.
I couldn't save her if I tried to.
I'm sorry.
When she does lose control of her power,
the Quirk she's modifying will transform infinitely,
and the person she's enhancing will become unstoppable.
I won't let that happen.
Just now, when you and
I were both stuck inside that villain's illusion,
I watched as you and Anna smiled at each other.
You looked at her with care and kindness.
I don't think you have it in you to go through with your plan.
I haven't smiled since that awful day. I don't remember how to.
Then I'll make you remember, Giulio.
I'll save Anna and make sure both of you can smile again!
How are you going to do that?
We don't have time for hypotheticals.
If she loses control, we're done.
The whole world could be destroyed.
We don't have any choice but to end her life.
Weren't you listening? This is what she wanted.
But now she has us to help, too.
I may not know the particulars of what's happening to her,
but I absolutely believe we should find another way
to aid Anna in her struggle.
It sounds like her power hasn't been dialed up to eleven yet.
There must be more than one way to keep her ability in check.
We have a lot of experience with temporary Quirk erasure.
You're not the only solution to the problem.
First things first. We save the babe.
We'll figure the rest out after she's back.
Totally!
Even if the chances seem slim to you now...
...it's too early to give up on her.
And I agree with my classmates.
If you lend us a hand, we can save Anna together.
What are ya standing around for?
We've got a fake All Might to explode.
Much to my dismay, Paulo
and Simon disgraced the Gollini Family.
I know you won't disappoint me like they did, Deborah.
No, Dark Might. Of course I won't.
I've already chosen a successor.
The heroes who're no doubt closing in on you at this moment!
Full of indomitable spirit, even in retirement. It's commendable.
But he's an ordinary man now, devoid
of the power to make a real difference in the world.
Careful, youngsters. You must be open to change.
Today, you'll realize my predecessor is dead. A memory.
If you want to survive the coming days,
you'll have to pledge your loyalty to a new master.
The fortress has changed its course.
What direction is it headed?
If it stays on its current route, it'll be on top of us in no time.
So we're his target.
He plans to unravel hero society.
The UA barrier and defensive systems
are crucial parts of our fight against Shigaraki.
We can't allow this new threat to damage them.
Yeah. We know.
Call in whoever you can. We'll form
a defensive line and stop his approach.
Citizens! Do not be afraid.
Follow our lead, and we'll find a way out of this place.
We've got plenty of food from the shelter
that was sucked into the light.
It's a feast!
Here.
No need to rush. There's plenty for everyone.
How adorable! Play-acting as real heroes.
What does he want?
Since you're so young, you may not know what must happen
before a new era can truly begin.
So, I'll tell you.
The old values and status quo
must be abandoned and destroyed.
The previous society has to be dismantled
to usher in a glorious new order!
Which is why UA High, All Might's alma mater,
must be swept from the face of the Earth.
He's after our school?
That's right. I will demolish and then rebuild.
Erase one legacy and welcome the dawn of a new legend!
This is the story of how I come to power.
I'm gonna murder that guy.
Class reps!
Lead these people out of the city and find some way to escape.
-Of course!
-We'll do our best!
Ashido and Sato.
Go with them and make yourselves useful with acid and muscle.
Carve 'em a way out!
Kirishima, Kaminari, and Shoji.
Make sure no one tries to stop 'em!
Todoroki, Tokoyami, and Deku. You're with me!
We'll show this loser he messed with the wrong class.
Let's do this!
We'll make sure the school is safe.
And stop this madness.
Shortsighted peons stuck in the past.
You're about to learn how weak you are.
Compared to the new symbol, you're inferior creatures.
I'm counting on you all.
So this is Dark Might's stronghold.
It looks a whole lot bigger when you see it in person.
I agree, and I become an actual giant.
Get ready. I'll provide us a way in.
Prominence Burn!
Even hotter. Maximum fire!
Nice! He did it!
No, wait. Look!
It repaired itself that quickly?
This is going to be a bit more difficult than we expected.
Hawks, come in.
Don't worry, I'm way ahead of you, All Might.
I've already sent an ace hero to help inside.
You mustn't panic! Move quickly, but remain calm.
Class rep. There was a huge explosion somewhere down below.
My guess? Someone on the outside's trying to get in.
Ooh, I bet it's the pro heroes!
Yes.
Jiro, help us point these people toward the blast site.
No need for that. I can show ya the way.
-Togata!
-Lemillion's here!
Sorry it took so long to arrive.
I was patrolling in a totally different area
when they said to head over.
Right. We should prioritize civilian safety.
- Follow me to freedom!
- Roger that!
You heard him. This way!
No freaking out! We gotcha covered!
Watch your step. Look out for the people around you.
The four of you had better return safe and sound.
But show that faux symbol what Class A stands for!
Nice of him to provide a bridge.
I've spotted an entrance up ahead.
The moron wants us to find him.
He underestimates what kinda heat we bring.
- You're coming, too?
-Beat it, cool side character!
- I refuse.
- You got a death wish?
I'm the person who knows the most about Miss Anna's power.
You need my insight. And besides...
if you really want to see me smile again,
then I'll need to be there when she's rescued.
These brats have courage.
They face impossible odds, and yet they refuse to give up hope.
Let's raise a toast to the next generation.
I invite you inside with open arms.
Yes. My welcome committee can't wait to meet you.
Not these lackeys again.
Dark Shadow!
I can take them on myself. You run ahead. Go.
Leave them to me and Dark Shadow!
Yeah, yeah.
Tokoyami. Be careful!
Of course. You as well.
That way! Stick to the stairs and make sure you don't slip!
Look! Monsters!
Togata. We'll leave the evacuees to you.
Wait. Hold up.
You're the only person among us
who can guide them back to safety.
You guys.
Asui. Koda. Sero. Hagakure.
Help Togata and make sure those evacuees get out of here.
Everyone else? Let's stop these monsters. Come on, Class A!
Yeah!
You lookin' for a fight?
I hold no personal grudge against you lot,
but the boss's orders have to be followed!
Midoriya. Keep moving forward
while Bakugo and I take them out.
You actin' all tough, too?
Hope you're holding on tight, Giulio!
I don't get it. They should've been trapped in the ice.
Just great. One of them's a teleporter.
I think it's safe to assume you've come
for this very special girl, yes?
Too bad for you, I happen to have grown rather attached to her.
-Miss Anna!
-Don't rush in!
The one who can slow movement.
Time for Delay Spot.
I was barely out of his Quirk's range.
One more bug to pin down.
How sad. You're retreating already?
Hmm.
Float. Fa Jin. Air Force. Synchro-activation!
I applaud this act of desperation.
Hmm?
What?
He's still fast? How?
Slow down! No! Stop!
Deku. Deku!
Yeah. I'm still alive, I think.
But where did Anna go?
Dark Might took her with him. Up there.
Then let's go after them.
You're wasting your time!
You're pissing me off!
Where are they?
Bastard!
There's no end to these beasts.
Heartbeat Distortion!
Fire!
You're not going anywhere!
Keep fighting! Defend the civilians!
We still haven't heard back from the scout?
This thing is getting dangerously close to UA.
All Might, look! Our inside man's sending signals.
He says, "Act fast. Many in need of help."
"Destroy this spot and start
the rescue operation. Over and out, heroes."
And that's it.
Focus attacks on the designated spot. We can't hold back now.
Give this everything you've got
and make sure every evacuee is safe.
Now, Endeavor. You got this!
Yeah. I do.
How about a Plus Ultra Prominence Burn?
Flare Circle!
This is part of the plan! Don't panic!
- Get 'em!
- Right!
These kids are the last ones.
What about the others inside?
Class 1-A's on top of things. They're fighting
the enemy. We've got to support them!
You did an excellent job, Endeavor.
Agreed. But the fortress is still on the move.
That's fine. I'll keep firing Prominence Burn until I've stopped it.
All Might. Make sure the entry team is ready to move!
But your body. It can't take much more heat.
Are you forgetting? We're a bunch of heroes.
Where are we now?
Is this still his Quirk in action?
Yes. It's Alchemy.
What's that?
A Quirk that allows him to create any
form of matter by using a catalyst.
That's how he changed his face
and created his Dark Might persona.
In reality, Dark Might is a mob boss and wanted criminal.
Valdo Gollini, head of Europe's largest mafia.
Okay, but why would he change his face to look like All Might?
To become a symbol.
I'm the one who'll replace him.
So why not inherit his face, as well?
I am his destined successor.
And now, it's my turn.
Isn't that right, Anna?
Stop! Don't do this!
No. She can't take it. Get away from her!
With my boosted power, I'm easily stronger than All Might was.
I'm going to remake this world in my image!
Do you see? I have surpassed him!
What do ya say, kid? Pretty awesome, huh?
Huh?
Gotcha.
Unlike All Might, I can't take any damage.
-I'm "Plus Ultra" personified!
-No!
Hah! It's no use.
You're starting to get on my nerves!
I'm having a heart-to-heart
with a youngster who still has a future.
This is what you get for interfering.
I'll make an example of you! Die, nobody!
Alchemy makes it seem like he has multiple Quirks,
but it's really one overpowered ability.
Deku!
Whatever he can do, saving Anna is our priority right now!
Sixth, maximum Smokescreen!
Aw, you're resorting to cheap tricks?
I'm afraid you're going to disappoint me, little hero.
Detroit Smash!
Torino Smash!
Miss Anna!
Can you hear me?
She's not going anywhere.
That's it! Wear yourselves out.
C'mon, aren't you ready to throw in the towel yet?
The big guy's our problem. He's the one who can teleport.
And the geezer's got telekinesis.
I think I see how they function.
Our silent friend can warp himself and whatever he's touching.
That's why the tiny one stays close.
His range is limited. He probably
has to stick to places he can see.
That means...
we destroy their landing spots!
Blow up everything!
Reduce it to ash!
Keep those flames coming!
Surprise. You aren't goin' anywhere.
Gah. Took us long enough.
Giulio, get up.
Anna. Be a dear and kill this man for me.
Yes. Right away, ma'am.
About time we had some real entertainment.
Giulio, you've got to move. Listen to me! Wake up!
Stop complaining and enjoy the show.
Once you know despair, your future will be clear.
You will have no option but to accept me as the new symbol.
That's never going to happen.
No, stop! You can't do this!
Please, Anna!
We're all in position. Shoot, Endeavor.
Until my flames burn out or my body quits.
Prominence Burn!
Must be the obsolete old pros.
They don't realize their time has passed.
You've gotta come to. Don't let them beat you.
Do it for Anna!
What's this?
His support items. Did they automatically activate?
Do they know who I am?
Huh?
Wait. He's out of bullets?
Hilarious. How dare you scare me?
No. No. What have I done?
Giulio!
Why would you try to run away?
You don't want to make me sad, do you?
Damn it.
Aw. Don't cry, child.
You have no use for a servant anymore.
I'll take good care of you.
Are you hurt, Midoriya?
No. But thanks!
What the hell, Deku? Is it your naptime or somethin'?
Kacchan!
Interesting development.
I didn't expect three of you kids would make it this far.
But then, I shouldn't be surprised
that All Might's pupils are exceptionally tough.
Shut it! You keep his name out of
your smug mouth, do you hear me?
Oh, I will. Actions speak louder than words.
I'll demonstrate how much stronger I am than you
and your desiccated husk of a teacher.
- You're hurting her!
- Get him!
That's the spirit.
Keep fighting, young ones. You're providing me
with some riveting entertainment!
Report from the rescue team. Everybody made it inside.
We're almost out of time.
I can't keep going.
You're just going to give up?
That doesn't sound like you at all, Tsukuyomi.
What are you doing here?
Not good.
You've woven a fine defense.
Allow us a turn.
What now?
Keep at it! Don't let up!
You got it!
I'm coming.
- Keep it up.
- Focus!
Stop him!
Now! Heaven-Piercing Ice Wall!
That's the stuff. Gimme everything you've got!
Keep it up, fledgling heroes.
I think in that last round I almost felt one of your attacks.
I'll blast that grin off your face!
As I said. From now on, it's my turn.
Like hell it is!
We're the future!
It's our turn!
The symbol I admired so much made us smile.
He brought the world happiness and gave us hope!
What? Did he just get stronger?
His power didn't take from people!
He used it to make everybody's lives better!
He's right. All Might was our idol.
He never lost a fight. He's the best.
But he taught us that winning isn't everything.
I don't care how strong you are.
I hate what your phony ass stands for!
No, don't. Not my face!
So that's what this imposter actually looks like.
We knew that despite your look, you were nothing like him.
-Isn't that right, Midoriya?
-Isn't that right, Deku?
All Might gave me his power, and I've trained hard to wield it.
But I still have a long way to go
before I get anywhere close to his level.
Luckily...
I'm not fighting alone.
I have friends who battle at my side no matter the enemy.
And it's not just them. There are plenty of heroes I can rely on.
I know they have my back.
Together, we'll be victorious.
Just like All Might!
We're gonna save people with smiles on our faces!
Detroit. Texas. Wyoming. Carolina. Missouri.
California. New Hampshire. Oklahoma. St. Louis.
Smash!
Valdo. Your desire for power is your weakness.
You will never lead our Family to greatness.
People are not inspired by what they fear.
Tell that to All Might. He used his power
to become great and achieve his ideal.
His ideal called for strength, not power.
You're nothing like him.
That's not true, old man!
Father. You were...
We did it!
Does this mean...
Yeah. I think we've won.
No, no, no. Dark Might's Quirk flamed out?
I gotta get out of here.
Oh, hey. I found you.
Power!
The fortress stopped. We're saved!
Yeah!
That was incredible work, everyone.
Giulio!
How bad are you injured?
It feels like I've got a few broken bones, but I'll survive.
Anna.
Miss Anna!
What's happening?
It must be Anna's power.
She's losing control!
-You have to get me closer to her!
-Are you sure?
Just do it!
No. Deku!
Oh, no!
What's this light?
The fortress. It's putting itself back together.
This is unexpected and does not bode well for us.
Something's happening up there!
I am the new symbol.
No, not just that. I am the new world!
Damn it. I thought maybe I could still use my Quirk.
Come on. Work.
My power has to save her again.
The only thing I ever wanted was
to give Miss Anna the life she deserves.
Yes. I can't get enough. Give me more power!
I've got you!
How much stronger can this guy get?
Crap. Get it together, damn it.
Look alive, Deku!
Please, Miss Anna. I swear.
From this moment on, I'll always
be right here whenever you need me.
As long as I'm by your side, you'll be Quirkless. Normal.
Well... ...apart from being rich.
Giulio.
Giulio! Say something! Come on.
Wake up! Giulio?
No. Please. I can't lose you!
Don't leave me.
Miss Anna.
Please don't label me a corpse just yet.
You're alive!
You were pushed past your limits back there.
But you won't be able to use your Quirk again.
You mean you neutralized it forever?
Yes. Because my ability
was modified by yours. You enhanced me.
I wasn't sure I'd be compatible. It was a slim chance.
We're lucky it worked out the way it did.
Going forward, you won't suffer any more of those seizures.
You no longer have a Quirk, Miss Anna.
I'm glad to have been of use.
With that said, my contract with you has come to an end.
You don't need me anymore.
No one is going to come after you.
You may touch whoever you like and go wherever you want.
You're free now.
Perhaps I wasn't being clear enough before.
No, I heard you.
I don't work for you any longer.
I know. I'm glad.
That means we're on equal ground.
Miss Anna, I—
Just "Anna."
Anna, then.
Hey. Giulio. Have you noticed?
You're smiling again.
Together, we'll recover everything we've lost.
We'll create a better tomorrow in ways that only we can.
We'll make sure that everyone smiles.