News from abroad.
2 pandas,
named Yuan yuan and Manman...
...who moved to Noah's Zoo
on Noah Island, 3 years ago,...
...recently
gave birth to a baby panda.
According to statistics from the Alliance
Global Live Streaming Platform...
...this unique baby panda is now
has over 700 million followers.
Previously, we have seen
pink panda...
...chocolate...
...black furless panda
on his back.
THE RESIDENCE OF NOBLE FARIHA
All of these are very rare and...
...an unusual gene.
Panda with 2 eyes
black different sizes...
...very rare...
...along
history of animal genetics.
This little panda baby...
...is the only one that exists.
Sir, we can get it.
at some place.
We can buy it, right?
It's just a request
their prices are ridiculous.
Just pay them.
Do you want to think about it?
No matter how much it costs...
...I will pay for it.
You don't understand what I'm saying?
As requested...
...the item will be sent
to you on time.
Okay, "Cut"!
Friends.
Are you okay?
Yes.
That's good.
- Hey, those cables.
- Take it down.
Don't let the cable hang.
That's very, very, very...
...authentic!
1 vs 30.
Extraordinary!
Come on! Give a round of applause
cheers to Jackie!
Yes!
- Yes!
- All departments!
Fast...
...fix the set
and do this fetch again.
Taken again?
We've done it many times.
Stop!
Let's take a break!
The director wants
buy us milk tea!
That doesn't make sense!
I am alone
finish off the entire assassination squad?
Am I a superhero?
This is a commercial film.
Should be entertaining, right?
- Right, right. You're smart and cool!
- Hey.
Next I will
take a romantic movie.
Good.
Jackie.
I just wrote love story trilogy.
The first.
"A Love Story Amidst the Brawl."
- Sounds like an action movie again!
- The second...
Sorry. The device is short-circuited.
What about the second one?
The second film...
"Love...
...In the Midst of Bloodshed."
Then the third one?
"Love...
"Love In The Middle Of Anything."
Let's sign it
contract for this trilogy.
Oh, oh.
Hey.
You don't know the rules?
You should know, right?
Who are you?
dare to ask for a break?
If I don't ask for
rest, what am I asking for?
Asking to finish filming
Today?
What's next on my schedule?
Arctic International Golf Tournament...
...invite you to
playing golf.
Play golf? I don't want to.
Okay.
Ouch.
There was an invitation from Stallone
to attend...
...her housewarming party.
Send her flowers.
I don't need to go.
Okay.
Aah!
South African Ice Festival
The first...
...asking you to cut the ribbon
at their opening ceremony.
Ice Festival in South Africa?
Maybe man-made.
Of course I don't want to,
if man-made.
Okay.
Ahh.
Ocean Film Festival in Somalia
invite you to the opening.
Somalia?
Just forget about this.
It seems a bit dangerous.
Noah's Zoo invites you
to adopt a panda.
Panda?
This is the panda.
So, this is the panda?
The largest animal
which is famous in the world.
- So cute!
- Are you going?
Ouch!
- Sorry, sorry.
- Ouch.
The panda is so cute.
KUNG FU STAR JACKIE
BECOME A PANDA HERO
JACKIE ANNOUNCES PANDA ADOPTION
DREAM COUPLE
JACKIE AND THE PANDA
JACKIE ANNOUNCES PANDA ADOPTION
WELCOME,
Dear guests.
- Hello.
- Welcome to Noah's Zoo!
- Thank you.
I'm the director here.
I'm Peter.
You can call me Old Pi!
- Can you speak Mandarin?
- We have a lot of Chinese tourists coming.
This is my assistant, Anastasia.
- The car is here.
- Is that your car?
- Correct.
- Through this way.
Wow.
Thank you.
NOAH ZOO
Look, your fans.
Through this way.
NOAH ZOO SHOPPING AREA
Hi, hi.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Look here!
Thank you.
- Don't eat this.
- Why?
- Too sweet. Your sugar level.
- But why did you buy two?
Because both of them
only half price.
Hey, you can't eat that either.
Too oily!
Sir, please order.
1 hot dog.
Hello, hello.
Come on, come on.
I've eaten this!
Hello, Amy.
- Hello, Tony.
- You look beautiful today.
Oh, hello, Cherry.
Hi, Tony.
You look beautiful
wearing a uniform.
The robot is passing by.
Hi, Tony.
At work. Keep your distance.
At workplace...
Hello, Zhuzhu.
You look beautiful today.
NOAH ZOO
Oh no.
You don't talk to me anymore.
Your order has arrived.
Baby Gemoy.
Come down, Little Baby.
If you don't want it, I'll drink it.
Can you come down?
so as not to embarrass me?
Cute Baby!
Let's get a drink so I can get home from work.
Baby Gemoy, come down.
Okay.
You have to make me
working overtime, huh?
Hello.
I want to order ice cream.
Of course.
Did you see Jackie today?
Yes.
Wow...
Are her legs O-shaped?
Right! It really stands out.
What about the nose?
Big! I tell you, yeah.
His nose is covered
half of his face.
I missed a lot of things.
I didn't see him today.
Thank you.
Mr. Jia.
Is this the rest of your ice cream?
You are so stingy.
You never pay.
Don't ask for too much.
By the way...
...I can't stand seeing you guys like this
never seen the world before.
So what if he is a star?
What do you see?
Don't think I'm just an ice cream seller.
I tell you.
I used to work in Hollywood.
I sell ice cream too.
There are many movie stars.
Will Smith.
Keanu Reeves.
Tom...
...and Jerry.
We are very close. Am I showing off?
I face everything calmly.
Really.
Hello.
This nose also covers
half of his face.
Ice cream.
Hello.
Jackie Chan.
Jackie.
His name is Jerry, not Jackie.
Jerry is American cartoon mouse.
Jackie is Jackie Chan.
He is from Hong Kong.
Jackie!
She's totally Jackie!
Oh my gosh! Jackie Chan!
Jackie! Jackie Chan!
Let's take a photo.
Can we take a picture?
- Let's take a photo.
- Hey.
Get the phone.
- Hello.
- Yes.
- Excuse me.
- Hello.
Can I sit here too?
Please.
Thank you.
Mr. Jia is so arrogant.
Oh...
I can't finish it.
I'll give you a little.
No need.
I eat ice cream every day.
- Do you want to?
- Yes, no need.
I am the panda caretaker, Su Xiaoshu.
- Panda nanny?
- Yes.
- I came to adopt.
- I know.
I got the news.
Can I ask a personal question?
Should not.
I am just kidding.
- Just ask.
- Ah...
How rich are you?
Next question.
How many boyfriends have you had?
How rich are you?
Apart from these 2 questions,
ask something else.
Jackie.
I just improvised
artwork for you.
- Try it.
- It's beautiful. Thank you.
- Thank you sir.
- Thank you.
- Eat. There's more.
- No need.
- There must be more.
Accompany him. There's more.
No need.
I can't finish it.
Calm down, Mr. Jia. Hey.
He...
He is very friendly.
This is too much for me.
Why don't we go somewhere else?
Do you want to see the panda?
- Is it allowed?
- Of course.
Ah, come on, let's go now!
I will eat later.
AIR CLEANING
Wow...
Cute Baby?
What?
- His name is Baby Gemoy?
- Yes.
- Hey.
- The name is strange.
It's strange indeed.
My pet's name is Baby Gemoy.
Baby Gemoy.
He is too naughty.
He's hiding again.
Cute Baby!
- Cute Baby.
Baby Gemoy.
What is it?
He surprised me.
The magic trick...
Hug the legs.
- Can I hug her?
- Yes.
He likes you.
How do you know?
Because he's going to fart.
How...
How did you know he was going to fart?
He just relaxes when
seeing the person he likes...
...and when he saw it, he farted.
He is indeed unique!
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Come on, beat it.
Who else? Huh?
Okay.
Our men
have arrived on the island now.
Boss, we have received the down payment.
The client wanted it delivered immediately.
Beat him up.
Hello, man.
Please believe in Chaikun.
I would be happy work with you.
James! James! James!
James! James! James! James!
Who wants to go?
to the zoo?
- Zoo?
- Why?
Shut up!
Hey, Boss.
We are elite mercenaries.
And now we
have to kidnap a panda?
Seriously.
We will be a laughing stock
in this business, right?
Naturally.
But this joke...
...worth 100 million dollars!
Wow, 100 million?!
Boss... boss... boss.
Come on, come on!
Good effort.
PANDA HOUSE
Now. Lately I haven't
can sleep soundly, for some reason.
Oh yeah? I don't feel like it
have any appetite at all.
I don't want to eat anything.
Very weird.
But at least today was relaxing.
Not hungry at all.
But at least
Today's work is easy.
Harry!
I'm stuck!
Unlucky.
FANTASTIC PANDA HOUSE
I'm stuck!
Get down here!
Unlucky!
YOUR SAFETY GUARD
Boss.
The CCTV camera has been turned off.
...united to create...
...wildlife reserve
this is amazing.
PANDA ADOPTION CONFERENCE
Now...
...Noah's Zoo...
NOAH ZOO - PANDA
...in the open ocean...
...belongs to all mankind.
Do you know him?
No.
Why greet him if you don't know him?
Soon
I will get to know him.
I want to use this opportunity
to thank Ronald...
PANDA ADOPTION CONFERENCE
...for having adopted...
...our young panda,
Yuan Yuan and Man Man...
...and also Jackie
has adopted...
...our little celebrity panda
which is very special.
Gentlemen, please come forward...
...and sign
certificate of adoption of the baby panda.
Of course.
- Please.
- This way, sir.
Thank you.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
I attended the event with Jackie.
How many times have I told you?
Single. I'm single.
I'm single now.
It's not what you think.
Wow.
Ugh...
I remember the last time
when I feel really nervous...
...I received an Oscar.
O.
Hello.
I am very happy and flattered...
...can adopt a baby panda.
If you want a photo with Jackie,
I can help you.
Thank you. That's it.
If you want his signature...
I already have one.
Then if you want...
...all over the world.
I promise.
I will try my best
to take care of it.
Let us all pray
so that the baby panda grows strong...
...and healthy!
CENTER CONTROL ROOM
PANDA HALL
NOAH ZOO PANDA HOUSE
Wow wow.
Naming a baby panda
is a very important thing.
I'll think about it, okay?
Thank you!
CCTV camera in panda house
has been turned off.
And all the exits
has been locked.
This is the only exit.
The access card.
Boss.
There is an unexpected situation
that just happened.
Who adopted his panda
is a famous movie star...
Come on!
He never listens to you.
Look at that.
Cute, right?
Please take a photo.
The panda looks like yours?
INTERESTING FACTS ABOUT PANDA
Who is cuter?
Panda or Jackie?
Hello?
Overall,
you can take more photos.
Hello?
Hello.
Glad to be of service.
If you need guidance...
Hello!
Step back!
Move!
Don't move! Stand back!
Get down!
Kneel down!
- Ladies and gentlemen!
- What happened?
Don't panic. We are here.
not to hurt anyone.
We are here just for
the baby panda.
But, excuse me. Excuse me.
Whatever happens?
Call the police.
Okay!
Yes.
CENTRAL CONTROL ROOM,
NOAH ZOO
Do not move!
Kneel down!
I said get on your knees, did you hear me?
Do not move!
How dare you!
I'm the director here!
I won't allows you to take...
...a single wild boar
from my zoo...
...especially pandas!
Oh yes?
Okay. The boar is negotiable.
- Oh yes?
- Yes.
- Yes?
What's that...?
It's Jackie!
Jackie?
What is he doing here?
Move!
Get down!
Get down! Get down!
Move!
Step back!
Get down!
What is the star of this movie?
can really fight?
Yes. He's great.
He is good at kung fu.
Oh yes?
- Let's see.
- What?
Let's see later!
CALL 911
How?
Huh?
- Have you called the police?
- No signal.
No signal?
- Hold the panda first.
- Good.
Let me check what happened?
Jackie, Jackie.
Is that you?
Yes. I'm Jackie Chan.
- Hi.
Okay.
Where's the baby panda?
Panda?
Ugh...
Through this way.
Catch the panda.
Hey, be careful.
The panda is very fragile.
Okay, Boss.
What do you need it for?
That baby panda?
Who are you?
You really can
fight like in the movies?
Ugh...
I'm just a kung-fu movie star.
Go!
Go now!
Oh I see?
Don't mess around, Jackie.
- Hey.
- Stop!
Stop!
Load
Intensive disinfection begins
Hey.
You are great.
Let go. I can't fight.
I'm just a filmmaker.
I just...
Friend. Okay?
Let me go.
Okay.
Forgive me.
It was just an accident.
You...
...has no martial arts morals.
Wow.
Can you speak Mandarin?
I know your tricks, Jackie.
I've watched all your movies.
Can't escape, right? Got you.
Wait, wait.
Wait.
Why do you want to fight?
You have to, Jackie.
Okay...
...in that case.
Wait.
I think it's better here.
Here.
Look?
The arena.
Here!
Okay.
Come on!
Yeah!
This isn't a movie, Jackie.
Get up!
Where are you going?
Stop, stop.
Okay?
You win!
I will surrender!
I give up!
Do not come close!
Do you want this?
Feel this!
I will whip you!
Feel this.
Feel it.
I will whip you!
Feel it!
You deserve this!
I will whip you!
You lie!
You said you couldn't fight!
You don't have one either
martial arts morals.
I will kill you.
BABY CARE
It's me.
Come in.
Come in, the door is over there.
I'll bang your head!
Unlucky.
Have you seen the panda?
No, I haven't seen it.
What's happening inside?
Who knows.
A group of people suddenly came
to kidnap the panda.
- Call the police.
- No signal.
No signal?
It doesn't matter.
There is me.
I will protect you.
Harry?
Did you see anyone passing by?
No.
Don't let anything get out, okay?
Good.
Harry.
There isn't any?
There isn't any.
It's over. Come on.
BABY CARE
Hello.
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Hey.
You!
- You idiot! Stop!
- Stop!
Stop!
I'm not good at beating people...
...but I can stand being beaten!
- Is he okay?
- He looks hurt.
Unlucky.
Do not move.
How can I move?
Calm.
What is this place?
good enough for you, Jackie?
Come on.
Okay.
Why is it so difficult?
fight with him? Damn!
Come on.
Close the door!
Closed!
Hurry up!
What should we do?
You ask me?
If not for you,
then ask who? Him?
I can't help it.
- I'm not familiar with this place.
- 3rd floor.
Tony.
Jackie Chan.
I'm your big fan.
Who's he?
She is the socialite of Noah Island.
My name is Tony.
Getting there.
Hello, Handsome.
- Can you let me through?
- "Oshi' in Korean.
Korean: Handsome Brother,
can you let me through?
- There is no way out!
- Huh?
I'll just look for it.
They're coming!
Come on, come on!
Come on. Don't be afraid.
There is no way ahead!
There is no road here.
- Get on!
- This is a tall building!
No, no!
I can't do it!
Do not be afraid.
I I...
I'm just a panda nanny!
Let's just say the road is flat.
- Walk as if it's flat.
- It's flat! Flat!
Yes!
Don't look down!
Which way is it headed?
This...
Like a dead end!
Come on.
Here.
Where are we going?
We jump from here.
What?
We can't go back anymore.
This panda balloon will hold you.
- Trust me.
- I don't believe you.
Jackie.
I'm just an ordinary nanny.
I'm not your substitute.
Jump on the count of three.
- I don't want to try!
- One...
Are you okay?
- Car!
- Get on!
- Where are we going?
- Seatbelt.
Straight ahead.
Come on!
Ahh...
Where are you going now?
Straight ahead.
They escape in a panda tour car.
Find them!
They entered the storage area.
It's out of reach
our supervision.
James.
They headed to the storage area.
He is very heavy.
Hey, Boss. Someone's calling you.
Boss.
Jackie suddenly appears
and took the panda.
- Jackie?
- Movie star.
Tell James...
...so that he...
...find the panda
before I got there.
Come on...
...we go to the pier.
CHARGING
I'm awake.
I'm awake. I'm awake.
Do not rush.
Game Completed
Fast!
Come on, Everyone!
What?
Borrow your gun.
Come on! Jump!
I'm coming!
Get down. Come on!
Let me go!
Everything.
Get out.
Find a safe hiding place.
Everyone, follow me.
This way. Come on, hurry!
I will repair the tools
communication and calling for help.
How about you, David?
I'll look for Jackie.
Good.
Wow, your machine...
...why is it working so slowly?
All our equipment here is slow.
Maybe for safety reasons.
- He goes.
- Come on, find him!
- Cute Baby!
Cute Baby!
Baby Gemoy.
Cute Baby?
Cute Baby!
Su Xiaozhu.
Did you find it?
Look.
He slept soundly like a baby.
He must have eaten too much.
That's all he eats.
Is it really delicious?
- Huh?
- No.
Hmm.
Hey.
Check your cell phone signal now.
Oh yes.
I think they already have
take over the central control room.
It's finished.
Then this place is not safe.
Don't say
something that brings bad luck.
Come on, come on. Hide.
Is there any other way out?
There's a side door there.
Okay.
- Go when I say go.
- Okay.
Ready?
Go!
Here!
Hey.
Don't shoot, you idiot!
- We need the panda alive!
- Okay.
- The door won't open.
- You can't open it?
- What's wrong with your mouth?
- Forget it.
- Come on, come on!
- I found it!
Come here.
Unlucky!
Come on, come on!
- Come on, come on! Get on!
- Come on.
Come on, come on!
Step on my back!
Can I?
- Yes! Just do it!
- Okay!
There are stairs!
- Look, there's an elevator!
- Good!
He's down!
Good grief!
He's just like in the movies!
I have to take a photo.
You stupid,
do you want his autograph or what?
- Well.
Boss.
What should we do?
Jackie is up again.
Who chose to take the elevator, huh?
Calm down, Xiaozhu!
Watch out for the panda!
Don't say anything!
I'm afraid of heights!
Panda! Throw the panda!
Hurry up!
Jump now!
- Very clever!
- I'm great!
- Wow, that's dangerous.
- Where am I going to be thrown?
Jump!
- Cute Baby! Cute Baby!
- Oh yes.
You are okay?
Xiaozhu!
Huh?
You didn't manage to escape?
How can I escape?
If you can't?
What a waste of time!
- Jackie.
- Huh?
Give me the panda.
I give you the panda,
you let him go.
Okay.
He hasn't said anything yet.
No, no.
Stay there.
- Roy.
- Yes?
- Take the panda.
- I?
You win.
Don't be afraid, Little Baby.
Be careful.
You're like in a movie.
So cute!
Wow, so smooth.
Gun!
Don't... don't move!
I have never fired
real gun before!
- Can the gun go off?
- I just scared them.
The more I'm afraid,
the more they fear.
- Calm.
- Watch out.
- Okay, I'm calm.
- Yes, calm down.
Where's your gun?
Hey.
Cute Baby!
Move!
You sent Baby Gemoy...
NOAH PACKAGING MACHINE
PACKAGING FRESH MEAT
Cute Baby!
Not you guys again!
No!
You guys move so fast.
Help me, Jackie!
I'm surrounded!
- Jackie! Save me!
- Hey.
You guys don't move!
I pointed my gun to his head!
I can't breathe.
Hey, keep an eye out!
Tell everyone to
drop their guns!
Everyone, put down your guns!
He pointed a gun at my head!
Hurry up and say it!
Or I'll blow your head off!
Listen to him!
The gun in his hand was shaking!
- Xiaozhu!
- What?
Take their guns!
Tony!
Hello, Zhuzhu.
Help me!
It's still up to me if it's important.
I'll shoot!
Fast!
In the box!
Say!
Fast!
Put it in the box!
- I hate working overtime.
- Go as far as you can!
Xiao Zhu.
Go with Tony.
The three of us will go.
Okay, Jackie, take care of yourself.
I'll go first.
I can't go, Jackie.
Get rid of him!
Let him go!
Fast!
Come on!
I'll go first, Jackie.
Boss!
He doesn't have a gun!
Don't have a gun?
Do not move!
Get me out of here!
Shut up!
What should I do?
ELECTRIC FORKLIF OPERATOR'S MANUAL
Raise your hands!
Don't touch my post!
Jackie!
I came to save you!
I will kill you!
Jackie!
Wait a moment.
There are only 3 words
that I don't know!
T... R... A...
V... E...
Die you...
Jackie, I came to save you!
♪ Bring my beautiful song home, darling ♪
♪ Leave your smile here ♪
I came to save you!
♪ Because tomorrow my beautiful song will go global ♪
Jackie, come on up!
You almost killed me!
You're welcome!
Come on!
♪ Because tomorrow your happy smile will be
become spring flowers everywhere ♪
Go on!
Get on now!
♪ Will become a spring flower
everywhere ♪
That's 100 million dollars...
...stupid!
Unlucky!
♪ Leave your smile here ♪
Can you?
Wait!
- Hey, hey.
- Geez!
Where are you going?
Wrong way!
Do you have a driver's license or not?
Stop!
Get in the car!
Director.
We have started evacuating
visitors from the island.
Good. Let's find them.
How long before the tool
our communication working again?
They are destructive
communication base power module.
It takes time until
can be fully operational again.
Hurry up.
Director, look!
Check out the panda!
He is fine!
Hey.
They're after us!
Get close to them!
- They're coming!
- Right behind us!
- Come on, come on!
- Blue hair, Jackie!
He's trying to catch me, Jackie!
Ouch.
Hold me tight!
Jackie!
Hold on tight!
Are you okay, Jackie?
Jackie!
Oh.
Jackie, help me!
Jackie!
He's up!
You'll be fine, Baby Gemoy.
Do not be afraid.
Help me, Jackie!
Jackie! Are you okay?
Let go!
You're okay now.
You're already down.
Point the camera at the car.
Even faster!
Get close to their car!
No!
What's that?
Take it down.
Hey, stop.
Stop.
Put me down!
Don't!
Unlucky!
Even faster!
Jackie, give me the panda.
Chase them! Chase them!
- Jackie, they're after us!
- I know!
- This is a dead end!
- What?
Open the gate!
The gate is open!
Hurry up!
Don't let them get away!
Okay, Boss!
Wait.
Stand.
Close the gate...
...Now!
Why is the gate closed?
Do not move!
Come on!
Come closer! Come closer!
Succeed!
Yes!
They did it!
Stop screaming!
The gate is closed.
YOU ARE ENTERING A WILD ANIMAL AREA
This should be the easiest job.
Open the door now!
- Good work!
- This gate...
Someone help us.
- Director!
- What?
Definitely the director!
The director is in the central control room!
There! There!
We are safe now.
WILD ANIMAL AREA
DO NOT GET OUT OF THE VEHICLE
- Jackie.
- Yes?
- We're safe now, right?
- How do I know?
Even now more dangerous now.
NOAH ZOO
- The petrol is out.
- Out of gas?
How come the gas is running out now?
Is this my fault?
Unlucky!
What is it?
Why are you swearing?
Lion.
Unlucky.
- What now?
- He's hungry.
He is hungry, so is the lion.
Feed him.
Do not let
he groaned again, okay?
He only drinks milk at this hour.
- Milk?
- That's all, right?
- Yes.
Jackie.
Is rhino milk also included?
I think so. In Mandarin,
the name is the same, namely 'niu'.
What about woniu snails?
Shut up.
Who's going there?
Don't shout.
Not me.
No.
Jackie!
Just run, don't wait for me!
You said you were a lousy athlete, right?
Are you going to leave me?
Watch the docks.
No ships are allowed to pass.
Make sure we follow the meal schedule
all animals strictly.
Director.
Alright, Everyone.
You guys should
get out of here now...
...and looking for a place
safe hiding.
- How about you, Director?
- I?
You know what my job is
before I became a director?
I am the deputy director.
Safe!
Do not move.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Hello...
...Director.
Please open the gate.
With pleasure.
Oops!
Forgive me.
You have to find it yourself.
Is that all you're capable of, coward?
In that case,
we just have to blow the door down.
Search carefully!
Don't let them escape.
- Okay sir.
- Understand.
Now there is a wild animal
or mercenaries in the mountains.
Be careful.
What should we do?
Here.
This lighthouse long abandoned.
No outsiders know about this.
This is the electrical box.
Be careful, Jackie.
- What is it?
- What are you doing?
There's a spider up there.
- Spider...
- Calm down!
- Slowly, Jackie.
- Yes.
Hold him.
I mean the panda!
Whether there is danger or not.
I'll check it first.
- Jackie!
- Jackie.
Hey.
It's safe.
Get on!
Boss.
Our men are still searching.
But, this place is too big.
We have an extra person
search in this area.
Search the entire area.
Your team will search there.
You two come with me.
Okay.
- Are the pandas full yet?
- Yes.
Thank you, Jackie.
What for?
I was the one who adopted him.
It's my job to protect him.
Why did you become...
...a panda nanny?
I like.
When I was in elementary school...
...I went to the zoo
during a spring outing.
I am very impressed
when seeing the panda.
While in college,
I study zoology.
During the holidays...
...i went to the panda base
as a volunteer.
I work and
spending time with pandas...
...for 5 consecutive years.
If you think about it
it's like a dream.
So, you will work as
nanny forever?
RESIGNATION LETTER
Do you want to stop?
My parents want me to stop.
They are getting older...
...and hope I can
live with them.
Every time I try to stop...
...he will hug my legs...
...and I can't
move at all.
How about you, Jackie?
You have fought for decades.
What's holding you back?
What's holding me back?
What's holding me back is...
...the word "Action".
"Action"?
I remember
when I was 8 years old.
I went to the shooting location
and heard the director scream...
... "Action!"
At that time I was young,
and don't know what it means.
But every time I hear the word
"Action" is, somehow...
...I feel a sensation of energy
which never runs out.
After that...
... "Action" has become my synonym...
...my trumpet...
...and my initial trigger.
Before they say
the word "Action"...
...I'm like all of you...
...I can feel afraid,
pain...
...and tired.
But as soon as I heard
the word "Action"...
...I will be a hero...
...who can do
any action...
...and achieve everything.
In the blink of an eye...
...decades have passed.
Life is like a dream.
But people always wake up
from a dream.
So, what should we do?
Rolling...
...and sleep again.
Jackie!
Jackie, don't forget
naming the panda.
Oh yes.
What's a good name?
Hey, help me.
You also gave me an idea.
It's easy to name a panda.
For example...
...Pingping, An'an, security...
...Gaogao, Xingxing, happiness...
...Mimi, Huhu is confused.
They were fast asleep
like a dazed person.
One we call "Mimi"
and the other one "Huhu".
Panda Huh.
Good name.
Come on! Get out!
There!
- They are upstairs.
- So noisy.
Catch them!
Someone's coming!
Come on! Come on, let's go!
There's someone here, Jackie!
Get up!
Someone's coming!
What are we waiting for? Let's go!
Come on, come on!
Don't let them get away!
Catch them!
Boss, we did it.
Boss, we've caught them.
We have to get him on board.
We're back and I
will talk to them.
Boss.
They are already here.
What about my panda?
He was vomiting
and don't eat anything.
You.
Take care of my panda.
Possible...
...I can let you live.
- Come on.
- What should we do?
- Meanwhile Jackie...
- Hi.
...stay here.
The ransom must be large.
Okay. Let's go.
Come on!
No!
I will meet...
Stop!
You...
Throw him into the sea.
- Oh...
- Okay, Boss!
No!
Come on!
Please! No!
Don't!
Come on!
Enter!
Cute Baby?
Cute Baby!
Wait a minute, Baby Gemoy.
I'll get you out soon.
CALL 911
Come on, come on!
This is your last meal.
Eat it.
Eat and go.
Are you still alive?
What do you think?
Are you surprised?
Surprised.
Me... They both...
They are my best friends now.
Harry.
Roy.
Say hello to Jackie!
- Jackie.
What is this?
No, no!
Perhaps!
I can give you money.
I will give...
Don't...
No... Don't...
No...
No, no!
Please.
Can I have a life jacket?
I give you money.
What do you want?
What do you want?!
Forget it!
Just throw me into the sea!
Love!
No love!
No, no.
We love...
- Jackie!
- Yes, yes!
Jackie.
Jackie. We love Jackie!
Geez!
Ahh.
You two, my fans?
Yes!
Show.
- Time to show it.
- Show me!
Okay, okay!
No, no.
I believe in you guys.
Sitting.
Okay, okay.
Jackie, here's the thing.
They kidnapped the panda
to be sold to rich businessmen.
But they don't know
who is this entrepreneur.
So, that's how this ship will be
anchored, the panda will be delivered.
Oh no.
What about Xiaozhu?
Find the panda and Xiaozhu soon.
You can make sure that
all communications are active on the island?
We'll go first.
See you tomorrow.
Be careful.
Okay!
What are you doing?
- Stop!
- Get your hands off me!
- Just leave it!
- Take off the box!
- Stop, please.
- Go!
Take off the box!
- Stop!
Don't touch the panda!
Stay here.
- Save Xiaozhu! Quickly!
- Okay.
Xiao Zhu.
I came to save you!
What are you doing?
- Get away!
- It's me!
It's me!
CARGO
Okay friend.
It's time to play.
Hear.
I...
...will stay
and follow the truck.
You two get out of here now.
Then call the police, okay?
You're wearing my watch, okay?
What?
Your watch?
I can't use it.
Jackie is great.
Boss.
- Boss.
Friends,
Don't trust this person, okay?
How about
Our 100 million dollars?
Already in the car, Boss.
Continue.
They saw me.
What?
You mean the two of them?
It doesn't matter.
They are one of us.
They are one of us now.
They have defected.
What does it mean?
Oh, oh.
The motorbike, right?
- Lower your voice!
- Okay, okay!
What do they mean?
They told us to...
...ride a motorbike and run away.
Do not be afraid.
I will count to 3.
1, 2, 3. Run!
- Who's driving?
Hello!
Hello.
Can you ride a motorbike?
James!
The police came.
Take the weapon!
Take a defensive position!
Come on!
Hold on! Cover the exit!
The panda was successfully captured.
Wait.
This job...
...it's harder than I thought.
So...
...100 million is not enough.
We need more.
That's the price we agreed on.
Do not move!
Why are you here?
Give me the panda.
I don't want to
hurt anyone, okay?
Pack.
Sir will be home soon.
Wow.
- Jackie, how are you?
- I am busy.
You just talk.
The police already know your location.
They are on their way there.
- I found Baby Gemoy.
- What?
Baby Gemoy.
- Jackie, is Baby Gemoy okay?
- Caught!
What happened to him?
Cute Baby!
I mean me!
That means Baby Gemoy is fine.
- Jackie, the police will be here soon.
- What did you say?
Hang in there.
Ugh...
I can't...
I can't hold it in anymore.
Why?
- Jackie!
- I can't stand it...
Jackie, just hold on a little longer!
Jackie!
Jackie, speak up!
What's wrong with you?
I'm like all of you...
...I can feel scared...
...pain...
...and tired.
But as soon as I heard
the word "Action"...
...I will be a hero...
...who can do
any action...
...and achieve everything.
Jackie!
Listen!
Action!
- Do not move!
- Perhaps.
Perhaps.
Don't...
Jackie, how are you?
Are you okay?
Hello? Jackie? Jackie!
Jackie, what happened?
What happened to Baby Gemoy?
Hello, Jackie? Jackie!
- You're so troublesome!
- I know!
- Jackie, how is Baby Gemoy?
- He's fine.
Me too.
Stop it.
- We met at the pier.
- Okay! Jackie...
Are you the one who wants pandas?
Why?
6 months ago...
...Pasha was diagnosed
suffering from leukemia.
And at that moment...
...the baby panda is born.
And Pasha saw it
first time on TV.
Since that...
...we went to the garden
the animal almost every week.
Pasha leaned in front of the glass...
...and stare at it all day.
Pasha's condition deteriorated rapidly.
I just want that panda...
...stay with him for just a moment.
Possible...
...he will get better.
He doesn't even know
what happened.
All...
This is all my fault.
Allah...
...please forgive me.
Hey.
- Where is the panda?
- Brought to the port.
Harbor?
Please.
Am I dreaming?
You are not dreaming.
Are you hungry?
Do you want to eat?
Ahh...
He shouldn't drink this.
I'll just drink, okay?
You are okay?
I've been here for a long time
want to meet you...
...but I'm sick.
Do you know?
That's why he came to see you.
You will recover, be healthy...
...and get well soon.
Can I play with him?
Of course.
You can play with it
as long as you want.
6 MONTHS LATER,
PANDA BASE IN CHENGDU, SICHUAN
Hello, Panda!
David!
Clean the swimming pool.
Then come here and
clean the panda's poop.
I'm not hungry, Jackie.
I'll eat when I'm done.
Hu Hu!
Here.
- Here.
Hu Hu!
Come here. Come on.
HUHU... DATE OF BIRTH: JULY 10, 2023
HOMELAND: SICHUAN YA AN
"HUHU" HAS A SWEET FACE. SHE IS ENERGETIC,
LIKES TO PERCH TO PLAY AND SLEEP.
Jackie, Jackie!
We will be in Shanghai at 3 o'clock.
for film festivals...
...and go to Milan for the weekend
to promote your new film.
By the way, the Corgi dog that is owned
The Queen during her lifetime, was stolen.
So the British government called...
...to ask what you are
have a plan to save him?
Have.
Wow, what?
Plan T, T for no plan!
THIS STORY IS COMPLETELY FICTION
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMFUL
IN THE MAKING OF THIS FILM.
ALL MAIN ANIMAL CHARACTERS
IS A VISUAL EFFECT
THANK YOU TO PANDA XIANGXIANG,
YAYA AND AN'AN AT PANDA BASE
♪ Welcome to Noah ♪
♪ Sunshine,
like the wind, feels so free... ♪
♪ ...and fun ♪
♪ Put everything aside... ♪
♪ ...and our leader is coming too ♪
♪ She's so cute ♪
♪ He has 2 black eyes
different sizes, cool, right? ♪
♪ Her adorable appearance... ♪
♪ ...can make you
forget all your troubles ♪
♪ Whoops, Whoops ♪
♪ Everyone loves him ♪
♪ He was daydreaming,
chewing bamboo leaves ♪
♪ If there are stupid bad people
trying to get close to him ♪
♪ He will secretly find a way
to avoid them ♪
♪ ...and overcome all obstacles ♪
♪ Whoops, Whoops ♪
♪ Everyone loves him ♪
♪ Life is colorful and rich ♪
♪ If anyone is in despair,
come quickly to Huhu ♪
♪ He will come with good intentions ♪
♪ To give happiness ♪
♪ With the sound of gunfire
the scary one ♪
♪ There is a cunning villain ♪
♪ But she's still in my arms,
without knowing what to fear ♪
♪ Execute our plan now
in the most familiar way ♪
♪ No matter how much
the villain is here ♪
♪ Let's defeat them all ♪
♪ Even if I get hurt,
tired or scared... ♪
♪ ...face
all the difficulties and obstacles ♪
♪ I won't be easily defeated ♪
♪ When I hear the screams
"Action" ♪
♪ I will be energetic
do any action ♪
♪ And become a person
who defeated all the villains... ♪
♪ ...and save Huhu.
This is the "Panda Plan"! ♪
♪ Whoops, Whoops ♪
♪ Everyone loves him ♪
♪ Let's protect it together ♪
♪ Even though there are many criminals,
defeat them one by one ♪
♪ We will make
the future is bright ♪
♪ And share the love
and our love ♪
♪ Whoops, Whoops ♪
♪ Everyone loves him ♪
♪ What makes you
survive this far? ♪
♪ No matter if I'm afraid,
hurt or tired ♪
♪ As long as I hear the screams
"Action" ♪
♪ All my strength will return ♪
♪ Whoops, Whoops ♪
♪ Everyone loves him ♪
♪ Let's protect it together ♪
♪ Even though there are many criminals,
defeat them one by one ♪
♪ We will make
the future is bright ♪
♪ And share the love
and our love ♪
♪ Whoops, Whoops ♪
♪ Everyone loves him ♪
♪ What makes you
survive this far? ♪
♪ No matter if I'm afraid,
hurt or tired ♪
♪ As long as I hear the screams
"Action" ♪
♪ All my strength will return ♪
♪ Action ♪
♪ Welcome to Noah ♪