[traffic rumbles]
[mournful music]
[static hiss]
["Paint it Black" by The
Rolling Stones instrumental]
[whooshes]
[whirring]
[♪]
[electricity crackles]
[whooshing]
[♪]
[static hiss]
[reporter] The trial for the
chairman of Kwang Industries
is set to begin in high court.
The trial is a culmination
of a year-long investigation
of Korean seafood tycoon,
Kwang Gim, or "King" Kwang.
Chairman Kwang faces charges
that range from selling
counterfeit carbon offsets
to violating bans
on net fishing.
[reporters shout all at once]
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm here to apologize
to the true victims today.
The Kwang family,
and our 200,000
hard-working employees.
For them, I look forward
to proving my innocence.
Thank you.
[indistinct]
[reporters shout all at once]
- What the hell was that?
- Kwang.
The charges are bullshit.
You control trade routes.
Distribution centers.
You're a billionaire, and what,
they come up against you with
fishing charges?
- Get out.
- Oh, okay.
[reporters shouting]
Where's my wife?
[phone dialing beeps]
[phone buzzing]
["Moon River" by Henry Mancini
instrumental]
Good morning, madam.
May I help you?
Just looking.
Please.
- Hmm.
- A brand-new model.
[♪]
The Ferrari 488 Pista Spider.
It is the most beautiful
thing in this room.
Hmm.
Second only to you, of course.
- Can I look inside?
- Yes, for sure.
No, inside.
Of course.
Behold, Ferrari's most powerful
V8 engine.
Twin turbocharged, 3.9 liter,
over 700 horsepower.
Let's try it.
Yes.
[car door slams]
[engine starts, revs loudly]
[♪]
[music builds]
Ready?
[engine revs]
[engine roars]
[shallow panicked breaths]
You know how--
how to drive, huh?
- Yeah.
- [indistinct]
[engine revs]
Whoa!
- [engine roars]
- Whoa!
[panting] Whoa!
[grunts]
- [tires squeal]
- [horns honk]
[roar of engine]
[whimpering]
Thank God.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
[groaning]
Whoa!
[panicked gasping]
[roar of engine]
[whimpering]
[horns blare]
[salesman whimpering]
[roar of engine]
[tires squeal]
What the hell are you doing?
This just came in.
We haven't even
calibrated it yet.
Oh, I'm sorry, Ms. Kwang.
I didn't see it was you.
The timing's off.
How long would it take
to adjust the timing?
Two days.
Fine, for you, just one hour.
Thank you.
[tense music]
[car rumbles]
[♪]
[button beeps]
[gentle music]
[soft classical music
plays over speakers]
Joey, my love, you're home.
Champagne?
What are we celebrating?
Just another day with
my beautiful wife.
Cheers.
Where were you today?
You didn't pick up your phone.
Bad signal.
Bad battery.
Just, my trial started today.
How did it go?
Officials want an investigation.
Board members want my head.
Other than that, just great.
I'm sorry. Who's the snitch?
That's an excellent question.
You don't think it was me?
Oh, darling, your imagination
is priceless.
You do know that a wife
can't testify.
Then it's a good thing
we're married.
Is it?
Of course
it is.
You know, there is a thing
I want to discuss with you.
Is it necessary for you
to buy everything you see?
Where does it all go?
Oh me, darling.
I'm merely asking.
Do you need another Ferrari?
- [button beeps]
- [doors whir]
I bought it for you.
Happy birthday.
Sweetheart.
Thank you.
[soft hum of chatter
from television]
[reporter] Shares of Kwang
dropped over 30%
after today's allegations.
The stock had already
dropped to its all-time low
earlier this month,
after officials assembled
a task force
to investigate Kwang...
- [soft knocking]
- [door bangs]
Mom! It's knock, wait,
then enter.
You can't just barge in.
I'm not a baby.
You'll always be my baby.
[laughs softly]
[sighs]
This is the best part of my day.
Yeah. Love you too, Mom.
[Joey sighs]
Oh...
What are you doing?
Unpacking, Mom.
Getting out.
Stop for a second.
What's going on?
Kwang has just made the list
of all-time assholes.
Right next to Freddy Krueger
and Leatherface.
- Not funny.
- Sorry. Bad joke.
But he's gonna be in jail
by the end of the week.
And I don't want to be here
when that happens,
and neither do you.
And where will you go?
Paris. The Ocean Outlaws
is docked there right now.
They're starting a new
mission next week.
Heading to Milagro.
Kwang has boats in Milagro.
How's that going to look?
Like I have the will
for revolution and change.
Like somebody's finally
standing up to Kwang.
He's destroying entire
marine ecosystems.
- Shhh!
- [door slams]
Mom, no.
Just because you like
spending Kwang's money
doesn't mean I have
to stay here.
Hey, stop it.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
[sighs] Fine.
[gentle music]
I know you and Kwang
don't get along.
- He's gross.
- He's not.
I don't know why
you married him.
Because a long time ago,
I needed help.
We needed help,
and Kwang was there.
We can't forget that,
no matter what you think of him.
Do you understand?
I'll take you
to Paris next weekend.
Okay?
Do you miss Dad?
Of course I do.
Then why don't you
ever talk about him?
Because sometimes it's easier
to forget the past.
- Besides, I told you everything.
- He was a pastry chef.
He died in a car accident.
The end.
Seems there's a lot more
to fill in.
All you need to know
is whatever happened,
he brought me you.
And I wouldn't change
any of that.
[Raymond sighs]
[Joey laughs softly]
[sirens wail]
[traffic rumbles]
[muffled police radio chatter]
Any of you guys got a cigarette?
Hands up, dirtbag!
I'm not gonna say it again.
Yeah, I heard you
the first time.
- Hands up. Now!
- All right, officer, please.
Come on. I will comply.
Just give me a minute.
All right?
You're scaring the fish.
[police radio chatter]
- [handcuffs rasp]
- [siren wails]
- Wait. Whoa, whoa! Come on.
- [officer] Let's go.
Officer, get those cuffs
off my agent, now!
- [officer] Your agent
didn't have any ID.
- Because he's undercover.
Where do you suggest
he keep his badge? His ass?
Up yours? Get out!
- Give me the key.
- Get out!
Look after the fish.
John, you okay?
I will be,
once I get a cigarette.
- Where's Santiago?
- He's fine.
[Santiago whimpers]
Santiago?
[paramedic] Everything's
gonna be fine.
You were supposed to observe
and report, not crash and burn.
What the hell happened?
Our shift was going
really smooth.
We were getting through
a lot of Kung Pow orders.
- They're very good, by the way,
here, you should try it.
- John, stop stalling.
All right, fine.
I was finishing a tray
of crème brûlées,
and the perps showed up.
[utensils clatter]
[flame whooshes]
[tense music]
We were getting it all
on camera, and then Santiago...
[♪]
- Hey! [chuckles]
- [man] Is it yours?
No, it's a fake. No, it's
a fake one. It's a fake one.
You know, yesterday was a party,
and-- with my kids,
and I was police, you know?
No, tranquilo. Tranquilo.
No, no, no.
- Tranquilo, por favor.
- Hey, hey, buddy, buddy, buddy.
It's a friend of mine.
He-- it's a joke, dude.
It-- it's not even real.
It's not even real.
[fighting grunts]
["Ring of Fire" by Johnny Cash]
♪ Love is a burning thing ♪
[fighting screams]
♪ And it makes a fiery ring ♪
[fighting grunts]
♪ Bound by wild desire ♪
[metallic clang]
[man screams]
♪ I fell in to a ring of fire ♪
- [screaming]
- [water sizzles]
♪ I fell into a burning
Ring of fire ♪
♪ I went down, down, down ♪
♪ And the flames went higher ♪
♪ And it burns, burns, burns ♪
♪ The ring of fire ♪
[Santiago whimpers]
[fighting grunts]
[pots clang]
[men screaming]
- [heavy thud]
- [screaming]
[metallic clang]
[fighting grunts]
♪ I fell into a burning
Ring of fire ♪
♪ I went down, down, down ♪
♪ And the flames ♪
So, I just want
to stop fighting.
- What do you want?
- I just want to eat.
- [laughs]
- Well, you know
I don't like spicy.
[fish tank bubbles]
♪ I fell in to a ring of fire ♪
Oh, man.
[all gasping for breath]
♪ I fell into a burning
Ring of fire ♪
Oh, my God.
All right, just hang on.
All right? Hold up.
♪ And the flames went higher ♪
[sighs]
♪ And it burns, burns, burns ♪
- [aggressive grunt]
- Huh? Dude, please.
Come on. Give me a minute.
[sighs heavily]
Oh, man.
[sighs] Okay.
All right.
[machine beeping]
- All right.
- [fighting grunts]
[screaming]
- [whimpering]
- Sorry, man.
[grunt of effort]
[Santiago moaning]
[tense music]
[fighting grunts]
- [screaming]
- [bone cracking]
[fighting grunts]
[John screaming]
[tense music builds]
[loud clattering]
Ah!
[struggling grunts]
- [heavy thunk]
- [groans]
[fighting grunts]
[screech of metal scraping]
Ah!
[struggling grunts]
[indistinct]
[fighting grunts]
I'll kill you!
Unh! [gasps]
Fire! Ah!
[groaning]
[splashing]
[screaming]
[diners all shouting at once]
[plates and utensils clattering]
This way. This way, please.
- [Santiago coughing]
- All right, buddy.
Come on, up you get.
Let's go.
- Ah! Oh!
- You stay here.
Just stay here, all right?
- [Santiago groaning]
- I'll be back.
[groans]
[fire whooshes]
Oh, no.
[splashing]
As an agent of the DEA,
I'm authorized to offer you
asylum for any information
you have on Kwang Enterprises.
No.
- [groaning]
- [splashing]
[gasping]
I can offer you a green card,
at an apartment in Arizona.
It's very nice.
No, no. Ai!
[gurgling screams]
[groaning]
- [gunshots boom]
- [screaming]
- [glass shatters]
- [roar of water]
[John groaning]
- [panting]
- [fire roaring]
[smoke alarm beeping]
[water pattering]
[splashing]
Come on, come on, come on,
come on.
Come on.
[water pattering]
And that's when they put
the bracelets on.
[distant police radio chatter]
I suppose you want to go see?
Let's go.
[John] Watch your step.
[splashing]
[Charlotte] Ah! Is that a fish?
John, what the--
Six months of undercover work
up in smoke.
Please tell me, how am I
supposed to build
a case on this?
You can't. There's absolutely
nothing useful here.
- [hiss of air]
- [door beeping]
I don't know.
Maybe you can use this?
[hopeful music]
[chuckles]
[birds chirping]
Sir! Sir.
[Charlotte] With the help
of local law enforcement,
we were able to recover
nearly 400 kilos of heroin.
Estimated street value,
$300 million.
But there is still
much to be done.
Every day in the United States,
120 people die
from drug overdose.
We are committed to fighting
this problem at its source,
and stopping those
who would profit
from this death and suffering.
Don't care who you are,
where you are,
you cannot run, you cannot hide.
We will find you.
Damn it!
[ominous music]
[sighs heavily]
[music turns melancholy]
[♪]
[Joey sighs]
[gasps] Oh!
Oh, you scared me!
I'm sorry about earlier.
I wasn't mad at you.
[Joey] Hard to tell these days.
It's just this ridiculous trial.
[Joey sighs]
Let's go to the summer house
for the weekend.
- Get out of here.
- Oh!
Sure. That will be nice.
[Kwang] Thank you
for my birthday present.
I like it a lot.
[Joey sighs]
[Kwang] But you know
what I would love more?
[Joey sighs]
Let me go freshen up.
Joey, let's just talk.
- About what?
- About us.
About love.
I don't know if I have
any love to give.
Of course you do.
You love Raymond.
You love shopping.
You love me.
Do I?
No.
[melancholy music]
Joey, it's been 15 years.
15 years since I've taken
care of you and Raymond.
Whoever broke your heart
is not coming back.
Don't you think
it's time to move on?
Together?
[♪]
I love you.
[office din]
[sighs]
[siren wails distantly]
[knocking on door]
[Charlotte] What is it, Lawlor?
Hey, um, I've been going
over this tip sheet,
and there's a confidential
informant that's come forward.
Kwang Industries.
Why am I not surprised?
Illegal net fishing.
Killing dolphins.
You want to take
Kwang down for this?
We put away Al Capone
for tax fraud.
I mean, the C.I. wants
to give us his ledger.
No one with real information
is gonna rat out on Kwang.
They're all too scared of him.
This is chicken shit.
What if it isn't?
What if this is everything we
need to finally take him down?
- What's the handoff?
- Taipei.
No. Absolutely not.
After what happened last time.
- That was 15 years ago.
- [Charlotte] And look
where it's landed you.
15 years of bouncing around from
field office to field office,
and doing mostly desk work.
Look, we all want
to take Kwang down.
- You stopped the shipment.
- One shipment. One.
Take your wins as they come,
and leave the rest alone.
Charlotte, it's one weekend.
Just a couple of days, to
finally take him down for good.
Even if we wanted to, I can't
send an agent down there,
and certainly not you.
I will go deep cover.
My own assets.
- No one'll even know I'm there.
- [Charlotte] No.
- I am literally going
to pick up a ledger.
- No, absolutely not.
- Charlotte, think about--
No!
- All right, thanks.
Thank you so much.
- What is wrong with you?
You're like a dog with a bone.
Let it go.
Here.
To be perfectly clear.
A leave of absence?
You're sending me home now?
No, John.
I'm sending you on vacation.
It's what happens
when people do a good job.
Actually, a great job.
It was a solid bust.
Now, go relax.
The drugs will still be here
on Tuesday, and so will Kwang.
- Just, so, it's a long weekend.
- Yeah, John.
Go drink something fruity
on a beach somewhere.
All right.
Okay. Thanks.
Um, I will definitely
make the most of it.
- Oh! Can you do me one favor?
- What?
- Could you just watch my fish?
- Get out!
[door bangs shut]
[low hum of chatter]
[whistling a tune]
[man] Hi, I'm checking
on Flight 726 to Taipei.
- You're George Washington?
- Yep, that's me.
Welcome aboard.
Walk this way, please.
[passengers chatter]
[mellow guitar music]
[girls giggle loudly]
[video narrator
speaking in Chinese]
- Uh, excuse me, miss?
- [flight attendant] Yes?
Can I get a bourbon?
Two doubles.
Oh, after take-off.
[plane engines rumble]
[plane engine roars]
[majestic music]
[landing gear screeches]
[♪]
[music turns ominous]
[sighs]
[statue scraping]
Raymond. Good morning.
Can I help you with something?
Oh, I'm just looking
for a pencil sharpener.
Hmm.
[drawer rasping]
You know, I'd love to see
your drawings one day.
Hey, how about we go play
golf together sometime, huh?
No.
Raymond.
You know, I'm trying my best.
Why do you hate me so much?
[door bangs shut]
The Austrian women's volleyball
team will face off this weekend
against Chinese Taipei
in a preseason exhibition game
that will test
both team's new lineups.
Austrian head Coach
Jaime Newsome had this to say.
How long have you been a team?
[Jaime] We've been,
uh, together--
[reporter] ...say. How long
have you been a team?
[Jaime] We've been--
[dramatic music]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[soft hum of chatter]
Mm! Hey! Yo!
Over here.
You don't look like
a George Washington.
Yeah? You look like
you gained weight.
Hmm! Haven't you heard?
Dad bods are cool now.
- [Simmons] Say hello to Freddie.
- [John] Let's get to the hotel.
[dramatic music]
[music turns melancholy]
[people on street shouting]
[♪]
[car rumbles]
[clerk] Welcome,
Mr. Washington.
I see we have you
for the weekend.
- You do.
- [clerk] Any luggage?
Yeah, three pieces.
[clerk] Now, welcome to Taipei
Marriott Hotel.
[cases thudding]
- Ooh la la.
- I'm here to pick up
a ledger, man.
- Pray for the best.
- Pray for the worst.
Yeah, yeah.
- Hey, what time's the drop?
- [John] Five p.m.
Ooh, we've got time for a late
lunch or an early dinner.
- Which one you prefer?
- Shower.
- Shower. Hey, but this is good.
- Yes.
Yeah! [laughing]
[gentle music]
[footsteps thudding]
Come with me now.
[ominous music]
[Raymond] No! [whimpering]
What are you doing? Stop it!
Stop it!
Don't have him killed!
- Enough.
- [Joey screams]
Enough!
[Joey sobbing]
- W-- Why?
- Because our beloved son
is the snitch.
No.
- I don't believe it.
- Well, believe it.
He's trying to ruin me.
Destroy everything we've built.
You're wrong. You're wrong.
You promised to protect us.
Sweetheart, I am trying
to protect us.
You think you're so clever,
don't you, huh?
[suspenseful music]
[computer keys click]
- Now, where is the ledger?
- Raymond!
Is this true?
Give it back! Give it back.
His tuna boats
are killing dolphins.
- Dolphins?
- [Raymond] His processing
plants--
You did this because
of some dolphins?
You're destroying our ecosystem!
I had to do something.
Good for you.
Taking initiative.
But where is my ledger?
Because the rest of it has
nothing to do with any dolphins!
[screaming] Leave me!
Kwang? Just give me a minute.
I'll talk to him.
Please?
Okay.
Just tell him.
Hey, it's fine.
Just tell him
what's going on, hon.
Please, Mom. Five minutes.
I just need five minutes.
I need to get the ledger
to Lawlor.
What?
Some agent, John Lawlor.
[Joey gasps]
[Raymond] John Lawlor. [panting]
He emailed me back.
I just need five more minutes.
- What are you talking about?
- Mom, please.
Five minutes.
What?
- Please, Mom.
- No. No, what-- what--
Oh my God.
Oh! What are you talking about?
- Please, Mom.
- [Kwang] Okay,
that's enough, now.
All right.
Five minutes.
[Joey sighs]
[tense music builds]
- Hit me.
- What?
It's the only way he'll talk.
Now, hit me.
I won't hit you.
[Joey sighs]
[sighs heavily]
I hate smoking.
[clock ticking]
[lighter clicks]
It's filthy.
And a burnt smell
gets into your hair,
your clothes, your fingernails.
No matter what you do,
you just can't get rid of it.
It's awful.
But when we got married,
I had to start.
The smoking smell
is nothing compared
to the smell of my husband.
The smell of sweaty desperation.
It makes me gag.
[ropes rustle]
[Joey exhales forcefully]
No matter what he does
or how much money he spends,
or how much he scrubs,
the putrid stink...
[clock ticking]
...never goes away.
[blows forcefully]
[bodyguard chuckles]
[ominous music]
- Funny?
- Ah!
Ah! Ah!
[pained grunts]
[♪]
- [blows thud]
- [clock ticking]
[tires screech]
[engine shuts off]
[♪]
- [Kwang] Die!
- [Raymond sobs quietly]
- [Kwang groans]
- [gunshots boom]
- [Raymond] No!
- Now, you tell me.
Where is my ledger?
- [Joey] Stop! Stop!
Don't touch him!
- Hmm?
- [Joey screaming]
- I gave you everything.
And you do this to me?
- Don't touch--
- [Raymond] Stop. Stop.
Please, stop.
I'll tell you where the ledger
is. Just stop it.
[Joey] Stop it! [sobbing]
I had a friend take the ledger
to the Marriott Hotel.
It's Room 2018.
What do you mean, "had"?
Hey, John. Get involved.
- They ain't got chicken feet
like this in Minnesota.
- You got xiaolongbao?
No. We got shumai, though.
You like shumai?
[doorbell chimes]
[John] I got it.
[dramatic music]
[pages rustle]
I don't believe it.
- [John] It's all here.
- [Simmons] What's that?
All this for a little red book?
You took too many guns.
Go find the ledger.
[bodyguards] Yes.
You! Keep her.
You! Come with me.
[Joey whimpers]
- And as for you...
- Mom.
...during the Joseon Dynasty,
anybody that would
break the law...
- Mommy! -...was forever
marked as a criminal.
- [Raymond] Mom!
- No! No! No!
[Kwang] And depending on
the severity of the crime...
No! Oh, no! Please! Please!
Stop! No! No! No!
...they were cut into quarters.
[screaming] Stop! Stop!
- [Joey whimpers]
- Ah!
And they would start...
- with the limbs.
- [Raymond whimpering]
- [Raymond] Oh no!
- [Joey] Oh my God!
No, Mom! No!
Don't worry, son, we'll get you
the best prosthetics
- that money can buy.
- [Raymond] No! No!
No!
[Joey and Raymond screaming]
[Joey grunts with effort]
- [Joey screams]
- [gunshots boom]
[panting]
Let him go.
Sweetheart.
What, you're killing people now?
Let us go!
You're not gonna shoot me.
Who's gonna protect you?
Who's gonna love you?
- [Raymond] Ah!
- Oh!
[sword clatters]
What?
[engine revving loudly]
Mom, slow down.
Where'd you learn
how to drive like this?
Gotta get to the hotel.
- Warn him.
- What? Warn who?
Wipe your nose.
[engine revving]
[grunts]
[shouting] Help!
[tense music]
[grunting]
[flame hissing]
[camera shutter clicking]
I can't believe you're still
on Kwang after all this time.
With all this, I can put
him away for two lifetimes.
[elevator dings]
This way.
[♪]
[in Chinese] Take them out.
[doorbell chimes]
Ooh! Dessert is served.
[♪]
[dog yaps]
Hello, boys.
Are you my club sandwich?
[dog panting]
Thank you, sir.
[Simmons] A little bit of sugar
ain't gonna ruin that six-pack.
[phone buzzing]
- What?
- Kid lied to us. No one here.
Well, they have to be somewhere.
You go check the rest
of the hotel, okay?
[elevator chimes]
[receptionist]
Can I help you, sir?
I'm looking for my American
partners. They check in today,
[doorbell chimes]
[knocking at door]
[♪]
[hushed] I take it.
[Joey panting]
[knocking]
- Hey.
- Joey?
We need to talk.
It's an emergency.
What are you doing here?
How did you find me?
Hey, what happened to your face?
Mom, who's this?
- "Mom"? You have a son?
- John, you're in danger.
- Wait, wait. His name's John?
- Shh! Quiet. Mommy's talking.
- What-- what's going on here?
- Listen, they know you
have the ledger.
Kwang is sending men
right now to kill all of you.
- Go to the bathroom.
- Okay.
How do you know about Kwang?
Because I'm married to him.
Wait, wait. Okay, Mom,
seriously, who is this guy?
- Why is he looking at me like--
- Quiet! Both of you!
If you want to know more,
we have to leave right now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hold on a minute, all right?
I'm just gonna need a minute.
I haven't seen you in,
what, like, 15 years?
Just give me a minute.
All right?
[elevator dings]
[dramatic music]
- Get in.
- Okay, okay.
[♪]
Come on!
Cover us! Get to the bathroom.
Cover us, please.
[♪]
Get under the sink.
Open the door.
[rapid gunfire continues]
[♪]
[buzzing]
- What?
- Yo, boss. We found them.
- Your wife's here.
- You bring me my wife...
and you kill everyone else.
What about the kid?
- Hello? Hello?
- [gunfire continues]
Hold on.
[Simmons]
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
You guys have the wrong room.
You have the wrong room.
[indistinct]
[Simmons yelps]
Go find them.
[panting]
[low, tense music]
[Freddie shouting]
[♪]
[hissing]
[Bolo] Shoot!
[Joey exclaiming]
[shattering]
[intense music]
[boom]
[alarm wailing]
[all panting]
You all right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
[alarm wailing continues]
Follow me.
Follow him.
[♪]
Go.
Stairs. Stairs.
[♪]
[gunshot]
Step away from the door.
[alarm blaring]
[♪]
[in Chinese] Stairs.
Open it!
[rapid gunfire]
[siren wailing]
[♪]
[Bolo shouts]
[overlapping chatter]
No, no, no, no.
Come this way. To the bar.
What are you doing?
We need to go.
It's just the cops.
Just let them go past.
[indistinct]
So he's really Kwang's son?
- No.
- Definitely not.
Raymond, meet your son, John.
John, meet your dad.
What?
[coughing]
Raymond, meet your dad.
John, meet your son.
[coughing]
Any questions?
So you're not a chef?
No.
Come on, let's go. Come on.
[staff speaking Chinese]
Hey! Excuse me, sir.
Hey! After them! Hey!
- Is this yours?
- Yeah.
- There's only two seats.
- Get in here.
- [engine revving]
- [police shouting]
[in Chinese] Stop him, hurry!
Stop the Ferrari.
[sirens wailing]
Stop looking at me.
- Are we going to the police?
- [both] No.
- Why not?
- Kwang knows every cop in town.
And I'm not even
supposed to be here.
What? Why?
I was going after Kwang.
I'm not officially here.
I came alone.
So you came back after all this
time for Kwang, but not for me?
How was I supposed to
even know you were here?
Because I live here, remember?
You're supposed to be dead.
Yeah, well, give it
another minute,
kid, and your mom
will take care of that.
[sirens wailing]
I see you haven't changed a bit.
Thanks. I moisturize.
- And no sugar. It ages you.
- I meant your driving.
Sir.
The guest name is George
Washington. He's American.
And what is George Washington
doing with Kwang's wife?
[sirens wailing]
All this time
I've been taking cooking
classes to get close to my
dead pastry
chef dad,
and he's not even dead.
- Pastry chef? Seriously?
- Shh. Quiet, please.
- And why am I a dead pastry
chef? -[Raymond]
Yeah, Mom, why?
Everyone, shut up
and let me drive.
[sirens wailing]
Actually, uh...
I was a pastry chef
for about a month.
I make a mean crème brûlée.
Well.
[grim music]
Sir.
[exhales]
You go find my wife.
Mom, I'm bleeding.
- What?
- No, it's not you, kid. It's me.
Raymond, put pressure.
Right there.
No, no, no, no, no. Down. Yes.
- We have to get to a hospital.
- No. No hospital.
- Mom?
- I've got an idea.
[car approaching]
- [crashing]
- [clattering]
What the--
- Hey, hey!
- [Joey] Hey, I'm so sorry.
[in Chinese]
Driving a sports car, so what?
Who do you think you are?
So sorry.
Once you've hacked in,
check all the traffic cams.
Flag anybody in a red Ferrari.
That'll be her.
[sirens wailing]
[police shouting in Chinese]
Get off the car!
Hands, hands!
Show me your hands!
[in Chinese]
Watch out of my car.
Don't scratch my Ferrari.
My car!
She gave my Ferrari
to a pizza guy?
What did she say?
Ha-- happy birthday.
[chuckles]
"Happy birthday."
[pleasant chiming]
[woman speaking Chinese over PA]
Let's go.
[John] Hey, this one.
[Raymond] This one. Come.
- Ew, Mom, gross.
What are you doing?
- Shh!
Hey, guys.
What are you doing here,
[John] Ah, man,
we-- we forgot our keys.
- Can I just borrow
your flashlight for a second?
- What?
Take that.
[Joey] Get in.
[engine sputters]
Who are you people?
I mean, you're stealing cars
and he's punching everyone?
Are you really my parents?
Your will for revolution and
change had to come
from somewhere.
- [engine starts]
- Get in.
Listen to your mother.
[gentle music]
[♪]
Why didn't you tell me
you were pregnant?
You didn't give me a chance.
What do you mean?
Now's not the time
to rewrite the past.
We need to figure out how to
get us out of this shit
you put
us in.
- Me? I put you in this?
- Yes.
You clean this up.
You better have a plan.
All right.
That's it?
That's your plan? Sleeping?
No. I think better when I sleep.
[in Chinese] Who is going to
believe that things
can be figured out
while sleeping?
You just showed up from nowhere
after 15 years and
gave me a mess.
And now I have to fix
all your shitty things.
You better have a plan
when you wake up...
[♪]
[John grunts]
[distant seabirds squawking]
I told you no hospital.
It's safe.
We're in my village.
The fishing village?
Things have changed.
Doctor said you were lucky.
But you lost a lot of blood.
They had to
give you a transfusion.
Lucky for you, your son
has the same blood type.
Raymond.
Where is he?
So he's really my son?
And Kwang's been raising him?
Kwang was around.
I raised him myself.
Yeah, well, you didn't have to,
if you'd told me.
The last time I saw you,
you told me to run away.
[John] I didn't tell you to
run to someone like Kwang.
No one else was here for me,
so you don't get to judge.
There are many things you don't
know and you'll never
understand.
No, no, no.
I understand completely.
Love your bracelet.
What is it? Tiffany's? Cartier?
Yes, John.
You understand me completely.
I ran to the one person who
gave me the riches and pearls
that I deserve.
And Raymond,
stop pretending you're asleep.
You two do anything but fight?
- [Joey] Yes.
- No.
[knock at door]
Mrs. Kwang? Some of our
patients wanna say thank you.
- [Joey in Chinese]
Oh, thank you.
- Why all the flowers?
[doctor] Mrs. Kwang
is our biggest donor.
Actually, the only donor.
Thanks to her, we have
the best hospital in the area.
She saved countless lives.
[Joey] I have to go.
Let's go.
Yeah, Raymond.
[Joey in Chinese] Thank you all.
- [doctor in Chinese] Thank you.
- [in English] Appreciate it.
[sentimental music]
[car approaching]
[♪]
[Joey in Chinese] Granny?
[Po Po gasps]
[in Chinese]
I left him. I did it.
Mom, who's this?
Come here.
Raymond!
[in Chinese]
How much you've grown.
[laughing]
My grandmother.
Your great-grandmother.
[in Chinese] Granny, we're
going to change our clothes.
[in English] Let's go clean up.
[♪]
Sorry.
Whoa.
[♪]
Mom, is this where you grew up?
I know it's not much.
Are you kidding?
This is awesome.
Why have you never
brought me here before?
Sometimes it's easier
to forget the past.
Get out of those stinky clothes.
Dinner soon.
Hey, uh, do you have some water?
Water?
Fridge?
I see you still
know your way around.
I don't remember this.
Po Po hates Kwang's money too.
But she likes cold beer more.
Change.
[birds squawking]
Oh. Hi, Joey.
[Joey] Hi!
Mom, anything else you wanna
tell me about our family?
Say hello to your cousin,
Raymond.
- Hi.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi, Po Po.
- Put it there.
- You're not eating?
- [Raymond] Not until
I get some answers.
I just found out that I have
a great-grandmother, a cousin.
What else aren't you telling me?
You never talk about family.
You never talk about the past.
I know nothing about you,
both of you.
So please, no more lies.
I deserve to know.
He's right.
Fine.
When your mom was young,
I wasn't exactly who you think.
Both my parents died
in fishing accidents,
so Po Po refused to
let me near the water.
So, I have to find
something else to do.
Joey!
[engine revving]
[fishermen exclaiming]
- [in Chinese] It's dangerous.
- [in Chinese] Can you slow down?
Turns out I was
a really good mechanic.
I could do anything with cars.
Which was fun, but not
very useful in the village.
- [in Chinese] Wash up.
Dinnertime. -[Joey
in Chinese] Okay.
Until one day,
something terrible happened.
[ominous music]
[in Chinese]
Put them into my garage.
[Joey] But Po Po was smart.
If she went to the police,
they might arrest the villagers.
By hiding the drugs,
she could keep everyone safe.
Until the day the gang
came to get them back.
[♪]
- [knocking at door]
- [in Chinese] Joey, wake up.
[Joey] When these men
came to the small villages,
they would not just
take back their merchandise.
They would also take away
all the young girls.
But lucky for me, I could drive.
[engine revving]
[intense hip-hop music]
[♪]
[tires screeching]
Ugh!
[shouts]
And then what happened?
I was offered a job.
A job? What kind of job?
Only thing I was good at.
Driving.
And then a few years later,
I met your dad.
These are really good dumplings.
John. Your turn.
All right.
What do you wanna know?
How did you two meet?
- Can't remember.
It was so long ago.
- John. Tell the truth.
- It was a work thing.
- What kind of work thing?
[clears throat]
I was a cop. A DEA agent.
I was sent over here undercover
to track a drug shipment.
And, uh,
I was pretending to be a client,
following the mule car
that was transporting drugs.
And it turned out that
the driver of the car was
none other than your mother.
What?
- These are really good
dumplings. -Yeah,
they are, huh?
Yeah,
you should get you some more.
Now, she thought I was a
competitor trying to
steal her drugs.
Playing hard to get.
I remember her hair
blowing in the wind,
and as soon as our eyes met...
[tender music]
[engine revving]
[tires screeching]
...that was it. I was hooked.
No, no, no.
That's not how I remember.
- Oh, yeah?
- No.
Well, how do you remember it?
First, I remember his shoes.
[grunting]
Can't really remember his face.
I don't know why.
But, um,
I do remember our first kiss.
[blowing]
[grunting]
You sure that was
our first kiss?
Yes, I remember it.
Why don't you?
- Oof. You're in trouble now.
- No, no, no. Hold on.
Um, okay, I may not
remember our first kiss,
but I definitely
remember our second.
[♪]
And our third.
[camera shutter clicking]
And our fourth.
[♪]
And our fifth.
No. That's our sixth.
No, no.
I'm talking about...
our fifth.
Oh, yeah.
How could I forget?
[♪]
Oh.
That one sounds less romantic.
- More dumplings?
- Yeah.
I don't understand. What
happens? Why did
you break up?
Some people just--
they can't make up their mind.
Some people care only about
one thing, their career.
Yeah, but some people's jobs
are about saving people.
And for some people, that's
easier than raising a family.
It's a little difficult when no
one tells you that you
have a family.
Excuses.
[in Chinese] Weasel out of it.
- It's not an excuse!
- Whoa, whoa. Guys, guys, guys.
I think I've heard enough.
- It's been a long day.
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Help me clean up.
- Sure, Mom.
You too. Please.
Yeah, of course.
[crickets chirping]
[distant dog barking]
[grunts]
[Po Po in Chinese] Why are you
so awesome? Such a good job.
[in Chinese] Thanks.
Hey. You seen your mom?
- Morning to you too.
- Sorry, man. Good morning.
[in Chinese] Peel peas there.
[clears throat]
So, uh... you like cooking?
Not really.
So why are you studying?
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry to disappoint.
That was a brave thing you did,
stealing the ledger.
Just wanted Kwang
to stop killing dolphins.
Yeah, I hear you.
Actually, I saved some fish the
other day. There was
this big fire--
Dolphins aren't fish. They're
mammals, just like
you and me.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Well, these were definitely
fish. You know, that
little cute ones.
I interned for Kwang
last semester.
That's when I found out
that his fishing boats kill
over 650,000 dolphins a year.
They get caught up in the nets.
And the fishermen actually chop
them up and used
them as bait.
Kwang's a piece of shit
dickhead dolphin killer.
Hey, hey,
watch your language, kid.
Okay, Dad.
Sorry, I meant John.
Or is it "Agent Lawlor, sir"?
Cut me some slack, huh?
It's not that
I don't wanna be Dad,
it's just, you know, it's just--
this is all new to me.
Yeah, well,
I'm not really an expert either.
Pretty good at these beans,
though, huh?
[distant engine sputtering]
[tool clatters]
- Stay here.
- All right.
Hey. I've been looking for you.
I was in town getting
some spare parts for the buggy.
We're meant to hide, remember?
Don't worry, I know how to hide.
But you, you're the expert.
You're really good at it.
All right, can we, uh,
take some time out for a minute?
There's a lot of details
in your story that are missing.
Just fill me in.
- What happened to you after I
left? -My past is
mine, not yours.
You know what? Don't tell me.
Just, you know, keep all
your secrets to yourself.
But just know that one day
they will come around and
they will bite you in the ass.
Do you remember the last time?
- What?
- Do you remember the last time
we saw each other?
Yeah, of course I do.
All I ever do is
remember that night.
- Hey!
- Hey.
- I got something
I need to tell--
- Oh, sorry.
- No, you first.
No, you go.
Yours sounds more serious.
Mine can wait.
I'm not a buyer.
I'm not even a client.
- [laughs]
- I'm an undercover agent.
I work for the DEA.
My real name is John Lawlor.
I was sent here to
dig into Kwang's operation,
figure out the players,
who he's working for,
who's working for him.
The worst part is, uh...
they want me to bring you in.
I-- I don't understand.
You were using me?
Yeah.
At first I was.
But then
I fell in love with you.
Deeply.
I thought, uh,
when the time came,
I could just protect you,
protect us.
[voice distorting]
The system is rigged.
They just need someone
to blame, and, uh...
it's never the shark, you know?
It's always the little fish,
and that's not gonna help.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
[normally] Listen to me.
You're gonna get up from here,
you're gonna walk
to the bathroom,
you're gonna crawl
out the window.
- No.
- You're gonna take my car,
and you're gonna drive away
from here as fast as you can.
Where should I go?
I-- Just go wherever.
Wherever you want.
Just disappear, okay? Use cash.
I will scrub your records.
Don't leave a trace.
- No way for anyone to find you.
- How will you find me?
I won't.
[sobbing]
- No. No.
- Please. You have to go.
No, John.
No. No.
Joey, please, go. Now.
That's not exactly
how it happened.
Well, that's how I remember it.
You never wondered
what my news was?
Never wondered
what I had to say?
Congratulations.
[Joey] Thank you.
[sirens blaring]
[♪]
[sobbing]
[muted screaming]
So you knew?
You knew you were pregnant
and you didn't tell me?
You said go, get out.
But if I knew...
Then what?
You arrest me?
Raymond is born in prison?
- No, thank you.
- So, what, you--
You run to someone like Kwang?
You don't get to
judge my choices.
I did what I had to do
to protect my son.
I sacrificed everything.
So did I.
I sacrificed you.
The one thing
in my life that meant a damn.
Okay, okay.
Fine.
You want to be part
of this family?
- I do.
- You sure?
I'm sure.
And no more secrets,
everything out in the open.
I can do that.
If it doesn't work, we stop.
I don't want Raymond
getting hurt.
Neither do I.
And we take it slow.
That's fine by me.
[♪]
[Joey sniffling]
[phone buzzing]
- What?
- The police want
to talk to you about
the shootout at the hotel.
Kwang, this is serious.
What do I tell them?
[slow, tense instrumental]
[♪]
[music intensifies]
[knocking on door]
- Yes.
- See?
That's how it's done.
Knock, wait, then enter.
Good.
What's up?
Just looking for John.
- Huh?
- You know John.
Tall, grumpy guy, hates smiling,
not dead, not a chef.
Yeah, I'm sorry. Um...
I haven't seen him at all... no.
- You all right, Mom?
- Yes, I'm fine. Yeah.
Why are you looking for John?
[Raymond] I was pretty harsh
on him yesterday.
Just wanted to say sorry.
[Joey sighs] Don't worry.
He's a tough guy.
Yeah, I know.
Still thought
he'd want to hear it though.
[Joey] He's probably in the
mountains, getting his work out.
- Okay. Thanks.
- [Joey] Yeah.
[sighing]
I do not hate smiling.
- I love smiling.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Show me.
All right. Well, this is
my "Pizza for dinner"smile.
- [Joey giggling]
- And this...
is I found passports
and $10,000 in cash smile.
Give me that.
You said no more secrets.
Fine. It's our escape plan.
Some traveling cash,
fake passports.
Everything we need to get away.
- Except...
- Except what?
I only have passports
for me and Ray.
Don't worry.
We're not gonna split up.
I'm not gonna lose you again.
[Joey screaming, giggling]
[Liu] This incident
at the hotel,
six of your bodyguards
were found there.
What time was the incident?
Around, uh, 5, 6 pm.
Hm.
That is hard to explain,
But, Deputy Liu, you know,
this doesn't seem like
any of my concern.
But as you can see, my employees
clocked out at 4 p.m.
and what my employees do
on their personal time
is their business, not mine.
How do we know these are real?
Deputy, the real question
you should be asking is
who killed my poor employees?
Why question me
when there's a real murderer
running out there free?
Makes me think of
the Chinese proverb:
Why kill the chicken
to scare the monkey.
Are you a chicken
or a monkey, Mister Kwang?
You know, it sounds to me like
you're dealing with a real pro.
Someone that is trained
with a unique set of skills.
You know,
if anyone should be a suspect,
it's this person, not me.
You mean the American,
George Washington.
George Washington...
Not George Washington!
Meet Agent John Lawlor.
My men sacrificed their lives
trying to stop him from
kidnapping my wife.
Why would he do this?
Because this John Lawlor
conceived a child with my wife.
The very child
I've been raising as
my own son for
the past 13 years.
His first case here in Taipei
was here to investigate me.
We will see.
Please look into it.
Any news?
Looking everywhere.
Finding nothing.
Check their airports,
train stations.
All staked out.
Try her village.
She said she never go back,
but you never know.
[♪]
[John] Listen to me
very carefully.
This is really important, okay?
Kwang's ledger.
Were there any others?
I don't know. Maybe.
I didn't see any other ledgers.
There's only one.
He's in control
if we can't find hard evidence,
Kwang's not smart enough
to keep all that
information in his head.
Well, I was in his study
one afternoon.
Maybe it was the rhino.
He has
a rhino sculpture on his desk.
What if it's not
a sculpture at all?
- It's a hard drive.
- I can go get it.
No.
- It'll be easy--
- [Joey & John] No.
- We'll find another way.
- What other way?
You said it: without
any evidence, Kwang wins.
We will find one.
Don't worry.
We got this.
Hey, don't go too far.
[slow, tense instrumental]
[♪]
[bons snapping]
[Kwang] Did you find her?
- No.
- Then why are you calling me?
Huh?
Good boy.
[in Chinese]
Don't drink beer that much.
Your hands are cold.
- Drink some hot tea.
- No... No beer, no enjoyment.
It's time to go.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
No, you promised.
We're only gonna split up
for a little bit.
I'll create a secure email for
us to communicate,
all right?
It's a shitty plan,
but it's the only one we have.
- [Joey] Raymond!
- [John] Po Po, where is Raymond?
Raymond. Where is Raymond?
Hanging out with his friends.
[door opening]
- Hi, guys.
- Where's Raymond?
He took my motorcycle.
Said he has something to do.
[♪]
- Hi, Raymond.
- [Raymond gasps]
Need another pencil sharpener?
[tires squealing]
- [Kwang] Did you find her?
- It's me, Kwang.
Joey, darling, you okay?
- They hurt you?
- Where is Raymond?
You don't have to worry
about Raymond, sweetheart.
He's here with me.
He won't escape this time.
[tires squealing]
[John] Kwang, it's me,
Agent Lawlor.
Agent John Lawlor.
Nice to finally meet you.
Kwang, let him go.
- [Kwang] And what do I get?
- What do you want?
What do I want...
What do I want?
What I want, Agent Lawlor,
is for you to go away
and leave me and my wife alone.
Go back to where you came from.
Okay, then we swap.
Me for Raymond.
Ximending District,
American Alley.
American Alley?
You sure you don't want
to try some delicious
Taiwanese food before you go?
- Noon.
- [phone beeps]
- What are you doing?
- You said you would do anything
to protect our son. So would I.
He's going to kill you.
- We'll see about that.
- [Joey sighs]
Trust me.
Okay? Go.
["Paint it Black" by The
Rolling Stones instrumental]
[♪]
Where's Raymond?
He's in the car.
Mom!
- No. No. No.
- [Raymond] Mommy.
[Kwang] Let's go.
No, that wasn't the deal.
Deal?
Don't talk to me
about some deal.
Joey, remember
the first time we met?
Oh.
She didn't tell you.
Let me tell you about our story.
[♪]
Tea?
Looking for some
lost merchandise.
[Joey grunting]
Easy! Get your hands off her.
[panting]
What did you do to her?
No, don't worry about her.
Worry about you.
There are consequences for
what you've done.
For one,
you killed my best driver.
Good help is hard to
find these days.
Sorry.
I'm sure you are.
You like?
Porsche.
RWB 964 twin turbo.
Why don't you come work with me?
What are you gonna do?
Rot away in
this little fishing village
for the rest of your life?
You're way too smart,
beautiful for that.
[sobbing]
- You killed her.
- No,
- I'm not some kind of--
- Po Po!
- [screaming] Po Po!
- [shushing]
Shh. Stop. Calm down.
Calm down.
Shh...
It's okay.
Hey.
See? You can trust me.
I'll never lie to you.
I'll always protect you,
you and your family.
And I'll give you
the life that you deserve.
We could make
a great team together.
What do you say, hm?
Deal?
It's a new deal. Now.
Come on.
[♪]
[gunshots]
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Get down.
[gunshot]
[horn honking]
[♪]
- Go.
- You sit down!
[♪]
[Kwang] You do this to me?
We're supposed to be family.
You do this to me?
Huh?
After everything
I've done for both of you?
You do this to me?
[♪]
Everything's gonna be okay.
We start over.
We'll be a family again.
Don't worry.
[glass shattering]
You all right?
Kwang, he still has
the USB drive.
Stay here.
[♪]
Get out of the way, man.
[biker, in Chinese]
Hey, watch out.
[♪]
[panting]
[actress speaking indistinctly]
Kwang, hold it there!
Don't move.
Keep your hands
where I can see 'em.
You are under arrest.
On the floor now, now.
No.
[in Chinese] People are leaving.
It's over, Kwang.
You're under arrest.
This has nothing to do with
your fishing case.
- This is between you and me!
- This is nothing personal.
Of course it is.
I've waited 15 years for her to
love me, and then you show up.
What can you give her
that I can't, huh?
You can't even
take care of your own son.
I'm just doing my job.
It's the last time, Kwang
Get on the fucking floor.
Go ahead, shoot me. Huh?
I'm unarmed.
[♪]
[fighting grunts]
[in Chinese] Is this a 3D movie?
They fight for real.
- Don't watch it.
- Just a bit.
[fighting grunts]
[♪]
[in Chinese]
Oh my, it's too violent!
[fighting grunts]
[♪]
[panting]
- See, I was right.
- About what?
You want her.
You're fighting for her.
But you're gonna
have to kill me.
'Cause she needs me.
She needs no one.
[loud smack]
[in Chinese]
Good fight, I like it.
[shouting]
[♪]
In shocking news,
business tycoon King Kwang
has been arrested
for illegal possession
of firearms in Taiwan.
Which has some of the toughest
gun-control law in the world...
Cigarette?
Anyone? You got a cigarette?
Quit smoking.
You want a lollipop?
Yeah, all right.
I made bail?
Someone wants to see you first.
Hey, thanks for bailing me out.
It wasn't me.
They want a million for you.
Way too much for the agency.
- Thanks, boss.
- I told you to go on vacation,
a weekend escape.
Instead, you went rogue.
You couldn't
even bring the ledger.
Yeah, well, I got
something better.
All of Kwang's records,
shipping manifests,
supplies, buyers,
illegal carbon offsets.
- This is real.
- More than real.
Okay, let me handle
it from here.
Until then,
you better disappear.
For real this time.
- Vanish. All of you.
- For the weekend?
Make it a couple of weeks...
couple of years.
All right, what's next?
You leave Taipei, immediately.
Robin Hood, thank you
for bailing me out.
- Not, my money.
- [John] Here.
Thanks.
So what are we doing now?
Um...
Family vacation?
Ooh, yes. Yes.
No, you still have school.
Come on, a couple of days
isn't gonna hurt.
What do they learn at
this age anyway?
Plus, I already aced
my last math test.
- No. Nope.
- There you go. Come on.
This kid has been through a lot.
Yeah, I'm emotionally damaged
for life.
Absolutely not.
I got this. Come on.
Hey, Joey, listen, I just
got my passport back.
- This is a really nice time for
us to go on our first
family trip.
- No.
- Come on!
Come on,
you're such a taskmaster.
I miss school, months at a time.
Look how I turn out.
[Joey] How you turned out...
Huh...
[♪]
You like it?
Oui.
Come on, Ray.
Ease up on the photos.
We have 13 years of empty
scrapbooks to fill in.
- [doorbell ringing]
- Oh, that's for me.
I'll get it.
- I have some--
- I got something I want to--
No, it's okay. You first.
This time you first for sure.
[Joey] I have a present for you.
Now you cannot say
you didn't know.
Wow, that was... fast.
How can you? I mean...
- You sure?
- [sighs]
What--
Is it--
- Is it--
- Is it yours?
Does it matter?
No.
[Raymond imitating fanfare]
Bonjour.
Madame, you want croissant?
Merci.
Hell yeah.
[♪]
["Moonlight" by
Henry Lau playing]
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh
Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
♪ It's been a day in my head
I'm hanging on my last thread ♪
♪ There's things I gotta forget
[Oh-oh-oh, oh] ♪
♪ I'm catching up
with it lately ♪
♪ Spinning out a bit crazy ♪
♪ Know you're feeling
the same thing ♪
♪ 'Cause we've been driving
and riding ♪
♪ Just killing the time
♪ And it's like
we got nowhere to go ♪
♪ So meet me underneath
the moonlight [Ah-ah] ♪
♪ Light the fire,
get your mood right [Alright] ♪
♪ Must be something in the air ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't even care ♪
♪ Gonna dance until
the sunrise [Alright] ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh
Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I'm waking up in a daze,
get it outta my face ♪
♪ The sun is shining on
every move that I make, so ♪
♪ Let's get to forgetting
everything that went wrong ♪
Everybody here,
we been crying too long
♪ We can dance about it
to our favorite song, song ♪
♪ So meet me underneath
the moonlight [Ah-ah] ♪
♪ Light the fire,
get your mood right [Alright] ♪
♪ Must be something in the air ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't even care ♪
♪ Gonna dance until
the sunrise [Alright] ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh
Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Let's get to forgetting
everything that went wrong ♪
♪ Everybody here,
we been crying too long ♪
♪ We can dance about it
to our favorite song, song ♪
♪ So meet me underneath
the moonlight [Ah-ah] ♪
♪ Light the fire,
get your mood right [Alright] ♪
♪ Must be something in the air ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't even care ♪
♪ Gonna dance until
the sunrise [Alright] ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh
Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
[♪]