All units.
Robbery in Porte Maillot at 11:58 p.m.
To all police stations, please copy.
This is CP16, copy.
CP8, copy.
Three suspects
riding black TMAX scooters.
Heading towards
Porte de Saint-Cloud on the ring road.
This is TN51 from TN51 Alpha.
Units 1 and 2 approaching Porte Maillot.
Copy, TN51 Alpha.
TN51 Alpha, we have priority,
the scooters are in sight.
To all units
in proximity of TN51, give way.
TN51, I need backup.
I need backup.
Heading towards Saint-Cloud.
Copy that. All stations,
backup needed at Porte de Versailles.
Bravo, Charlie, close the gap.
Bravo, one's splitting.
Flank him on the right.
Copy. I'm on him.
Bravo is down! Bravo is down!
Copy that.
Ambulance en route.
Porte d'Italie's clogged.
Where's the backup?
Unavail, TN51, fall back.
Fuck!
They're going through Austerlitz.
Send backup for Christ's sake!
No backup. You're ordered
to stop pursuit, Lieutenant.
- Charlie, let's keep going.
- I won't lose 'em.
Charlie's down.
Alpha, we ordered you
to stop pursuit--
Assholes.
Charlie, you okay?
TN51 Alpha, stop pursuit.
I repeat, stop pursuit.
No way. They're within reach.
Stop right now!
TN51, report.
Answer me. What's going on there?
- Fuck!
- Respond.
TN51, Alpha, Lieutenant
Delvo. We need an immediate sitrep.
What's your location?
Lieutenant Delvo, respond.
Respond.
Fuck.
♪ Feel good ♪
♪ Feel good… ♪
…beautiful day for a race,
and we have an exciting one for you.
♪ City's breaking down on a camel's back ♪
♪ They just have to go ♪
♪ 'Cause they don't know wack ♪
♪ So while you fill the streets
It's appealing to see… ♪
Michael.
Get off your phone, please.
I need you right now, not in two hours.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
♪ All I wanna hear is the message beep ♪
♪ My dreams, they got a kissing
'Cause I don't get sleep, no… ♪
Michael Carella.
The race starts in 20 minutes, hotshot.
All right, I'm coming.
There's only one hotshot here, Kevin.
Damn, check him out. Such a show-off.
The guy's in full Yamaha.
His team with their headsets and tablets.
- It's complete bullshit.
- Hey. Hey!
Keep your mouth shut and focus.
It's the qualifying round.
It's high level.
If you this mess up,
Dad is going to kill us both.
Relax, I got this.
- Triple bump?
- Third gear, full throttle.
- Your position for the exit?
- Lean on the bike, and put my elbow out.
- Your eyeline?
- Up high, I've got it.
- Whatever happens?
- We stay alive.
This GP8 track is
a labor of love,
built for us by the '90s legend himself,
a man who dominated the podiums
during his years of supremacy
over the dirt bike riding world,
and who is with us here today.
A huge welcome
for one of the giants of this sport,
Mr. Daniel Carella.
Thank you, Jean-Yves. Thanks very much.
Thanks, everyone, for your friendship
and for your presence on this racetrack,
which, uh, my wife, Clara,
and I dreamt up together and created
quite some time ago.
It's been with gratitude
that for the past two years,
me and my family, and my sister,
have welcomed you here.
Together, let's keep Clara's legacy alive.
Uh…
All I want to say
to the upcoming generation is
may the best racer win.
And hopefully,
the best racer today will be a Carella.
Thank you all for your friendship
and your support.
Now, have a good race.
Thank you for that, Daniel.
A round of applause for Daniel Carella!
Today's event is the last
of the qualifying races.
A final showdown that we've been
looking forward to for weeks.
It's Michael Carella who has
the best time trial for this finale,
and today, he's racing on his home turf.
Michael, wearing number 107,
is in second position,
just behind Kevin Lautier, number 187.
Lautier is just two points away
from first place and qualification.
I see the green flag now,
which means the race is about to begin.
And it should be an explosive one.
Five seconds.
Ladies and gents, here they go.
The riders are all full throttle,
heading into a crowded first turn.
Carella is off to an aggressive start.
He moves in front of rider 110.
He's a little slow on the brakes,
but Michael Carella is leading.
Michael is going full throttle as Lautier
comes around the turn in second position.
Michael leans into the turn
with incredible speed,
and over to the other side
as he flies away,
maintaining his lead position
on this hill.
It's crowded back there behind him,
with everyone really pushing.
But Michael Carella is
on his home turf today,
giving him a huge advantage.
Come on, Mikey!
Still leading,
as he flies away,
tailed by his opponent, Kevin Lautier,
who is still in second position.
Two more laps to go
and Carella has retained his lead.
The heat is on! But it's not over yet,
and Kevin Lautier closes in
on Mr. Carella.
Oh, careful!
Wow, wow, wow! Lautier is going for it.
The pressure is on.
He's on Michael's tail,
taking the bumps aggressively.
And… double whip!
- These guys are on fire!
- Come on!
Go on, yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
…as Lautier seems
to be catching up to Carella.
Come on. Mikey, push it.
And Michael keeps
his position,
barely making it from inside.
107 still leading by a margin,
but will he lap 122?
These two are fighting ruthlessly
in this race for the World Championship,
while the others look for an opening.
Oh, yes, look, he's coming back!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- He needs to hold out…
- Come on. Don't do this.
…the front mudguard!
Close the doors, Michael.
Close the doors because he's coming back.
Can you feel the tension?
Anything can happen now.
- No, no, no.
- What a final!
The heat coming off this racetrack!
My, oh, my, what a race.
Only 400 meters left to go.
- The final stretch!
- Come on…
He's going for it! He's going
for it. He's overtaking Michael!
Oh, fuck!
Michael has just lost the pole position.
And Kevin Lautier is the big winner today.
Finishing just ahead of Michael Carella,
who ends his championship run in second.
You could've won that race.
You really could have beaten him.
I'm still runner-up.
The runner-up is
just the first loser, Michael.
Come on.
You're good, Michael,
but mere talent doesn't matter.
It's the bare minimum.
Winning is a matter of choice and will,
you know that.
- As for today, you were missing that.
- Dad, enough, he gets it.
We'll train.
There's the whole season still ahead.
No, there's no more training.
It's over.
What are you talking about?
Just, uh,
finish cleaning the stalls.
I'll see you guys
both at home later, okay?
We haven't made much progress.
I nearly caught them three weeks ago.
But they're organized. They're trained.
They ride powerful bikes
they upgrade themselves.
They stole half a million euros
of luxury watches
carried by an anonymous employee,
so they had an informant.
Now you're asking for more men
and resources to catch them.
I need more support here.
I'm asking for police headquarters
to intervene.
With more vehicles,
I could've stopped them, dammit.
Fuck, Vincent!
Your watch.
- Get the fuck away.
- Take off your watch.
- Give it to him, Vincent. Now!
- Hand it over.
Stay on the ground, asshole.
What you got, dickhead?
Vincent!
Get up.
Stop it!
What's going on?
Back in the car!
Get back in your car!
Vincent, look at me.
- What are you doing?
- Call the police!
Vincent!
Don't go. I'll call an ambulance, okay?
Yeah, get out of here, asshole!
Two colleagues hospitalized.
Your moto squad costs a lot,
in terms of men and equipment.
We're officers, not accountants.
And my guys know the risks.
Those bikers are in this
for the adrenaline rush.
Not for the money.
And they love to make us look stupid.
They're not done. You can bet on that.
Well, all I know is that
it's getting near impossible
to justify your operation
to my higher-ups. I want results.
The Crystal Week.
What?
Elsa, please.
We know they specialize
in jewelry theft. Check this out.
The most anticipated event
of Crystal Week is the presentation
of these red diamonds,
the rarest of stones.
Diamond dealer Mazetti will reveal them
at auction, but until then,
their appraisal remains confidential.
These--
There'll be jewelry worth millions
transported between Roissy, Orly,
Le Bourget and Paris.
They're going to strike.
Do you have concrete information
or is this one of your hunches?
I know how these guys think.
I've analyzed their past hits
and operating methods.
These guys won't miss
an opportunity like that.
You know, Lucas, the rest of my day
will be spent getting yelled at
by elected officials
and cops who want your ass.
So don't ask me for anything.
And one more thing.
I don't even want to speak to you again.
Have a great day.
So, what now?
Did you get forensics
back from the bridge robbery?
- No, not yet.
- Call the lab again.
Okay.
Let's meet at 3 p.m.
at the school in Saint-Ouen.
- How much?
- Three thousand.
- Can we count on you tomorrow or not?
- Michael?
Maybe. I'll think about it.
- Well, don't think too much.
- Yeah, okay.
What was that with Yacine?
He offered me a gig.
Three thousand euros, easy job.
What type of job?
It's a jump Yacine can't do because
he's injured. I don't know any more.
Except the man pays cash.
Hey.
Is it legit?
Of course it is.
Well, come on, Dad's waiting for us.
Okay.
Thanks.
Not too much.
Hmm.
So?
What's going on?
We're about to run out of money.
We could've lasted another year,
but the sponsors are dropping us
because of Michael's loss.
There.
Why wouldn't you tell me this
before the race?
- I don't understand.
- Wait, wait.
What's going on?
Tell us the whole situation.
I won't get into details,
that's my business.
Come on, explain it.
We're a 150,000 in debt.
The racetrack rental is not turning
enough of a profit.
The bank wants to sell
the house and track ASAP.
Preferably yesterday, if we could.
She has a point. They're not kids anymore.
All right, don't start.
But why did you wait so long
to tell us all of this?
- We'll end up homeless, Dad.
- Course not.
That won't happen.
- I have a solution anyway.
- What solution?
I'll sell the bikes.
Sell the bikes?
You mean Mom's bikes?
Mmm.
What're you talking about?
But you and Mom spent years restoring
those bikes. You can't sell those.
I asked around.
We could make 100,000 euros at least.
So then…
You and your brother would be set.
You'd be able to start over.
Aunt Hélène, did you know?
I did.
And?
Well, he isn't going to be buried
with those motorcycles. They won't fit.
So nobody even cares?
We'll get rid of Mom's bikes on
a stupid website and no one seems to care?
Honey, what your mother really liked
was seeing those bikes come alive.
It wasn't collecting them.
She wouldn't hesitate if she--
But Mom is gone!
Our mom's gone.
Dad, if you sell those bikes,
it would be like a second funeral.
Yacine offered me a jump.
We can make 3,000 euros.
We can use the money, right?
I just win races and we're good.
The race you really needed to win
was today, all right?
So you can keep
your cheap little schemes for yourself.
Why won't you be honest, Dad?
Honest about what?
What's really on your mind.
- What's on my mind?
- Just say it.
That if I'd crashed instead of Soélie,
we wouldn't be here today.
Hey, Michael, you're talking nonsense.
Come on.
Oh, really? Ask him about it.
Am I right, Dad?
Who's a better rider? Me or Soélie?
- Soélie doesn't want to ride anymore, so--
- That's not what I asked.
That's my only answer anyway.
Who's a better rider,
me or Soélie?
Just answer.
It's really simple. Who's the best biker?
- Soélie or me?
- Soélie!
Okay. The great
Daniel Carella's legendary honesty--
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Easy, okay?
- Some respect, huh?
- Some respect?
- What good is that?
- I don't like the way you're speaking.
- What good is your respect?
- Stop!
You know what?
If I could have chosen who got cancer,
it would've been you instead of Mom.
Do you have anything to add?
Jump in, now's the time.
Michael wants to help.
And you humiliate him.
I'll speak to him.
I'll explain.
There's a couple of things
he must get through his head.
He doesn't have the mindset or the drive
to become a champion. It is what it is.
The same goes for me.
I'm sorry.
You're his father.
Not simply his coach.
You should remember that sometimes.
- Right here?
- Yeah, maybe.
Is this it?
I don't see a ramp or anything.
Yes, it's here. I see Yacine.
- Okay. But I don't trust him.
- Don't worry.
Let me check everything first.
Here's the biker.
- Your timing's perfect.
- What's up, man?
How's it going? All right?
How are you, Soélie?
Yeah.
She seems good.
- Your hand feels better?
- Yeah, it's better.
- That your bike?
- Yeah.
What a monster.
I'll introduce you to Théo.
- We'll talk about that.
- Théo!
- See you later.
- The biker.
Hi. Michael.
- You're a bit young.
- I'm 20.
Been riding for ten, so I'm good.
And does the miss ride as well?
The miss repairs the bikes.
And examines the racecourse.
We're ready and the bikes are set.
Relax. There won't be any issues.
That's my decision, not yours, to make.
My brother will jump, but with our bike.
All right, just stay calm
because it's more than a jump.
Come again?
You said one jump, right?
Okay, follow me. I'll show you.
- You talk to the man about the watches?
- Yeah, he said 200, tops.
It has to be more.
No, don't go below 500.
- Elyas!
- I'll do my best.
I have to go.
This is Michael Carella.
The man I told you about.
With a sister who wasn't
part of the whole deal.
- Hello. Elyas.
- Soélie.
- How are you? Welcome.
- Hi. Michael.
This thing was originally a scooter?
Mm-hmm.
A Yamaha, I believe, no?
Right.
Mmm. So, it's a battle tank
disguised as a dirt bike.
Exactly. That's the beauty
we need to test.
My brother's not riding that bike.
It's too dangerous.
- Soélie, be cool.
- Let's go. I'm over this.
- Come on.
- Do you ride as well?
Théo is my top mechanic.
You can trust him.
- But I know what a dirt bike is.
- Mm-hmm.
That monster was never intended
for the racetrack.
It's an obstacle course, not a racetrack.
We need to test the speed
and the bike fork's resistance.
My client is looking for something
that's reactive and powerful.
So what I'm looking for is a good rider
to push it to its limits.
Think you can do it?
- Yeah. I can do it, yeah.
- Yeah?
What's wrong, then?
- Did you convert that TMAX yourself?
- Yes.
Good work. It was done pretty well.
Still heavy as a tank though.
What do you mean?
The couple won't be strong enough.
You need to reprogram the mapping
to get its full speed
then couple the fork with a tighter--
The variator will compensate. I tested it.
But it's less powerful.
The bike's extension won't keep up.
Especially riding obstacles.
And your hoses are for crap, man.
And how would you know?
Michael, do you want
to test it out or what?
Mmm.
Okay.
- You good?
- Do you trust this guy?
- Comfortable?
- A hundred percent. He's my friend.
He's a pro.
Okay, so what did you tell him?
I told him nothing, bro. He's supposed
to test the bike, get paid, and leave.
How's your wrist doing?
It'll be fine. This comes off tomorrow.
- I got it.
- Keep your eyes on me.
Did you do something stupid?
Are you interrogating me?
You don't trust me, Théo?
- Chill out, man.
- Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure.
You're pissing me off.
- Yacine.
- What?
You'd better not be lying.
- Have you seen the fork?
- That's a piece of wood.
You'll make do. It'll be all right.
Just stay focused on your surroundings.
All good?
- Check the brakes, especially…
- Yes, don't worry.
- Okay.
- Whatever happens?
We stay alive, I know.
Go for it.
Okay, he's prepped.
Whenever you're ready.
It's not powerful enough.
Don't let the engine slow down.
Try revving high.
Whoa! Oh, crap.
The brake.
He'll never make it.
The problem is not my brother.
It's the speed of the bike.
I suppose you can make it better?
This thing is super heavy.
Do you have a lifting bridge?
Bring the bike. I'll show you--
- Don't touch the bike, all right?
- Let her try.
Let's see if she's really that good.
What the fuck?
What's happening? Why are the cops here?
- Mr. Farah?
- That's me.
Lieutenant Delvo.
One of your employees said
we'd find you here.
- Where's Yacine Meflah?
- Yacine?
I think I saw him outside earlier.
Training some bikers.
Don't move! Don't move!
What is he doing?
No! Hey!
Stop!
Get down!
Stop him, stop him!
- Come on, let's move.
- Fuck!
Hey! Hey!
Fuck!
Are you okay? I didn't see you.
It's gonna be okay.
Don't move.
Uh, easy. My arm, hey.
Yeah, yeah.
Take the bike over to the impound lot.
Easy on my arm, easy, man.
You didn't get far, huh?
The bike.
Come on, let's move.
You keep yourself away from Yacine.
Do you hear me?
He's a motocross friend.
I couldn't have known.
A motocross friend? A guy
who runs from the cops is not a friend.
We're leaving without the bike.
What am I supposed to tell Dad?
Why bring him up? Who cares about Dad?
"Who cares about Dad?"
His name's on the insurance.
He's the one who'll get in trouble.
Really. "Who cares about Dad?"
Can't the two of you
ever stop fighting like ten-year-olds?
Try acting like grown-ups.
It would make things easier for me.
The way he talks to me.
- He's always undermining me.
- Yeah, but you're asking for it.
Jeez, come on, "asking for it."
You're impossible. Just talk
to each other. It's not that complicated.
Yes, it is complicated.
It's complicated
when your dad drags you down.
Your fucking egos.
- Want me to come?
- No, wait for me.
Get the door.
There you go.
Won't be enough.
The impound will cost money.
Fixing the bike will as well.
Will this be enough?
Thank you.
How come you don't ride?
Your brother listens
to every word you say.
You know all about it,
so I wonder why you're not on the bike.
I had an accident.
So what?
I just don't ride anymore.
I have a job for you.
It's right up your alley.
As a bike mechanic.
But this job requires absolute discretion.
What's the risk?
Making a ton of easy money.
I don't want trouble with the police.
Ah… That's something I can't guarantee.
Then I'll pass.
I've had my share of crazy for the day.
Too bad.
I hope to see you around.
Why would you give the job
to a girl you just met?
Any word on Yacine?
He knows enough to keep
his mouth shut in there.
Do we know why he was arrested?
No one said. His lawyer will tell us more.
What about the 15th?
Should we get someone else?
Missing a glove? You lost it on
the Bir-Hakeim bridge. Your DNA's on it.
I want to speak to a lawyer.
Type out his interrogation.
How's your wrist?
- Want a doctor?
- You're the one who broke my wrist.
I want a lawyer, man.
- Carjacking?
- Yeah, yeah. Get me a lawyer.
You'll spend time in jail
with this track record--
Whatever. Stop talking to me.
Yeah, but you don't care.
You already knew that, right?
- Get me a lawyer.
- I don't understand.
Can you repeat that for me?
To be frank?
Hey.
I don't care about you.
You're a little piece of shit.
There are hundreds
of pieces of shit like you in jail.
I'm interested in your TMAX.
Where did you get it?
You have a supplier?
Do you know other guys
with that kind of bike?
Mazetti.
Mazetti, the jeweler.
Ring a bell?
You know, if you have
answers to my questions,
we'll forget about that lawyer,
you and me.
I ain't sayin' nothing, guy.
Don't you get it?
Take him away.
You get me a lawyer.
- Hey, come on. That's painful. Go easy.
- Yes. Come on. Get up.
Easy. I want a lawyer.
- I want a lawyer. You heard me.
- We'll call a lawyer. Relax.
- Stop struggling.
- Move!
I want a lawyer.
Call me a fucking lawyer!
Calm down!
Go ahead.
I'll close and join you later.
Okay.
I never understood
why your mother loved this bike so much.
The engine lacks power.
The frame isn't rigid enough.
It's difficult to maneuver.
And that color.
Yeah.
She loved it though.
Oh, well.
Maybe she liked its flaws.
Then I see why it was
her favorite.
Same reason she loved you too.
I really miss her.
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT. I'M IN.
You're being transferred.
- Put your jacket on.
- Did you call my lawyer?
Just forget about your lawyer.
Put your jacket on.
I'm not kidding. I want my lawyer.
Get the fuck out. I'm sick of you.
- And I'm sick of you too.
- Move. Move.
- Get out. Hurry up.
- Your handcuffs are hurting me!
I don't give a fuck!
- I don't give a fuck. Fucking cops--
- Get out the car.
Go fuck yourself.
Hey, back off.
Stay here. Don't move.
Let go of me!
Argh, Vince!
Hey! Catch him!
Let go of me, you asshole!
- Are you okay, Yves?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
It worked. The tracker's activated.
What the fuck?
You were supposed to struggle a little.
What? You wanted it to look real.
Well, it did.
What's wrong, Delvo?
I go overboard?
- Did I go overboard?
- Fuck!
Fuck! We had a deal.
There's no more deal.
Get out of here, prick.
Go fuck yourself. Fucking cops.
We can't trust you.
- That's the last time I'm helping you--
- Do not lose Yacine.
- Keep a constant eye on him.
- Take a walk.
Fucking cops. Don't you dare come
back to the neighborhood!
- Now get lost.
- Bastard. I was just helping out.
The bike'll be ready tomorrow.
- We're a little behind.
- No worries. I'll come back.
- Thank you very much.
- See you then.
What's wrong?
- Did you know?
- Know what?
Yacine robbed a guy on his bike.
Did you know?
- What do you mean? What's this about?
- What do I mean? You don't know?
Are you accusing me of something?
- You still don't trust me?
- This is a paranoid business.
So you bring a woman we know nothing about
and it's me making you--
She's not the problem. It's Yacine.
He's on the run.
Did he snitch?
If he had, we'd be in jail already.
We never should've hired him.
- I'll take care of it.
- You do nothing.
Stick to the plan.
Hello, Soélie.
Hi.
How are you?
Happy to see you again. This way.
Here are the beasts.
These bikes need to be
ready in three days.
You'll work with Théo.
He's already made good progress.
There's the T-Cross
you already know, the Naked,
and in back, the Turbo.
Why all the names?
The T-Cross you saw yesterday?
It has to clear any obstacle.
Even if we soup up the engine,
you'll still have problems with the fork.
Right, yeah. I still need to work
on the suspension travel.
And the Naked is square-rigged.
It needs more agility and power.
The goal is to make it as light
as possible, so it's ultra-easy to ride.
And the Turbo needs to gain speed.
It needs to hit 150, long distance.
We can get there with a boosted variator.
Well, that won't make top speed,
but it's worth a shot.
One question.
And a request.
Well, go on.
Why transform these scooter bikes?
Use dirt bikes instead.
Top speed, more mobile,
and better stability for the rider.
And your request?
A hundred grand.
A hundred thousand is a lot of money, kid.
You aren't planning a picnic though.
You don't have to tell me what.
It's that or I'm out.
Then I want you to begin right now
and work all night if you need to.
And I want you available 24/7.
Okay.
That's great.
So we have a deal.
Oh, you motherfucker.
Fuck!
Here she is.
Tell me, where's the Yam?
- We had a problem.
- A problem? With what?
Just a problem.
- This man is a police officer.
- Lieutenant Delvo.
We met on the training course
two days ago.
So, what brought you there?
Yacine asked me to replace him.
To test a bike.
Is he a friend of yours?
Well, we've trained together a few times.
- What about you?
- I've seen him around before, that's all.
Why didn't you tell
your father his bike had been stolen?
I'd forbidden them from going there,
but apparently, that didn't matter.
We'll fix it.
Since then, have you and Yacine spoken?
No.
Miss, and where were you last night?
Your father was surprised
you weren't here this morning.
With a friend. You want more details?
No.
We're keeping the bike
while we investigate.
We'll give it back after.
Thank you, Daniel.
You're welcome.
Daniel?
Call from the bank.
Be right there.
Yes?
Care to tell me what kind of shit
you two got into this time?
Huh?
Just that type of shit.
What is this?
Where'd it come from?
It's thanks to Michael.
He tested a bike.
It's a job like any other.
- We just want to help you.
- Really?
Help by bringing home a cop?
That's supposed to be helping us?
- That officer, what's his name again?
- Delvo.
- He's a tough one.
Remember? He's a former champion racer.
Was relentless back then.
Yeah.
And do you know what Delvo told me?
Your little friend Yacine has been
accused of armed carjacking.
Were you aware of that?
That has nothing to do with us.
Oh, really?
I sure hope it doesn't because I am just
up to my ears in trouble.
I know this is a bad situation,
but things will work out.
And it's very touching
that you feel concerned.
But I'm going to handle
the problem by myself.
Is that clear?
Who is this friend of yours?
You want details also?
Am I not allowed to have a private life?
What? Hélène, your cigarette!
Go outside. Come on, it's not the '80s.
What a shame that is.
BESTOFFER.CO
Need a hand?
No.
Okay.
I'm going to sleep for an hour.
Try not to fuck up my work.
He should land
around 11:30 in the morning.
That's the route
from the heliport to the hotel.
- What security?
- Only one vehicle.
- You sure?
- Quite sure.
That's the tracker.
It sticks on.
Be careful, it's fragile.
The remote, push that button.
Give me one of those.
Here you go.
Can't we just get
the exact apartment and floor?
We know he didn't leave
the building. We're staying alert.
I've never seen
anything quite like this.
What an incredible comeback.
Soélie Carella takes the lead of this
championship and it is simply incredible.
With this spectacular last win,
we reach the final…
Drives like a fucking bicycle.
I don't know what you did to it,
but you nailed it.
- Yeah, you seemed to dig it.
- Feels like a different ride.
How's it going with the Turbo?
It's getting there. What?
Yeah, it's done. The first half of
your bikes are in a secured box.
I'll get the rest when you're done.
Here's a spare key.
Nice guy, your pops.
Sure. When he wants to.
Thanks.
Awesome.
Well? This is it.
You can get the rest of your bikes back.
Thank you.
Not to be annoying, but I have a question.
Go for it.
You never got back on a bike
after your accident?
I don't really want to talk about it.
Okay, sorry.
My mom died from cancer.
I was furious.
I was angry at the whole world.
So I took her bike out.
And rode at full speed.
Without thinking.
I was in the hospital for a whole month
and did a year of physical therapy.
I was never able to ride after that.
Just reliving my crash every time.
It was constant panic attacks,
tremors and all.
Now I'm barely able to ride a bicycle.
You can overcome
that sort of stuff.
Oh, yeah?
Sure, maybe.
Maybe if you took it
step by step, you know?
Well, I don't know shit, but I'm assuming
there are people who can help
with all that, right?
Hmm.
That stuff supposedly helps
people with trauma, so…
Why wouldn't it work for you?
Hmm.
YO, BRO! I GOT A NEW GIG.
20K FOR YOU.
I'll CALL YOU IN AN HOUR, OKAY?
OKAY, CALL ME. THE COPS LET YOU GO?
Got movement over there.
That jackoff's been holed up all day.
Boss, we have a visual.
He changed his jacket.
He's taking his scooter. What do we do?
- Okay, follow him.
- Okay.
I'm putting the walkies down.
Don't get too close.
Watch out for that red light!
- He's taking the bike path.
- Light 'em up!
It's chaos. We're stuck.
Boss, it's over.
We lost him. No way to locate him.
Dammit!
- What are you doing here?
- It's Yacine.
What about him?
- He told me to meet him here.
- Yacine is coming here?
Yeah, he's on his way.
I heard you might have a job for me.
We're good, Elyas. Everything's clean.
- What's he doing here? Is there a problem?
- Yes, there's a problem.
Get inside.
You too.
You're a real fucking idiot.
Don't talk to me like--
You, stay here.
I'll speak how I want.
With the cops after you,
you come and jeopardize everything--
I have a solution for the biker.
The biker's not your problem.
Michael will ride. If you're ready.
If I'm what? If I'm ready?
Ten months of work for nothing,
and you ask if I'm ready?
I've been doing hold-ups for three years
but never got caught. Do you know why?
Ask me why.
Why?
Okay, why?
Because I'm a professional.
I have everything timed perfectly.
I gave you a chance.
And you behave like a piece of shit.
On top of that,
you bring us your friend.
What did he tell you? What do you know?
He told me about a run on a scooter bike…
a robbery or something.
How much did he offer?
Twenty grand.
You're a real piece of shit.
Twenty grand?
And the cops? What happened there?
How'd you make your escape?
What? I just ran away.
- You ran away?
- Yeah, I ran away.
He ran away.
Okay.
So, you were arrested for…
for armed robbery
and the police had you locked up.
And you manage to escape?
Just like that?
I mean, are you serious, Théo?
You guys getting paranoid or what?
I'm clean. I ran away.
The cops were fighting
with some drunk guy.
I saw an out and ran away.
Come on, let's stick to the plan.
I do the hold-up.
I take my cut and leave the country.
End of story.
Hey.
Elyas, don't fuck around.
Stop right there.
Hey!
Hey! You wanted to do a hold-up?
Here, go ahead.
Here, show me what you can do.
That's what a gun is for.
Your brother's fingerprints are on this.
So you have no choice.
You're my third rider.
Come on, let's go! Everyone on the bikes.
You okay, Mikey?
- On the bikes!
- Come on.
I can't.
The cops are coming. We're running
out of time. Come on, come on!
Hurry, time to go.
Stop it!
See you tomorrow.
I'll send you the address.
- Théo!
- I'll follow her.
Come on, let's move.
Come on. Let's go, Soélie.
You'll be fine.
I'm right behind you, okay?
Lieutenant, it's a bike laboratory
in here. Only high-tech.
It's all hidden over there
behind the shop.
Any sign of the TMAX?
There's nothing left.
They must've cleaned up recently.
- What do we do about him?
- Meaning what?
He wasn't supposed
to get murdered when we released him.
You know nothing.
I'll deal with it.
I fucked up.
I just wanted the money.
I know, I know, I know.
I know.
But we were at the movies,
okay? That's all.
Hey. Hey, look at me. Look at me.
Look at me. Look at me.
We were at the theater. Together. Okay?
Come here.
Sleep it off.
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
Soélie?
Mmm?
Thanks.
- Where did the bikes go?
- I hid them in the shed.
Where's Elyas?
Somewhere hiding away.
- Super.
- Don't worry. He knows what he's doing.
Stop, already.
Your friend just killed somebody.
Remember? Now I'm stuck.
I'm sorry, it wasn't supposed to--
I don't give a fuck if you're sorry, okay?
It's my brother who's framed for murder.
Not you.
Now I don't have a choice.
I never thought he'd go that far.
Soélie, you have to trust me.
Trust me, okay?
Is there somewhere I can sleep?
Whoa!
Hey.
I thought I saw a ghost on a bike.
You looked just
like your mother out there.
I didn't know how to feel.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
I should be the one apologizing.
I've realized
that I wasn't too upset you'd quit.
It was reassuring, actually.
I was able to protect you.
The way I wish I could've protected
your mother from her illness.
Hmm.
The thrill you get on this bike, my girl?
I haven't seen anything
that beautiful for a long time.
Well, it's time to practice now.
Knew you'd never let anyone buy it.
This one? Never.
I did sell the other bikes, however.
It will give us some time.
Sorry.
I think you forgot something
in the kitchen?
A guy in his underwear.
What?
- He's just a friend.
- Just a friend?
- A biker.
- A biker in his underwear?
I'll take care of it. All right?
Take this.
Thanks.
What the heck is going on?
Don't worry.
Mm-hmm.
- I'll wait for you in the shed.
- I'll meet you there.
It will be all right.
- I'm coming with you.
- No.
No.
You have to stay here. To deal with Dad.
Whatever happens…
We stay alive.
Here's what we know.
Mazetti will arrive via the heliport.
There will only be two cars.
And it's this convoy we're interested in.
If you have second thoughts,
now's the time.
- Théo?
- I'm good.
Soélie?
Are you ready?
I have to be.
Okay.
So…
As I've already said,
11:30 a.m., ready in position,
Panama Square.
I'm over here.
Théo, right here.
Soélie, I want you waiting here
for the convoy.
Mazetti will arrive
at Crystal Week in force.
There'll be six convoys. Four from
the airports, and one from the heliport,
and the sixth one in an armored van from--
Come on, Lucas. Calm down.
That's not the plan for today.
I can cover two transfers with my team.
With the use of the special police,
we'll have enough men available
to intervene on every convoy.
You're going to be suspended
until Yacine's escape is investigated.
If everything goes as planned…
we'll stick to the program.
But if the cops follow us? We'll split.
And pass off the goods.
Then it gets technical.
We'll use the GPS.
I want us to be in constant communication.
We'll drive them crazy.
- That kid died because you fucked up--
- Oh please. "That kid"? Be serious.
You're obsessed with these people
and don't have the courage to admit it.
Judge me as much as you want.
The outcome will be the same.
They'll strike tomorrow,
and you'll be blamed for it.
Your badge and your weapon.
I can't do anything for you.
Okay.
Pretend I'm not here.
Mr. Mazetti.
Here we go. Stand by.
Copy that.
Copy.
- How long will the drive be?
- Fifteen minutes, Mr. Mazetti.
GPS activated.
Soélie, on my mark… Go!
Whoa!
Look out.
Watch out!
Come on, let's go! Move in!
Move the fuck off!
Drive!
Come on. Get lost!
Come on!
Move, move! Get lost!
Get out of here! Go!
Get moving! Run!
I said move!
Théo, behind you.
Back off! Back off!
Cover me, Théo!
The stones!
Don't fuck with me.
Hurry up, Elyas.
- I've got the diamonds. Let's move.
- Okay.
Come on. Let's move.
Whoa!
What now?
I got you this time.
Plan B, let's split up.
Biker on my tail, I'll make him
dance a little. Stay in touch.
Suspects on the run
towards Rivoli.
This is V32,
we'll follow them.
V32 has priority.
Careful!
What the fuck?
- Elyas, are you okay?
- Move it!
What the fuck?
Watch out!
It's the cop from the ring road.
He won't back off.
Théo, are you ready? It's your turn.
I see you. I'm coming.
Easy!
Come and get me.
Soélie! Your turn!
Where the fuck are you?
Shit.
What's going on, Théo?
Théo, come in.
Théo, goddammit!
- Are you all right? Are you hurt?
- I'm fine.
Sir, sir!
Get on.
No, we'd be too slow. Go for it!
Damn it!
Hey, talk to me.
Did you find him, Soélie?
Théo crashed.
I've got the stones.
What's going on? Where's Théo?
I'm heading to the meeting point
and the cop is right behind me.
And another one, in a police car.
Get rid of them. Figure it out.
Hey!
There's too many. I can't shake them.
Hold it!
I'm changing routes.
Fuck!
We need to stop him. He won't let me go.
- Elyas, do you hear me?
- Stay focused.
What are you doing?
He's gonna catch me!
Just go.
The stones are all that matter.
Yes!
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
The weapon?
I've disposed of it.
I never even thought
about selling out your brother.
I needed a third rider.
And you were available.
Come on, release me now.
Give me the key.
Help me already. Théo's waiting for us.
You won't be seeing him again.
Three of us watched you murder Yacine.
If you talk, we will too.
Enough with the bullshit, all right?
Give me the keys.
You don't tell me what to do anymore.
It's over.
Okay.
- ♪ Ready! ♪
♪ Set! ♪
ONE YEAR LATER
♪ Go! ♪
♪ Back to business, back to rip this ♪
♪ Whole scene to pieces
Now check my thesis ♪
♪ Making moves
With my mind like telekinesis ♪
♪ They try really hard
But none can see this ♪
♪ They don't want it… ♪
Don't forget to keep your left foot in.
Daniel!
Soélie.
How are things?
I see you've been able
to keep your racetrack.
You here to watch or ask questions?
I'm done with questions.
Well, officially, anyway.
- But I'll get the answers.
- Huh, what answers?
Come on.
We're going to miss the whole race.
- All right? What did he want?
- Nothing. Everything's fine.
Okay, it's your big day.
- Have fun and try to beat your sister.
- Nothing to worry about. Stay focused.
♪ Ready! ♪
♪ Set! ♪
♪ Go! ♪
- Have a good race.
Here we are.
Welcome to the Carella racetrack everyone
for this international trophy event.
Today, we're witnessing Soélie Carella's
comeback, the two-time World Champion
who literally grew up on the tracks.
A round of applause now, please.
She's come back to us
after two years away.
And riding next to Soélie
is her brother, Michael.
And I can tell you that these two
were born with a taste for competition.
All the riders here today are ready
to push their limits,
at the start of this new season.
This should be exciting.
A huge crowd has come out today
to witness this major sporting event.
We can see brother and sister warming
up now, getting ready for the race.
They won't take it easy on each other.
Meanwhile, a proud
and attentive Daniel Carella looks on.
The atmosphere might be cheerful,
but I can assure you
that their competitive spirit is fierce.
We're ready to start.
All the riders are here.
Just have the final preparations now.
The motors are warming up.
We're in the process
of clearing the starting line,
and the race is imminent.
It promises to be explosive.
Are you ready for an epic race today?
Make some noise, Carella fans!
Make some noise!
We can't hear you!
Fifteen seconds!
I'll remind you that Michael Carella,
riding the Yamaha, number 107,
had the fastest trial time. Five seconds!
Soélie, wearing number 106.
Racers are ready!
And… here we go!
♪ They say they're coming for me
But I don't want none ♪
♪ 'Cause I really don't care
And I'm still kinda young ♪
♪ Ruthless ready renegade
They all want some ♪
♪ This may be communism
But I tell you this is mine ♪
♪ Watch what you've been thinking
I set it off ♪
Now carry on ♪
♪ Watch what you've been thinking
I set it off ♪
Now carry on ♪
♪ All these people popping round
I swear I need an Adderall ♪
♪ But I won't let them witness
It's enclosed what I think ♪
♪ Teacher keep on questioning
And pointing out my novice ♪
♪ Now they jamming to my jingles
Like they're on an ice rink ♪
♪ Rocking jeans from Crossroads
And reading out the Cosmos ♪
♪ If they're looking like an issue
Wipe them off the windshield ♪
♪ Nothing left to lose
I'm stepping with the same attire ♪
♪ And I know you feel the heat
Because I'm nothing less than fire ♪
♪ They say they're coming for me
But I don't want none ♪
♪ 'Cause I really don't care
And I'm still kinda young ♪
♪ Ruthless ready renegade
They all want some ♪
♪ This may be communism
But I tell you this is mine ♪
♪ Watch what you've been thinking
I set it off ♪
Now carry on ♪
♪ Watch what you've been thinking
I set it off ♪
Now carry on ♪
♪ Hey, Tkay, baby
They be hating your fresh ♪
♪ The more you rise
They tell you comprise your best ♪
♪ I say fuck 'em
I say get that bullshit off your chest ♪
♪ Don’t let a hater cause
A bead of sweat on your breast ♪
♪ Baby keep it cool
It’s the first day of school ♪
♪ Knowing you’re a rebel
About to break the rules ♪
♪ The old folks scared
And they want you to be too ♪
♪ Handling you like a toddler
What they want you to be two? ♪
♪ Shit handling like pride
Tell them no, bish, no ♪
♪ The world is for the taking
Take it all, bish, all ♪
♪ You the game oner
I say ball, baby, ball ♪
♪ You the shit
No toilet paper, no stall ♪
♪ And baby
I’m the butt-naked truth, no drawl ♪
♪ Anybody this squeaky
Get the ooh and the uh ♪
♪ And that’s from your brother
From another mother ♪
♪ Make sure you stunt hard
And you shine on a suckmother ♪
♪ They say they're coming for you
But I don't want none ♪
♪ 'Cause I really don't care
And I'm still kinda young ♪
♪ Ruthless ready renegade
They all want some ♪
♪ This may be communism
But I tell you this is mine ♪
♪ Oh, I set it off ♪
♪ Oh, now carry on ♪
♪ Still kinda young, still kinda young
I set it off ♪
Now carry on ♪
♪ Still kinda young, still kinda young
I set it off ♪
Now carry on ♪
♪ High like the Himalayas
I'll keep it and they be nothing ♪
♪ Tryna get on this scale
But they tripping, slipping and puffing ♪
♪ Killing the mic with Killer Mike
Busy, and moving moving ♪
♪ The circle is smaller, smaller
But focus made me a nuisance ♪
♪ Witness, witness got no business
I don't hinder, why you vicious? ♪
♪ Minutes, minutes I don’t have
You not really fitted, then forget it ♪
♪ Carry on, you'll never find me
If you get in there ♪
♪ You see that I don’t care
'Cause I’m too young to be prepared ♪
♪ They say they're coming for you
But I don't want none ♪
♪ 'Cause I really don't care
And I'm still kinda young ♪
♪ Ruthless ready renegade
They all want some ♪
♪ This may be communism
But I tell you this is mine ♪
♪ Watch what you've been thinking
I set it off ♪
Now carry on ♪
♪ Watch what you've been thinking
I set it off ♪
Now carry on ♪