[whimsical music]
[wind blowing]
[inspirational music]
[foreboding music]
Since its formation, the Earth
has experienced five mass extinctions.
-The sixth is just beginning.
-[music increases]
[ominous music]
[echoing bubbling]
[echoing thudding]
[gentle music]
CARIBBEAN SEA
off the coast of Puerto Rico
[water gently lapping]
Eating that crap again?
Gimme a break. Give it back.
Eat some fruit.
Back off.
[music continues]
[loud splashing]
When you unlock the reel,
you have to make sure
you hold the line
with one finger,
like this, okay?
-Now you can open it.
-[soft clicks]
Now you're ready to cast it.
And while you cast it,
you need to release
the line, okay?
[echoing bubbling]
[panting]
[light ominous music]
[gentle music]
Now you try.
-Okay.
-Okay?
-Um--
-You remember?
I think so, sir.
-[soft rattling]
-Very well.
You unlocked the reel
and now you're ready to cast it.
-[sharp zipping]
-Nice! Great!
Yankee overboard. [laughs]
[light ominous music]
[heavily breathing]
-[Tom] It's fighting!
-[Ben] Really?
Yeah, sure. Okay,
give it some slack.
[screaming] Tom!
[screaming]
[panting]
Help!
-[music playing from headphones]
-[distant screaming] Tom!
Help!
Tom!
[Julia screaming in distance]
-Dad.
-[shushes]
[grunts]
-Dad!
-[Tom] Julia!
[Ben]
Dad, where are you? I need help!
Help me!
[gasping]
Julia!
-[Julia screaming in distance]
-Fuck!
-Cassie! Hey! Cassie!
-[screaming continues]
Cassie! Come in! I need you!
-What?
-Mom needs help! Come in!
[dramatic music]
[gasping]
-[Ben mumbles] What happened?
-[line snaps]
Grab onto something.
Wait.
[engine starts]
I can go, Dad.
You just need to stop the boat,
I can go. I've got my swimsuit.
I can just jump
-and I can--
-You're staying here!
-Dad! Dad!
-Stay here and keep her steady.
-I can go and help her!
-You stay here
and keep her steady!
[splashing and bubbling]
[gasping]
-[coughs]
-I got you.
I got you. Don't worry.
[coughing and panting]
Dad! Go to the back!
We're gonna go to the back
and we're gonna help you!
Dad!
-Okay.
-[Cassie] Come here!
You're almost there! Mom!
-Mom, I've got you.
I've got you.
-[Tom] You're okay.
[panting and coughing]
[shakily breathing]
I don't know what happened.
I got caught in a current.
I couldn't do anything, I--
I-- I really thought
I wasn't gonna make it.
Now listen, everyone.
I've already told you,
but let me say this again.
When you go swimming,
you tell the others first.
Okay?
Ben?
-Yeah.
-And you never
swim away from the boat.
Is that clear? Cassie?
What, you really think
I'm gonna go and, like...
[chuckling] ...swim
in the middle of the ocean?
This is serious,
I'm not kidding.
We don't even know
what's down there.
Hmmm?
Aye, aye, Captain.
[gentle music]
[water running]
[door creaks]
[gasps and laughs]
What?
I was thinking...
...how lucky I am
to have such a beautiful wife.
Are you saying that
because I almost drowned?
How about I lock in the kids?
[laughter]
Silly.
[music continues]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
[all]
♪ Happy birthday, dear Ben ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ And many more ♪
Hey, my love.
-Happy birthday, kiddo.
-Dad, please! Stop it.
I'm 13 now.
I'm not your kiddo anymore.
You'll always be my kiddo.
Oh, come on,
just blow out the candles.
-You made a wish?
-Sure, I did.
-Bravo!
Bravo!
-[mimics drum roll]
-Here we go.
[Tom chuckles]
It's exactly the one I wanted!
And it's not just
only for gaming, okay?
-It's beautiful, isn't it?
-Yeah, it's really cool.
-And this one.
-[Tom] Oh, my gosh.
[all laughing]
-Even you?
-Yeah.
Well, that's not that different
from your actual face,
but you know, whatever.
-[mockingly laughs]
-Show, show.
-[laughs] Oh, my God.
-[Julia] Mm.
And another one.
I hope you like it.
It's Dominican.
-[Ben] I love it!
-[laughs]
-You see?
-Mm.
A good luck charm
to ward off evil spirits.
I mean, are you sure though?
'Cause Cassie's
still right here.
-[Julia] Uh-huh.
-[grunts] Stop that! Okay.
Ins-- instead of saying
stupid stuff, go on,
let's take a picture.
-Okay, get into position.
-Okay, okay, okay, one second.
-You guys too!
Obviously. Yeah, move.
-[cross talk]
Just go there.
-[Tom] It's got the timer?
-Yeah.
Okay, get ready. Five, four...
[all]
Three, two, one.
-Cheese!
[whirring]
-Okay, that one's gonna be good.
-[Tom] Okay.
-Can I have some cake?
-[Tom] You are a bottomless pit.
-[incoming call on laptop]
-Oh, wait. Miami's calling.
-Get out. Damn.
-It's gonna be Adam.
[chiming]
-[Adam] Hey, everyone.
-Hey.
-How you doing, guys?
-Look.
-It's Ben's birthday.
-Hi, Adam.
Hi, Adam. How are you?
-Hi.
-Okay, hold on.
I'm gonna get some privacy.
Stop. Stop it.
-Seriously, stop!
-[Adam] Where are you going?
You're walking
so long right now.
It's impossible to get
some privacy over here.
[sighing] Okay. I'm back.
-So, how's the cruise going?
-Uh, well,
my mom almost
drowned this morning,
but apart from that,
it's actually pretty boring.
-Boring, you said?
-Yeah.
I honestly
can't wait to see you.
Yeah, me too.
Will you be here on Saturday?
-Yeah.
-It's going to be a great party.
It would be a shame
if you weren't there.
-But I guess I'll have
to call Naomi or something.
-Very funny.
-Seriously, Adam,
don't you dare--
-[thunder rumbling]
Are you seeing this right now?
This is crazy.
-I've never seen
clouds like that.
-Yeah.
Yeah, me neither.
[choppy voice]
[audio breaks up]
Adam.
Shit! What--
[light ominous music]
Dad! Dad!
So soon?
We lost the connection.
There were really weird clouds
in the sky,
and then we just got cut off
-and I can't reach him anymore.
-[shushes] Listen.
[wind chime rattling]
[distant echoing wailing]
We've got to be
at least five miles away
from the coast of Cuba.
You will try again later. Ben?
[water lapping]
[Ben]
It's whales.
[softly laughs]
[loud splashing]
[Tom]
You know, whales follow
the Earth's magnetic field.
Well, sometimes storms
can cause abnormalities.
And so, the whales head in
towards the coast,
convinced they're actually
headed along it.
Nothing weird about that.
[foreboding music]
[boat cracking]
[Ben grunts]
-Ben, you good?
-Yeah.
-Okay, Cassie?
-Yes.
What was that?
Are you sure
you wanna go down there?
Don't worry. I just need
to take a look at the shafts
and the propellers.
Be careful.
[suspenseful music]
-[gasps]
-[Cassie] Dad.
-[Tom] Oh, shit! [grunting]
-[Cassie] Are you okay?
[Cassie]
Hold on.
Let me see.
I felt something behind me.
And when I turned around,
I cut myself in the propeller.
Hold still.
Wha-- what was it?
Like a sh-- a shark?
I don't know. It was big.
It was really big.
How bad is it?
Well, the shafts are bent.
And one of the propellers
is shot.
-Can you fix them?
-No way.
-We need to call for help.
-Best holiday ever.
Well, yes, I'm sorry.
If you keep moving, I can't do it.
Dad?
[wind chime rattling]
[soft squelching]
[engine starting]
[loud rattling]
[Julia]
Orca, Orca, engine failure.
Pan-pan, pan-pan, pan-pan.
This is motor yacht Orca.
Orca, Orca. Coordinates--
Engine failure, coordinates,
two-zero degrees,
three-zero minutes north...
Fucking hell!
...zero-zero minutes west.
Four passengers on board.
Pan-pan.
-[yells]
-[Cassie screams]
Ben, seriously? We're in deep shit here!
This is motor yacht Orca, Orca.
Engine failure.
Coordinates, two-zero degrees,
three-zero minutes north.
Zero-five forward degrees,
zero-zero minutes west.
Engine failure.
Coordinates...
-[engine rumbling]
-[hissing]
-...zero minutes west.
-[Tom] Shit!
Four passengers on board.
Pan-pan, pan-pan, pan-pan.
-[man speaking
indistinctly on radio]
-What is that?
I don't know. Check by yourself.
[indistinct chatter
on radio continues]
This is motor yacht...
Beat it.
Get off my bed. Move!
Fucking move!
It's gross.
You got crumbs everywhere.
-[Tom] ...four passengers, over.
-[sighs] Fucking shit!
[tense music]
[screams into pillow]
[Tom]
Pan-pan, pan-pan. This is
motor yacht Orca calling.
Orca! Oscar, Romeo,
Charlie, Alpha.
-Anyone hear me? Over.
-[radio chimes]
[man speaking
indistinctly on radio]
Oh, fucking shit!
[indistinct chatter continues]
Well, we have
26 gallons of water.
-And food for at least
four days. We'll be fine.
-How can you be so sure?
Well, I'm not sure!
But we're on a shipping route.
There's no way
we won't see anyone.
[beeping]
[distant rumbling]
[light ominous music]
[beeping continues]
What the fuck?
You see that?
[loud rumbling]
Dad, what is that?
I've no idea.
-[Cassie] Holy shit!
-[Tom] Whoa!
[explosion]
Let's have a look from up there.
[grunts]
-Dad, watch out!
-[Tom] Whoa!
[loud rumbling]
-[explosion]
-[Tom] We need to move!
[dramatic music]
-[click]
-[rumbling]
[grunts]
[engine rumbling]
-[explosion]
-[clacking]
Dad, Dad, a third one! Up there!
[loud explosion]
[panting]
[Tom]
Those are not meteorites.
They're satellites.
Da-- Dad, Dad. Dad.
-Wha-- [mumbles]
-Th-- there's smoke there.
-[loud creaking]
-[grunts]
[hissing]
There's nothing we can do.
[door creaks, closes]
[foreboding music]
[water lapping]
[wind blowing]
[thunder rumbling]
Get inside, everyone.
[rattling]
[ominous music]
-[grunting]
-[thud]
[waves crashing]
[grunts and shouts]
[clattering]
-[Ben groaning]
-Ben!
-Dad, Ben's hurt. Ben's hurt.
-[Tom] Come on.
[groans]
[Tom]
Sit down, okay?
-Are you okay? All right.
-Yeah, I'm okay.
[waves crashing]
Watch out!
-[groans]
-[clattering]
[grunts]
[waves crashing]
-[clattering continues]
-[grunting]
[indistinctly mumbles]
...okay, sit down.
[panting and grunting]
Mom...
[high-pitched white noise]
[shakily breathing]
[white noise increases]
-[loud rattling]
-[grunts]
[Tom]
This is motor yacht Orca.
Oscar, Romeo, Charlie, Alpha.
-Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
-[Cassie retching]
[Tom]
Can you hear me? Anyone? Over!
[Cassie retching and coughing]
[Tom]
Mayday! Mayday!
-Help! Mayday! Mayday!
-[retching and coughing]
Mayday. May--
mayday, mayday, mayday!
This is the Orca!
Oscar, Romeo, Charlie, Alpha.
-We're in a storm! We need help!
-[rattling]
-[high-pitched white noise]
-[groaning and gasping]
[shakily breathing]
[dramatic music]
-[grunts and pants]
-[wind howling]
-[Ben screams]
-Ben!
[glass shattering]
[wind softly blowing]
[soft rattling]
[foreboding music]
[Cassie grunts]
[groans]
[creaking]
Kids?
[grunts, groans]
What?
-[heavily breathing]
-[grunting]
[door creaks]
[panting]
Ben!
[loud scratching]
[water dripping]
[music continues]
[dramatic music]
[wind blowing]
Still nothing.
-Dad. Wha--
-Mm?
What are we going to do?
[gasps]
There must be other survivors.
We need to contact them.
I'm not worried.
You always find a solution.
You're right, Ben.
Every problem has a solution.
This is weird.
This is simply not possible!
Well, north is not
where it should be.
[grunts] North indicates south
and south indicates north.
As if the poles reversed.
-Is that even possible?
-Last time it happened
was more than 700,000 years ago.
-Where's the sea?
-[sighs]
It seems it's
where it shouldn't be.
Wait.
Wait, so does that mean
that the sea just went--
Maybe to where the land was.
So that would mean
that... Adam...
[light ominous music]
[gasps]
[mumbling] No, no, no, no,
no, no... it can't be true.
-[Cassie indistinctly mumbles]
-Cassie.
...no, no, no, no, no, no,
that doesn't make
any sense, right?
That doesn't make any sense,
the poles cannot
just reverse like that.
-[Tom] Wait. We need to--
-It doesn't make any sense.
It's ridiculous!
We don't know anything for sure.
-Cassie, please!
-[Julia] Cassie, Cassie!
[Cassie sobbing]
Honey...
We don't know for sure.
Don't go imagining the worst.
[sobbing]
Come on.
Go away.
Go away, will you!
[melancholic music]
-[sighs]
-[sobbing]
[shakily breathing]
[wind blowing]
[shouting] Mom! Dad!
Where is he?
[echoing]
It's for the other survivors!
They'll see it from far away!
See? I can think
of good solutions too.
[wind continues blowing]
[soft rattling]
-[clicks]
-[radio static]
[beeping]
[loud static]
It's working now. Julia.
It just needed more power.
Mayday. Mayday. Mayday.
This is the Orca motor yacht.
Oscar, Romeo, Charlie, Alpha.
The ocean has gone.
Four passengers.
-Over.
-[loud static]
-Mayday.
-[static continues]
This is Nao.
Captain of the Shanghai 6500.
-Over.
-[chuckling] Hey! Hi.
Hi, I'm Tom.
So happy to finally
hear someone.
Do you have
any idea what happened?
[Nao]
Reverse of the magnetic poles.
We were deep diving
when the ocean retreated
and submerged the mainlands.
-[Tom] How far?
-Impossible to say as it stands.
I can't believe it.
The conspiracy theory nuts
were right.
Maybe the earth has decided
to eliminate the men
before they destroy it.
[static continues]
Well, you could be right.
Have you come into contact
with any other survivors?
No. Most communication systems
are down.
Anyway, there are
systemic movements
which indicate that the poles
are going to reverse again
-and the sea could return.
-When?
According to my instruments,
no more than a week.
This is going to be
really violent.
Try to climb
as high as possible.
We gotta go. Pack up your stuff.
[Tom]
Ben, move.
Come on, let's go.
Come with me.
[tense music]
-[radio whining]
-How many people
can you take on board?
The Shanghai is
a scientific bathyscaphe.
The capacity is for three.
My partner didn't have
his safety harness.
He did not survive.
We're sorry for your loss.
So you can take our kids?
Please, y-- you can trust us.
We really just want
to save our children.
[radio clicks]
Look, I'm an oceanographer
from the University of Miami.
My wife's a doctor.
You can really--
We're just asking you
to save our children, please.
[radio clicks]
[panting]
[Nao]
18.30 north, 83.00 west.
[softly] Okay.
[music continues]
According to your coordinates,
you're two or three days away.
I will stay connected
on channel 16.
Don't worry.
Only the children.
-[radio clicks]
-Good luck.
We're getting
a good night's sleep.
And we're leaving tomorrow
early in the morning, okay?
We have a good chance
of making it there
before the ocean comes back.
[whispers] Okay.
[melancholic music]
We are gonna make this.
[sobbing]
And I'll be with you.
Okay? Let's prepare the kids.
[shakily breathing]
[soft chirping]
[wind blowing]
[dog barking]
[barking continues]
[dog panting]
[distant barking]
[music playing on headphones]
[barking continues]
[wind blowing]
I'm so glad to finally
run into someone.
I'm Tom.
Are you hurt?
My wife's a doctor
if you need any help.
[indistinct mumbling]
[mumbles softly]
[foreboding music]
-Are you sure you're okay?
-[heavily breathing]
-[grunts]
-[Julia] Hey!
-[dog barking]
-Stop! Stop!
[grunts]
Stop it! Stop!
[dog snarling]
[dramatic music]
-[groans]
-[dog barking]
[Julia screaming]
[dog barking]
[gasping]
[grunts]
-[flesh squelching]
-[gasping]
[gagging]
[screaming]
[dog barking]
[music playing on headphones]
[screams and cries]
[grunts and pants] Cassie!
[gasping]
Cassie!
[crying]
[dramatic music]
Mom!
What's going on?
Hide back there!
Mom?
[dog barking]
[panting]
There! Move it!
Get in.
Fast! Come on!
[grunts]
[heavily breathing]
-[thuds]
-[door rattling]
[grunting]
[panting]
[screaming]
If it's not me, the flare's loaded.
Shoot!
Get it? Shoot if it's not me.
-[man screams]
-[shushes]
[door rattling]
[man grunting]
-[grunting and screaming]
-[thudding]
[blade ringing]
[screaming]
[screaming continues]
[clattering]
[panting]
[muffled breathing]
[light ominous music]
[shakily breathing]
[music increases]
-[wind howling]
-[grunts and whimpers]
[suspenseful music]
[dog snarling and barking]
[dramatic music]
[grunts and groans]
-[blade ringing]
-[dog whimpers]
-[dog whining]
[heavily breathing]
[whining continues]
[dramatic music]
[softly sobbing]
[panting]
[groaning]
[grunting]
[panting]
-[man grunts]
-[groaning]
[music continues]
[Julia groaning]
[Julia groaning and panting]
[grunting]
[groans and screams]
-[thud]
-[groans]
[groaning and panting]
[screams and cries]
-[groaning]
-[blade clinking]
-[grunts]
-[crying]
-[thudding]
-[heavily breathing]
-[Julia groaning]
[crying]
-[thud]
-[groans]
[gasping and choking]
[ominous music]
[choking and coughing]
[gun clicks]
Shoot.
[gasping]
[panting]
Shoot!
-[gunshot]
-[screams]
[glass shattering]
[fire whooshing and crackling]
[Julia breathing heavily]
Get out!
[coughing]
Get out.
[panting]
Mom, what the hell are you doing?
[man shouting]
[groans]
Forget the supplies!
Hurry!
Forget the bags!
[coughing]
Come on, Dad. Please!
[crying and coughing]
[sobbing]
Please, Dad.
Come on.
[somber music]
[crying and sobbing]
[Ben indistinctly mumbles]
[ominous music]
Let's go!
[fire whooshing]
[echoing] Dad!
[inaudible]
[explosion]
[glass shattering]
[wind blowing]
[muffled panting]
[muffled grunting]
[water trickling]
-[panting]
-[deeply exhales]
[exhales]
Drink. A few sips.
You think he saw the balloons?
What?
The psycho.
You think he saw the balloons?
Stop.
Don't say that.
[sighs]
Don't blame yourself.
There was no way of knowing.
Don't blame yourself, okay?
It's not your fault. Got it?
It's not your fault.
I'll do all I can to protect you.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
No one.
[heavily breathing]
[kisses]
[wind howling]
[ominous music]
[water gently lapping]
[panting]
What?
[gasps]
Come on!
[dramatic music]
[all panting]
[panting continues]
Go!
[Julia grunting]
Keep going!
[panting]
[foreboding music]
[wind blowing]
[panting]
[Julia grunts]
[groans]
What's wrong?
Dehydration. You need fluids.
Hold on.
Who the hell did this?
Drink what's left.
I think I left it unscrewed.
Shit, Cassie, it's empty!
It wasn't on purpose.
How do we survive without water?
Don't yell at me. Back off.
It's not like we won't die anyway.
-Don't say that!
-Why? We're gonna croak.
It's the truth!
You think you can save us
but you can't!
Nobody can save us.
We're gonna croak here.
Dad got slaughtered by a freak.
and you're obsessed about a bottle.
A fucking bottle!
Enough!
Shut up, that's enough!
Shut up!
[heavily breathing]
[wind blowing]
[panting]
[ominous music]
Go right.
[foreboding music]
-[grunts]
-[door loudly creaking]
[birds screeching]
[chirping]
Thanks.
Try to get some sleep.
[melancholic music]
[deeply exhales]
[lighter clicks]
I can't believe he's gone forever.
I feel like...
I've fallen off a cliff.
I know.
Tell me the story of how you met again.
[softly chuckles]
The first time I saw him,
I was 22.
I was training
at the hospital in Nice.
And one morning...
a German was brought in
after a diving accident.
What was he doing?
Research for his thesis
on red gorgonians dying out
in the Mediterranean.
On what?
They look like coral.
Anyway, he'd had a...
decompression issue on a dive.
[gentle music]
He spent three days
in a hyperbaric chamber.
There are better first meetings.
As soon as he got out,
he started hitting on me.
It worked?
Not right away.
I set him straight.
As his doctor.
As if that would stop him.
[sighs]
Two days later,
outside the hospital,
he was waiting with flowers.
Old school.
We spent a whole week together.
It was...
[deeply inhales]
He had to go back to Germany.
I thought...
I'd never see him again.
And then?
Six months later, he...
He was there,
outside the hospital.
And...
he declared his undying love.
With a poem by Victor Hugo.
[music continues]
"It's enough for you to fly away.
"For me to fly too."
Then,
he explained
he'd got his degree
and been offered a job in Miami.
And he'd only accept it
if I agreed to go with him.
Not an easy decision.
To practice in the USA,
I had to requalify.
You know what he said?
Every problem has a solution.
[Julia crying]
[wind howling]
[soft chittering]
[gasps]
[wind howling]
-[blade ringing]
-[Cassie screaming]
[man groans]
[dramatic music]
[shouts]
[grunting and screaming]
[flesh squelching]
[screaming continues]
[heavily breathing]
[screaming]
[panting]
[ominous music]
[wind blowing]
[door creaking]
[grunting]
[flies buzzing]
What could have done this?
Whatever it was, it's not human.
So there's something out there
even nastier than this wacko.
[buzzing continues]
Come on.
Let's go.
[ominous music]
[water faintly trickling]
[water bubbling]
Wait!
Where you going?
Wait for us.
[suspenseful music]
Get out of there right now!
Don't!
Are you nuts? You'll get sick!
[coughing]
[wind blowing]
[grunts]
[foreboding music]
[softly groaning]
[panting]
[echoing heavily breathing]
[echoing thudding]
[melancholic music]
[wind howling]
[deeply exhales]
[wind blowing]
[faint chittering]
[foreboding music]
[chittering increases]
[panting]
[tense music]
[grunts and groans]
Kids!
We can't stay here.
What's going on?
Move it!
[chittering continues]
[panting]
[chittering increases]
[grunts]
Look!
People.
Let's go.
[music continues]
There's a woman and children!
Forget about it.
Look, behind them!
Help!
-There's more of them. Get inside!
-[Cassie] Help!
Help us!
Help! Help!
-[Cassie] Help! Please, help!
-[Julia yells] No!
-No!
-[thudding]
[Julia]
Open up! Come on!
-[high-pitched screeching]
-Open up!
[chittering continues]
Go on, Cassie, climb up.
[Cassie grunts]
[dramatic music]
[grunting]
-[screeching]
-[indistinct shouting]
-[gunshots]
-[crabs screeching]
[screaming]
[grunting]
Keep going!
-[gunshots]
-[people screaming]
C'mon, kids.
Back up.
[screeching continues]
[people screaming]
[all grunting and groaning]
-[gunshots]
-[crabs screeching]
[panting]
-[gunshots]
-[indistinct screaming]
[man screaming]
-[crab screeching]
-[screams]
[panting, whispers]
Okay. Okay. Okay.
-[crabs screeching]
-[grunting]
[Julia groans]
[groaning]
[echoing grunting]
[grunting and panting]
[high-pitched ringing]
[loud bubbling]
[muted]
[wind gushing]
Mom!
We went for help. There's no one!
Where's Ben?
[panting]
[wind howling]
[loud creaking and thudding]
[groaning]
[groaning and heavily breathing]
[whimpering]
[gasping]
[wind howling]
[gun cocks]
Where'd you learn to do that?
[panting]
[gasps and sharply exhales]
[light tense music]
Cassie, keep watch.
Shit, a radio!
Grab that gun!
[Julia panting]
Work, dammit.
[gun clicks]
Channel 16.
Work.
[beeping]
Nao?
Nao, this is Julia, Tom's wife.
Are you there?
-Come in. Nao?
-[beeps]
Nao, this is Julia, Tom's wife.
-Where are you?
-[flies buzzing]
[radio whining]
I don't really know.
Uh, I lost the nautical chart.
[wind blowing]
We found a freighter
and containers.
We got attacked by something.
[Nao]
I got attacked last night.
What is this shit?
Arthropods from the abyss.
The sea released them
when it retreated.
The oxygen seems
to drive them crazy.
-They have no more food.
-[flies buzzing]
They attack to eat.
Life adapts to the environment.
Are there still four of you?
No.
Only three of us are left.
-My children and myself.
-[radio whining]
-Are you there?
-Yes.
[softly] Just save
my children, please.
You save my children, okay?
You need to hurry.
According to the movement
of my instrument's recording,
the sea is coming back
faster than expected.
How long?
It's a matter of hours.
Okay. We're leaving right now.
But, uh, I don't know
in which direction.
Just watch in the sky.
-[flies buzzing]
-[gun clicks]
[static]
[heavily breathing]
-[gunshot]
-[hissing]
[suspenseful music]
Okay, we see you!
[grunts]
[both panting]
Look, over there.
Shit...
That rift.
[soft splashing]
Let's go.
[bird squawking]
[music continues]
What's with "save my children" earlier?
Ben, c'mon!
[sharply exhales]
[loud rumbling]
[panting]
Mom, all good?
Keep going.
[water splashing]
[rocks rumbling]
[Julia gasps]
Watch out!
Hurry!
[Cassie panting]
[Cassie whimpers]
[grunting]
[loud rumbling]
Here we go again.
-[rumbling continues]
-[grunts]
Shit!
[screams]
Watch out!
[loud rumbling]
[loud crash]
[grunting]
[Cassie screams]
[grunting and panting]
[gasping]
[coughing]
[groaning]
Mom?
[somber music]
Climb over!
Hold on, listen to me.
Keep going!
-What?
-Just go!
No!
Keep going, I said!
No, climb over it!
Just go!
Climb over it!
Hurry!
Climb!
Mom, we're not going anywhere.
Come with us, for fuck's sake!
Not without you!
Take Ben and go!
You hear me? Just go!
[Cassie sobbing]
I'll find you.
I'll find you. Now go!
We're going. Come on!
[music continues]
Careful.
[clacking]
[both grunting]
[panting]
There!
Nao!
Nao! Are you in there?
[panting] Oh.
Oh, my God.
[whispers] Oh, my God.
[distant screeching]
It's a matter of minutes.
Get inside. It's over for me.
[flies buzzing]
I'm gonna go and get her.
-I'm gonna go and get her.
-No.
-I have to! I have to. Ben!
-Wait!
[beads rattling]
[panting]
[dramatic music]
[gunshots]
[crabs screeching]
-[grunts]
-[gun clicks]
[gasps]
[screeching continues]
[grunting]
[gunshots]
[screeching increases]
[crying]
[panting]
Come on.
Grab my hand.
There's room for you.
[screeching continues]
[panting and grunting]
[suspenseful music]
[panting]
[grunting]
[chittering and screeching]
[dramatic music]
[gunshots]
[panting]
Climb up, come on.
[crabs screeching]
Give me that.
Inside!
Go on, get in.
C'mon, now!
-Fast!
-Get inside!
Hurry up, Ben!
[gunshots]
-[grunting]
-[gun clicks]
How does this shut?
-[rattling]
-[panting]
Turn it.
-[metal clattering]
-We're good.
Push it.
[panting]
[screeching]
It's coming.
[waves crashing]
Sit down. Get in your seats!
Fast!
Strap in!
[grunting]
-Fuck it!
-Look...
Cross them in front.
[grunting]
[panting]
[waves rumbling]
-[loud rumbling and bubbling]
-[groaning]
[metal creaking]
[Cassie grunts]
[metal rattling]
[groaning]
[grunting]
[dramatic music]
-[shouts]
-[gasping]
[screaming]
[barking]
[gasps]
-[grunts]
-[all] ♪ Happy Birthday to-- ♪
[explosion]
[groaning]
[loud bubbling]
[vomiting]
[gasping]
[waves crashing]
[echoing groan]
[silence]
[water dripping]
[shakily breathing]
-[groans]
-[sighs]
[groaning]
[light suspenseful music]
[panting]
[Cassie whispers]
Fuck.
[grunting]
[panting]
[melancholic music]
[Cassie grunts]
[panting]
SURVIVE
[music continues]
[ominous music]
[somber music]
[music turns ominous]