cuckoo!
There she is,
the Almost Birthday Girl.
Oh, but...
it seems I wore my long legs today.
What happens if I...?
♪ Well, I've got a little babe ♪
♪With jewels upon her lip ♪
♪ Her hair's like a river♪
♪ It's fast and slowly drips ♪
♪ How, how ♪
♪ She bathes in thunder♪
♪ The elves are under her♪
♪ She walks the wind ♪
♪And has a panther
with silverfur♪
♪ How, how ♪
♪ Ow! ♪
All right, kids.
This is the part where you
get to do the things
the grownups don't wanna do anymore.
Door to door, on foot,
knock-knock, "Have you
seen this man?"
Just like in the movies.
Partners have already been assigned,
so no one gets hurt feelings.
Suspect likes to visit a certain
kind of neighborhood.
He's a middle-aged Caucasian male
and not likely to go quietly,
so let's always assume he's armed.
We'll go alert and careful.
That's all.
Okay, well,
I am good to be the one who
goes up and knocks,
if you wanna be the one
who hangs back.
Harker?
You good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Subtitle | www.movieddl.me
That kid smelled like narcotics.
Harker.
It's that one.
What's what one?
3525.
He's in there.
What makes you say that?
I don't know.
We should call it in.
What? No.
No, we're not gonna call in a hunch
on our first day out doing this.
Just relax.
But I'll go take a look.
All right?
Lee, relax.
FBI!
Hi there!
Hi, I just wondered if you'd take a
look at that for me--
Don't move.
I won't.
State
your name an drank.
Special Agent Lee Harker.
Can someone tell me what
I'm doing in here?
Special Agent Lee Harker,
are you ready to begin?
Ready to begin what?
State the first word
that comes to mind
to accompany each image.
Are you ready to begin?
Yes.
Camera.
Table.
Legs.
Tiger.
Door.
Mother.
Father.
Piano.
A number has been generated
between zero and 100,
inclusive.
What is the number?
I-I don't know.
33?
A number has been generated
between zero and 100, inclusive.
What is the number?
Zero.
You a baseball fan,
Harker?
No, sir.
Damn.
I need to talk to someone about my
beautiful Mariners,
but...
Well, my wife's getting pretty
good at faking it, so...
That's a slippery slope.
Damn, Agent Browning, that's cold.
I only work with what you give me,
Agent Carter.
You beat that numbers
generator eight times.
How'd you do that?
I also missed
it eight times.
Hmm.
Half-psychic is better than
not psychic at all,
I'd say.
Family of four lived in that house
for 12 years.
The Horns.
Nice people.
Dad taught college, coached T-ball.
Mom ran the church bake sale,
and then, two months ago,
they all get murdered inside.
Four victims,
but technically three
murders and a suicide.
The father?
Yeah, he didn't do
it halfway, either.
Stabbed his wife 61 times
before the blade snapped
off the handle.
What about the kids?
What about 'em?
How many wounds?
You can read about it in the file.
You said four were murdered.
I don't understand.
Neither do we.
A letter was left with the bodies,
written in a coded alphabet,
and not in the hand of anyone
in any way connected to the family.
So...
We have ten letters like it,
made by the same hand.
Ten houses, ten families, over
the past 30 years,
and all of them signed
with one word...
"Longlegs".
Someone or something is making
the fathers do it.
So far, we've been goddamned to
figure out what or who.
I'm telling you, she's
not ready forth is.
You got a better idea, Browning,
then you can run with it.
There you go, Harker,
take a nice long look.
Tell me your version
of what happened in Colfax with the
shooting of Agent Fisk.
It's hard to explain, sir.
It's like something tapping
me on the shoulder,
telling me where to look.
You identified a suspect's house,
with no prior knowledge,
no real indication that it was
any way different
than all the
cookie-cutters all around it.
Anything like that ever
happen to you before,
Agent Harker?
From time to time, sir.
Well, maybe we'll just call you
"highly intuitivet".
Yes, sir.
Uh-huh.
Tell me what you see.
What do the families have in common?
That's a good question.
All the victim families
have daughters whose
birthdays are on the 14th
of any given month.
But only the Horns
were actually murdered on that date.
Get to work.
9-1-1. What's
your emergency?
It's...
It's my daughter.
It's... it's not my daughter...
Sir, who's
not your daughter?
I gotta be quiet.
I've gotta be quiet.
Sir, where are you?
When she's sleeping...
When she's sleeping,
it's the best time to do it.
Do what?
When here yes are closed.
Sir, can you stay
on the line with me?
Sir?
Hello?
Can you stay on the line?
Sir?
9-1-1. What
is your emergency?
Help!
Harker!
You know, there's such a thing
as looking too long.
I must have lost track of time.
I'm still thirsty.
Are you thirsty?
Come on, let's go for a drink.
You'll have to excuse me, I...
it's late, and I don't drink.
You don't drink, you're right.
I'll drink
while you tell me things.
Agent Harker.
Come on, bag it up!
Ah, thanks, Melissa.
Go ahead, Harker.
Well, there's no signs
of forced entry.
In fact, forensics says
there's no indication he was ever
in the house at all.
There's only the bodies
of the victims,
and they've all been killed
with something from
inside the house.
Two times, a shotgun,
both legally registered
to the father.
Eight times, a knife from the
family's kitchen.
Once, a hammer from the
family's too"ox.
All right.
And...?
Longlegs would have to be
inside the house
to use the shotgun, the knife,
the hammer,
but according to physical evidence,
he never is.
If it wasn't for the
letters he left behind,
it's almost like he was
never there at all.
He murders them,
but not in person.
Maybe he tells the families what
he wants them to do--
To themselves, to each other--
Then they do it.
Well, now, that...
that reads like a page
out of Manson.
Manson had accomplices.
His Family.
You think Longlegs has help?
Hmm.
All right.
Mm!
Oh, man.
Whoo!
Okay, bedtime.
I'll drive.
You take a left right here.
And the lights are on.
I'm busted.
Well, all right, Harker,
you get to come meet my
wife and kid.
Um, sir...
do I have to?
Yeah.
Come on in.
Hey, there she is!
You didn't call to say goodnight.
Oh, 'cause it was late,
and it was past your bedtime.
Well, now it's even later,
and way, way past my bedtime.
Uh, yeah.
I guess I screwed that up, huh?
Hello.
Oh, hey, this is, uh,
Agent Lee Harker.
Harker, this is my beautiful wife,
Anna,
and our daughter, Miss Ruby.
Nice to meet you, Harker.
- Hi, honey. -Hey, babe.
I'm glad you're home.
Do you want to see my room?
What happened to this one?
Its head got cut off,
and I don't know where it is.
I guess that's more my job...
finding things, I mean.
What about that thing,
do you go in it?
It's too babyish.
Dad says he wants to keep some of
my old stuff around
so I don't grow up too fast,
but I'm gonna grow up anyway.
Even veals grow a little,
and they live in a box
with their legs all tied up
and everything.
Veals have it pretty tough,
don't they?
Did you wanna be an FBI agent when
you were a little girl?
No.
I actually wanted to be an actress.
That messes up kids.
So they say.
Is it scary being a lady FBI agent?
Yeah.
Yeah, it is.
All right, you two.
I'm sure Agent Harker's got
a lot of very important work to do,
and, Miss Ruby Carter, it's...
Well, it's tomorrow.
Can she come to my birthday party?
Sounds great to me.
Why don't you ask her?
I'll be there.
Yes?
Hello?
Hi, Mom.
Lee?
Yup, still only me.
Are you okay?
Yeah, spent the day at home.
Where else would I be?
What are you doing in the house?
Do you have to let the
phone ring so long?
Trying to go through some
stuff over here.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I just can't sleep.
A lot on my mind.
Work stuff.
Nasty stuff?
Um, yeah.
Want to tell me about it?
No...
No.
Don't forget I was a nurse
for eight years.
I saw more than my fair
share of nasty stuff.
I think I just need to be
quiet for a little bit.
Somebody's birthday's coming up.
Honey? Are you still there?
Mom, I gotta go.
I-I'll call you back, okay?
Hello?
Hello,
no one is available to
take your call.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
Lee?
Are you there?
Call me back.
Yes, Mom, I'm fine.
Harker?
Carter's looking for you.
Um, yeah, It'll be right in.
Can you have a look at this?
Him again.
We are real late on this one.
Looks like the family was
planning a trip.
A friend assumed they'd gone,
so no one bothered to
check in on 'em.
Found plane tickets for Los Angeles
and reservations for Disneyland.
Sounds like a nice idea.
And the girl's birthday
was the 14th?
Seems like it.
How'd you figure that out?
I only looked long enough, sir.
Yeah, well,
there's a dead family in
the master bedroom,
so let's go take a long
look at that.
We found dad in the garage.
Wrists and throat,
kitchen knife in his hand.
His wounds look self-inflicted,
but we'll be sure when we're sure.
This is everyone else here,
and it's not great.
How long ago?
I'd say about a month.
Jesus.
Okay.
Let's take a look.
Are you sure she--
Yeah, she's good. You're good,
aren't you, Harker?
Pull it.
How old's the girl?
I'm guessing nine or ten.
Fuck.
Yes, who is it?
Hi, Mom.
Lee?
Yes.
Still your only daughter.
Anyways, I was calling
to let you know
that I'm gonna busy now,
with work,
and I probably won't be
able to make it.
I want to, it's just--
Mom, are you still there?
Be careful they
don't work you too hard,
all right?
Yeah, but it's good.
It's really good.
They put me on something important.
Yeah?
What is it?
Well, I can't tell you.
You wouldn't wanna hear
about it anyways.
Not nice things.
I don't think the Bureau has a
division for nice things.
Will I see you on your
birthday next week?
I'll try.
Lee?
Are you still saying your prayers?
Yeah.
Listen I gotta go.
Lee, honey,
our prayers protect us
from the Devil.
I know.
I know, Mom.
I'll call you later, okay?
Help me out here.
It's an algorithm.
His algorithm.
Help me out more.
The first murder happens on
July 14th, 1966.
The rest occur within six days of
the daughters' birthdays,
either before or after...
...creating an inverted triangle.
Okay, what am I supposed
to do with this?
I also decoded all his letters.
The one thing that stood out
was the repeated reference
to "the fine time we had at the
Camera family farm,"
where X's mark the spot.
The Camera family.
I was at Georgetown when
that happened.
Their local priest makes
his weekly visit,
but it goes bad,
due to Carrie Anne's father and the
axe from the tool shed.
He kills the priest, his wife,
and then himself.
Carrie Anne's at school,
so she survives.
Look at the date.
March 8th.
Now look at Carrie Anne's birthday.
March 14th.
Six days apart.
Well, no shit.
I believe Longlegs was at the
Camera family farm,
and it's possible that
Carrie Anne saw him.
What about the 13th?
It's missing.
I'm still not sure about that,
but it's three days from now.
Maybe Longlegs will kill again.
And this Carrie Anne,
she still alive?
Water Rock Psychiatric Hospital.
That's not far from here.
132 miles, sir.
And the old farm?
89.
Let's start there.
It's over there.
Xs mark the spot.
Carter?
Yeah?
She's handmade,
that's for sure.
And beautifully handmade at that.
Porcelain head, hands and feet,
unbleached canvas body,
cotton stuffing.
The hair is human,
what's left of it.
All in all, it's beautifully made,
by a highly-skilled craftsman.
But what about
the ball there?
Mm.
It was inside the head.
So I've been calling it the "brain".
It's hollow, empty of
object or matter,
but listen...
And what's your name, little angel?
Nice to meet you, Carrie Anne.
Now...
I know you're not afraid
of a little bit of dark...
...because
you are the dark.
The other night, I
could have sworn
it was whispering my ex-wife's name
over and over again,
but...
I've been working very late,
and of course it--it wasn't.
Yeah, can the-- Can the "brain"
be opened up?
Of course,
but it's not likely
there's a solution to
your case in there,
because there's nothing in there.
Well,
let's go see Carrie Anne Camera at
the mental hospital.
Can I help you with
anything else today?
Cuckoo.
Cuckoo. Cuckoo.
I don't know what that was
supposed to be.
And what day is your birthday,
little angel?
Daddy!
That gross guy is back again!
Mommy!
Unmake me!
And save me
from the hell of living!
Two days ago, Carrie Anne is
postcard catatonic.
Well, slumped in a chair by the door
for as long as I've been here,
and I've been here eight years.
Then yesterday, she gets a visitor,
and I've never seen that
happen either,
and like someone flipped a switch
on the back of her head,
and all of a sudden,
she's right there.
Wide awake,
eyes bright.
You saw this visitor?
No, I wasn't on site at the time,
unfortunately,
but the log should say.
Does the guard check IDs?
Well, it does sound like a
good idea, but no.
No, we do not require that.
Thank you, Carrie Anne,
for taking the time to
talk to me today.
I've seen you before,
ain't I?
I don't think so.
You...
been to my house...
...or someone s'looks s'lots
like you, anyways.
How are you feeling today,
Carrie Anne?
Mm...
...different.
It's like...
a long dream...
...and so dark.
A world of dark.
Like a nowhere
'tween here and there.
What's that called?
Doin' the limbo?
And before...
the long dream,
do you remember anything?
Do you remember coming here?
Do you remember your parents?
They didn't a'know what to
do with themselves.
I mean...
gosh, and I knew I was a
handful as it were's.
Momma always hated me,
'cause how I'd come out wrongly
when I was borned.
Bled her up too much.
Poppa was a good man.
That's the somethin' I
remember good.
That's why he done it.
You had a visitor yesterday.
Can you describe him for me?
Don't ever wanna forget 'im.
I was jus' waitin' on him to
come and get me.
To come and tells me
somethin's to do for 'im.
Or even better,
to do somethin' for the Man
Down The Stairs,
and, boy, I just wanna do
whatsever-so he says me to do.
Like, if'n he told me to take a
jumpy out a window,
I'd surely do.
Just happy as peaches
to watch the ground as it
come up to meet me.
Or if'n he told me
to kill you right-right here in this
room with my bare hand,
I'd surely do.
Just happy as peaches
to watch your heavy
heart go pop-pop,
and your eyeses to go all to blood.
Do you remember having a doll?
A special doll that
looked just like you?
Nope.
And you don't remember neither,
you dirtsy, flirtsy ol' angel bitch.
A'ight, a'ight,
so he murders a family in '75,
but he probably isn't
even in the house
when they're killed.
Then comes back almost
20 years later
to visit the only survivor,
signs in as the agent chasing him,
and then leaves his only
surviving victim
feeling much, much better
than before he got there.
Mm.
She came out of her catatonia the
same day we found the doll.
Yeah, that couldn't be anything
but a coincidence.
Look, we opened the ball in
the doll's head,
and there's nothing inside.
Maybe we're missing something.
Something that...
I don't know, makes it work.
In some cultures, dolls
are used in magic,
to control people.
So, he kills them with a doll
from somewhere else
by what, remote control?
Longlegs is just a man, Harker,
not a witch doctor.
Sit down.
How does Longlegs know your name,
Harker?
I don't know, sir.
You know, last week,
this investigation is ice-cold.
Then you come on to it,
and all of a sudden, it's
flowing like...
I don't know, hot lava.
What aren't you telling me?
I revisited your file.
When was the last time you
talked to your mother?
Sorry, sir,
but what does that have to
do with the case?
She called in a police report,
January 13, 1974.
That's one day before
your 9th birthday.
That makes your birthday
the 14th.
She did?
She did.
Gave a description of a trespasser.
Tall and pale.
Harker...
look at me.
Do you remember someone
at your house
that might have looked that way?
I don't know, sir.
You go see your mother,
and tell me what she says
about the person who
came to your house
when you were a kid, understood?
Yes, sir.
Hi, Mom.
Mm.
Will you tell me the honest truth
about something?
I'll try.
Do you still say your prayers?
No, Mom.
I never said my prayers, never once.
They scared me.
Ah...
What's so funny?
You're right.
All our prayers don't help us.
Prayers don't do a goddamn thing.
Make you something to eat.
Jesus Christ, Mom.
Good news.
I got Deborah to cover my
shift tomorrow,
and it's somebody's birthday.
Lee?
I can't believe it's gonna be your
birthday again so soon.
What a day that was.
I bled...
bled... bled...
bled...
bled--
Mom.
You remember my 9th birthday?
No, I don't think so.
I don't remember anything.
Do you?
What happened that day?
No.
What do you mean, "no"?
"No" is just the way it sounds,
baby girl.
But you called the police,
about a trespasser.
No one ever came to visit us.
Not any family.
No strangers.
No big, bad wolves.
No anybody.
But these are things a little
girl shouldn't know.
I'm not a child anymore, Mom.
You're not a child
because you were allowed to grow up.
Allowed?
This is a cruel world.
Especially for the little things.
Not all of them are allowed to live.
What are you talking about?
I might have forgotten
everything I possibly could,
for both of our sakes,
but I never threw anything away.
All of your things...
...it's all in your room.
Cheese and crackers!
Hey!
Excuse me.
Who are you,
and why are you talking to my kid?
Let me in now! ♪
♪And it can be nice ♪
♪ Make me go now ♪
♪And I'll have to come back ♪
♪ Not once ♪
♪ Not twice ♪
♪ But as many times as I like! ♪
Harker.
Did you go see your mother?
What's this?
It's him.
It's him how?
I found it in a box of
photos at my house.
You really don't remember this guy?
Okay.
We're gonna need to bring her in,
see what else she remembers.
We will,
but for now, we have this.
You sure you wanna start a
manhunt with this?
I'm sure.
Sir!
I'm gonna need you to get down on
the fucking ground.
State your name
for the camera.
Dale Ferdinand Kobble.
Ever call
yourself -Longlegs-?
When do I see Lee?
Lee who?
Harker...
the herald angels sing.
How do you know Lee Harker?
A friend of a
friend of a friend...
...and this friend wants me to say,
Happy Birthday,
Lee Harker...-
...and he wants you all to know...
that he'll be there...
...and you'll be there, and
you'll be there...
...and you'll be there.
Happy Birthday ♪
♪ To you♪
♪ Happy Birthday to you♪
♪ Happy Birthday, Lee Harker ♪
♪ Hap--♪
It goes on like that for a while.
For how long?
24 minutes.
A'ight, everyone out of here.
Browning, Harker, you stay.
Go. You guys go.
His luggage was stuffed
with notebooks
filled with handwriting.
Handwriting that matches the
letters found at the scene,
and, suffice to say, it's
all heavily Satanic.
Agent Harker,
while the Bureau does appreciate
your contribution here,
it also puts us in an odd position.
So far, there's no physical evidence
that Kobble has ever killed anyone.
I mean, he worships the Devil,
that's for sure,
but in the United States of America,
he's allowed to do that.
I'm more concerned about the fact
that he knows who you are,
Agent Harker.
But...
he can't do anything else about that
now that we have him.
"And I stood upon the
sand of the sea,
and I saw a Beast rise up
out of the sea,
with seven heads and ten horns.
And on his horns, he
wore ten crowns,
and on each head was written the
blasphemous name."
Book of Revelations, isn't it?
Revelation.
There's no "S". It's singular.
Longlegs isn't alone.
He has to have someone helping him.
Maybe multiple, but it...
it has to be someone
that the families felt comfortable
letting into their house.
Someone they know, or
have met before.
Maybe a child, or...
someone that could pass as a child.
A'ight, Harker, come on.
We got the guy who
wrote the letters,
and if we do this right,
he'll spend the rest of
his life in jail.
But it's not over.
The triangle isn't complete,
we're still missing the 13th.
The 13th is today,
Agent Harker.
What are we supposed to
do about that?
We can expect his accomplice
to kill at least one more family...
...and Kobble's the only one who
knows who that is.
Kobble...
where is he now?
He's downstairs.
Right under your feet.
I'm a friend of a friend.
What friend?
My friend.
That lives downstairs.
Downstairs?
Downstairs from where?
Everywheres.
You can even call him "Mr.
Downstairs".
Oh...
there she is!
The Almost Birthday Girl.
Oh...
It's funny.
The day you decided to go
into law enforcement,
you were...
20.
We had such a big laugh about it.
Although, it was only me who
laughed, not she.
Who is the "she" that
you're talking about?
The seventh "she".
To be given the same choice that
they've all been given.
Crimson or clover.
Accept the gift, and destroy it,
and destroy yourself,
and yourselves,
or keep it,
and bow down.
Bow all the way down,
and get right down
to the dirty, dirty work.
Work that gets dirty as it cleans.
Like a mop.
Like a ra...ag.
But...
you don't work alone, do you?
Someone's been helping you.
An accomplice.
Knock-knock, on the farmhouse door.
A nice lady with a Bible and a,
"Congratulations!
You have been selected.
You may now collect your gift
from the church."
It says it right here,
right here on the orders.
On the orders from the
man downstairs.
The Camera family farmhouse will be
so bright and white,
you can't miss it!
Are you referring to
Carrie Anne Camera?
What did you say to her at the
mental institution?
Oh, but, Lee,
your house was even whiter
when I came to visit.
January 13th, 1974, right?
House Number Eight was so white.
Whiter than a fish's throat.
Whiter than tits.
I knew then
that the work we were doing
was immaculate.
But your work's over.
It's done,
and you're gonna be in here for
the rest of your life.
Yes.
I am done...
...but I won't only be in here.
I'll be a little bit of everywhere.
Waiting...
in the wings.
In the father's wings.
Who's been helping you?
Well...
I'll let you get started now.
Who is the man downstairs?
Why don't you ask your mommy?
My mother doesn't know anything.
Hail Satan.
Stop!
That's it,
Harker.
That's more than enough.
We had the guy,
and now we got nothin'.
We let all those families die,
and nothin' about any of that
is better, or okay,
but it's done!
Oh, and as for the 13th--
While you were in there,
Carrie Anne Camera jumped off the
roof at Water Rock.
Yeah.
He must have told her to do
that when he saw her.
Just like he somehow told
all the others
to do what he wanted,
but he did it alone, with
no accomplices!
No black magic, no voodoo,
no nothing!
You didn't have to come with me.
I wasn't gonna let you drive after
what you saw today.
How do you wanna do this?
I should go in alone.
I'll tell her
we need to bring her in
for questioning.
That we think she could help us
identify the accomplice.
All right.
I'll stay right here.
Mom?
Mom!
Put the gun down!
What is that thing?
You caught him.
Now he's free.
You mean Kobble?
But...
But Kobble's de-- he's gone.
Kobble's dead.
It's okay, Mom.
It's...
It's okay.
it's done now.
And you're free, too, baby girl.
Once upon a time,
there was a girl named Lee.
She lived in a little house
with her mother...
and no one ever came to visit them.
No family.
No big, bad wolves.
No anyone.
One day, a man did come...
Cuckoo!
...a doll maker.
Just dropping off an
early birthday gift,
a gift from the church.
You've won!
The doll maker
started his work...
...his terrible magic.
The work of the Devil...
...with a little bit of him...
in everyone.
The doll made the little
girl forget...
and told her where to look...
and whatnot to see.
The Devil wanted the little
girl for his own,
but her mother could never
let that happen.
You could've
made nice with me,
- but you didn't... -
...and now that has led
to all of this.
So her mother begged
for the little girl's
life to be spared.
In exchange, she would
have to help him.
She had once been a nurse.
Now her work would be...
murdering families...
...and so it went like this...
...knock-knock-knock,
on the farmhouse door.
A nice lady with a Bible...
and a -Congratulations,
you've won!
A gift from the church.-
All her mother had to do...
was get it inside...
...and from his hiding place
within the dolls,
the Devil did the rest.
All her mother had to do...
was watch...
...and make sure it happened the
way he wanted it to.
That was the deal that she made.
You're late...
for Miss Ruby's birthday party.
Hey, Harker, you made it!
Hi there, Harker.
It's really nice that you came.
Is everything okay?
Of course, everything's great.
In fact, you're here just in time,
because Miss Ruby just started
opening her presents.
Come, sit. Sit.
No, Carter, that's my mom.
She's the accomplice.
She's Kobble's accomplice--
Sit down!
Oh, I'm so sorry, I've
forgotten your name.
I'm a terrible, terrible,
terrible hostess.
Oh, don't mind me.
I'm just a friend
of a friend.
No...
Carter, you have to listen to me.
Honey, maybe now would
be a good time
to bring out the cake.
The cakes.
Yeah,
I'll find something to cut
up the cakes with.
Uh...
What did you say, honey?
I just said, do you have to...?
Do I have to-- Do I have to
cut up the cakes?
Yeah, I gotta cut the cakes.
It was your stupid
fucking suggestion
in the first place,
so I have to cut the cakes.
The woman is
already dead...
and the little girl will be next.
Anna...
would you like to join me in
the kitchen, honey?
I'm so sorry, I'll be right back.
No, I'll be right back.
You'll still be in the kitchen.
All three of
them have to die.
Mom, why are you doing this?
If they don't die,
then we will burn...
...and twist,
and burn, and twist,
in hell...
forever...
and ever.
I'm doing this for you...
...just like I've always done.
So that the little girl named Lee
would be allowed to grow up...
...and that makes it right...
...and so I'll do it again...
and again...
...and again...
...And I'll do it
until I stand upon the
sand of the sea,
and I see a beast rise up
out of the sea.
Hail Satan.
Carter, stop!
Move
away from the girl!
Mom, please...
Don't call me that!
Hey...
Hey, come on.
Come on.
♪ Happy
Birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy Birthday to you♪
Ruby, let's go.
♪ Happy Birthday, Lee Harker ♪
♪ Happy Birthday to... ♪
♪ ...You♪
Hail, Satan.
♪ Well, you're dirty and sweet ♪
♪ Clad in black, don't look
back and I love you ♪
♪You're dirty and sweet oh, yeah ♪
♪Well, you're slim and
you're weak ♪
♪You've got the teeth of
the hydra upon you ♪
♪You're dirty, sweet and
you're my girl ♪
♪ Get it on, bang a gong get it on ♪
♪ Get it on...
♪ Bang a gong, get it on ♪
♪ Well, you're built like a car♪
♪You've got a hubcap
diamond-star halo ♪
♪ You're built like a car, oh,
yeah ♪
♪ Well, you're an untamed youth ♪
♪ That's the truth ♪
♪With your cloak full of eagles ♪
♪You're dirty, sweet and
you're my girl ♪
♪ Get it on, bang a gong get it on ♪
♪ Get it on... ♪
♪ Bang a gong, get it on... ♪
♪ Well, you're windy and wild ♪
♪You've got the blues
in your shoes ♪
♪And your stockings ♪
♪ You're windy and wild Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Well, you're built like a car♪
♪You've got a hubcap
diamond-star halo ♪
♪You're dirty, sweet and
you're my girl ♪
♪ Get it on, bang a gong get it on ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Well, you're dirty and sweet ♪
♪ Clad in black Don't look back ♪
♪And I love you ♪
♪You're dirty and sweet Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Well, you dance when you walk ♪
So let's dance Take a chance ♪
♪ Understand me ♪
♪You're dirty, sweet and
you're my girl ♪
♪ Get it on, bang a gong get it on ♪
♪ Get it on... ♪