first love makes you feel alive
sweet like honey it makes you thrive
first love lights the fire in your heart
and sends you spinning around
spinning around
bound to you I am free
you clear up all my misery
first love makes you feel alive
sweet like honey it makes you thrive
first love lights the fire in your heart
and sends you spinning around
first love makes you feel alive
sweet like honey it makes you thrive
first love lights the fire in your heart
it sends you spinning
sends you spinning around
Thank you.
I am a man, that's all I know.
Did I exist as a real person?
- Yes. Right.
Do I smell bad?
You really reek.
I won't say what you reek of,
but you don't smell nice.
It's very noticeable. Okay.
- Give me a tip, please.
You smoke in your office,
which is forbidden.
I am Mrs Courtois.
She smokes everywhere.
Well.
How are things here?
- Hi, dad.
Is this my successor?
first love
makes you feel alive
sweet like honey...
- it makes you thrive
What did you think?
- It was great fun, really nice.
Did you sell?
- Yes, loads. Large has sold out.
Wonderful. Mum told me.
She already put in a new order.
They will be delivered on Monday.
- Really? You are incredible.
I'm going to sleep, sweethearts.
Why don't you do the same.
Good night.
- Us as well?
Have a good sleep, Valerie.
Good night, buddy.
Be good.
I better leave the door open.
Dad.
Night-night.
...the computer...
- Good morning, buddy.
It's Saturday morning.
I'm having breakfast with my family.
Is it okay to have a call tomorrow?
Thank you. Bye.
When you pass by grandad's later,
give him these pancakes.
Look, we already
made it to the papers. You guys too.
An exclusive: Luk Montero scores a hit
with First Love.
Here's Yvette.
- That's us. So cool. Here I am.
Can you pick up some more papers?
Take another ten or so.
Shall I tear it out for you?
- That would be great.
So you can show your mum.
Read it out loud.
We were kept waiting,
but finally we have a new superstar.
Luk Montero will be
this summer's sensation.
He wrote a new hit, a really catchy tune.
First Love makes you feel like you did,
falling in love for the first time.
A full page. Not everyone gets that.
My mum's here.
- Already?
Give her my regards.
- Will do. Thank you for the pancakes.
See you tomorrow.
400 euros for appearing on TV
with your summer hit.
3000 euros for wearing a costume
in The Masked Singer. Can you believe it?
Good morning.
-Hi, playboy. Where were you yesterday?
Did you eat something?
-I went to the movies with Line.
We went to the chip shop after.
You should bring her next time.
It was really great.
No, seriously. Valerie agreed.
- It was really fun.
It was great.
Martin said they moved from Brussels.
A single man.
They're pretty young kids.
He looks like he's your age.
You're making a mess.
Hi, Elias.
- Hi, Tom.
Do you know where grandad is?
- In the stables, I think.
Hi, kid.
- And?
Still no luck?
I brought pancakes.
Can I?
- Go ahead.
Ready?
- Yes, fire up.
It's your turn. Take over.
Grandad?
Yes.
Do you know
where grandma's grease pencils are?
No, kid, I don't go in there anymore.
Found them.
Good morning, sweetie.
You should get ready. Come on.
When does it start?
- What?
A beard.
- Your beard?
Some get it sooner than others.
I got it pretty early on.
So did your brother.
You'll have your mother's genes.
Do you want to try?
Come here.
Usually it starts here.
The moustache.
We saw dolphins and everything.
Are you allowed to steer it yourself?
- Yes.
Has anyone heard
about courtly love before?
No? Let's analyse the expression.
We hear 'courtly' and 'love'.
Has anyone ever fallen in love?
I heard Mieke's in love with Harry Styles?
Who's been saying that?
That's so not funny.
But it's a great example
of modern courtly love.
Because the lover is out of reach. Yes.
Hello, Mrs Courtois.
This is your new pupil, Alexander.
Alexander, very happy you're here.
Sweeties, this is your new classmate.
It's his first day,
so please look after him.
Alexander, you can sit there at the back.
Right, thank you ma'am.
The new guy is all by himself.
You know what,
I'll just go and get him.
Incredible. She always connects
with the newbies.
She's a real people person.
Look, they're coming this way.
Everyone, this is Alexander.
He's in our group now.
Alexander: Valerie, Elias,
Matteo and Lukas.
Hello.
- Hi.
We've already met.
- He lives next door. Right across.
Why didn't you say so before?
- Just didn't.
Where did you live before?
- In Brussels.
Do you speak French then?
- Yes.
Say something French.
- Bonjour.
You're funny.
So why did you specifically move up here?
'Specifically'.
- It's a normal word.
My dad found a new job here.
- Right.
And your mum?
- She passed away a couple of years ago.
That's terrible.
- Isn't Brussels super dangerous?
There's fights and explosions and stuff.
Isn't it like that?
He may look tough,
but he's scared of everything.
He's even too scared to bomb dive
into Valerie's swimming pool.
What are you on about?
Are you okay?
- I've got cramps.
I'll run along with you.
That's that new guy.
- Go on, then.
Sure?
- Yes, go.
Breathe through your stomach. It helps.
Well done, Valerie.
Come on, Alexander.
Yes, Elias, well done.
Come on, Lukas.
One more.
Come on, Lukas. Well done.
Come on, Lukas.
Hey.
Hi.
Isn't it beautiful here?
Is it so much different then?
It is.
There's all these fields,
in Brussels not so much.
Are those strawberries?
Strawberries and cherries.
Do you want some?
Yes.
- Alright then. Let's go.
Hi.
- Hello.
What would you like?
- A box of cherries.
What did you think of today?
- Alright.
It was a bit scary though.
A new school and without my friends.
You can still see them at weekends.
Yes, suppose.
Did your mum pass away a long time ago?
Yes, when I was nine.
It's okay. Now it's just my dad,
my sister and me.
I do find it hard to let new people in.
But Zoe is really nice.
Yes, Zoe's a nice girl.
Have you noticed Matteo and Zoe
are madly in love?
Have you ever been in love?
I have.
What does it feel like?
- It's the best feeling ever.
You haven't?
I don't think so.
Aren't you with Valerie?
I am.
So you know what it feels like.
Dunno.
Don't you think it's weird
you don't know?
Are you with someone?
No. I was last year.
What was her name?
It wasn't a girl but a boy.
His name's Arthur.
I really should go. Will you come with?
I'm off to see my grandad.
- Okay, see you tomorrow.
See you then.
Hello, sweetie, there you are.
This is our young one.
- These are the new neighbours.
Hello.
- Hi.
This is Marc.
- Alexander. He's in my class.
Check it out.
You should come along.
Maxime, could you pass me your phone?
I want to play them my song.
Wait.
- It will only take a minute.
What about yours?
- It's charging.
one lazy Sunday
you popped right back into my head
once upon a time
you were all I wanted in life
Come on, dad.
- Just wait until...
Can you bring out the champagne?
- Get it yourself.
Right, I'll bring these around again.
For this snack I made a pesto
from radish leaves.
From our garden.
- Great.
Thank you.
Here we are.
It's nicely chilled.
Sorry, sweeties. Everyone okay?
Here we are, friends.
To the new single.
And to our new neighbours.
- Of course.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
I'm going upstairs.
I'm going up with her.
- Okay.
Ella, get your pyjamas on.
Is this your mum?
- It is.
You look like her.
Do you play the piano?
I don't play any instrument.
Come here.
Right, you put these two fingers
on the black notes.
There, like this.
Like this?
- Yes.
Then, you take the three at the back.
These ones?
- That's it and then like this.
VALERIE: Have you learnt
French vocabulary?
Almost
VALERIE: I will let you copy
Weren't you going to sit
next to Alexander?
VALERIE: Hahaha.
VALERIE: I prefer to sit next to you
What are you guys up to?
What is this?
- Nothing.
DICK
Where did you find it?
- It was stuck to the vending machine.
Shouldn't we tell Mr Van Daele?
What's wrong?
Elias, wait.
DICK
- Hi.
Did your dad also get up
with a headache?
He was on the sunbed.
He reckons it's the best cure
for a hangover.
At my previous school I was also
being bullied by two boys.
I took up judo for a year.
Show me who they are
and I'll beat them up.
They're seniors. You couldn't beat them.
Have you taken a good look at me?
I've never been on a farm before.
Never?
- NO.
Can I show you something?
Come on.
It's here.
Do you want to hold one?
- Can I?
Sure. Go on.
Easy now.
It's stuck, look.
Take him.
Grandad, this is Alexander,
our new neighbour.
Hello, sir.
- Sir isn't home, kid.
Call me Fred.
Do they have a name?
We don't really name them.
- We could for once.
Well, I guess so.
I think this one looks a bit like you.
Hey there.
Hey.
Come on.
Are you brave enough to get on top?
See you tomorrow.
Everything okay?
Are you coming?
- Where to?
I have to go to the radio station.
I have to study.
Listen, buddy.
I wanted to have a one-to-one with you.
Now that your brother is...
He's going steady.
And you're with Valerie.
You are still too young really,
but mum wanted me to...
That we had a talk, so...
If you are doing things.
It's not really my business, but...
Just be careful.
Dad, really, seriously.
Turn on the radio later, right?
No, really, I saw it on television.
A woman was talking about it.
This one means...
that you are...adventurous.
And this one..
So here you can see.
No, seriously.
about a jaguar in the woods..
- No, not about a jaguar.
You can make a wish.
Hey, gaylords, get home safe.
What are you doing?
- Come on.
Little bastard.
You'll get a good kicking one day.
- Let them try.
Come on.
What is this?
- You'll see.
I used to come and draw here
with my gran.
Does anyone still live here?
- No.
Cool, right?
What are you doing?
- It's unlocked.
I don't think that's allowed.
- Just a quick look.
And if someone turns up?
What are you doing?
Come on.
Alex, let's not go too far. Come on.
It's really old.
Duel?
And now?
- En garde.
Go on, hit me.
Ready?
- Yes, go for it.
Hello there.
How do we get in here?
Let's go.
Come on then.
They will see us. They will.
Look, you two go up. We'll go there.
- Okay, let's go.
Come on, quick.
Nice pants.
Elias.
Ready?
Get in. It's really nice.
Come on.
Are you cold?
A little.
Wait, I know a trick.
Does it help?
- Yes.
Elias, where have you been?
Hi, aren't you hungry?
- NO.
It's beautiful.
Everything okay?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Why are you being so quiet, then?
I'm talking, aren't I?
You're talking, sweetie, yes,
but you're not telling me anything.
Eat something. You shouldn't
sleep on an empty stomach.
Will do.
That's a cool car. But in yellow?
Do you want one like that?
Alexander.
- He came too? Cool.
He always looks so cool, right?
How are you?
- Fine.
Guys.
- Hi, there.
All okay?
- Hello.
Are you okay?
- Now that everyone's here.
I have a great idea.
It's my birthday in a couple of weeks.
I want to throw an amazing party.
The theme is famous duos.
- Why didn't you wait for me?
That's so cool.
- Who could we go as?
I don't know: Salt-N-Pepa?
They're a famous duo, aren't they?
- That's not a winner.
You have to try harder.
At the end, the best duo will get a prize.
Cool.
- I'm really curious.
Do you want to have a swim?
- Okay.
I want to get the prize.
I will get it.
- A bad-ass party.
Oh my God, he's so good-looking.
Yes, he is.
- What are you saying?
Why can't I say that?
- I don't know.
You have to admit he's good-looking.
That would be weird for me to admit.
- Why?
Well, I'm not into boys.
You can be so stupid.
That's not what we're saying.
Let's go for a swim.
Is that beer?
- I stole it from my gran's garage.
I've never had a beer, or any alcohol.
Careful my mum doesn't see it.
- No, she won't.
There you go.
Let's give this a try.
Do you want one?
- No, I have to go.
You're already leaving?
Aren't you sleeping over?
No, my dad's here already.
Alexander, it was really great you came.
- Bye.
Bye.
- Byee.
I'm scared.
That's quite a lot.
- Just don't start singing.
Here, I found it.
I'll be an angel and you a knight.
It's from a movie I just saw.
What do you think?
Cool.
Today was great fun, wasn't it?
Night-night.
Alex.
Wait, I'll come down.
What are you doing here?
Elias.
Alex?
What are you doing here?
- Go away.
Weren't you sleeping at Valerie's?
Have you been drinking?
Seriously, have you?
Really. Seriously.
- Go away.
Stop it.
Stop.
Dude, gross.
What's up with you?
- Hand me that towel.
Are you okay, Elias?
Elias.
Sorry.
- That's okay. Take a seat.
We're on page 340, on the dreams.
The task about dreams.
Where did you go?
I didn't feel well.
He's getting aggressive.
Try twisting it.
Your turn.
Wait, try again.
- From here.
And we're off.
I just want to be with you.
What are you doing?
What's up with you?
What happened?
Elias.
Boo.
If you fancy it,
I'm going to Brussels tomorrow.
You could come along.
Hey.
- Stop it.
Yes?
- Elias, where are you?
I'm about to go on stage.
You and Valerie were meant to be here.
first love lights the fire in your heart
and sends you spinning around
sends you spinning around
Thank you.
Dearest people, apologies.
Today, you can all witness
this amazing moment about to take place.
Dear Luk, First Love...
became a golden record.
- No way.
Incredible. You knew already?
Man.
- Congratulations.
Nathalie, did you know about this?
Come up here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my greatest support, Nathalie.
Right, well...
Patrick.
VALERIE: Don't come near me again.
I would like to offer you all a gift.
Patrick, could we play the new single?
Would you like that?
Let's do it then. Let's go.
This is Valerie's voicemail.
Leave a message and I'll call back.
Alex?
I'll come along tomorrow.
So this is it?
Yup.
Let's go.
Hi. Would you like a picture?
Thank you. Great.
Right, let's go. Smile. Very good.
You keep it.
Really?
- Sure.
Thanks.
Let's go.
Uncle Tony.
Aunt Pia?
Look who's here.
Darling, what a lovely surprise.
So nice to see you.
-Darling, Alex.
I brought someone along.
This is Elias, my boyfriend.
Well, hello, you're handsome.
- You betcha. Hi, Elias.
What would you like to drink?
A bottle of champers?
Two Cokes would be great.
- Two Cokes coming up.
What does that mean 'petit copain'?
- Well.
How is it going?
- It's okay. Everyone's very nice.
How's your dad and your sister?
- They're fine.
miss you guys loads.
- It's really great you're here.
Thank you.
- Cheers.
We're so happy.
But it's Alex, my darling.
Come and give us a kiss.
Come here, it's been so long.
I'm so happy to see you.
Hello, are you well?
- Yes. Are you going to rehearse?
Yes, if you don't mind.
- Not at all.
Can we watch?
- Of course.
But not without you.
- NO.
You'll be playing piano with Tony.
You don't get a say. Come here, Tony.
Take a seat. Enjoy Diva's show.
- You know how we do it in Brussels.
In Bruxelles.
- I'm happy to see you.
Yes, it makes us happy. You've grown.
Are you ready?
- Yes, I am.
I see the people who've let go
as if their life's a big zero
I'm only fifteen and I know
whoa whoa... cherish life
you must believe me, I have too
a flash of hope, some white nights too
but after all, the sun for me
will always shine
crazy, crazy for life
from the very start
it's deep in my heart
crazy, crazy for life
from the very start
it's deep in my heart
crazy, crazy for life
I don't care if it rains on me
all of the time
my life
yes, I hold on to you
Bravo, Diva, bravo. That was great.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Being your 'petit copain'.
Do you want to try at the wheel?
Am I allowed?
- Of course.
Okay then.
The boys.
Fancied showing up?
Take your seats. We've started.
Elias, this is your second time. Third
time you're in the principal's office.
Understood?
We're at page 384, right?
Okay, where was I? The stories.
Last time you chose a story.
Last time we looked at
where you can find these stories.
In the library, newspapers or some
magazines, specialised in teen fiction.
Someone mentioned the internet, but
there texts might be of lesser quality.
It's better to use the other sources.
Good work.
Yes, great.
Now, score.
- Finish it.
Did you see me?
We won thanks to you.
The training next week will be great.
Yes, but careful you can keep up
your schoolwork.
That should be fine.
- Do you have time to study?
We start at 9am till 4pm and even
afterwards we continue footballing.
Do you actually like me or not?
I do.
I just don't want anyone to comment.
- What does it matter?
Say something.
I don't know any boys
who are in love with another boy.
I don't want you to feel ashamed of me.
What do you want me to do?
Valerie doesn't look at me anymore.
Why are you suddenly acting like this?
Elias, I've been dealt
enough shit already.
Sweetie, there you are.
I'm almost done.
- I'm not going along.
Why not?
No reason.
- But you were looking forward to it.
What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Are you and Valerie fighting?
- NO.
Nathalie, hon,
which one should I wear tonight?
Not now.
Can you leave us alone a minute?
Can you take the laundry up?
Thank you.
Hey, sweetie.
Something's up with you lately.
I don't like to see you sad like this.
Go on, try it on at least.
I've been working on it all day.
It looks beautiful.
Go on. You'll have a nice time.
All your friends are going.
Okay?
You should call the school tomorrow.
- Maybe I should.
Who does that?
Look, 'Luk Montero sucks'.
Are they making fun of me?
- Luk, it's not always about you.
They wrote 'DICK' on my head.
- They're bullies.
Did he mention it to you?
- No, he didn't.
Nothing? He mentioned nothing?
- I told you he didn't.
What is this then?
- Luk, really.
What are you doing?
Are you being bullied at school?
Mum.
- Sweetie, we're only trying to help.
Did you do this?
- No way.
Please, Luk.
Elias.
What's going on here?
- Luk, stop it.
What do you care?
Of course I care.
You wouldn't even notice
if the house was on fire, idiot.
Elias, please.
- What did you call me?
Have you lost your mind?
Come in.
You're a knight.
Leonardo di Caprio in Romeo and Juliet.
I haven't seen it.
Me neither.
You're here with Valerie.
is time right
what do you think
is it too early for that first step
will you mind if I stay
or are we better off without
my heart seems to be taking over now
but I’ll go ahead
now you're here with me
One, two, three, four.
everything feels different now
Oh, my God.
Lukas?
- It's no biggie.
I can't do it.
- Come on, please.
It's really nothing. Just do it.
That's cool.
Right, next.
Who will be next?
Thomas?
Turn it again.
I don't mind.
- Yes.
So cute.
They really did it. So cool.
Your turn.
- Okay, next.
Where is he off to?
Elias.
Elias, wait up.
- What? Isn't it hilarious?
I'm not like him. I'm not gay.
- Stop acting like an idiot.
Alexander is also our friend.
I don't care about him, Lukas.
Wait.
Lukas.
Why didn't you just stay in Brussels?
None of this would have happened.
F*ck you, Elias.
Mum.
Hello?
Is anyone out there?
My boy.
What are you doing here?
Come on.
Come here. Come here, you.
Alex, sorry.
It will be fine. I swear.
It will be fine, Nathalie.
No worries.
Are they angry?
Of course not. No one's angry.
I just told them you'll be staying
with me a couple of days.
I wish I could just disappear.
- Right.
That would do me good as well.
How do you feel about going
to the Ardennes, just you and me?
Don't I have to go to school?
Oh, boy.
You can't go to school
with such a fever.
Impossible.
I hope we can meet up again.
My dear Magaly.
I'm so happy to see you.
It's been a long time.
Yes. Here he is, my grandson.
Finally, we meet, Elias.
You look like your grandmother, Léonie.
Do you know she adored you?
I'm not surprised. You are very cute.
Look at those eyes.
How are you?
- Me?
What can I say?
And you? How are you?
- I'm fine.
Do you fancy a drink, Elias?
No, I don't.
What do you fancy then?
I want to die.
Right.
If you need me once you're dead,
I'll be on the terrace.
When I met your grandmother,
we drove down here many weekends.
This was her favourite spot.
I haven't been here since...
Since she passed away.
Do you miss her?
- Every single minute.
Alexander told me being in love
is the best feeling ever.
Sometimes when I go to sleep...
I hope everything will be back to normal
when I wake up.
That he won't be in my head.
I try liking Valerie in the same way.
Try being in love with her.
I've hurt all the people I care about.
It's fine.
We all make mistakes.
Look here.
Léonie and Frederic.
Yes.
What you should focus on right now...
is to enjoy what you're feeling.
If your feelings for Alexander are
anything like what I felt for grandma...
That's not something you come across
twice in a lifetime.
He's very handsome.
You should be happy about those feelings.
If there's one thing that life taught me,
it's that you should always
follow your heart.
And don't get so stuck
in that head of yours.
Mum, can you pull over please?
Pull over, here?
- Yes.
Mum, I have to get to basketball.
- Maxime.
Sweetie, what's wrong?
I have to tell you something.
I am...
I'm in love
with Alexander.
I don't know how you're going to react.
Just know that I tried to change.
- Sweetie, you don't have to change.
How long have you known?
Since he moved here, I think.
Elias, look at me.
Sweetie, I love you to bits.
You know that.
All of us.
It doesn't matter
whoever you fall in love with.
Don't cry, sweetie.
It will all work out in the end.
It always does.
Sweetheart.
We're so proud of you.
We're all here to support you.
Why didn't you tell us before?
I was scared to.
We love you so much.
My beautiful boy.
Everything's fine. Really.
I'm right here.
Shall we go home?
Buddy, you're back.
How was it with grandad?
Fine.
I'm happy you're back.
Will you get ready?
- I'm not coming along tonight.
What? It's the Harvest Parade.
Everyone is going.
Dad, I want to tell you...
- I'm presenting my CD. You have to go.
Are you ill?
Do you really know me?
What are you saying?
Go on.
Get ready. We're leaving soon.
You go.
Good luck tonight.
Hi.
Hi. Where are you?
- At home. And you?
I'm at your door.
I want to kiss Lore and I need your help.
What? Wait, I'm coming.
Everything okay?
- Yes.
We were so worried about you.
So, there's a couple of steps.
First step: swing it down a bit,
like this. With both your hands.
Then clap.
Is she here already?
- She's over there.
So... Off you go then.
- Hi.
- Hello, Elias.
I'm happy to see you.
Is Alexander here?
- We were going to come together.
But he suddenly felt unwell.
Dad, can we go to the carousel?
- Yes, let's go.
See you later?
See you later.
Elias.
What the f*ck?
Come on. Get up.
I saw Alexander.
Off you go then.
so just let yourself go now
sing and dance along
Let's go, ladies and gentlemen.
we go ahead
and we look back
but here and now is all that counts
'cause happiness
is in your heart
when you'll allow It in at least
and everyone
feels alone sometimes
Elias.
Why are you sitting here?
I thought I'd seen Alexander,
but I must have imagined it.
No, you haven't. He's really here.
Really?
- Yes, he's at the bar.
What are you waiting for?
Go on then.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Where did you first kiss?
Do you remember?
- Of course I do.
I'm not just asking. Last night,
I told you, you may have heard...
Dad has a new song.
I was inspired.
A song about the first kiss.
kiss me softly on the lips
I forgot the cream.
I'll get it.
- It's on the counter, next to the fridge.
Okay.
- Thank you.
Grandad, I have something for you.
For me?
- Yes.
But today is not my birthday.
That's very sweet.
It's you with granny.
Did you draw this?
- I did.
Do you like it?
This is the most beautiful present
I've ever had.
Come here.
Hello.
Alexander.
- Have you eaten?
I have.
- There's some left.
Go on then. Get out of here.
Bye.
Shall we go?
See you later.
- Bye.
Hi, everyone.
- Hi.
Come on, let's go.
I lost my mind, you your shoes
what are you doing, dancing barefoot
now that our eyes are meeting
I can’t believe our lips touching
and when I close my eyes
I can still see your face
everywhere I go
your beauty makes me speechless
I have you, can’t do without you
door’s always open for you
any day, any time
I keep losing my cool with you
talk way too much and start stuttering
oh, shh, th, th, there I go again