-Wait, wait, wait a second.
-What? What is it?
-Hold on.
-What's wrong?
-You came out.
-Oh, okay.
-You like that?
-Yeah. Just go a little faster.
-Faster, like this?
-Yeah. Come on. Go faster.
-You wanna go on top, maybe?
-No, no, no. Just keep going.
- I'm about to--
- Come on.
Faster, Fernando.
Faster, faster.
I'm out of breath, babe.
I can't go any faster.
So, this is Fernando, my ex.
The guy I swore to myself
I'd never hook up with again.
That was
totally incredible, babe.
Mm-hm.
Wasn't it amazing?
-Yeah, it was.
-What's wrong?
Well, as I'm sure you can tell,
my sex life
leaves a lot to be desired.
But I guess you could say
that love and sex
were never
my biggest priorities.
I'm gonna take a shower.
-But believe me...
-Want some company?
That's okay.
You're gonna be late for work.
That was about to change
in ways
I never could have expected.
By the way, my name's Judith.
Judith Flores.
And a few months ago,
all I could think about
was becoming the youngest
account executive
in the history
of Muller Pharmaceuticals.
But as they say, if you wanna
make God laugh, make a plan.
Sorry.
They say the first
10 sentences in a novel
are the most important ones.
Those 10 sentences
need to entice you,
seduce you into reading
the rest of the story.
Well, Eric and I
didn't need 10 sentences.
We didn't even need 10 seconds.
Miguel. Miguelito. Good morning.
Morning, Monica.
Come in.
So, games and beers tonight?
I've got to finish
this report first.
Come on, take a break.
- Dinner, anyone?
- I'm still working
on the Q1s
for the branch office.
Send it to me when you're done.
Monica, I'm sorry
if this isn't the right time,
but I was wondering if
you'd considered that promotion
to Finance we talked about.
I've been here for three years.
You're totally right.
It's not a good time.
-So, Miguel, are you in?
-Am I in?
I would have every breakfast,
lunch and dinner with you
if you asked.
Well, we'd better
get going then.
See you tomorrow.
-Traitor.
-Sorry, I'm a sellout.
Next time I'm buying.
When your salary
is anywhere close to mine, baby.
Well, I'm gonna have
to repay you for dinner
somehow, right?
Oh, really?
-What did you have in mind?
-Do you really wanna know?
All kinds of things.
Careful, Miguel.
I'm still your boss.
Maybe in the office.
But out here, I'm in charge.
Okay, then.
Who's the boss now?
You are. You're the boss.
Damn, Monica.
-You want it?
-Yes.
-You want me to fuck you?
What?
Don't stop.
Shit.
Oh, shut up.
I see you spend all day
licking your balls,
and I don't say a single word.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
It's a nice day out there.
Hard to tell
from inside an elevator.
Yeah, that's a good point.
You okay?
Honestly, I've always
had this sort of phobia
of being stuck in an elevator.
So, if the doors
don't open pretty soon,
I'm scared I may have
some kind of meltdown.
Meltdown?
Uh, yeah,
like a little freak out.
You start frothing at the mouth,
and then your head starts
spinning around violently
like that little girl
from the Exorcist.
And you get a cute little rash
on your neck like I have now.
No, don't do that.
You'll make it worse.
Um...
Want a piece of gum?
I'm definitely gonna have one.
They're strawberry flavored.
Judith Flores.
Well, it's nice to meet you,
Ms. Flores.
And you. What's your name, then?
Eric.
You didn't tell me
you were coming in today.
I didn't think I had to.
Oh. Have you met
Judith Flores yet?
She wrote the report
I sent you last night.
Mr. Zimmerman,
my deepest condolences
about the news
of your father's passing.
I'd really appreciate it if,
from this point onwards,
we don't mention my father
in this office anymore.
Eric, come on.
We have a lot to discuss.
-Mm.
-Shall we step into my office?
After you.
Have you seen the new boss?
He's sculpted like a Greek God.
I don't know.
To me, he's just another
Calvin Klein model with a nice
face and zero personality.
That's all I need.
Greek gods
wear underwear too, you know.
I care more
about what's in his underwear.
This has to be rewritten.
He didn't like
your restructuring proposal.
He wants to maximize profits
by any means necessary.
Typical rich-kid-who's-just-
inherited-Daddy's-company
bullshit.
He wants results,
but has no concrete ideas
on how to get them.
And who ends up
getting screwed in all this?
We do. Because he's untouchable.
Judith, are you listening to me?
Yeah.
-Untouchable.
-Sweetie.
I don't know for sure,
but it seems like
he wants to get rid of
the branch offices.
But hasn't he seen the numbers?
I doubt he's even
looked at them.
Anyway, it has to be redone
with the new targets.
The offices that
can't get it done are toast.
-But by when?
-By today, Judith. Asap.
New bosses are impatient.
Get used to it.
And please close the door
on your way out.
-Huh?
-Close the door, Judith.
- I just love an empty office at night.
-  -Shh.
- What if Judith's still here?
- Even better.
She might enjoy herself
and forget about work.
Look, she left the report
and went home.
That means we're all alone.
So, tell me.
How are you gonna fuck me today?
The real question is, how are
you gonna fuck me, Monica?
You like to watch?
Mr. Zimmerman, I thought you...
I thought you left. I...
I left the new numbers report
in your office.
Call me Eric.
You're my boss.
So, if you don't mind,
I'm gonna call you
Mr. Zimmerman, Mr. Zimmerman.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Wait. Stay here with me.
Relationships between
company employees
are strictly forbidden.
Being strictly forbidden
is what makes it so hot.
No?
We shouldn't. This isn't right.
What's so wrong about it?
The whole thing.
Them here, us watching them.
-It's all a really bad idea.
-Yet you seem to be enjoying it.
I'll pick you up at 8
for dinner tomorrow night.
-What? No.
-Why not?
Because you're my boss,
and I don't date my bosses.
You'll date this one.
I could end your whole career,
Mr. Zimmerman.
That's what makes it so hot.
Yeah. Faster. Faster.
Get off.
- What?
- That's enough.
Curro.
What do you say the two of us
have a little chat, huh?
What's up with you?
Look, I bought you a toy.
You like it? No?
You don't give a shit, do you?
Go on.
I gotta say, I'm underwhelmed.
I mean, it's cute and all,
but maybe a little informal
for dinner.
Mr. Zimmerman,
did you go snooping
in the company files
to get my address?
I thought we agreed to go out.
I guess listening isn't exactly
one of your best qualities.
Well, then, let me apologize.
My mistake.
I'll see you Monday.
Mr. Zimmerman.
Meet me downstairs in one hour.
Nice ride.
I see they do things properly
in Bavaria.
I was born in Berlin.
You certainly seem to know your
way around cars, Ms. Flores.
I'm impressed.
I think you'll see I'm full
of surprises, Mr. Zimmerman.
To Moroccio, Thomas.
Wow.
You know, I always dreamed
of driving one of these.
Well, it's a very powerful car.
Do you think
you could handle it, Ms. Flores?
Trust me, I know exactly
what I'm doing, Mr. Zimmerman.
And since we're going out,
call me Judith or Jude.
I like Jude.
It's hot in here, no?
Mr. Zimmerman. Welcome back.
It's always a pleasure
to see you.
Follow me, please.
Jude.
Sea urchin can be
a little challenging at first.
The first bite
might be unpleasant,
but sometimes
we need to push through
and put our prejudices aside
so we can learn to savor it.
The most important thing
is to take your time.
Do you like it?
No.
I've never been a fan.
But it does taste like the sea.
Reminds me of home.
All right, well, in my defense,
I kind of got trapped
there, okay?
It wasn't like I wanted
to be there or anything.
You don't need
to justify yourself, Jude.
Not to me.
Mmm.
Aren't you having your dessert?
If you don't mind, I thought
I'd try some of yours.
Yeah.
Take what you want.
Jude.
How far are you willing
to go with me?
Huh?
As far as we're gonna get, no?
Eric. What is this?
A game, Jude.
We can just stay here
and watch.
Or join in.
No, no.
No.
-Jude.
-This was a big mistake.
I'm leaving right now.
-Jude.
-Goodbye.
Shit.
Good morning, Curro.
Wanna play with Mr. Mousington?
Yes?
Oh, old guy. Come on.
Don't you wanna play
a little bit, huh?
Hear that?
I think that means
your special food is here.
Someone order a Porsche?
Don't tell me
we arranged another date
I didn't know about.
I just wanted to see you.
You know you could have
just replied to my texts, right?
Hey.
And who's this little one?
Curro.
How are you doing today?
Little sick, huh?
He's getting older. Yeah.
Can I come in?
Can I get you
something to drink too?
I want you to go get dressed.
For what?
Because I wanna
spend the day together.
-I've got other plans.
-I'll come with you.
Yeah. Uh, listen, Eric,
I don't know about this.
You keep showing up uninvited.
And after last night's
little show--
Last night was amazing.
Dinner was perfect.
Sure, it started out great.
I was having a nice time.
But then you pulled that shit
with the curtain.
Listen, Jude.
I understand if maybe
games aren't your thing.
In that case, I'm probably
not what you're looking for.
It's too bad.
Because I like you a lot.
And how do you know
what I'm looking for?
I come to the shelter
every single week
and walk as many dogs as I can.
Do you like animals?
Yeah, they're okay.
-Do you have any pets?
-No.
-No cat, dog, parrot?
-No. No.
A turtle, a canary?
-A pig?
-No. No.
Most animals
need time and attention.
I can't give that.
You make time
for the things that matter.
Or maybe you're just scared
of getting your suit dirty.
-Huh?
-What?
Hm, maybe?
Prove me wrong. Get down.
-That's it. Keep going.
-Mm-hm.
-Get him, boys.
-No.
You rich folk really
do live the good life, huh?
Mm. Thank you.
I was just
saying you rich people
really live the good life, huh?
Everything has a dark side.
Put this on.
Tell me about it.
The dark side. Tell me about it.
Hmm. Well, it can be a little
difficult to describe to people.
Mm, okay.
Then let's talk
about something else.
What do you wanna
talk about, Jude?
Well, how about
how your nice jacket
got all covered in dog hair,
for example.
Because it's really,
really filthy.
-It is?
-Yeah.
And...
You should probably take it off.
So, Jude, do you wanna play?
Okay.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Anything?
Yeah.
Perfect.
Jude.
Tell me what you want.
Fuck me.
Wait.
There was someone else
in the room with us?
Relax. She's my best friend.
And you enjoyed it.
Are you fucking
kidding me, Eric?
You said you wanted to play.
I wanted to play with you, Eric,
not some random stranger.
Without asking my consent.
-Turn it off. Turn it off!
-Judith.
-Fucking turn it off, I said.
-Look, I'm sorry.
-No, you're not.
You're a sick, fucking pervert.
-Turn it off.
-Judith.
Judith. Judith.
No, no, don't touch me.
-Don't touch me.
-Judith, I'm really sorry.
It was a surprise.
It's part of the game.
-If I told you--
-If you told me. Yeah.
But you didn't tell me, though.
'Cause you knew I'd say no.
There's a name
for shit like that.
Please don't do this.
You should know it's not a game.
This is what sex is for me,
Judith.
-I'm used to doing this stuff.
-You're used to always having
whatever the fuck you want
all the time.
And you know why?
Because you're just some fucking
rich kid who's never
had to work for a damn thing.
And you don't deserve
any of this shit. None of it.
You should count yourself lucky,
Mr. Zimmerman,
that I don't report you.
Got it?
Judith, can you come
here for a sec, please?
Everything okay, Monica?
Eric's looking
for someone to accompany him
to the Barcelona branch offices.
Okay. Uh, you should.
No, I have
too much work to do here.
And Eric thought that since you
wrote the report, you could go.
Of course, Ms. Flores, the offer
does come with a bonus,
which I believe
you'll find to be considerable.
As a special thank you.
Well...
Thank you for the opportunity,
Mr. Zimmerman,
but frankly, I've wasted
too much time
writing reports for you,
and I'm behind
on all my other work.
Besides, the latest data
you showed me
laid the groundwork pretty well
in terms of what you expect
from the numbers.
-Mmm.
-Ms. Flores.
Do you, by any chance,
still have the data
that we discussed last time?
Well, I'd have to go through
my files.
If you could, because I'd very
much appreciate your opinion
before finalizing
any decisions on this.
I doubt that's necessary.
I've made my opinion clear.
Anything else, Monica?
Oh, no. That'll be all, Judith.
Thank you very much.
Thanks.
Curro.
Curro, what's wrong?
What is it, Curro?
Curro.
Judith.
Please, just--
Let me say something.
What's wrong, Jude?
I'm getting snot
all over your suit.
It's been through worse.
This doesn't mean
I forgive you yet.
Mmm.
Wow. I didn't even know I had
all this stuff in my fridge.
Well, to be honest,
you only had the cookies here.
I had to call Thomas
to bring over the rest.
Try my little toast masterpiece.
Were you serious
about Barcelona?
Do you know anyone
more serious than me?
And what if I still
don't wanna play?
That's not a problem.
There are lots of women
out there I can sleep with,
but none of them can defend
the branch project
as well as you, Jude.
Listen.
I need you to understand
that this is who I am.
I'm not looking to fall in love
or find someone
to sleep next to.
I like to play
and experiment with people.
And I know we definitely
have a lot of fun together.
But it wouldn't be exclusive.
I'll have to think about it.
I don't think you should
keep Thomas waiting.
Thanks for the food.
Yes. Would you read it again,
please?
From the beginning?
Huh.
No, I don't like
that first sentence at all.
I'd want a separate room.
-Absolutely.
-And if I'm gonna play,
I wanna know
all the rules up front.
-I don't like surprises.
-No surprises at all.
I'm not kidding.
Neither am I.
So, does this mean you're coming
with me to Barcelona?
Well, right now it just means
that I need a hand
with the photocopier.
You can answer that
if you need to.
It's not important.
Maybe grab a little bite.
Yeah, well, may I remind you
that last time we ate out,
I was out of commission
for weeks.
So, I think
I'll hold off for now.
Amanda, may I present
my colleague, Ms. Flores.
-Oh, pleasure.
-Amanda is our director
of finances.
She overlooks the numbers
and targets.
All the reports you write
go through her.
And I was just saying those
numbers are no good anymore.
Unfortunately,
since Eric took over,
the Muller brand has lost
a lot of credibility
in the investors' eyes,
and our market numbers
have just plummeted.
They all assume
he's the typical nepo baby
who destroys
the entire family empire.
So, now many of them
have opted to invest
in businesses that
are slightly more conservative
in their choice of CEO.
I'm sorry, it's, um...
I just don't understand
because our numbers have
consistently stayed the same.
-Why is there suddenly-- Huh?
-Das Blendwerk.
The market
doesn't care about the numbers.
It only cares about
who's running the show.
-Let's go.
-Mm-hm.
The metrics show us
that the Q1 forecast
- will be exceeded
by double digits.
Allergic reactions,
rising temperatures.
There's also
more pollen than average,
reaching peaks of up to 800
to 1,000 grains per cubic meter.
That's even in the metro area.
That's gonna create
an uptick in demand
specifically for
over-the-counter medication.
Marketing is also working
very closely with communications
to ensure the central region
remains the main focus.
Pharmacies staffed
with multilingual personnel,
especially those
who speak three languages,
-are key to this--
-Ladies and gentlemen,
pardon my interruption,
but something's come up,
and I'm gonna need the room
for a few minutes.
-Well, sir--
-Please, if you'd all
just step out.
All right, I guess we can, um...
Wait. Not you, please,
Ms. Flores.
I'll need your assistance.
What's going on, Jude?
Hmm?
Why did you bring me here, Eric?
Why bring me if your financial
director slash lover or whatever
was just gonna take
my hard work and throw it away?
If I'd known I was gonna be
a third wheel on this trip,
I'd have saved myself the time
and trouble
and stayed in Madrid.
I could have gotten
some actual work done.
What's so funny?
Jude.
We already talked about this.
Someone might come in.
Isn't that what makes it hot?
God, you're incredible.
-Jude.
-Hmm?
I want you to come
with me somewhere tonight.
Do you trust me?
It'll be just the two of us.
Just the two of us?
-Yes.
-Yeah?
Yes.
Okay.
What now?
Oh, Jesus.
Give me those back.
Okay, so let's
get back to it. Are you ready?
- Everything okay now?
- Yeah.
There's a couple of things
I still need to go over,
but we can proceed for now.
All right, then.
Well, let's continue on.
Mmm.
There's lots of
different ways to play, Jude.
For example, me, personally,
I find the biggest
erogenous zone
to be the person
I decide to share myself with.
Your pleasure
is my pleasure, Jude.
And if I don't like something?
If you don't like it,
we don't do it.
That's the great thing
about playing.
Putting your old taboos aside.
And discovering yourself.
And your body.
The very first thing
I learned when I started
is that our minds are the most
powerful pleasure stimulator
there is.
For example,
without touching you,
I can imagine running
my tongue across your lips.
I like to savor it.
So that when we get there,
it's all the more explosive.
Do you see
how they're looking at you?
They wanna fuck you, Jude.
How does that make you feel?
It turns me on.
Open your legs for me.
I'm gonna
turn this stool around.
But you can't close your legs.
Is that okay with you?
I think so.
Jude.
Tell me what you want.
I'm ticklish.
Eric, you okay?
Eric, open the door.
Go back to your room.
-Eric.
-Judith, please, go.
Just double-check it.
Yesterday's meeting
went very well.
From this point forward,
Amanda Fisher
will be my contact
to the branch offices.
You did a great job.
Thank you, Ms. Flores.
You deserve
to have some downtime.
So, you're just
gonna send me away?
When you're ready, your car
will take you to the airport.
-You ready? Let's go.
-Yeah.
Sorry. Could we actually
go to Jerez, please?
Oh, my God.
My girl.
Auntie Judith.
Go on.
Boo!
-What are you doing here?
-I missed you guys.
Come on down, it's ready!
-Coming, Dad!
-Hurry before it gets cold.
We've got all
your favorites here, Judith.
Pretty cool surprise, huh?
I missed you so much.
So, did the beast
behave herself?
-She rode great.
-Good.
-Well, except...
-What?
The front suspension
feels a little soft,
so some of the bumps
were a little tricky,
-but that's about it.
-I didn't realize.
-I'll fix it up.
-No, it's okay.
-I'll fix it right now.
-No. Dad.
What are you doing here, Eric?
I just really missed you.
That's nice.
That's it?
-What do you mean, that's it?
-I mean, I don't get it.
What do you want from me?
Because if you thought
I'd just run back into your arms
because you showed up here
saying you missed me,
then you're dumber
than I thought.
I know you're right.
In Barcelona, I...
What? Go on.
Jude, I...
I want you in my life.
I don't know what else to say.
I'm sorry.
It's not that simple, Eric.
Do you realize what you did?
You used your position of power
to push me away because what?
You got scared?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I'm really lost, Jude.
- Tell me how I can fix this.
- Honey?
-Dad.
-There a problem here?
This is Eric Zimmerman.
Eric, this is my father, Manuel.
It's a pleasure, Don Manuel.
Wow. Don Manuel.
He's far from home, huh?
You don't like
motorcycles either, do you?
I enjoy driving them.
Okay.
You ride bitch?
Ride bitch?
Aren't we going a little fast?
You remember that first night
you took me out to dinner?
-Is this payback?
-No.
That guy there is Julius Caesar.
And that smoking hot guy
up there is Hercules.
It's interesting.
You're both kind of cute.
Uh, this place has been a museum
of anthropology, a library,
pretty sure a school. What else?
I don't actually know
what else it's been.
-So, do you come here a lot?
-To Jerez?
With all the hours
you make me work at Muller?
I wish I had the time, but no.
But I've really enjoyed
being back here this time.
And getting a chance
to see the neighborhood
I grew up in through your eyes
is cool
because I suddenly understand
how my mom fell so in love
with this city.
She's not Andalusian.
She's from Catalonia.
And well, uh... And your mom?
-She was born in Spain.
-Uh-huh.
That's why my Spanish
is so damn good.
Well, I don't know about that.
How about some humility,
Mr. Zimmerman?
-Is that Judith?
-I can teach you a couple words.
What's up?
I gotta make this delivery.
-See you later. Good to see you.
-Yeah, okay.
-Judith.
-Fernando.
How are you? I missed you.
-Eric Zimmerman.
Zimmerman.
So, is he related to your boss?
Yeah, it's a little complicated.
Yeah, seems that way.
Can I talk to you, Judith,
please? Alone.
This isn't exactly a good time.
-Maybe later.
-Judith, please.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, yeah.
Take all the time you need, pal.
-It's all right.
-Listen, Superman.
-Asshole.
-What the hell?
What'd you have to be a dick
and insult him?
Are you really doing this after
what happened at the party?
Nothing happened at the party.
We're just friends, so back off.
Fernando,
this really has to stop.
-It's been months.
-You're fucking him, aren't you?
-Let's not do this here.
-Just admit it.
-Admit what?
-It's disgusting.
You're killing me,
you know that?
It honestly
feels like every other day
-I find out
about a different guy.
-Okay, Fernando, that's enough.
No more.
-Judith, listen. Just listen.
-No, I think I'm done.
You mean nothing
to that spoiled douchebag.
Literally nothing.
-But to me, you're special.
-Oh.
-Babe. Hey.
-Stop.
Fernando,
we're done talking now.
-Let's just get a drink.
-No.
Sorry about that.
-Everything okay?
-Yeah.
Damn exes. Am I right?
So, now that you're officially
running Muller Pharmaceuticals,
do you think you could invent
a pill to cure lovesick people?
I think someone
already did that.
-They're called antidepressants.
-No, I mean like...
Like, imagine you created a pill
and people could just take it.
It would be like, "Oh, no,
I guess Judith doesn't love me.
Well, I'd better take
one of these pills
and move on to the next one."
Bingo. Problem solved.
-Yeah, that would be nice.
-Right?
Now I'm gonna have
his stupid face in my head
for the rest of this vacation.
I might have a solution.
Well, I was wondering
if maybe you'd consider
coming with me
to meet some friends later.
Uh...
Like friends, or you know,
"friends"?
To be honest, all my friends
like to play, Judith.
If that's possible.
I don't believe
you have many friends.
I think you'd be surprised.
And where exactly
are you meeting
these close friends of yours?
Don't worry, close by.
They have a big house in Zahara.
And...
And they invited us both
to a party.
A very, very big party.
But I'll only go if you go.
A party sounds fun,
but it's a lot, Eric.
Judith, listen. I don't need you
to make a decision right now.
We can just go to Zahara,
and then it'll be your choice.
Auntie Judith, please don't go.
Mom only lets me
eat chocolate omelets
-when you're here. Stay longer.
-'Cause they're disgusting.
I'll never forgive you
for showing her those.
-Honey.
-I'll leave some chocolate
-in your room, troublemaker.
-Here.
What's all this, Dad?
Some food to take with you.
-I'm not going to Madrid.
-Here, Dad.
I'll take it
if she doesn't want it.
No, stop it.
Look, I have some collard greens
and this oxtail.
You're gonna die. It's so good.
I also brought some ortigillas.
You should eat those tonight.
Does he even know
what ortigillas are?
No, Dad. He has no idea.
You shouldn't have done this.
This is too much.
We're not gonna eat all this.
You will.
It's a delicacy in our region.
It's good, I'm telling you.
Oh, my God. Let's go.
Hey. Whoa. Your suitcase.
Oh, right. Thanks, Dad.
Aren't you forgetting something?
-What?
-A goodbye hug.
It was so nice seeing you guys.
-Listen.
-What?
Take care of this guy.
He looks at you
the way I looked at Mom.
It's been a pleasure,
Don Manuel.
Don't call me Don, okay?
Manuel is good.
You and I are family now.
Get in here. Give me a hug, huh?
Okay. Manuel it is.
I can't wait
to try the ortigillas.
Take care of her.
Come on.
Good morning.
It's 8 a.m. or 7 a.m.
in the Canary Islands.
And oh, boy, it's a beautiful
day in our beloved Andalusia.
We're continuing on and playing
some of the greatest hits.
This next one's a song
from Malu.
It's one we all know well.
"Blanco y Negro."
Here it goes.
I hate to break it to you,
Ms. Flores, but you suck.
-You're not gonna answer?
-No.
Eric. Who's Betta?
That's none of your business.
All right. Great.
Judith, slow down.
Tell me who Betta is.
-Judith.
-Eric.
It's a simple question.
Who is Betta?
Okay, okay, okay.
Slow down.
Please, Judith.
Betta is my ex.
We were together two years,
and then...
Then what?
And then
she slept with my father.
Wow.
I caught them in bed together
one night.
And obviously decided
to end things.
With both of them.
I'm sorry. I don't know
why I didn't just tell you this.
I guess it's just hard for me
to really let people into
my life on a personal level.
Thank you for telling me now.
- Hey there.
- Eric.
-Judith.
-Hi.
You're just in time
for le petit dejeuner.
Judith,
this is Frida and Andres,
-two very good friends.
-Nice to meet you.
It's nice to
see you again, Judith.
-I'm sorry, have we met before?
-Yes, you guys have met.
-When?
-Are you hungry?
-How are you?
-Good.
It's a great spread.
Wait, you're saying the woman
in the video with us was you?
Oh, my God.
I heard it made you
a little uncomfortable.
Isn't that right, Eric?
No, no, no.
Eric apologized to me.
But if I'm being
honest with you,
I have to admit, you gave me
the best orgasm of my life.
Cheers to that.
Cheers.
We were both studying medicine
at the University of Nuremberg.
One day I was parking, I didn't
see him, and I ran him over.
No way.
Are you serious?
-It was love at first hit.
-Yeah, it was.
Been together eight years.
I got my ring and our son.
-You have a son?
-Yeah.
Andres and Frida
are committed to each other.
They know how to
separate sex and feelings.
You guys going
to Maggie's party?
It's black and white.
It'll be pretty hot.
Yeah. We haven't
actually decided yes or no.
Or have we?
Hm.
Do you want them to watch?
Or do you wanna watch them?
I want to play.
God, this place is so gorgeous.
I can't believe it.
-Is that Megan Maxwell?
-Mm-hm.
Oh, my God.
I've read every single one
of her books.
Don't be surprised if you see
some recognizable faces here.
Maggie's little
promiscuous parties
attract
all kinds of celebrities.
But you, babe, you're a novelty.
-So, what do you think?
-I think six months ago,
I could never imagine myself
at a place like this.
I mean, it's kind of insane.
Thank you.
Well, sweetheart,
you better get used to it,
because from now on,
you're one of us.
Oh, should I be scared now?
We have to dance to this.
Judith, I want you to meet Alex.
He's a very close friend.
Mmm.
So smooth.
Jude. Tell me what you want.
Touch me, please. Touch me.
Tell me you love me, Eric.
Tell me you love me.
Morning, Judith.
Hey.
Um...
Where's Eric?
He didn't say bye to you?
No. He didn't say anything.
I'm sorry, sweetie,
but when we woke up,
his car was already gone.
He didn't leave you a message?
Eric does this sometimes.
It's just the way he is.
Eric Zimmerman,
Muller Pharmaceuticals.
I am not currently available.
Please leave a message
after the beep.
-What's up, Miguel?
-Oh, you're back.
How was it with Zimmerman?
Is he as big an asshole
as he seems?
Way bigger.
He's a fucking iceman.
Egotistical and capricious.
So, pretty much like all bosses,
but I don't
have to tell you that.
How did you find out?
"Maybe in the office.
But out here, I'm in charge."
Oh, s--
What are you doing?
-Miguel, cut it out.
-I'm hiding.
Get back out here
before Monica sees you.
-I don't care if she does.
-Don't worry about it.
You were quite the stud. I'm not
gonna lie. I was very impressed.
-You were?
-Yeah.
I didn't think
you had it in you.
-You wouldn't believe how she--
-No.
No, no, that's enough of that.
-I don't wanna know any more.
-All right.
Judith, I just sent you
the analysis from London.
I need you to look it over.
Okay.
Um, yeah, the thing is,
I'm actually
heading to the gym now,
but I'll make sure to have
a look at it tomorrow morning.
Then tomorrow morning it is.
Hi there.
Uh, hi there.
Sorry.
No, I'm sorry. I didn't
hear you over the music.
Did you wanna use it?
There's tons.
No, there's a bunch of them.
Um...
I'm Judith.
Rebeca. Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
I was just wondering
if maybe you wanted
to do some sparring.
Okay. Just be gentle with me.
Come on.
Hey. Be gentle.
-That felt kind of personal.
-Sorry.
Try a jab. A short one.
No?
Here. Try this.
Try again. Go slow.
Good. Now extend the elbow.
And then back.
Protect your face. Chin down.
Try it again.
Okay. Where are you aiming?
- Like, his face.
- No.
-Here.
-Okay, I got it.
Punch straight. Go for the kill.
For the kill.
Judith, can I talk
to you for a moment?
Hey, what's up, Monica?
As of next week,
we're gonna be transferring you
to the financial department.
Congratulations.
M... Monica, you...
You know, I've wanted
this promotion for a while,
but I don't want
any kind of special treatment.
What are you talking about?
Why would I give you...
You're getting this
because of you.
For the hard work you've done.
This is coming from me.
I'm your boss.
And you've earned it.
Also, if you're not
working overtime,
you're of no use to me.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm very busy.
And your new office awaits you.
-Thank you, Monica.
-Mm-hm.
Oh, shit.
Judith.
-Hey, Dad.
-You okay?
Yeah. I just had a couple
minutes at the office here,
and I figured
I'd give you a call
to see how everyone's
holding up over there.
We're doing all right.
Everything's pretty much
the same.
Lots of expenses and not
enough work. That's about it.
Oh, and by the way,
did your German
enjoy the food we gave him?
He didn't even leave me any.
Well, your mom's recipes
are always a hit.
Honey, what's wrong?
Dad, we've never
talked about Mom's death.
Ah.
Because there's not much
to talk about, sweetheart.
The important thing
is that she's not suffering
anymore.
It's okay, really.
But you...
You're lonely, Dad. I can tell.
Oh, Judith, don't be ridiculous.
I got my hands full.
I got Raquel, huh?
And I've got the little one
running around,
keeping me young.
And I got you, right?
-Yeah.
-Honey, I...
I loved your mom
more than anything.
I was happy before, but
the moment I met your mother,
she made me
the happiest man in this world.
And now I have all of you.
We have to focus
on the present, honey.
And the people
who are still with us.
I love you so much.
I love you too, Dad. I miss you.
It's okay to cry.
No. No, I'm not crying, Dad.
Take care. Talk soon.
Bye. I love you.
Judith.
I love you.
Judith, if you don't
open the door,
I'll scream it for the whole
office to hear.
I don't care.
I'll get down on my knees
and make a fool of myself
if I need to.
Do you hear me?
Not here. My place.
Where were you, Eric?
In Germany, with my family.
I needed to get away
from everything and just think.
Away from me?
Yeah.
Look, I...
I didn't think I was capable
of falling in love, Jude.
I never expected to feel
everything I felt for you.
And it scared me,
to be honest with you.
Jude.
You're the person
I wanna be with.
As a couple.
Do you wanna be with me, Jude?
Eric.
I just...
I just don't trust you.
Please. I can change. You just
have to give me a chance.
And what if you can't?
What if this happens again
and then...
And then you get scared
and take off on me?
-You don't care if you hurt me.
-Of course I care, Jude.
No, because if you cared,
you wouldn't be doing this.
It wouldn't have happened.
You wouldn't be here
asking again,
apologizing to me again.
I'm just tired.
I know this is
what we both want.
And what if I'm not in love
with you anymore?
If, uh...
If that's the truth,
then just tell me
and I'll walk away for good.
Please forgive me, Jude.
You're such an asshole.
I know.
But I promise,
if you give me a chance,
I'll prove to you every day
that I love you.
No more bullshit.
Do you understand that?
No more.
You're gonna
have to work for it.
Work.
Day and night.
How about we stay in, make
some popcorn and watch a movie?
I'm out of popcorn.
-Good morning.
-Good Morning.
You snore a little,
you know that?
-No. No. You're such a liar.
-You do, but it's okay.
It's like cute,
adorable snoring.
It sounds like a little dog.
-You're lying.
-It's true.
I'm telling you,
it's so adorable.
No, stop it.
Eric, you can't
tell me things like that.
It doesn't matter.
-Eric.
-What?
I want to try something out.
Whatever you want.
Really?
Okay.
You know how I've done
everything you ever asked
-because I knew
it was important to you?
-Mm-hm.
All your games or, you know,
your kinky stuff.
-And you enjoyed it.
-Uh-huh.
All right, fine.
I enjoyed it a little bit.
But... One time, you told me
that it's important
to experiment
to find out what you like.
But you have to be willing to.
-No?
-Mm-hm.
Okay, so then I'd like
to try something.
For this one time,
I want to be the one in control.
And I wanna
tie your hands
and blindfold you.
-Ah, Jude.
-And give you pleasure.
-Jude. Jude.
-What?
You... You know I don't like
not being the one in control.
Yeah, okay there, buster,
but it's your turn now.
Give me a chance
to try it out for once.
That's what you always
said you wanted, isn't it?
I've created a monster.
-So, what are we playing?
-It's a surprise.
Did you miss me?
Judith, untie me.
-Fucking untie me!
-Okay, calm down.
How long
have you known her, Judith?
She's just a friend.
-Don't bullshit me.
-I'm not.
-Don't bullshit me!
-What's wrong?
Eric? Eric.
Wow, that was dramatic.
What are you talking about?
Oh, he didn't tell you?
Come on, Judith, think about it.
No.
Okay, then.
I probably better get going.
By the way,
all my friends call me Betta.
Ciao.
Oops.
I'd never let myself
get swept away
by love like this before.
Never. And even though
I'm still not sure
exactly what happened
between Eric and I,
I do know
that ever since I met him,
my life has taken on
a new meaning.
-Monica.
-So, listen,
I just read
your letter of resignation,
and I can fire you
if you'd like.
Judith,
you deserve severance pay.
That's so kind of you, Monica.
It really is.
But I think right now it's best
that I stay away from money.
Judith.
"Stay away from money."
I've come to understand
that some people
just aren't ready to be loved.
As for me,
I never would have imagined
I was capable of loving the way
I have these past few months.
But I haven't
just rediscovered love.
I've become so much
more aware of my body,
of who I am, and what I want.
Now I know
how to set my own boundaries.
There is a whole world
of sensations
waiting to be explored.
And above all,
I can now honestly say
that I feel completely free.
Love
doesn't always start off well.
But you should never forget
that yours is a love story.
Hey, Judith. Have a seat.
How are you?
I know right now you probably
don't even know how to feel.
But don't worry, Judith.
I know for you
the best is yet to come, hm?
You're a warrior.
You're one of us now.