Q: IS THERE AN EASY WAY TO DIE?
A: A TALL BUILDING, I GUESS?
KINKI MEDICAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Such lovely colors.
Oh, I mean...
Those are Faber-Castell pencils, right?
They're nice.
I wanted some too, but they're expensive.
I've heard Chagall
and someone else used them.
Van Gogh.
What?
Van Gogh used them too.
Right...
What are you drawing?
Heaven.
Heaven?
I'm headed there soon.
And you? What brings you here?
What?
Were you gonna
stun us all and take flight?
No.
I was just, uh...
I'm joking.
Are you visiting someone?
Yeah! A friend.
But you shouldn't joke about that.
Going to heaven, I mean.
That part is true.
Pretty soon,
I'm going to die.
In six months.
It's a rare disease that only affects
one in hundreds of thousands.
I was born with it.
I see.
So that's it.
You're not surprised?
What?
It's nothing.
Say...
Aren't you scared?
Of what?
Of dying.
You don't... seem scared.
I'm not.
I've known for a while
that I wouldn't live long.
Compared to hospitals,
I imagine the scenery is better
on the other side.
You could even say...
I'm excited to see heaven.
NEW POST: WHAT WOULD YOU DO
IF YOU FOUND OUT YOU WERE GOING TO DIE?
Akito!
Hurry and eat, or you'll be late!
Ow!
You have the worst luck, huh?
You're a genius
at drawing the short straw.
Natsumi...
- We'll have to buy you a new palette.
- It's fine.
Don't bother.
Buy Natsumi that lacrosse stick
she wanted instead.
No way! The Crux Pro?!
Okay, everyone.
It looks like you're done.
Let's go over the answers.
Please look at the blackboard...
"A genius at drawing the short straw..."
She's not wrong.
Akito.
You should apply for this.
NIKA ART EXHIBITION
It'd be quite a feat to win
a new artist award in high school.
Right.
The exhibition was
my most imminent and important goal.
Art would open doors to my future.
I really believed that.
A malignant tumor?
Tumors in the heart almost never occur,
but in rare cases,
it can be the primary development point.
They found a tumor in my heart
and told me I have one year to live.
Much will depend on how it spreads,
but I estimate you have a year.
It took days to wrap my head around it.
No, a week.
NIKA ART EXHIBITION
You could even say
I'm excited to see heaven.
I wanted to know
how she could be so excited.
KINKI MEDICAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
If I could run into her again,
asking might ease my mind.
And so, the boy who was afraid to die...
met the girl who looked forward to it.
DRAWING CLOSER
Come on in.
HARUNA SAKURAI
Sorry to intrude.
What luck. I've been looking for a model.
I don't have
any friends who visit me, so...
Your name is Haruna Sakurai?
Haru means spring, right?
That's when I was born.
My parents aren't creative.
Wait, my name's Akito.
Akito Hayasaka!
Aki for autumn, when I was born.
- How old are you?
- Seventeen.
Me too!
What are the chances?
Oh, you can sit over there.
Uh, right.
Say,
do you like drawing too?
Huh?
You knew about Faber-Castell.
- I'm in the art club.
- I knew it.
But I've been skipping lately.
I'll bet you're aiming for art school.
In the future, you want to be...
a real painter?
The future, huh?
Yeah, your future dreams.
- Actually, I...
- Art school sounds fun.
I wanted to go too.
Maybe you'll enter
the Nika Art Exhibition.
I'd love to exhibit,
but I've got no time left
to paint something big.
That settles it.
You'll be my surrogate!
We'll do art school
and the Nika Art Exhibition!
Somehow, the words just wouldn't come out.
Hey, can I have a look?
Sure, go ahead.
You're pretty good, Ms. Sakurai.
- Did you take lessons?
- No.
I've never even been to a museum.
For real?
Oh, and call me Haruna.
What?
So, uh, Haruna,
why are you able to, um, draw like this?
It's the only world where I can be free.
When I'm with my sketchbook,
nothing ties me down.
I can paint over my illness
and fly off to anywhere I want.
If you have a problem,
I'll paint over it for you too.
Hey.
This statue is near
Aoba Junior High School, right?
Yeah. That was my junior high.
I barely attended class though.
I often ride my bike past there.
A guy in our art club went there too.
His name's Takada.
Really?
Then, do you recognize
the elementary school on the page before?
It looks like
you were close with this girl.
Is she a friend?
Well, I guess you could say that.
Or rather, she was a friend.
"Was?"
Haruna! Time for your IV!
Okay...
Sorry.
- Oh, is he a friend?
- Yeah.
That's new.
In that case,
I'll get going.
Okay.
Hey, um...
Can I come again?
What?
I'd like to...
see more of your drawings.
Sure!
You're an authorized visitor.
But in return, bring housewarming gifts.
Housewarming gifts?
Something new to draw.
I'm bored with drawing what's in here.
It's a deal.
Well then, see you next time.
Right. See you then.
That's all. School event organizers,
please visit the faculty room.
This concludes home room.
- Goodbye!
- Bye!
Sorry.
Akito!
You're skipping art club again?
I'm a little tired. I think I'll pass.
"You'll pass"?
But what about the Nika Art Exhibition?
You were so excited.
The Nika Art Exhibition...
Huh? What is it?
Did that bike injury
change your personality too?
No way.
- His knee's already healed.
- Cut it out!
Seriously! What's wrong?
Sorry, my bus is coming.
The next stop
is Medical University Hospital.
Those visiting Flower Shop Bel Fiore
should exit here.
- Thank you!
- Are you looking for something specific?
- Huh?
A present for your girlfriend?
Oh, no, I...
Well, you seemed very intent.
My friend is in the hospital.
Avoid the potted plants then.
Anything with roots
is said to make illness worse.
Oh, I know!
How about these flowers?
There are so many colors.
Like a painter's palette.
They're called gerberas.
There are over 2,000 species.
2,000 species?!
Each carries its own sentiment,
but no matter what the color,
none of the sentiments are negative.
They're quite rare.
Colors brighten the mood too.
Perfect for get-well-soon gifts.
I'll take four.
No, wait! Five, please.
And the colors?
I guess I'll go with pink.
The sentiment for pink is "gratitude."
Will that do?
Um, then what about orange?
Orange means "patience and endurance."
And yellow?
Yellow means "the ultimate beauty."
White means "purity."
And blue...
I almost forgot.
All together, they mean "hope."
That's it!
Five in different colors, please.
Haruna?
Haruna, can I come in?
Don't enter without permission!
Oh...
Sorry.
After all, this is still a lady's bedroom.
Sorry about that.
Will this make up for it?
Flowers?
Gerberas.
Thank you!
They're lovely!
I like gerberas. They're so cute.
The shop owner recommended them.
She said their sentiment is "hope."
Hope, eh?
Oh... sorry.
I didn't mean to...
Don't worry!
For me,
my illness is a wonderful magic spell.
If someone is bothering me,
the minute they hear I'm ill,
they all turn and run away.
The spell failed to work
on only one person.
What?
It's nothing.
Shall we drink something in the lounge?
Sure.
A new friend?
Akito Hayasaka, who was born in autumn.
We met on the roof.
He's a future Nika Exhibition artist.
I see.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but she has tests scheduled.
Oh, I forgot.
Sorry.
No, it's fine.
We'll save the fun for next time.
Right. See you then.
Um, excuse me.
If you don't mind,
could you come again?
I will.
So that's how it is.
Unlike me,
Haruna can't go to people,
even if she wants to.
She can only lay
and wait for them to come to her.
THE ONE IMMUNE TO THE SPELL
Or rather, she was a friend.
ART ROOM
Hayasaka.
I heard you're quitting.
Oh, uh... yeah.
Running away, huh?
Not that it matters.
Hey, Takada.
You went to
Aoba Junior High School, right?
That's right.
Do you remember
a girl named Haruna Sakurai?
Oh, her...
She was sick or something.
I barely remember her.
Was she close to anyone?
- A good friend or...
- A friend?
She barely ever came to school.
Oh, actually,
I might have seen her
with Miura a few times.
Miura?
She's in my class.
You mean that Miura?
Yeah? What do you want?
Better yet, who are you?
Oh, I, uh...
- I'm Hayasaka...
- I don't need your name.
But you...
It's how I say no.
You're not the first boy to ask me out.
- Let's go, Ayaka.
- Yeah.
It's not that!
I just wanted to ask you something.
Huh?
Then why didn't you say so?
Why are you acting so weird?
Just spit it out.
Do you know Haruna Sakurai?
I heard you were close with her.
Sorry, I'll catch up later.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Why do you know about Haruna?
Oh, she's uh...
- You could say we're comrades.
- What?
By any chance,
did you play on a swing set
with Haruna as kids?
Or take in a stray cat together?
I see. She's in the hospital again.
It could be a long stay this time,
and it seems like
I'm the only friend that visits.
I thought she might
be happy to see someone else.
So you're trying to win her over.
It's not that!
I just want to do something for her.
Hayasaka, right?
Sorry, but no can do.
I haven't seen her once
since high school began.
You could hardly call us friends now.
I doubt she wants to see me either.
This is why you have no friends!
I'm home.
Oh, hi.
Where have you been?
Shopping.
Is it true you're skipping art club?
Eri was worried and came to ask about you.
Oh, is that so?
Why not talk to her?
About what?
I'd feel a lot better
with her watching out for you.
- I'm sure you...
- This doesn't concern her.
I don't want to be a burden.
Huh? What's going on?
Let me guess, she rejected you!
You really are carefree, aren't you?
It must be nice.
There's more to life
than lacrosse. Study too.
Akito, can I come in?
Yeah?
There's a holiday coming up.
Why don't we go
on a family trip or something?
- A trip?
- Yeah.
You said you wanted to travel Japan
with your sketchbook once you could drive.
Did I say that?
Even if it's not all over Japan,
let's give it a try.
Natsumi wants to go too.
Let's do it together.
I'm fine. The three of you should go.
I'd only be a burden if I went along.
It's okay to be a burden.
You can ask us for things.
You worked so hard on painting.
- I'm sure there are still things you can...
- There aren't.
Besides, there's no point
in making memories now.
Sorry.
Is that all?
For three straight weeks of visits,
here's your reward.
Thanks.
I didn't think you'd come this often.
I've grown attached to the flowers too.
Let's live another week together.
You can do it.
- Mako!
- Long time no see!
- Are you doing well?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Yeah, right. Look at this thing.
- Oh, man...
- It must really hurt.
- You're the one who dropped it on her.
Let's head back.
I'm not a fan of all this chatter.
Sure.
Haruna, is there anyone
you wish would visit?
Well...
What about the friend
you mentioned before?
The one I'd like to see
is my dad, I guess.
- Your dad?
- Yeah.
You don't see him?
It's been five years.
I'd apologize to him.
Apologize?
My dad... always took the time
to do things I'd like.
When I was hospitalized,
he came every day after work.
No matter how busy he was.
But actually,
he was always an outdoors man.
Once I was born,
his dream was to go camping
or to the beach together.
But I was never able
to go anywhere with him.
So that's why
I want to apologize
for being born with this body.
I'm sorry I wasn't
the healthy daughter he hoped for.
Here it is.
- Thanks.
- Of course.
Um, excuse me!
You're the chief nurse, right?
It's about Haruna Sakurai's family.
Her family?
Well, you see,
I've never seen them visit.
For some reason,
she said she hasn't seen her father.
I know it's not my business,
but couldn't the hospital
contact her father?
Or maybe if I could talk to her mother...
Could you tell me
when she might be here?
That would be me.
What?
I'm...
Haruna's mother.
Please forgive me.
I didn't know a thing,
and yet...
I'm only trying not to mix
work and personal feelings.
When I saw that you came back,
I was so grateful
that I wanted to jump up and hug you.
As for her father...
I'm sorry.
Even if I tried,
he's out of reach.
What?
He died in an accident.
On that day, we got permission
from her doctor...
A little more.
...and for the first time,
they left for the beach together.
That'll do.
All right, there we go.
- Okay, we're off.
- Have fun!
We will!
Off we go!
But Haruna...
hid how sick she was
for her father's sake.
Haruna!
Hey, Haruna?
Are you okay? Haruna! Hey!
Are you okay? Can you hear me?
Are you okay?
Can you say your name?
But Haruna...
blamed herself for everything.
It's like she can't
forgive herself for living
and wants to join her father soon.
She closed herself off from the world.
But since you came,
she's opened up a little.
As long as
it doesn't interfere with school,
please keep being her friend.
CASES OF PRIMARY CARDIAC SARCOMAS
CANCER OF THE BLOOD VESSELS
Thanks.
If we hadn't told him the truth,
maybe he... would still smile
like he used to.
I've asked myself
that very question many times.
It may be true
that he'd have been happier
not knowing.
But then,
perhaps there is something
he can do only because he knows.
No one can say
what the right or wrong answer is.
This is good tea.
FOR GAKUENTOSHI STATION
Darn it!
My bus!
Are you late for morning practice again?
- Good morning.
I'm doomed. I missed practice.
Don't let it get you down.
Oh, if it isn't Mr. Gerbera.
Could I have five like last time?
If you're skipping school to visit,
they must be someone important.
No, it's not that.
We're more like comrades.
Better make it six then.
This one's free.
- But I couldn't...
- Don't worry about it!
Depending on the number,
gerbera bouquets change meaning.
Six gerberas mean
"I'm crazy about you."
Hey, there's one more than before.
- What?
- Huh?
Oh, um...
I'm a regular,
so the owner gave me one for free.
It's so nice to get
such cute flowers every week.
I wish I could freeze them
in time as they are now.
Oh, that's right.
Look!
My mom bought me this.
Your mom's the chief nurse, huh?
Yeah.
I heard she blabbed a lot of things.
Sorry about that.
It's fine.
Once I master the camera,
maybe I'll upload it to social media.
What do you think?
You don't have to compliment me.
Um, this is a video.
What?
It's more artistic that way!
What about the others?
Is this a selfie?
Hey! You're not supposed to look
at that one!
Huh?
Oh!
I'll go put the flowers in a vase.
Okay.
WELCOME TO HARUNA'S ROOM
Hey.
I'm happy you come so often,
but do you have the time?
Huh?
Don't you have friends?
I guess I do,
but I wouldn't say I have a lot.
What about a crush?
I guess I do,
but I wouldn't say I have a lot.
What's that mean?
Then... what about a first love?
I guess I do,
but she's a childhood friend.
But then, so is Shota.
Unrequited love?
That's why you were sulking on the roof.
What about you?
Do you have a crush?
What?
I mean, have you ever liked someone?
Or been in love?
Just wondering.
I'm scared
of a love that's short-lived...
Huh?
A romance with me
would be over before it's begun.
I envy you, Akito.
Even if it includes unrequited love,
you have a future.
You're wrong.
I have no future either.
- Actually, I...
- You'll live a long life.
So don't give up on romance.
I want to see who you fall in love with,
what kind of family you create,
and what kind of old man you'll become.
I'll watch it all from heaven.
So you have to live a long life, Akito.
That's my wish.
Will you grant it?
I decided
not to tell her I'm dying.
I'll come every day.
What?
Sure.
I'll be waiting.
I'll wait every day.
What would you do
if you found out you were dying?
For me, the answer was
to use the time I had left
to make her happy.
WHAT TIME WILL YOU COME TODAY?
I HAVE SIXTH PERIOD,
SO IT MIGHT BE JUST BEFORE VISITATION ENDS
HMPH.
MOM, BRING ME A BLANKET!
YOU SENT THAT TO ME, GOOFBALL.
Akito!
You never hang out these days.
It's hot enough already. Grow up!
Oh, and this Sunday,
let's all go to the movies.
I guess there's no choice.
It's settled then!
Okay?
Yeah, yeah.
My little sister has a big mouth.
She keeps saying I was born cursed.
Really?
Eri and Shota are always teasing me too.
Eri always gets good grades,
and she was class president
in elementary and middle school.
Shota's the ace of the soccer team.
Hello, there!
- Just five?
- Yeah.
Actually, make it one more, please.
Hey Haruna,
what do you want to do
for summer vacation?
Well, I don't have one.
A summer vacation
from illness would be nice.
Sorry!
I...
Wait!
The 4,500!
Huh?
From this window,
you can see a show with 4,500 fireworks.
I didn't know about it at first,
so the explosions startled me.
I hid under my sheets.
When I peeked my head out,
I saw beautiful fireworks
out towards the sea.
So beautiful, it gave me chills.
But watching the fireworks alone
was kind of scary.
I'll watch with you this year.
You will?
Yeah.
You mean it?
All right, then.
Promise me.
Okay!
Whoa, wait a second!
- Hold out your hand.
- Huh?
What are you...
- Hey!
- Just hold still.
It's late. I better get going.
You have plans?
Yeah, the movies.
They wouldn't let me say no.
Your childhood friend?
Yeah.
I see...
Sounds fun.
A date, huh?
No, it's nothing like...
Don't keep her waiting.
And say hi for me.
Sure. I'll be back.
The fireworks are August 20th!
See you then.
Do you like to watch trailers?
- Not really.
- Akito! Over here!
Sorry!
What took you so long?
- You owe us popcorn.
- Huh?
Make it a drink set.
- Yeah, all right.
- Yay!
Hey, isn't that Miura?
Rumor has it, you asked her out.
I told you...
I'm kidding.
Come on, let's go.
- Cola, please.
- Okay.
Hey, Akito! Come on!
- This way?
- Yeah.
Let's watch an action movie next time.
FROM HARUNA: DID YOU GET THERE ON TIME?
Did you get there on time?
I just finished making teru-teru bozu.
They'll ensure the fireworks
happen on a clear day.
Are you okay?
Hey, is he okay?
- Are you okay?
- Akito?
Can you hear me?
- What the...
- Akito!
- Hey, Akito!
Call an ambulance!
Akito!
Akito...
Mom, Akito's awake!
Akito? Do you know where you are?
Take it easy.
You collapsed at the movie theater,
and they brought you here.
It's been a week.
What?
You had an irregular heartbeat.
They did an operation
to install a machine in your heart.
You'll be in rehabilitation
for the rest of the summer.
What day is it?
Huh?
What's the date?
It's August 20th.
This can't be happening.
KINKI MEDICAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Hey! Are you okay?
I don't see a "read" mark.
I made more teru-teru bozu.
Did something happen?
Are you on a digital detox?
Maybe you're out
with your childhood friend.
CALL HARUNA
Hello?
Hi.
I'm sorry.
I broke my promise.
I couldn't answer your texts either.
Thank goodness.
I thought you were mad at me.
The truth is that there's a reason
I couldn't answer...
That's fine. It's about Eri, right?
What?
You seem to be having a busy vacation.
But I'm glad if it went well.
As your friend, I'm happy.
I told you, didn't I?
I'm looking forward to watching
your happiness from heaven.
A little fireworks promise is no big deal.
I'm sorry.
For just a little longer...
don't hang up.
I won't.
Not while the fireworks last.
This might be my last time
seeing fireworks.
Don't say that.
Let's both live longer.
Then next year,
we'll definitely watch together.
My six months are almost up.
We'll watch together!
I did some research,
and some people
live twice as long as their diagnosis.
Sometimes ten years or more.
The diagnosis could be wrong
in the first place.
I mean...
There's still Christmas
and New Year's parties...
We'll celebrate your 18th birthday.
It's in April, right?
Yeah.
Akito...
You know...
I...
The truth is...
What? Did you say something?
No.
It seems...
the fireworks are over.
Why didn't you tell us?
It would feel like
attending my own funeral.
Besides...
I was afraid I'd take it out on you.
It's not like
we could have changed anything.
But even so...
I wish you'd told me.
Isn't that what best friends do?
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Can you come back to school?
It should be fine.
I'll be out after summer.
- Second semester...
- Akito?
So that's it.
Please.
Don't tell Haruna.
When I got my diagnosis, I was so scared.
Clinging to her
has given me a reason to live.
I know it's selfish. I'm sorry.
But rather than look forward
to seeing heaven,
I want her to enjoy her life now.
That's why...
I want us to spend the time we have left...
as ordinary 17-year-olds.
I might...
have been clinging too.
What?
Being her nurse
was my way of running.
I guess
I need to face things too.
Do you have everything?
Yeah.
I will face this.
So that Haruna
can enjoy her time here.
- I don't want to go back to school.
- Same.
Ayaka, those nails
might get you in trouble.
You think?
- She's right.
- Yeah...
I told the career counselor
I want to be a nail artist,
so it should be okay.
- I'll be your first customer!
- Really?
Then I'll be your second.
- Huh?
- Isn't he...
What?
Come visit her.
- Hey, wait!
- Huh?
Wait!
Let me go!
I said let me go!
What are you so desperate for?
Do you like Haruna or something?
Well, bad news.
- She won't fall for a weirdo like...
- Haruna...
She has no time left.
Just three months.
If she makes it that long.
You came.
I really am sorry.
I have no excuse,
and I know sorry isn't good enough.
It doesn't make up for it,
but today, I brought a special guest.
Ayaka?
Long time no see.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry...
No.
It's my fault.
It took me so long...
to come.
I'm sorry, Haruna.
What I said was awful.
No.
It's my fault.
Say it isn't true.
You can't die.
I won't allow it.
I'm sorry.
I won't allow it, even if you apologize.
Never...
Don't expect a thank-you.
I met Haruna in second grade.
Everyone avoided her
because of her illness.
Too slow!
Aren't you gonna join in?
I'm not supposed to run.
Yeah?
Let's see who can swing higher.
Go!
Come on. You too!
I've never been one to hold back,
so I asked all about her illness.
Somehow, we got along well.
We declared ourselves the ultimate team.
It's so cute!
Was it abandoned?
But in junior high,
she missed class a lot.
There was suddenly distance between us.
Graduation day was the final blow.
She couldn't attend the ceremony.
JUNIOR HIGH DIPLOMA
Ta-da!
Do you like your handmade diploma?
CONGRATULATIONS HARUNA
TOGETHER FOREVER!
Don't give up. Let's go to high school.
You can attend remotely at some schools.
Is this a joke?
What's wrong? You know it's not.
You thought a handmade diploma
would make me happy?
Oh, I see. Are you my teacher now?
It's nothing like that.
Why would you say that?
I skipped my club's graduation ceremony
to make this.
- As your friend, I...
- We're not friends.
Even when we were kids,
I never thought of you as my friend.
I just...
wanted to be like you.
But it's no use.
I can't do it,
and I don't really want to.
So this is a good opportunity.
It's time... we graduate from each other.
Don't visit me again.
What are you saying?
I always thought of you as my best friend.
This is why you have no friends!
Bye.
That was the last time.
She probably wanted to set you free.
Knowing she would die,
she didn't want to be a burden.
TOGETHER FOREVER!
Bye.
I understand what it's like
to distance yourself.
Oh, I mean,
generally speaking.
Akito, can I come in?
I wanted to talk to you
before school starts.
Do you remember the advanced
medical procedure we talked about?
Dr. Kikuchi made arrangements,
and he's agreed
to introduce you to a good specialist.
Really?
But it only extends life a little.
I think it's worth a try.
If it's successful,
you could be in the Nika Art Exhibition.
You'd miss three months of school though.
Three months...
I can't do that.
Sorry.
I think surgery is...
Right.
Sorry to push you.
Maybe I wanted it...
more for myself than for you.
Come in!
It's just you?
Thank good...
You don't like it when I'm here?
You came today too.
Actually, you've been here every day.
What about you?
You come so often, it creeps me out.
Yeah, well,
if you're gonna come,
at least make conversation
instead of just sitting around.
What are you, "The Thinker?"
My being here is enough.
Unlike you, I respect Haruna's time.
Who says I don't respect it?
I think you two would make a good couple.
- What?!
Don't make me laugh.
Nerds like him are my biggest pet peeve.
Ayaka's single, you know.
Hey!
Oh, really?
I'm just taking a break
from all you shallow men.
What are you laughing at?
You probably have an anime crush.
I don't have time
for silly things like romance.
This is fun.
This must be what school is like.
Hey... take this.
SNOW WHITE IN DA HOUSE
Two tickets to the school festival.
What?
My class is doing a hip-hop Snow White.
It was my idea.
You are so dense!
I'm telling you to invite Haruna!
It's not like I want to ask you.
Give Haruna a taste of being 17.
SEIMEI HIGH SCHOOL FESTIVAL
SNOW WHITE IN DA HOUSE
In elementary school...
we performed Snow White.
I was the Prince,
and Haruna was Snow White.
But she collapsed
right before the performance.
She couldn't see it or perform.
That's why.
Got it.
I'll take her.
I promise.
A school festival?
Yeah, let's go together.
I'll ask your mom
and get your doctor's permission.
Miura's looking forward to it too.
Okay.
I'll go.
I want to go!
I'll definitely go!
YEAR TWO, CLASS B
THREE DAYS UNTIL THE FESTIVAL
Have a look at my latest teru-teru bozu.
I may just be a genius.
Are the preparations going well?
I'm sad I can't see you two until then,
but that just makes me more excited.
Are you okay?
This will make things easier.
Hang in there.
I'm fine.
This is all so I can go to that festival.
Wow!
Party of two!
Oh, Akito!
Hello.
Enjoy the festival, okay?
I will.
What's this?
- Leave them be!
- Akito?
Right this way.
- Huh?
- Get back to work!
- Was that Eri?
- Yeah.
I see...
She's lovely.
You think?
Of course!
- The cupcakes look good.
- Yeah.
They look good together.
I know what you mean.
It's like they have
their own private world.
I'm a little jealous.
- Whoa!
- Zombies!
- Both of you, then?
- Yes.
Say cheese!
- One more.
- Now that's cute.
Sorry.
Can I rest for a moment?
Are you okay?
I've had too much fun.
It's hard to breathe.
Want some water?
Yeah.
Hello?
Haruna?
It's time to come back.
Better call it a day.
I'm sure you're tired.
I'm fine.
Just a little longer.
Save it for next time.
There won't be a next time.
Your mom?
This is Akito.
I'll make sure she gets back safe.
Please let her stay.
As the chief nurse,
I want her back right away.
But...
as her mother...
I'll let it slide.
Thank you very much.
SNOW WHITE IN DA HOUSE
I use cleanser, and I always wash
my face before putting on makeup.
- Of course, milky lotion is a must...
- Don't break the fourth wall!
Slash!
Snow White...
Are you all right, Snow White?
My prince!
You saved me!
Thank you so much!
Haruna!
You made it.
You really came.
Thank you, Ayaka.
You were as pretty as can be.
Thanks.
In my mind, you were up there with me.
- Okay, everyone! Let's take a picture!
- Gather over here!
- See you later, okay?
- Yeah.
- Ayaka, get in the middle.
- There!
No, you're here.
Huh? Where's Takada?
- Where'd he go?
- That's scary.
Thank you.
That was a dream I thought
would never come true.
Let's go to the beach next time.
You wanted to go
to the place in your sketchbook, right?
I hope there really is a next time.
The beach I drew...
is where my dad was taking me on that day.
We never got there.
Excuse me! Please let us off!
- I'm gonna move now.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Climb on.
We made it in time.
Thank you.
Hey...
If I die...
will you kiss me
and bring me back to life?
I wanted to experience love too.
Just once...
I wanted to fall deeply in love.
I'd fall in love with them...
and them with me.
I wanted to make someone happy that way.
I'm sorry. There's nothing...
I can't change anything.
What's wrong?
Are you crying?
Sorry, the kiss thing was a joke.
Did it bother you that much?
It was a joke. Don't cry.
I...
There's something
I've been hiding from you.
But I thought it was better not to say it.
So...
Don't say it.
I only want to hear
happy thoughts right now.
In return...
I'll settle for you today.
Haruna... won't hold on much longer.
Make her final hours
something to cherish.
Hey, what are you drawing?
It's a secret.
Show me.
No.
Why not?
I want to see...
one of your drawings.
Huh?
It's not fair that you only look at mine.
Hey.
Will you
draw me?
I want you to draw my portrait.
You look beautiful, Haruna.
Thank you, Ayaka.
It's like you're my mortician.
No, this is more like bridal makeup.
See?
Thanks.
It's pretty tiring to hold the same pose.
Now I know how Mona Lisa felt.
You can lie down.
Hey.
Do you remember the day we met?
What made you want to talk to me?
Oh, that.
I was lost in thought,
and then I found it.
An angel.
What?
Laugh all you want,
but in the midst of all my bad luck,
it was as if I saw
an angel for the first time.
That's why.
And this angel I found
only had six months to live,
yet she wasn't afraid of dying at all.
I was impressed.
I really was amazed.
You're wrong.
That was the day my doctors told me
I had six months to live.
I always knew that day would come.
But when it did, I was so scared.
I could barely contain myself.
Such lovely colors.
Oh, I mean...
So when you spoke to me,
you were the one
who looked like a hero.
I...
I said I wanted to die soon, right?
At that time, I really felt that way.
But not now.
I don't want to die.
I want to live more.
I want to be with you...
and Ayaka more.
It doesn't have to be...
ten or twenty years.
One day more...
One minute, one second more...
I want to live longer.
I decided so after meeting you two.
So from now on, I'll fight every day.
If I don't die today, I win.
So...
even when it's painful...
you have to give it your all too, Akito.
Right.
Show me...
the drawing.
Akito...
I like the way you draw.
Um...
Please let me
do the operation.
I know it will be expensive,
and the chances of success
are low enough without my bad luck.
So it's likely to fail.
But I'd like to try.
Is it okay?
Yeah.
Of course it is.
One more thing.
I think you were right
to tell me about my diagnosis.
It helped me realize what's important.
You too, Natsumi.
For everything you've done and will do...
thank you.
Your luck is just fine.
You've got us as your family.
Right.
- Blood pressure is dropping.
- She needs intubation right away.
Haruna! Stay with me!
- HARUNA'S CONDITION HAS WORSENED.
- ON MY WAY.
Haruna, wake up already!
When you wake up,
I have something to tell you.
So...
hurry and open your eyes!
Wake up, Haruna...
Wake up!
Can you hear me? Do you understand?
- Bring an AED.
- Right.
Akito!
Why...
Why weren't you there?
Haruna was strong.
She woke up one last time.
And then,
she called your name.
This is for you.
Will you accept it?
It's the last thing she drew.
No, I couldn't.
I believe you...
deserve to have it.
She began drawing as a way...
to retreat from reality...
into a world of her own.
But after you came into her life...
I think she drew...
for you to see.
I wanted...
to tell her something.
But I couldn't.
I couldn't even be with her at the end.
I couldn't...
Dear Akito...
This place
is heaven for me now.
Thanks to you,
this place that held only pain
became somewhere
warm and bright.
In this place,
I probably smiled enough
for one whole life.
In this place,
I shed a life's worth of tears.
Though I once wanted to die quickly,
I now want to live as many days as I can.
Thanks to you...
I was truly happy.
That's why...
you have to live
long enough for both of us.
Become happier and happier
and draw pictures
more beautiful than ever.
Hey, what are you drawing?
It's a secret.
Then one day,
when you're an old man,
we'll meet again beyond the sky.
I look forward to that day.
When that happens,
I hope you won't mind
if I call you
my best friend.
Finally,
in return for the countless flowers,
I give these to you.
Mr. Hayasaka, you should feel sleepy soon.
Right.
Okay, change directions slowly.
Nice work.
Thank you.
You were really trying.
Will you be okay?
Yeah.
ENTRANCE EXAM RESULT: PASSED
Not bad.
Can we go to a hot spring
on the way home?
- What?
- A hot spring?
Please!
- Here.
- Thanks.
- Can I eat one now?
- Sure.
Akito, for you.
Thank you.
Hey Hayasaka, you alive?
Alive, but back in the hospital.
Again?
Oh, if it isn't Miss Gerbera!
Boyfriend back in the hospital?
Not my boyfriend. He's my arch enemy.
- Will it be five today?
- Yeah.
Or should I
make it six?
Five.
I see.
Too bad.
By the way,
six would look like this.
Is that...
The pictures?
They're my arrangements,
but someone else uploaded them.
The photos are really nice,
so I couldn't resist.
Hayasaka!
Hey, what are you painting?
The last artwork of my life.
No.
It's the first artwork
of the second life Haruna gave me.
So, how you feelin'?
It spread.
Spread?
They said the tumors
have spread to my spine.
Isn't that bad?
I imagine so.
I mean, isn't it really bad?
Probably.
No, I mean...
Forget it.
Look at this.
Are these the gerberas I gave Haruna?
Once I master the camera,
maybe I'll upload to social media.
She uploaded them.
The last update was in December.
And after that, there's this.
It's password-protected.
"To the boy
born in autumn."
We need the password though.
ENTER PASSWORD: "0405"
PASSWORD INCORRECT
It's not her birthday.
Gerberas...
ENTER PASSWORD: "GERBERA"
PASSWORD INCORRECT
ENTER PASSWORD: "3GERBERAS"
The story of how
the girl with six months to live
met the boy with one year to live.
What?
To the boy born in autumn...
I've decided to bind my feelings
with photos of the gerberas you gave me.
You're the first person
I ever met who was immune
to my magic spell.
That day on the roof,
you heard my diagnosis,
but you didn't act scared
or look at me with pity.
It was me who was surprised.
In hopes of running into you again,
I searched all over the hospital.
For your visits,
I would wait in the hall every day.
If I saw you coming,
I'd rush back into bed.
When I realized
you really would come every day,
I was so happy, I hyperventilated.
Haruna?
But when autumn began,
I learned your secret.
Cardiology?
He's dying?
Akito too?
She knew...
Despite that,
you kept quiet for my encouragement.
You used all the time you had left
for my sake, didn't you?
I'm sorry!
I wanted to reward your kindness,
so I played along.
I wanted things to be normal.
For the two of us,
normal moments
were a rare and precious thing.
For me,
these final six months
were the happiest time of my life.
You know,
I think our coming together
wasn't a coincidence.
It was meant to be.
I bet we were born
only so that we could meet.
Thinking that
got me through the inevitable pain.
I'm okay.
So don't be afraid, Akito.
I'll shoulder your pain.
And then
I'll die first
and watch over you from the sky.
Thank you for Ayaka too.
Stay friends with her, okay?
Me and Hayasaka?
- I told Ayaka the same.
- No way.
Are you sure?
Ayaka.
She may seem tough,
but she has a gentle heart,
and I worry about her.
If you hold each other up,
it'll be a lucky friendship.
As for what I didn't tell you
during the fireworks,
I'll keep that to myself.
You know...
I...
The truth is...
Akito, I lo...
But if by some twist of fate,
you find this page,
I want to believe
that after picking on me for so long,
it would be God's way
of leaving me with a parting gift.
Hey, I'll bet you knew
what a bouquet of six gerberas means.
When you've been
in the hospital this long,
you learn the sentiments
of most flowers.
So I choose to believe
that you'll know
what these three gerberas mean
when I give them to you.
Three gerberas mean
"I love you."
I rarely recommend three
for a bouquet though.
Still, it's a lovely sentiment.
THREE GERBERAS MEAN "I LOVE YOU."
You and Haruna both amaze me.
In such a narrow window of time,
you had such a pure romance.
If that's "a love that was short-lived,"
all my romances
are ones with a one-month expiration date.
But then,
by visiting you like this...
I've come to appreciate that devotion.
Tell me, Haruna...
What will he think when he wakes up?
Hayasaka...
Will you be mad?
Annoyed?
Or maybe
will you smile?
Hayasaka passed away
three and a half years
after his diagnosis.
For someone with bad luck,
I'd say he held out pretty long.
Right, Haruna?
Do you moisturize or anything?
Nothing at all.
Oh, really?
They're a little dry...
But to think you'd even die
on the same day?
You really do amaze me.
TO THE BOY BORN IN AUTUMN...
AKITO.10,10
Huh?
There's a reply.
Hayasaka?
Haruna, I hope you're well.
I may be joining you pretty soon.
I'm half-scared,
half-excited.
Thanks to you,
I was able to fight to the very end.
The black brushstrokes of this world
turned colorful in the end.
Enough to blind me.
Oh, and thanks for Miura.
She came to visit me often.
In fact, she was a big help.
Though when I'm gone, she'll be set free,
and I'm sure she'll be relieved.
P.S.
When I woke up just now,
there were three gerberas
painted on my nails.
It must have been Miura.
She probably doesn't know what it means,
so I'll tell her next time
and have a good laugh.
I do know, you idiot.
NIKA ART EXHIBITION SELECTION
AKITO HAYASAKA & HARUNA SAKURAI
"OUR SKY"
THE COLOR OF LOVE PROVIDES THE MEANING
OF LIFE AND ART - MARC CHAGALL
Subtitle translation by: Brad Plumb