♪ Illumination! ♪
Eh!
Hm?
Mm!
One, please.
All creatures great and small,
welcome to the Moon Theater.
Please take your seats.
The show is about to begin.
A flat?
Oh no!
Now I'll be late for the party.
No signal?
You gotta be kidding me.
Okay. Pull yourself together.
I mean, how hard can it be
to fix a stupid tire anyway?
There's a spare back here somewhere.
What?
My car! It's gone!
But… But… But that's impossible!
Hello?
Is someone there?
I'm here!
♪ It's close to midnight ♪
♪ And something evil's lurking
From the dark! ♪
♪ Under the moonlight ♪
♪ You see a sight
That almost stops your heart! ♪
Oh my gosh.
♪ You try to scream ♪
♪ But terror takes the sound
Before you make it! ♪
♪ You start to freeze ♪
♪ As horror looks you
Right between your eyes ♪
♪ You're paralyzed! ♪
♪ You hear the door slam ♪
♪ And realize
There's nowhere left to run! ♪
Cuckoo!
♪ You feel the cold hand ♪
♪ And wonder if you'll ever see the sun! ♪
♪ You close your eyes
And hope that this is just imagination ♪
Oh!
♪ Girl! ♪
Yeah!
♪ But all the while
You hear a creature creeping up behind ♪
♪ You're out of time! ♪
♪ 'Cause this is thriller! ♪
♪ Thriller night! ♪
♪ There ain't no second chance
Against the thing with forty eyes, girl! ♪
- ♪ Thriller! ♪
- ♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ Thriller night! ♪
♪ You're fighting for your life
Inside a killer thriller tonight! ♪
♪ Night creatures call ♪
♪ And the dead start to walk
In their masquerade! ♪
♪ Masquerade! ♪
♪ There's no escaping
The jaws of the alien this time! ♪
- ♪ This time ♪
- ♪ This is the end of your life! ♪
So, Moon, you coming with us
to Clay's Halloween party?
- Uh, that's tonight?
- Yeah-huh! Party time, baby!
- Are we taking the bus?
- Nah, I got my dad's truck.
- Cool!
- Let's go, Moon.
- Clay will be mad at us if we're late.
- I'm coming!
…the building has been destroyed,
and trees surrounding the site
flattened to the ground.
Everyone has been safely evacuated
from the laboratory,
though it is not yet known
what caused the mysterious explosion.
Ow.
Let's go, Moon!
In half a mile, take the second exit
and then go straight.
Whoa!
Sorry, folks, there's been an explosion
and a leak at the science lab.
- Is anyone hurt?
- No, everyone has been safely evacuated.
Officer, what is that stuff?
Beats me. I'm no scientist.
But until we get it under control,
this road is closed, okay?
Thank you, officer.
You folks take care now.
Aw, dang. My new boots.
Okay, like, wow.
This guy, like, totally knows
how to throw a party, am I right?
- No way.
- Wow! This is so cool.
- Where is everybody?
- Ah!
- Look at that.
- Amazing.
Clay, we're here!
Uh…
He's probably trying to scare us.
See? This is typical Clay.
Okay, Mr. Spookypants, you got us!
Yeah, very funny, Clay.
You can come out now.
Clay, we know you're in there.
Clay?
Ew!
Guys? I found the other party guests.
Uh-oh. This is not my kind of party.
♪ 'Cause this is thriller! ♪
♪ Thriller night! ♪
♪ And no one's gonna save you
From the beast about to strike! ♪
♪ You know it's thriller! ♪
♪ Thriller night! ♪
♪ You're fighting for your life
Inside a killer, thriller!
Yeah!
- ♪ Thriller! ♪
♪ Thriller night! ♪
♪ 'Cause I can thrill you more
Than any ghoul would ever dare try! ♪
- ♪ Thriller! ♪
- ♪ Whoo-hoo! ♪
♪ Thriller night! ♪
♪ So let me hold you tight ♪
♪ And share a killer, thriller
Chiller, thriller here tonight! ♪
♪ Thriller! ♪
♪ Thriller night! ♪
♪ 'Cause I can thrill you more
Than any ghoul would ever dare try ♪
- ♪ Thriller! ♪
- ♪ Whoo-hoo! ♪
♪ Thriller night! ♪
♪ So let me hold you tight
And share a killer, thriller! Ow! ♪
Mr. Moon, run!
It's okay, Miss Crawly. We're safe now.
Miss Crawly? What… What's going on?
Oh, Mr. Moon,
I think you must have hit your head.
Ow. Yeah. I think you may be right.
Are you feeling well enough
to go to the party, sir?
Party? What?
Everybody's waiting outside
in the car for you.
Of course. The party!
Thank you, Miss Crawly, I'm fine!
Come on, let's go!
Remind me to fix those shelves, will you?
Yes, Mr. Moon.
Ow.