No!
Yesterday, at the abandoned market
Jiati Old Town...
...a shooting incident has occurred.
Police arrived at the scene...
...and found a car
which was overturned due to an accident.
- Hello, Bro Kang!
- Hello.
- Bro!
- Three passengers inside were shot,
- two dead, one missing.
- Bro!
- In addition, at the scene of the incident...
This is the money for this month.
It's all here.
Take it for yourself.
Thank you, Bro Kang!
According to police,
Don't be weak tomorrow!
Do your job well.
Good.
Thank you, Bro Kang!
- ...who are mother and child.
- Thank you, Bro Kang!
...who are mother and child.
While the missing man...
...is a husband and a father
from the victim,
named Bai An.
Based on the evidence found,
Bai An is suspected to be one of the
the main perpetrator in this incident.
Hello, Kun Tai!
Why haven't you arrived yet?
I've arrived with the money!
Hello?
Why are you silent?
...named Kun Tai...
...38 years old.
Before being killed,
Kun Tai has a history...
...violent crime
which is quite long.
He is also wanted by the police
on the case...
...the persecution that
causing death.
Why did you kill?
my wife and children?
Kun Tai was already dead with
several gunshot wounds.
You want to know the reason?
Follow me.
Come here,
don't grill the fish,
roast the person behind me.
Okay, Boss.
Come on.
Boss! Boss!
It doesn't matter.
Continue eating.
Okay, Boss.
Come on, cheers!
Why?
Why my family?
All of you,
whoever killed him...
...will get money
from Kun Tai.
Attack!
- Everything!
- Hiya!
Attack together!
MAISHI GROUP
Why?
Why did you kill my family?
I'm just doing my job
according to the boss's orders.
Your boss is He Yinghao, right?
Where can I find it?
I really don't know.
Okay.
Okay,
what I know there is a driver.
The driver who serves the boss.
We have met several times.
He once said to me.
He Yinghao picks up his daughter...
...to Jiati Middle School every day.
Tell me the plate number!
JIATI-6677
STRIKING RESCUE
JIATI INTERNATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL
Mother!
LAOS ECONOMY
DEVELOPING RAPIDLY
Hey, little princess,
in international schools,
there are wrestling lessons too.
Wow!
Your school life
very interesting!
None of your business.
Where is my father?
Your father is on business.
He's already home waiting for you.
At home.
Don't you like it?
I came here just like that
what you want, right?
You don't have to come either.
I can go home by myself.
Come on.
Princess, please get in the car!
Overacting!
Excuse me.
You are okay?
Watch the road!
Excuse me.
Let's go!
- Ting, you're home.
- Is that so?
- Hurry up and sit down and eat!
- Yes, I understand.
Take it easy,
we will definitely continue
support you guys next year.
Excuse me!
Put down your chopsticks.
There are rules when eating.
Look at your clothes!
Go change your clothes.
Ting, I'll accompany you to change clothes.
Leave him alone.
Yinghao,
company logistics department
having problems.
Police received a report that...
...drugs were found in
our shipment of goods.
Why is this so?
Drug crimes in Jiati
always rampant.
I suspect there are some employees
at the company...
...who secretly work together
with drug dealers.
I am always responsible
on security check,
so you mean I have a problem?
I'm not saying that
you have a problem,
but for local staff,
we can't be sure.
I'll find out.
Lu Ping.
If news about drugs spreads,
local government must
will be under great pressure.
At that time our company
will face big problems...
...regarding logistics inspection exceptions.
You handle this.
Good.
Mr. He,
I think our group...
Ting Ting!
What happened at school?
There isn't anything.
There isn't anything?
Then why are your clothes like that?
Spilled paint.
It's that simple?
Hmm.
Yes, that's all.
Then why the principal
call me...
...and begged me not to
defund schools?
How would I know?
The principal did not say
anything to me.
Yinghao,
maybe there is a misunderstanding?
What misunderstanding?
The principal has contact me.
And you still lie?
Those who start
bothered me first!
Is that how you become a student?
Huh?
By fighting?
Who taught that to you?
You said it yourself,
when faced with bullying
and injustice,
must dare to fight!
And about fighting,
I learned from him.
Sir...
Anyway,
it's not as safe here as in our country.
Girls must study
self-defense to protect yourself.
I told you to fight,
not causing trouble!
You even dare
threaten the principal?
You know how much money
that I spent...
...so you can go to school here?
You have no idea at all!
I don't care if your father
is He Yinghao.
In this school,
you still have to listen to me.
He doesn't care who is right
or wrong.
He only defended local students.
You are openly challenging
in the classroom.
Fight with other people.
Even carrying weapons.
Just because of your father
is He Yinghao,
doesn't mean you can
breaking the rules.
You should know,
I can get you out
from school right now.
I don't like this school or Jiati.
I don't even want to stay here!
This is your house.
Where are you going?
This is not my house.
My house is where my mother is!
I hate this place.
I hate you too.
You don't have to pretend
be a good father.
You are getting more and more impudent!
Am I being rude?
Since I entered the house,
have you ever asked
why am I fighting?
No!
Lu Ping vegetarian
and do not eat meat.
Have you ever cared?
Not really!
Today you promised to accompany me
to the temple to pray for my mother,
but did you keep your promise?
Not really!
You don't care about anyone!
You only care about
yourself and your business!
Ting Ting, stop.
You don't care at all...
...what is really
needed by others.
Yinghao,
calm down.
Ting Ting has grown up.
Don't always scold him
like this.
Lu Ping,
book me a flight
earliest for tomorrow.
I will go home to
meet his mother.
Yinghao,
return to our country?
But business in Jiati
still need supervision.
If you weren't here,
I am worried...
LU PING - WAREHOUSE - HE YINGHAO
NEWS CLIPPING ABOUT LAOS
KUN TAI
No!
Darling!
LU PING - WAREHOUSE - HE YINGHAO
Yinghao He!
Wow!
All our stuff has disappeared.
The police have confiscated everything.
The man being hunted in the news,
her name is Bai An, who did it.
He barged in
and kill all our members.
Maybe he was the one who called the police.
Brother Long!
You lost the item.
Do you know what the consequences are?
Please forgive me!
I will replace it.
I will replace with anything.
Is your life worth anything?
20 million dollars?
Brother Long!
Where is my stuff?
There is a problem with the transport chain
He Group.
The police have confiscated
all our goods.
Where is that trash Tai Kun?
Just keep the goods Can't.
What's the point of me keeping him?
Tai Long, listen!
If my father hadn't insisted on letting you go
stay alive as his dog,
I threw you away a long time ago...
Tomorrow meet He Yinghao.
Find Bai An for me.
Ting Ting,
come here.
Ting Ting.
Uh...
My little girl is all grown up.
What did you say last night?
truly extraordinary.
Today we go home to see your mother.
If your mother saw you now,
he will definitely be very happy.
Yinghao,
The police just gave the news.
What is it?
Police have checked for drugs
which was confiscated from a logistics warehouse.
The results of the examination showed
drugs this time...
...has the same composition as
which was discovered three years ago.
After private negotiations
with the police,
this problem is temporary
will not be published.
Hmm.
When I'm not around,
meet the higher ups on my behalf
and convey my thanks.
Don't worry about the cost.
Good.
GOOSE CITY - AIRPORT
Ting Ting!
Your father actually
care about you so much,
it's just that he's not good at it
show it.
Did my father tell you to?
say this?
You probably don't know why he
trust Lu Ping so much, right?
He is most worried about you growing up.
without a mother's love.
Hey, Wu,
can you learn to be quiet?
The police have determined...
...Bai An as the prime suspect...
How do you drive?
- Give compensation!
- You're blocking my way on purpose!
- This is your fault!
- Quickly provide compensation!
- Get out of the way!
- Give it first!
- Move quickly!
- Can't!
There they are!
Attack!
Step back!
Get down!
Help!
Let me go!
You are okay?
Capture alive!
Down!
What is this?
What happened?
Do not move!
Ting Ting!
We need to talk.
- Ting Ting!
- Let's go!
- Don't hurt Ting Ting!
- Fast!
- Wu Zheng!
- Hurry up!
- Save Ting Ting!
- Fast!
Mr. He!
Father!
Go out!
Let me go!
Rubbish!
Take Ting Ting away first!
Fast!
Good!
Let's go.
Mr. He!
Where is Ting Ting?
Ting Ting is fine.
- Go!
- Fast!
Catch him!
Let me go!
Wu Zheng!
FRESH
JIATI 57
I've caught him!
Follow me or die here.
Get in the car!
Come on, come on!
Reject drugs, clean up Jiati!
Demonstrations are useless.
The only way is to eradicate
drug criminals to the end,
especially criminal groups
led by Clay.
Its existence has become
the biggest tumor in Jiati!
Mr. Council Member,
every time you mock me on TV,
it really bothers me.
That's why I came
meet you today...
...bringing gifts.
Please enjoy,
free!
You really don't want to
respect me, okay?
Children!
Stay cool!
Mother!
Lan!
If only you had obeyed,
this is done.
Mr. Clay.
Go away from here!
Please,
let go of my son.
I am willing to do
anything for you.
Mr. Clay.
Let's do it a game.
Only one of them
who can survive.
Who dies, who lives,
you decide.
Or they both die together.
Xiao Di,
Sorry!
You are her brother.
Little Big!
This is your father,
who always talks
about goodness, morality,
but shot his own son.
Go to hell!
Take him and
forced to take drugs,
make him a drug courier.
Boss, Mr. He has arrived.
Chairman He Yinghao!
I hope you don't mind
brought in this way.
You kidnapped me
because of the drugs, right?
Not only that.
I have a big gift for you.
This is a company
local logistics in Jiati.
If you sign this,
everything is yours.
As for the 20 million dollars,
I can delete it,
as long as we work together!
Isn't this a great gift?
what you always dreamed of?
AGREEMENT
EQUITY TRANSFER
In Jiati,
only my company is free
from inspection.
You must want that.
Right?
I will not sign this,
even if you kill me.
Chairman He,
You are more precious to me when you are alive.
If I kill you,
He Group will not
it means something to me.
There is no point.
But your daughter is different.
Bastard!
Don't hurt my daughter!
Come on!
I've met you before.
At the school gate.
You...
You are a fugitive
that's in the news!
...in this shooting case.
Further investigation
still ongoing.
You killed your wife and child.
Shut up!
Who killed them is your father.
That's not possible!
You are not at all
don't know your family, do you?
I won't believe it
on a fugitive.
Without me,
You were dead a long time ago.
This is none of your business.
Get out of here!
Go!
Thank You,
you saved me!
Wu Zheng!
What really happened?
Don't ask first!
Listen to me carefully.
Did Ting Ting call you?
or have you returned?
No!
What really happened?
Most likely we will be replied
by drug cartels.
Mr. He has been arrested.
The others are all dead.
Then what about Ting Ting?
Wu Zheng,
you are really useless!
Your job is only keep safe,
but not a single person
can you protect!
Shut up now!
I'm the one who lost them,
and I will risk my life
to find it again.
Check CCTV footage immediately
at the gate of Jiati school.
The time was yesterday afternoon.
I stopped a man who wears a hat.
Who is it?
You don't need to know.
Please send the CCTV footage immediately
to me.
Wu Zheng, I warn you,
don't act rashly!
The police have arrived.
This time the travel route is only
notify your captain.
Who else knows?
Only the captain knows.
He just told us
just before leaving.
Brother Lu Ping!
It's me, He Ting.
Ting Ting!
Ting Ting, where are you now?
Are you okay?
Nothing happened, right?
I'm fine.
I don't know where this is.
Good.
Listen to me carefully.
From now on,
don't trust anyone.
Including Wu Zheng, Yes, right?
I'm not sure now either.
But before leaving,
only he knows your journey.
Ting Ting,
now hurry up and find a place
safe and hide.
I'll pick you up soon.
Understand?
Understand.
Help!
Are you Chinese?
I am He Yinghao's daughter.
I was kidnapped,
just managed to escape.
He Yinghao's daughter?
You are safe now.
I will take you
to the police station.
Come on!
I just got in touch my family.
They will pick me up.
Don't worry.
Once at the police station,
I will contact you soon
your family.
Come on!
Be careful!
Hello, sir.
I am patrol officer PDJ-663.
This is the daughter of the He Group.
Very good!
We received a report,
and the police are looking for him on the streets.
We have everything arranged here.
Don't worry.
Please come back.
Okay sir!
To Headquarters!
Do not move!
You can't run away anymore.
You are worth a million dollars.
Hey!
I just need an answer.
Who told you to?
catch it?
There are people,
who offers prizes.
The entire black market knows
he is worth a million dollars.
But I don't know who
who paid for it.
How did you find me?
We track the location of this pay phone
and found you.
He's dead?
Just fainted.
Let's go!
Why are you there?
Excuse me!
Are you okay?
Since we met at the school gate,
have you started watching me?
I don't know what to believe anymore
to whom.
The kidnappers have already
prepare everything.
But only Wu Zheng
who knows the route.
Also Sister Lu Ping.
Tonight I just contacted him.
We can work together.
Finish your food, then we go!
Don't you want revenge?
But you don't even know
where is my father.
I will find it.
Then why don't you just ask me?
What do you mean?
I want to find it too.
Because we have the same goal,
why can't we work together?
You know what that means
if I find it.
I know.
I'm sure you will need me.
But you have to take care of me
stay safe.
About what happens after we
found it, we'll see later.
Do you really want to
I killed him?
Why?
My mother died because of drugs.
Me and my father
hate drugs the most.
I'm sure my father is not a person
who killed your family.
I'm also sure you're not a person
who kills without reason.
Otherwise you won't
saved me twice.
I will not bring
someone who is troublesome.
No, I'm not a problem.
I am the only clue
that you have now.
IDENTIFICATION CARD
CRIMINAL POLICE
I found the person you were looking for.
Her name is Bai An.
He is a fugitive.
Was he the one who kidnapped Ting Ting?
Not him.
Hear!
From now on,
if He Ting contacts you,
tell me immediately.
Or,
you will endanger him.
What do you mean?
I'm on my way
pick up Ting Ting now.
I...
I didn't have time to tell you.
No need to come.
He is no longer there.
This must have something to do with it.
with drugs.
Before leaving,
I heard my father talking
with them.
Three years ago, my father fired me.
a group of employees...
...for smuggling drugs.
Police check for drugs...
...which was confiscated from a logistics warehouse.
The test results show...
...this time the drug has a content
the same as three years ago.
I heard them all
already out of prison...
...and become a desperate fugitive.
For money,
they are willing to do anything.
This is a logistics point
where they work.
On the supervisor's computer,
there should still be their data.
Are you sure
those who kidnapped him?
At least they are sure
know something.
I'll come in and switch
security concerns.
You follow after.
Help!
Help me!
What happened?
I am He Yinghao's daughter.
I managed to escape from the kidnapper.
Come in quickly!
Based on the latest reports
from the police,
two bodies found at the scene.
One of which is
a Jiati patrol officer,
while others...
...is a perpetrator
who disguised himself as a police officer.
However, the police did not find...
...the existence of the girl
from the kidnapped He family.
More details about this case...
...cannot be expressed yet
by the police.
Miss He Ting,
how did you get away
from the kidnappers?
I will introduce you to him.
Huh?
Who's that?
Want to die, huh?
The person who is called
This "Betel Nut"...
...is a small leader of
group of employees who were fired.
I remember his nickname very well.
They had a relationship.
Tell me,
where can I find it?
I don't understand
What did he say.
Where can found the "Betel Nut"?
Lese slum market.
The place is full of criminals,
even the police are afraid to get involved.
Going there would be suicide.
Your fate will be the same
like that phone,
if you dare to tell others.
What...
What did he say?
I don't understand...
Do you really like this bag?
Of course.
This is a birthday present from my mother.
Even though the color is a bit garish,
but I will continue to carry it.
Aren't all girls like pink?
That's just a stereotype.
What girls should like
pink color?
Seriously, it's outdated!
You are adults,
when was the last time
really care about others?
Happy birthday!
I love you, Dad.
Finally I have my own phone!
Seriously, Dad?
Neon pink that glows?
My friends will definitely
laugh at me.
LESE MARKET
Here he is!
It looks like these people
what we are looking for.
Give me the money!
I'll go in there.
And you wait here.
Wait.
These people are just
low-class dealers.
They are cowards
and always be alert.
As soon as there is a sign of danger,
they will disappear
with his group.
If they run away,
the harder it is for us to find it.
I'd better go in.
They probably don't know me.
I'm not a threat to them.
No.
You can't do this.
It's too dangerous.
I can protect me.
Yes, right?
Bald!
Take me to the "Betel Nut."
Who are you, kid?
Go away from here!
I am He Yinghao's daughter.
I'm worth a million dollars.
Boss, boss!
Yes, it is him!
TARGET
Follow me.
Let's go.
What do you see?
What are you waiting for?
Quickly drag him out
and cut open his stomach!
Before the drugs changed
so shit!
Take as much as
that can be saved!
Check!
Do not touch me!
Let him in.
Give it back!
Shut up!
You can't bring him in.
I return it after you go out.
So you really are He Yinghao's daughter.
So, son,
you came here alone.
What do you want?
I came here,
to offer a deal.
I want to hire you for
save my father.
Why should I help you?
Your father used to be
ruined my life.
He fired me and made me
go to jail.
If you want to help me,
I will pay you two million dollars.
Wait.
Where is Bai An?
I really don't know.
We are just co-workers.
After his family was murdered,
he suddenly disappeared.
Hello, boss!
We found it.
He is near you.
The person who kidnapped your father
named Clay.
He is a big boss, drug lord!
And you want me to fight it
for only two million dollars?
USING A KNIFE
TO CUT OFF THE VICTIM'S CRUELTY
Actually, about Clay...
Your father should know better
than me.
Over the past three years,
Clay's belongings...
...always sent via logistics channels
your company.
He knows better.
Impossible.
How could my father be involved?
with the drug lord?
Okay,
I won't make things difficult for you.
If you could take me home
safely,
two million dollars will
be yours.
I don't need two million dollars.
All I need to do is catch you.
And your family has to pay
as much as I want.
Once I get the money,
I'll hand you over to Clay.
You are like a money machine
who came to my door himself.
NO SIGNAL
Do not come close!
Bastard!
Catch him!
Let me go!
Screw you!
Do you know how much?
the price of this drug?
Which hand just now throw it?
Hold him!
I will cut off his hand
right now!
You're not afraid that Clay will
sue you?
Afraid?
But what I fear more is
live without money!
If I die, I can reincarnate.
But as long as I live,
nothing can stop me
to get money.
Unlucky!
Bai An!
You are okay?
Damn it!
Do not come close!
One more step forward
then I'll kill him!
You're lucky this time.
Next time,
kick between the legs,
don't bite!
Okay?
Where can I find Clay?
Okay,
out of town.
Clay has a production center
drugs outside the city.
Your father should be there.
The headquarters is closed.
The only person who can
in and out...
...is a courier named
Uncle Jiu.
He is one of the
Clay's confidant.
He's out of town.
There is an old hotel,
Jiati Hotel.
That's his territory.
If you go there,
that means suicide.
Come on!
Come on, quickly!
Let's go!
Jump!
I can't!
I'm not Tony Jaa!
Stop right there!
Run!
Kill him!
Leave him to me.
I will make sure
you died intact.
Good!
I like it.
Sadly,
you ruined my makeup.
Bai An!
Go!
Stop!
Stop right there!
Let me go!
Let go!
Ting Ting, come here!
Ting Ting!
What are you doing?
From now on, don't trust anyone.
Ting Ting!
Hey Ting!
Why did you run?
Bai An!
Don't kill him!
Ting Ting!
You can't go with him.
He's a fugitive!
Bai An!
Let's go!
I will kill you!
You are okay?
I will take you to the doctor
Now!
No!
We can't go to the hospital.
This place is still controlled
drug dealers.
We can't do that.
If this continues, you could die.
I have an idea.
ANIMAL CLINIC
Is anybody there?
Open the door!
Yes, yes, I'm coming.
Why knock so loudly!
It is late!
You don't want to
let people sleep, huh?
Doctor, please save him.
If you want treatment,
why not go to the hospital?
Look at this place.
This is a clinic for animals.
I am a veterinarian.
Veterinarians are also doctors.
Not just saving animals.
But it can also cure humans.
Relax, relax.
It will hurt a little.
Hold on a minute.
Okay.
ANIMAL CLINIC
According to my observations,
his condition should not be any more
in danger.
But why is he still cold sweats?
Infected wounds make it
having a fever.
So that's a symptom of the infection.
Give him some medicine.
Look at this.
I have medicine for cats, dogs,
even for pigs.
So...
Thank You.
It should be.
May I ask, how?
How to get to Old Jiati Motel?
What?
Oh, that's easy.
Exit here, turn right.
Skip three blocks.
At the crossroads.
But as far as I know,
that place...
...not a good place.
This...
Save lives.
Take this.
If you dare to tell others,
I will kill you.
Infinite kindness.
Magic touch!
OLD JIATI MOTEL
There are people?
Want to stay overnight, huh?
Show your identity!
According to the latest reports
from our station,
girl from the He family
previously missing, He Ting,
found in the market Lese slums.
He was seen with Bai An,
who is currently a fugitive from the police
in the case of the shooting.
Police suspect that...
- Older brother...
- ...the suspected kidnapper of He Ting...
- My father is sick.
- ...most likely Bai An.
We came here for medical treatment.
Our wallets and identities were stolen.
There is only a little money left.
Please help us.
Regarding this incident, the
police stated that... Please help us.
Regarding this incident,
the police stated that...
You two are invisible
like father and son.
Associated with local drug cartel network.
You two are invisible like father and son.
Associated with
local drug cartel network.
The police suspect that
Bai An was also involved...
I understand now.
Your mother is a foreigner, right?
Correct.
My mother is a foreigner.
My father is a local.
Usually,
standard room 20 dollars per night.
But you have no identity.
I'm in a dilemma.
All members of his family,
including his wife and children,
become victims and some
reported missing.
Upstairs, turn right.
Thank You.
Jiati police chief...
...in a press conference
States that...
...related to the brutal action
this drug network,
police in Ballyvina will
take firm steps...
...with a zero tolerance approach
against drug crimes...
...and do
massive operation...
Hello, Uncle Jiu!
...to prosecute the perpetrators.
The person appears.
When do we look for Uncle Jiu?
Let's just wait.
He will definitely show up.
This is the territory.
Eat this.
My mother taught me,
eat something sweet when injured
will make you feel better.
- Bai An!
- Yes?
I want to ask you something.
Please.
Is my father really drug dealer?
Why?
Why ask all of a sudden?
I don't know.
I used to trust him so much.
But now it's not just you,
even the "Betel Nut" said so.
I don't know what to believe
to whom else.
It seems like my father is not a person
that I have known all this time.
Bai An!
If...
I mean, if...
If my father really
hurt your family,
can you promise me one thing?
Bai An!
The man who was still sleeping...
...is my father.
He has to work overtime this time,
so can't go home with us.
I have to go to the airport.
I have prepared dinner for you.
Your favorite Thai fried rice.
Just bring it to the office
and heat before eating.
This...
Father,
Mother...
Mother, and...
...I!
Let's go.
Okay, let's go!
Kill him!
Fast!
Where is Clay's drug production base?
Say it!
In the forest near the Mei River port.
All drugs are shipped from there.
I know you are good at fighting,
but you better forget about this.
Police can control ordinary people,
but they couldn't catch him.
You can't do it get out alive.
Bai An!
You are okay?
I found Clay.
Let's go!
Finally I found it.
I can not wait...
...to return
all these wounds to your body.
Bai An!
Save him.
Ting Ting, are you okay?
Save Bai An!
Ting Ting, come with me!
I will bring Bai An with me.
Are you crazy?
He wants to kill your father!
Bai An!
Let's go!
Leave this place quickly.
Go!
Do not move!
Hand over the goods!
Everything is here.
Please don't hurt us.
No!
Darling...
Do not leave me, Darling!
Please...
No...
How are you?
Stop!
You are crazy!
If it wasn't for Wu Zheng,
we would be dead by now.
How did you find us?
You guys stay at the hotel
and put up resistance,
of course you have been detected.
Now news about you guys
has spread widely on the black market.
Previously,
my men reported to me
that Ting Ting called Lu Ping.
I tracked it via GPS.
But I came too late.
On site,
I just found fake police corpse.
Then,
I am also like you,
trying to find
Mr. He's whereabouts.
I even investigated former employees
who became a smuggler after being fired.
Then I found the "Betel Nut".
Captain!
We found Miss He there
in the hands of the "Betel Nut".
After that,
you know yourself what happened.
What is this place?
This is my safe house.
You are good at fighting.
It looks like you have
an unusual past.
Oh yeah, I'm returning this.
Who let you touch my stuff?
I accidentally.
It fell off by itself.
Let's go find your father.
This place is safe.
Wu Zheng will try
find my father.
You have to heal your wounds.
Bai An!
Can you stop?
act rashly?
The drug dealers are very powerful.
You're alone and still hurting.
It's like courting death.
Why when I
saved you many times...
...from the hands of drug dealers,
you're not against me?
Since the beginning,
You're just using me.
Now you have it new protector,
you don't need me anymore.
Our cooperation has ended.
That is not what I mean.
I'm just worried about you.
What you are worried about
is your father.
I've heard it all
about your father.
I will investigate it.
In fact,
Yinghao He killed my family.
My wife works at He Group
for eight years.
But some time ago,
suddenly he wanted to go home
to his country.
Darling,
why do you look weird today?
What is it?
Just tell me.
You can always trust me.
Okay?
There isn't anything.
I just want to take a leave.
We will wait for you at home.
Only then did I know,
my wife found evidence
drug smuggling by the He Group.
Because of that, he was killed.
It's all here.
Please,
don't hurt us.
Where's the copy?
There isn't any.
This is a flash drive,
which contains the evidence.
Because of this thing,
he had the heart to kill my family.
That's not possible!
He hates drugs the most.
He will never
touching the forbidden item.
It's no use talking.
I found evidence of the contest prize
to kill my wife on Kun Tai's phone.
And all the instructions
leading to Yinghao He.
Hello, Kun Tai!
Why haven't you arrived yet?
I'm here with the money!
Before you kill me,
I will kill him first
and avenge my family.
Come on!
Kill me!
Do!
Wu Zheng!
Because you have save Ting Ting,
I won't kill you.
But never show up
in front of me again.
Bai An!
Is he okay?
After I succeeded
save your father,
I will definitely let it go.
Why is that, He Ting?
Why do I feel
you care more about him...
...than your own father?
Ting Ting,
Ting Ting!
You are okay?
I'm fine.
Hope!
How did he get here?
Why didn't you tell me?
when you find Ting Ting?
I'll sort it out
almost all corporate affairs.
You think they dare to oppose me?
Ting Ting,
come home with me.
No!
I'm not going home.
I will look for my father.
Your father?
- Has Mr. He been found?
- Yes.
People from Clay's group
who did it.
Maybe because of shipping
The last time drugs were confiscated by the police.
It's more than that.
There is a traitor in the company who
secretly smuggling drugs.
Bai An's wife was murdered
because I found this.
Traitor?
And he must be someone inside the company.
Do not move!
Hope!
What are you doing?
Put down your weapons!
Or I will kill them.
Get down!
Take them to Mr. Clay.
I'll take care of this.
Let me go!
Ting Ting!
Let go!
Hope!
Since when did you start?
It doesn't matter anymore, right?
Okay, Asa.
You better run
as far as possible later.
You don't have another chance.
Life and death are determined.
Fate has been determined.
Do not blame me.
I'm just making a living.
Who are you actually?
I'm just a lost ghost
who lost his family.
Why do you risk your life?
I received money from the He family
and fight for them.
Easy to understand, right?
And you?
I'm just like you.
I get paid too.
In my opinion, steak is the most delicious
when half cooked.
Undercooked tastes fishy,
overcooked, it's too hard.
I think life is like that too.
What is most important?
Determine the right time.
If we fight to the end,
everything went bad.
I have my own limits.
And have nothing else...
...to talk to you about
drug dealers.
Just making small talk, Mr. He.
Small talk can't be eaten,
also can't be used as money.
Oh yes, Mr. He,
My overseas clients are still waiting
my shipment with anxiety.
Ting Ting,
Are you okay?
Ting Ting?
Ting Ting!
What do you want?
Mr. He,
sign the contract.
I'm not just will let it go,
but also make sure there is no
trouble again with He Group.
If not...
I will sign.
As I expected,
Mr. He, you are a wise man.
Come on,
let's cheers!
For us,
hopefully our cooperation
runs well.
Come on, cheers!
Don't rush to celebrate just yet.
The person who made us
the lost item is Bai An.
He may look
like a regular warehouse keeper.
But before that,
he is a specialist
professional security.
What do you want to say?
Bai An,
even though he protects the girl,
actually he is looking for
opportunity to kill Yinghao He.
I lost 20 million dollars.
And this is all that can be done
you got it for me?
Tai Long, listen to me,
if my father had not decided to
keep you as his dog,
I threw you away a long time ago.
Even you are lower from a dog.
Clean this up.
We will be there soon
there will be guests coming.
Good.
- What are you doing?
- Have a little fun.
- Come on.
- You have to stay alert.
There's an intruder!
Shoot!
Catch him!
Find him!
Interesting.
A person filled with deep grudges
apparently took pity on his enemy's daughter.
What if we do the game?
Kill him.
Kill him, and I will
let the girl go.
Your game sucks!
Interesting.
Maybe we can be friends.
I don't have friends.
Let them go.
At least we will not be enemies.
Enemy?
I have many enemies,
you are not the only one.
Go!
Enter!
It seems like...
...I think too highly of you.
You don't even deserve it
become my enemy.
What a shame,
I failed to unite
your family at that time.
What are you talking about?
Before dying, That loser Clay...
...only care about booze
and women.
All this is my plan.
Including your family.
Just like this?
Now...
...you can be together again
with your family.
Bai An!
Go out!
Father!
Tai Long!
Let go of Ting Ting!
I can give you anything.
Okay?
Ting Ting!
In this world...
...who can survive...
...not just you guys!
Your burden is too heavy.
If you want to save him,
kill yourselves!
It's time!
Next time,
kick between his legs.
Don't bite!
Bai An!
I never hurt your family!
The one I hate the most
is a drug.
If they don't threaten me
with Ting Ting,
I will never give up.
I believe in your daughter,
I believe in you too.
Thank you, Bai An.
In fact, all this time,
you don't know how much
I envy your daughter.
For their sake,
you are willing to leave everything,
fight against the world.
So far,
I think I never got
such a father's love.
But now I realize,
My father is just like you.
He always loves me with all his heart,
even though he is not good at it
express it.
Every father wants to be
a hero to his daughter.
But when the time comes,
it is the most difficult time.
Bai An!
Thank You.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Have you ever seen a butterfly?
caught in a spider's web?
They thought they could be free
because their wings are scaly.
But sometimes
they still can't run.
I don't understand
What are you saying.
Playing with fire,
finally you will burnt.
Who are you really?
I have never seen you before
previously.
But you must have seen
my wife and child, right?
You think you can get away with it,
after everything you've done?
Since the first time
He Ting contacted you,
you've planned everything.
He Ting has been found.
You leaked it on purpose
the location to the fake police.
Kill him when he fails.
Then you tell Wu Zheng
about the fake police.
You want to take advantage of Wu Zheng
to track me and He Ting.
Miss Lu,
He Ting has been found.
He is in a safe house.
You prepared two plans.
Do not move!
Pretend to be caught.
So, whatever the outcome,
win or lose,
will not affect you.
But you forgot about me.
I saw you bribing Asa.
He always follows your orders,
same as the employees you use
to smuggle drugs.
I've been trapped for so long
in this spider web.
But, Tai Long,
he is not a spider
who trapped me.
It's He Yinghao
which becomes your net.
I have followed him
to this foreign land for ten years.
But I never can be myself.
It seems like forever I'm just trapped
in a woman's body.
He Ting will never accept me.
I...
I'm just a substitute.
So, Tai Long is taking advantage of you.
to get rid of Clay,
and you want to free yourself
from He Yinghao's control.
My wife, my family by chance,
he can get in your way,
so you destroyed my family.
If you want to blame,
blame your own family
for crossing my boundaries.
It seems like he rejected you.
We can't let him
destroy everything.
I just want to control
my own destiny.
What did I do wrong?
He Group will forever be
belong to the He family.
Even though I almost got it
everything,
then you destroy it!
This is all because of you guys!
My family shouldn't
accept all of it!
What are you doing?
No!
Wait!
Don't kill me!
Listen to me,
I am wrong.
I was totally wrong!
Forgive me!
I shouldn't hurt your child,
and also your wife.
Don't kill me!
Please forgive me!
Please!
Excuse me...
I shouldn't have...
My wife and my daughter
are good people.
...maybe they
will forgive you.
But...
I will never.
Money!
I can give you a lot of money!
As much as you want!
Don't kill me!
Please, don't kill me!
This is all He Yinghao's fault!
He's the one who forced me to do this!
I have no choice!
Impossible...
There is a Chinese proverb
who said:
"Disaster that comes from the sky
still can be avoided,
but a self-made disaster,
there is no way out."
You are the one...
...destroy your own life.
Do not do it.
Don't kill me!
You have one minute
for a farewell greeting.
No...
Don't...
Do not leave me!
Don't!
Yinghao, do you hear me?
Sorry, Yinghao...
Sorry, Ting Ting...
This is all my fault.
I apologize...
I...
I want too much.
This is all my fault.
I shouldn't have done that
All of these.
Can you forgive me?
Ting Ting?
The person who is still sleeping...
...is my father.
He had to work overtime this time,
so he can't come home with us.
Let's go to the airport.
I have prepared dinner for you.
Your favorite Thai fried rice.
Just bring it to the office
and heat before eating.
Father...
Dad, then?
Mother!
So?
I!
Okay, let's go to the airport!
AFTER THAT, BAI AN VOLUNTARILY
SURRENDER YOURSELF AND BRING...
...EVIDENCE TO THE PARTIES
BALIVINA POLICE.
WITH THE SUPPORT OF VARIOUS EVIDENCE,
CLAY CRIMINAL GROUP SUCCESSFULLY...
...COMPLETELY DESTROYED
BY THE POLICE.
LU PING INVOLVED IN THE GROUP
CLAY CRIMINAL IN DRUG TRADE.
ALL HE GROUP EMPLOYEES WHO
POLICE INVOLVED IN SMUGGLING.
BAI AN RECEIVES SANCTIONS
LAW FOR ILLEGAL ACTS.
HE GROUP FULFILLS ITS PROMISE TO DELIVER
AID TO THE REPUBLIC OF BALIVINA.