Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
(Rustling)
(Sniffing)
Oh...
Hmm...
Whoa.
(Gasps)
Oh...
(Grunting)
(Screaming)
Wherever did you come from?
Well, you're here now.
- (Burps)
- (Chuckles)
And remember, little one,
if you ever get lost again,
just roar and I'll roar right back.
(Roaring)
That's right.
I'll hear you
however far away you are.
Hmm.
Hmm? Huh.
Er...
(Photo booth jingles)
'Thank you for using Photo-Me.'
Oh, not at all.
Thank you for having me.
'Please note that head wear
is not permitted.'
Oh, beg your pardon.
'Please note that head wear
is not permitted.'
Um...
Ha. Hmm.
'Please position your face
within the red circle.'
Red circle, right, um...
'Commencing photos
in three, two, one...'
(Mumbles)
(Camera shutter clicks)
- Oh, no! Wait!
- (Camera shutter clicks repeatedly)
Oh, no... no, no, no, no!
These aren't mine.
'You have paid for 12... 24...
48 photos.'
Mm-hmm.
Thank you. Keep the change!
- Hmm... Huh?
- (Cooing)
(Paddington) 'Dear Aunt Lucy,
'I am writing to you
with some very important news!'
- It's arrived!
- Special delivery.
(Gasps) Thank you.
How wonderful.
Your very own passport.
So now you can
"Pass Freely Without Let Or Hindrance".
'Aunt Lucy, I am now "Officially British"!'
- And we all chipped in to buy you a gift.
- Oh?
Well, Paddington, no British gentleman
should be without an umbrella.
And not just any brolly.
The Windsorman Deluxe,
London's finest!
Oh! Thank you very much.
(All gasp)
Goodness, that's quite an umbrella.
(Thunder rumbling)
- Oh, bottoms!
- London! There you go.
(Paddington) 'There have been a few
other changes at Windsor Gardens
'since you were last here.
'Judy is applying to university,
a process known as "flying the nest".
'Mrs Brown is helping.
'This involves visiting
a place called a "campus".'
And this is the common room.
(Paddington) 'Apparently, you have
to take a parent with you...'
- Really fun here, isn't it?
- (Paddington) '...so there's someone to cry.'
I'm so sorry.
(Paddington) 'Jonathan, on the other hand,
rarely leaves his room.
'He spends most of his time "chillin'".
The G is silent.
'Now, he's put a lot of effort
into doing as little as possible,
'which is why he's invented
"The Bicy-chill"...
'..."The Gobsleigh"...
'...and his most prized creation...
"The Snack Hack"...
'...patent pending.'
You know, we we're just saying
maybe it's time to take these ingenious
gizmos out of the bedroom
and into the real world.
- To say, a... a trade fair?
- (Jonathan) Hmm...
It could really open some doors.
(Paddington) 'Mrs Brown says,
"It's brilliant that the kids have grown up",
'because now she's got lots of time
for her new art project.'
"The Sofa Years"?
Do you remember when our whole family
could all fit on one sofa?
(Giggling and chattering)
I didn't finish a crossword
in ten years.
What happens next?
(Paddington) 'Mr Brown is very busy
at his insurance firm at the moment
'because he's got a new boss,
an American.'
Four 150 years now, Riskworth &amp; Hazardsby
has been assessing risk.
Our Risk Manuals contain analysis
of every risk in the known world,
itemised, categorised, alphabetised
and professionally bound.
- These triple laminated...
- Throw them away.
- But they're triple laminated.
- (Wind whooshing)
Henry, if wanna succeed here,
you need to stop avoiding risk...
...and instead
you need to start embracing it!
Your latte, Madison.
If you wanna work with me, Henry,
all you have to do is embrace the risk.
(Mr Brown) Embrace the risk.
Hmm...
(Paddington) 'Mrs Bird meanwhile,
has finally found some time
'to tick things off her to do list.'
(Mrs Bird) Next up, fuse box!
(Paddington) 'In fact, the biggest change
at Windsor Gardens,
'despite the Browns
living in the same house,
'they don't actually seem to spend
much time together anymore.
'But life in London
is still quite wonderful,
'and I still feel very much at home.
'Lots of love from P...'
Paddington, there's a letter from Peru.
It came this morning.
Oh! Thank you.
But this isn't Aunt Lucy's handwriting.
"Dear Paddington..."
"...forgive my contacting you,
we haven't met.
"I'm the Reverend Mother
at the Home for Retired Bears.
"And I'm afraid I have some rather
worrying news about your Aunt Lucy."
- (Cheering)
- Spot on!
"She's always been such a happy member
of our community."
Oh, bingo!
"But there's been
the most pronounced change.
"She spends her hours alone in her room
and seems to be missing you desperately.
"Please don't mention that I wrote,
"she wouldn't want you bothered
by such things.
"But I felt I had to tell you,
something is not right with Aunt Lucy."
(Paddington) "Yours sincerely,
Reverend Mother."
Something's not right with Aunt Lucy.
I had no idea.
Oh, Paddington.
She must really be missing you.
I can't bear to think of her feeling lonely
after all she's done for me.
- What can we do?
- There's not much we can do.
It's not as if we can drop everything
and fly to Peru!
Now, I-I know that look, Mary...
It's the perfect idea.
Aunt Lucy's missing Paddington.
He's just got his passport. This family
needs to spend some time together.
Does it?
Yes! Let's do it!
A trip to Peru!
A family holiday in Peru.
- Peru? Just like that?
- Yes!
Land of altitude sickness
and uncharted jungles.
Plus three of the world's most
dangerous roads, well, at least on a Harley.
Precisely! From a risk assessment
point of view Peru is...
'Embrace the risk, Henry.'
...exactly where we should be going.
Yes! Yes, it is!
Oh, Paddington, this is so exciting.
Peru!
(Mr Gruber) Paddington in Peru, eh?
When are you off?
First thing tomorrow.
I can't wait to see Aunt Lucy
and try this out, of course.
Mmm...
I'm officially British, you know.
And not before time.
We are very lucky to have you, Mr Brown.
That reminds me,
I have something for Judy for your trip.
Tuck yourself to the tea and buns.
(Thunder clapping)
(Gulps) Hmm?
Hmm?
(Thunder clapping)
(Roaring)
(Mr Gruber) A guidebook to Peru.
Perhaps ignore the chapter
on "Zeppelin Travel".
Mr Brown?
Have you been seeing a ghost?
Mr Gruber, that statue...
What is it?
Ah, you've noticed my Peruvian collection.
It just... roared.
Like it was speaking to me.
Things from my homeland
speak to me all the time.
It was very strange, Mr Gruber.
Mr Brown, you know,
becoming a citizen of another country,
while a wonderful thing,
can lead to... well, mixed feelings.
Oh, not me, Mr Gruber.
My feelings are very much unmixed.
But I will ask Aunt Lucy
about that statue.
Reverend Mother, my nephew Paddington
is coming to visit,
completely out of the blue.
Hallelujah!
(Bell chimes)
Get ready, everyone.
He's coming.
♪ Let's prepare for Paddington
♪ Paddington in Peru
♪ He's coming to stay from far away
♪ And there's so much to do!
♪ There's prepping and there's packing
♪ No plan must be lacking...
(Phoenix Buchanan's agent)
'Nice buns, by the way.'
(Reverend Mother)
♪ There's no time for slacking
♪ We'd better get cracking
♪ And bring your nephew to you...
(Rings bell) Careful!
♪ Let's prepare for Paddington
♪ Paddington in Peru
♪ Embarking today from the UK
♪ I pray that that they
won't suffer delays
♪ There's lots and lots to do and see...
Can he get me some duty free?
♪ Everything must go with a swing
for Paddington in Peru
♪ Let's prepare for Paddington...
Make sure your tray table
is securely stowed.
Pull the red cord
to inflate your life jacket.
They didn't mean now, Paddington.
I'm sorry.
(Grunting)
(Paddington) Hmm? Mmm.
Hmm? Mmm.
- (Mr Brown) Paddington?
- Oh, sorry.
♪ Let's prepare for Paddington...
Oh...
Ah.
Welcome to Peru.
(♪ "Paddington in Peru" continues
with Peruvian music arrangement)
Nice view.
Oh, yes.
(Mr Brown) Ooh...
Oh. Help yourself.
- It's called marmalade.
- (Burps)
♪ His travel plans have been confirmed
♪ No stone can be left unturned
♪ Holy sisters, novice nuns
♪ Action stations, everyone
♪ There's pinning and tacking
and washing and stacking
♪ Making and mending
and pruning and tending
♪ And waxing and buffing
and plucking and stuffing
♪ And slicing and dicing
and nightly de-licing
♪ For Paddington
♪ Paddington in Peru
♪ Paddington in Peru ♪
Oh... actual size.
(Sniffing)
Hmm?
(Gasps)
- Aunt Lucy!
- Paddington!
Aunt Lucy, we're here.
- Hello, good afternoon!
- Oh...
Aunt Lucy?
Oh! Hello?
(All) Hello.
Please could you tell me the way
to Aunt Lucy's cabin?
- Yes, it's that way, but I...
- Thank you.
Aunt Lucy!
Aunt Lucy, it's me!
Aunt Lucy?
Paddington...
Missing? Whatever do you mean?
She's gone, and we have no idea
where she is.
What do you mean "gone"?
Well, she seems to have set off
on some sort of quest into the jungle.
Now? But she knew we were coming.
Well, that's what's so mysterious.
She was so excited to see you,
counting down the days to your arrival.
But I'm... I'm afraid to say
that since I wrote,
your aunt's behaviour
has become even more worrying.
'She seemed to have been
researching something.'
Whatever it was,
she was obsessed with it.
I mean, very secretive
about the whole thing.
'And then we went to check on her...'
...and she wasn't there.
This isn't like Aunt Lucy.
Something's wrong.
We need to send out a search party!
Well, we already did, my dear.
I'm afraid all they found were these,
washed down the river.
Aunt Lucy's special bracelet.
She'd never take this off, un...
...unless...
(Gasps)
Broken.
Paddington...
I don't know what's happened to her,
Mrs Brown...
...but she may be hurt, or in trouble.
And she can't see without her glasses
and... I have to find her.
Well, Paddington, I hate to say this,
but the Amazon is quite...
...large.
- Paddington...
- We have to try.
Aunt Lucy would never give up on me.
Alas, there's nothing any of us
can do tonight.
And you must be very tired
after your journey.
- The nuns will show you your rooms.
- Thank you.
(Mrs Brown) Thank you so much.
(Paddington) Hmm...
All it takes to light the darkness
is one candle of faith.
Something will turn up.
Where are you, Aunt Lucy?
What were you looking for?
If only you had left me
some sort of... clue.
Oh, my goodness!
This must be it!
- (Creaking)
- This floorboard's loose.
Perhaps there's a secret compartment
or...
Oh! Ooh!
Mmm?
Huh?
(Mr Brown) Yes, I'd like to report
a missing bear, please.
Brown eyes, brown fur...
Well, in fact, just brown.
Yes, we've lost a jungle bear
in... in the jungle.
I-I'm not sure
I like your tone of voice.
And a good day to you too, sir.
- Morning.
Any luck with the police?
Apparently "too busy
looking for lost fish in the river".
It does seem odd, Aunt Lucy just leaving
like that, with no explanation.
Morning, everyone!
I found clue!
I know where to look
for Aunt Lucy!
It's a place called Rumi Rock,
and look...
...it's only a few days upriver.
We can take breakfast with us.
But wait, Paddington, what's going on?
Where did you get this old map?
I found it in Aunt Lucy's room.
In fact, I think she rather
wanted me to find it.
Rumi Rock? What makes you think
we should start the search there?
Well, Aunt Lucy has made a note.
"Start search here".
Fair enough.
The Lord be praised!
I knew something would turn up.
What is this Rumi Rock?
It's a sacred Inca stone circle
deep in the jungle.
And what's so special about it?
No idea.
Sacred Inca monuments
aren't really a nun thing.
But it's a clue
to finding your Aunt Lucy.
Seek out what she was looking for
and it may lead you to her.
If anyone can do it,
it's you, young bear.
Aunt Lucy always says,
"When skies are grey
hope is the way."
Right, well, just-just, you know...
hang on a minute.
Surely someone from here
would be in a much better position to go...
Oh, I don't permit myself or my nuns
to enter the jungle.
I find it somewhat...
...disquieting.
(Chuckles nervously)
I think it's best if I stay here
and tend my flock.
But I commend your bravery
and I have faith that you will survive.
That's reassuring.
Mr Brown, if you feel you can't come...
I shall go on my own.
Right. Well, obviously the Brown family
are clearly exactly the sort of people
with the requisite skill-set
to go looking for a lost bear in the jungle.
- Thank you, Mr Brown.
- Hallelujah!
Mmm? No... Hmm.
Now, don't forget to take these.
You can give them to your aunt
when you find her.
- Thank you very much, Reverend Mother.
- (Mrs Bird) I'll man basecamp.
I'll make sure everything's shipshape
for when she gets back.
Mmm... Mary? One thing.
Would you forgive an old nun
her comforts?
St Christopher, patron saint of travel.
I do believe
he will keep your family safe.
Keep him close?
Yes, of course.
Gosh, thank you so much.
Well, we need all the help
we can get.
Well, thank you.
Thank you.
I have to go now.
(Paddington) We just need to find a boat
that will take us upriver.
- I can do my own suncream, Mum!
- Just behind your ears!
Everyone, listen up.
We are on the threshold
of the actual Amazon,
- a place full of risk.
- (Honks horn) Careful!
(Mrs Brown) Oh!
So, we're gonna embrace that.
Mr Brown, why are you walking like that?
- It's his hard walk.
- It's a perfectly normal walk.
He does it
when the plumber comes round.
I do not!
Right. Look, whatever boat
we manage to get,
I don't think it's exactly
going to be the pride of the regatta, okay?
- Er... Mr Brown?
- Huh?
- Look.
- Mmm?
(♪ Opera playing on gramophone)
Oh, what a handsome...
- Mmm?
- Boat.
Good idea, we'll ask the handsome captain.
Excuse me, sir.
Is this boat for hire?
For hire?
Yeah, señor Bear...
and company.
It is your lucky day!
This is the best boat on the river!
Strong, smooth, easy on the eye
and... that's just the boat.
- Yah-ha!
- (Mrs Brown) Ooh!
Voilà!
Captain Hunter Cabot
at your service.
Oh, Paddington Brown.
Pleased to meet you.
Gina, tour.
Tour? We have many tours available.
We could see the pink dolphins?
- Take in some Inca ruins?
- Feed the piranhas.
(Both) Although it may cost you
an arm and a leg!
We need to go
to somewhere called Rumi Rock.
Er... Rumi Rock?
We don't go to Rumi Rock.
Well, we could do with a tour...
We don't need this one.
Yeah...
Well... I'm sorry, little bear,
but you'll have to take your sightseeing
somewhere else.
No, we're not sightseers.
It's an emergency, sir.
My Aunt Lucy has gone missing.
Now she's out there somewhere,
all alone.
I'm her only family...
and I've lost her.
Please can you make an exception,
just this once?
(Judy) University application travelogue.
Day two. We head off the tourist trail
and into the jungle,
our fates in the hands
of the charming Captain Cabot
and his daughter Gina.
(Blows horn)
Hey, Judy, take a photo with all this,
for the dudes back at the office.
Dudes?
Just take the photo.
Well, your cabins are ready.
From now on,
you must follow my orders.
To the inexperienced,
a boat can pose many dangers...
Boom!
Thank you, Gina!
She has to warn me.
Every time!
(♪ Plays "The Entertainer")
(♪ Harmonising melody)
(Mr Brown) Funny man.
Welcome aboard.
Who are these people?
Er... those are my ancestors,
the Cabots.
(Mrs Brown) Gosh, that's quite
a family resemblance.
(Cabot) All the generations
from every corner of the globe.
They like to keep an eye on me
just to make sure I bring glory on the family.
That's like your tattoo.
Oh, good spot, Mary.
- What tattoo?
- Oh, he's got a tattoo...
It's the Cabot family crest,
the fist of gold.
Very observant of you.
A drunken night in Cusco, was it?
- No.
- Ooh!
Well, this is a badge of pride.
All the Cabots have this tattoo.
This was a drunken night in Cusco.
- (All gasp)
- (Cabot laughs)
Follow me.
And finally, the Darwin Suite.
Oh, yes, well...
- That's more like it.
- (Mrs Brown) Isn't it so charming?
The old purple kneed tarantula.
It's... my husband's got
a bit of a thing about spiders and bugs.
In fact, he's got a whole folder...
Don't bother the Captain
with all that, darling.
No, sorry.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
It's so nice.
- Looks like a nice firm mattress.
- Yes. Lovely.
Rumi Rock, huh?
Do not fail us this time.
Uno, dos, tres, cuatro, cinco,
seis, siete, ocho, nueve, diez.
seis, siete, ocho, nueve...
I was going through my bag,
and look what I found: Travel Scrabble.
It's your favourite, isn't it?
Quick game?
Mum, I really need to work
on my travelogue.
Oh.
"Travelogue"...
Fourteen points.
That's without the triple word score.
(Chuckling)
(Paddington) 'I can't keep the line, Mrs Bird.'
You're breaking up, dear.
Mr Brown says these satellite phone calls
are very expensive.
- What?
- 'Expensive!'
E-X-P...
Ugh! It's gone again!
Oh, these satellite phones
are very temperamental.
Oh, no! No...
No, no, it's not that. It's...
It's like this building is filled
with electrical interference.
It's a very old building, Mrs Bird.
Nothing suspicious about it.
Suspicious?
Oh. Oh, knees...
What are you telling me?
Has there been any news
of Aunt Lucy?
Oh... no, dear, I'm afraid not.
(Sighs)
We'll find her, Paddington.
(Hunter) Tomorrow,
we will arrive to Rumi Rock.
- So, a toast...
- (Paddington slurping)
Mmm!
Oh, excuse me.
- ...to finding Aunt Lucy.
- Hear hear!
- Well, it's certainly interesting.
- (Mrs Brown) Mmm! Mmm!
So, uh...
- tell me, young bear...
- Hmm!
...why was your aunt so interested
in Rumi Rock?
We don't know, Mr Hunter.
The Reverend Mother said
she was looking for something.
She was wasting her time.
Rumi Rock is just a bunch of old stones.
A bunch of old stones that,
according to legend,
is the first step to finding...
El Dorado.
What? You mean...
- Hmm!
- (Electricity crackling)
Nice chips!
- He means the mythical lost city, not...
- Oh. Right.
When the Spanish invaders came,
they found all the treasures of Peru,
except for one.
The most precious treasure of all.
Hmm?
The gold which the Incas valued
more than anything else.
But it could not be found.
And this is because the Incas entrusted it
to "Los Espiritus del Bosque".
The spirits of the jungle
who promised to keep it secret
and hidden in the forest forever.
Now... that's El Dorado.
So, are you suggesting that
Aunt Lucy was looking for El Dorado?
Aren't we all?
In our own ways.
No?
But why would she be looking
for El Dorado, Mrs Brown?
She has no interest in gold.
Let's not get carried away with...
(Chuckles)
...some old pictures in a book.
If El Dorado exists,
why has no one found it?
Because none of them had... this.
It is said the only clue
the Incas left
to where the spirits of the jungle
hid the gold
was in a special bracelet.
- A bracelet... like this!
- Ooh!
(Mary gasps)
Where did you get that?
It's Aunt Lucy's.
She always wore it.
And it is the key to finding El Dorado
and all its treasures.
- Wow!
- (Scoffs)
There's no reason why Aunt Lucy
would have an ancient Inca bracelet.
- But she did! Look! It's the same!
- It may very well look the same.
Honestly, Henry,
you're really taking the fun out of this.
- It's just an ordinary stringy bracelet.
- It's not an ordinary bracelet. It is...
- (Paddington grunting)
- Oh!
(Paddington) I'm OK.
Nothing broken.
- ...Quipu.
- Quip-who?
An ancient Incan knot language
used for secret messages,
hidden in riddles.
So, if we work out what this says,
it might help us find Aunt Lucy?
Lend me this bracelet for a few hours.
I may be able to translate it.
Everyone who searches
for El Dorado dies.
Then... we can't let that happen
to Aunt Lucy.
Hmm... (Chuckles)
(Judy) 'Later came the Spanish conquest
of the Incas,
'and with them the gold hunters.
'The greediest of all
was Gonzalo Caboto.'
(Spraying)
Ugh! What is that smell?
Gotta smell good in the jungle,
you know?
- (Mrs Brown) Night night, guys!
- Night.
- (Judy) Night.
- Love you!
Clear. No spiders under here.
(Paddington) Night night, Mrs Brown!
(Mrs Brown) Night, Paddington.
Looks simple enough.
Mmm...
Mmm... ooh!
Uh-uh...
Oh...!
Now, the trick with a hammock
is not to let it see you... coming!
Whoa! Ugh!
(Grunting)
Nice hammock...
Steady! Steady! Ugh!
There we go.
It's not as comfortable...
(Grunting)
Argh!
(Mumbles)
(Snoring)
- What does it say?
- It doesn't make any sense.
- Why not?
- Cos it's a riddle!
- Who are you talking to?
- Uh-oh!
No one.
You're seeing the ghosts again,
aren't you?
Gina... I'm fine.
But you made me a promise.
- We don't need gold.
- And... And you are right,
but if we had it,
we could buy a real house
- with stairs and beds and square windows!
- Papa!
We could bring honour on the family.
But we only need each other,
and I'm scared
I'm going to lose you again,
for good this time.
Please... turn the boat around.
Don't listen to her!
She doesn't understand.
We need the gold! The glory!
Right!
- Let's turn the boat round right now!
- You mean it?
You are my treasure, and I love you.
Go untie the mooring rope.
Go! Go! Go!
Valiente idiota. ¡Nunca!
You were never a Cabot.
Never!
I'm proud of you, Papa.
This could be
a whole new chapter in our...
Papa?
- I love you, Gina...
- Papa!
...but I have to get that gold.
I have to!
You double-crossing pig!
Mentiroso!
I am doing this for the both of us!
I promise I'll come back for you
tomorrow!
(Gina) Argh! Papa!
You can't even drive that boat
without me!
Wow!
I think she took that well.
And you...
You had me there!
Maybe you're not a failure
after all, you know?
All right!
We have some work to do.
(Creaking)
What's that creaking noise?
Boom!
(Gasps, babbles) Oh!
Good morning, Paddington.
Did you sleep well?
I keep having the strangest dream.
Has anyone seen Mr Hunter?
I'd like to know
if he's translated the bracelet.
Or perhaps made us some breakfast.
It's after ten, Mary!
Hello?
Any chance of some coffee?
It clearly states that breakfast
is served between 8:30 and 10:30.
- Good morning, gentlemen... and madam.
- (Mr Brown keeps muttering)
Hello?
Mr Hunter?
Gina?
Is it me or is it getting a bit choppy?
- (♪ Piano strikes up)
- Ooh!
(♪ Johann Strauss II's "Blue Danube Waltz"
playing on piano)
(Paddington grunting)
Marmalade!
Shouldn't someone be driving?
(Feedback on PA system)
Gina? Mr Hunter?
Ah! Better make an announcement!
(Grunting)
There we... go! Oh! Ooh!
(Groaning)
Oh!
Huh!
Oh, dear!
Good morning. Please, could the Brown family
pop up to the front of the boat
- for a slight, uh... emergency.
- Huh?
- Left a bit...
- (Groaning)
- Right a bit.
- Paddington!
(Paddington) Rather a lot of rocks!
Paddington, what on earth
are you doing in there?
I appear to be driving the boat,
Mrs Brown.
- But where's Gina?
- She's not here!
I don't think Mr Hunter's here either!
Paddington, put it in reverse,
put the boat in reverse!
Good idea!
Reverse... That'll do it!
- (Engine speeding up)
- (Paddington) Oh!
- (All groaning)
- That's faster!
Get the lifejackets!
Where's Paddington?
Isn't he at the wheel?
(Paddington) No! I appear to be...
...on the wheel!
Clear the decks!
Henry, the lifejackets!
Here! Emergency supplies!
What?
- Hang on, Paddington.
- (Paddington groaning)
Come back!
Found the lifejackets!
Abandon ship?
Yes! Abandon ship!
Come on!
Come on, everybody.
Three, two, one... jump!
Aunt Lucy's glasses!
(Wailing)
Grab hold of anything that floats!
Triple-laminated.
Wait... Paddington!
- Paddington!
- Where is he?
Where's Paddington?
Paddington!
(Gasping for air)
Found them! Good piano!
Paddington!
Come on.
(Judy) Day Three.
With the Browns lost in the jungle,
everyone was thinking the same thing.
How long till we eat each other?
(Mr Brown) That's not helpful, Judy.
Whoop! Mmm!
(Grunting)
(Mrs Brown) Well, we wanted
a holiday to remember!
At this rate, we may not be around
to remember it.
Maybe we should just draw a big SOS
in the sand and chill here?
"Chill here"?
This is the Amazon,
not a shopping centre!
All we need is a... plan!
I have a plan, Mrs Brown.
Mm-hmm?
Um...
We find Rumi Rock ourselves.
It can't be far, and whatever's happened
to Hunter and Gina,
they're bound to look for us there.
Are you sure you can find the way?
You have spent rather a long time
in London, Paddington.
Mr Brown, you can take the bear
out of the jungle,
but you can't take the jungle
out of the bear.
- (Animal growling)
- (Paddington gasps)
- Uh... anyway, follow me.
- Yes.
Oh, and remember, whatever you do...
...never touch this plant.
- What's it called?
- The Spiky Red One.
This'll be fun,
a short stroll in the jungle.
(Mr Brown) And we're sure
this is a good idea, are we?
(Mrs Brown) I don't think it's gonna be
that far to get to Rumi Rock. It can't be!
People have gone there in the past.
(Phone ringing)
(Scoffs) What is wrong with this thing?
What have we here?
Oh! Very strange!
(Woman) It's Bingo time!
- Oh, pardon.
- (Woman) Eyes down for a full house!
- Noah's Ark, all the twos!
- Ooh!
- Days and nights, 40!
- Ooh, I got one!
(Woman) All the horsemen...
Horsemen of the Apocalypse,
number four.
The Holy Trinity, number three.
Do you play, Mrs Bird?
What's behind this organ?
Oh, nothing to be concerned about.
What about the lights and the humming?
It's just a secret room.
A secret room?
- Well, what have you got in there?
- Oh, well, I'm afraid I can't tell you.
That's strange.
I don't know what you're finding
strange about it, Mrs Bird.
It's just a secret room behind an organ,
and I can't tell you what's inside it.
Nothing suspicious about it.
D'you know, that is the second time
you've used the word "suspicious"?
Oh, is it?
Well, the Lord moves
in suspicious ways.
You mean "mysterious ways"?
Oh! You know your scripture,
Mrs Bird. (Chuckles)
Anyway, come along.
Time for Bingo!
Aye!
Bingo!
(Mr Brown) Do you think
it will be much further, Paddington?
(Paddington) Fairly sure
Rumi Rock should be just through here.
- Little bit further...
- Ooh! Oh!
Just along here...
...I think.
This way.
Just... over here.
Or here.
- And... left. Oh, no!
- (Mrs Brown) Oh!
(Paddington) That is a cliff. Right.
Yes, that is right.
(Mr Brown) Paddington,
don't take this the wrong way,
but are you sure
you know where we are?
Oh, yes, Mr Brown. We are...
Well, perhaps a little...
...lost.
(Sighs) Marvellous!
At least we've dried off.
(Thunderclap)
(Mrs Brown) I spy with my little eye
something beginning with...
- (Animal screeching)
- Whoa!
Doesn't matter.
Let's do our best
to get some sleep,
even if we are all completely drenched
in a snake-infested jungle.
(Mrs Brown) What happened to
"embracing the risk"?
(Mr Brown) I've tried that, Mary.
God knows I've tried.
But we don't belong here.
And quite frankly,
neither does Paddington.
(Thunder rumbling)
(Rain pattering)
Where are you, Aunt Lucy?
Aunt Lucy...
Aunt Lucy!
(Gasps)
Aunt Lucy?
I thought I'd... lost you.
Oh, Paddington!
Can't you see that it is you
who are lost?
(Paddington) Aunt Lucy!
- (Thunder rumbling)
- (Gasps)
Mmm..
Argh! Oh! (Grunting)
- (Bird squawking)
- Sorry!
Argh! (Screaming)
Oh! You again!
Oh!
(Thunderclap)
(Roaring)
- (Twig snapping)
- (Gasps)
Ha, little bear!
(Paddington) Mr Hunter!
Thank goodness you're safe!
- Whatever happened to you and Gina?
- Welcome...
...to Rumi Rock.
(Gasps) This is Rumi Rock!
Is Aunt Lucy here?
- No.
- Oh!
But I think she was here.
Remember I told you Rumi Rock
was the gateway to El Dorado?
Yes...?
That's why we can't find her here,
Paddington.
Because she has already found
her way there.
And what makes you think that,
Mr Hunter?
(Chuckling)
(Gasps) You translated the Quipu!
What does it say?
It says, "At Rumi Rock...
"...the bear will show the way."
Right!
And what bear would that be?
You-you-you tell me.
You are the bear.
Mmm!
I see!
And there isn't another message
written on the back? Because sometimes...
No, no, no, no, no!
It says, "The bear will show the way."
Now, you... are the bear!
That's a bear!
This talisman's got a bear on it.
You know? So...
This whole thing is really... beary!
Yes, really quite beary.
So, what do we do... Bear?
I don't know, Mr Hunter,
but Aunt Lucy always says,
"When you're faced with a problem,
sit down and put on your thinking cap."
(Snapping)
(Roaring)
(Echoing)
Oh...
Please excuse me, Mr Hunter.
It seems I sat on the Spiky Red One.
(Distant roaring)
What was that?
(Aunt Lucy) 'If you ever get lost again...
(Aunt Lucy and Paddington)
'...just roar and I'll roar right back.'
(Roars)
(Distant roaring)
Aunt Lucy! She can hear me!
That's how we find her, Mr Hunter.
Like she always said.
Follow her roars.
(Thunder rumbling)
(Thunderclap)
(Door creaking)
(Bell dings)
(Beeping)
What in God's name...?
Language, Mrs Bird!
What... Beg your pardon, Reverend Mother,
but this place...
It looks kind of like an evil lair.
- Oh, I can assure you it's not.
- (Whirring)
(Mrs Bird muttering)
But... Then, what is it?
What it is, is a perfectly innocent
secret surveillance control centre.
And why on earth
would you need one of those?
I confess, Mrs Bird, I have sinned!
I have been deceitful
in a way most unbecoming of a nun,
and I can only pray
for your forgiveness!
What have you done?
The St Christopher medal I gave Mary
is actually a secret tracking device.
I couldn't let what happened
to poor Aunt Lucy happen again,
so I've been keeping an eye
on them.
Oh, my!
That's a canny bit of kit!
Someone's been a busy nun.
Well, thank goodness I have.
You see, this is Rumi Rock...
...and this is the Browns' route.
And they were heading
in the right direction,
but now they're heading north
into uncharted, dangerous jungle,
and I fear for their safety.
I'll alert the authorities.
We'll mount a rescue party!
No! Because they'll be too slow.
(Chuckles nervously)
We must go ourselves.
I thought you didnae go
trekking in the jungle?
I thought it gave ye
the heebie-jeebies.
I wasn't planning on trekking.
Mary!
Not with the kids around.
- (Screaming)
- Shh!
There's something big out there.
Hello?
Whatever you are...
...you should know...
...that I've got a twig here,
...and I am not afraid to use it.
(Leaves rustling)
(Screaming)
Mary!
- (Leaves rustling)
- (Thud)
- (Gina) Ow!
- (Mrs Brown) Oh! Oh, no!
Oh, Gina, I am so sorry.
I... I thought you were some sort
of a fierce creature or something like...
¡Hola, Browns!
¡Gracias a Dios!
You're OK.
Pretty pleased to see you, too.
It was very clever using Jonathan's
deodorant spray as an odour trail.
Oh, yeah, I mean... that was the idea.
Where did you get to?
You and your father abandoned us
on an abandoned ship!
- It wasn't abandoned.
- Yes, it was.
It was only abandoned
after we abandoned it.
Where is your tattooed father?
There is something about him...
I knew it.
...about us...
...that I should've told you
from the very beginning.
My family are cursed
with a dreadful disease.
They call it el oro loco,
gold madness.
It began with my ancestor,
Gonzalo Caboto.
'He was greedy and ruthless,
'and when he heard
the legend of El Dorado,
'he came looking for it,
driving his men to exhaustion.
'He ate what he had to,
to stay alive,
'but it was pointless.
'Instead of riches,
'all he passed onto his descendants
was greed.'
(Evil chuckle)
Huh? Oh!
(Gina) 'Generation after generation,
fools in their pursuit of El Dorado.'
- (Thud)
- Crikey!
(Gina) 'Gold fever drew them
from every corner of the globe.'
♪ Onward Christian soldiers... ♪
(Gina) 'They came from all walks of life.
'But all any of them found was death.'
(Bubbling)
My father was different.
Mama died when I was young,
so it was always just us.
He was determined to beat the curse,
'but when he heard of Rumi Rock,
it took hold of him.
'He disappeared into the jungle.
'And I was left alone.
'For years.
'When he returned...'
(Panting)
Gina!
(Gina) '...he promised he would keep away
from the jungle and its ghosts.
'He would stick to the river
and never love gold more than me.
'I believed him.'
Seems I was a fool.
- Oh, Gina!
- Mmm! (Chuckles)
- Why, what is it?
- Nothing.
No, just goes to show you should never trust
a handsome riverboat captain.
- I never said he was handsome.
- You were thinking it!
Now he is haunted
by the ghosts of ancestors
and will do anything to get his gold.
I must get you and Paddington to safety.
Where is Paddington?
(Roaring)
(Echoing roar)
This way, Mr Hunter!
We'll follow her roars,
and we'll find her in no time!
(Gonzalo) 'Do it. Cabotos don't share!'
We're getting close, Mr Hunter.
And you're sure the river taxi service
will have rescued the Browns by now?
- Yes.
- Oh, that is a relief.
Mr Brown did have
some rather wet socks.
One more push,
and we'll be with Aunt Lucy.
Hey! What's with all the chitchat?
Get moving!
I know what I have to do.
Is everything... all right, Mr Hunter?
Yes...
There are just expectations
from my family.
Oh. I didn't know you had other family.
Hmm...
Do you see them much?
All the time, yes.
How lovely.
You know how families can be.
Yes. Well, sort of.
The only family I've known
is the Browns and Aunt Lucy.
Before that, all I remember is
my parents died when I was very young.
Boo-hoo! It's a sob story!
How about we cheer ourselves up
with a bowl of bear stew?
- No, we can't eat him...
- Huh?
- ...yet.
- What?
(All repeat) What?
You said something
about... eating someone.
Did I?
Probably it's just... the altitude.
Oh. Right.
Shall we get back
to finding Aunt Lucy?
Yes.
(Gonzalo) Don't lose your nerve.
Maybe there is another way.
We are too close for you to throw it
all away with your stupid feelings.
Stick to the plan!
You follow the bear, you find the gold,
you eat bear stew.
Follow bear! Find gold! Eat stew!
Bear, gold, stew!
Bear, gold, stew.
(Paddington) Are you coming,
Mr Hunter?
Right... right behind you.
I can see the camp fire. It's not far.
On the other side of the valley.
But the bridge is down.
Papa...
How do we feel
about crossing over... that?
We need a miracle.
(Aircraft overhead)
- (Judy) Look, it's Mrs Bird!
- (Jonathan) Yes!
(Roaring)
Oh! Hello. Beg your pardon.
Aunt Lucy!
(Gasps)
Oh...
(Roaring)
(Echoing roar)
- (Echoing roar)
- Oh!
Aunt Lucy!
(Roaring)
(Echoing roar)
Aunt Lucy!
(Roaring)
Almost there, Aunt Lucy!
(Echoing roar)
Aunt Lucy!
I'm here!
(Echoing) I'm here! I'm here!
Aunt Lucy?
(Echoing) Aunt Lucy?
Huh?
You mean, all this time...
...you were just an echo?
(Echoing) Echo? Echo?
Echo?
(Sighs heavily)
I'm sorry, Aunt Lucy.
You found me all those years ago,
and now I can't find you.
We're both lost.
I don't want to say goodbye.
(Hunter) So...
...the bear showed the way.
- Mr Hunter!
- But if this is El Dorado...
...where is...
where is the gold?
There is no gold, Mr Hunter.
And no Aunt Lucy.
There must be something,
some special mechanism,
that leads you to the... gold.
A-ha!
- What did I tell you?
- Oh?
Strange Inca symbols.
A triangle.
A circle with an 'X' through it.
"Dry clean only"?
It's a washing label, Mr Hunter.
"Barkridges of Kensington."
Aunt Lucy's scarf!
She bought this in London.
Are you... behind this wall?
Whoa! Oh!
(Grunts)
This must open!
(Groaning)
Oh?
(Gonzalo) The bear shows the way.
Those clever Incas!
The talisman... it must go in there.
Take it from him.
But...
...it feels wrong.
Wrong? Five hundred years
of searching for gold is wrong?
But... I have made a promise to Gina...
Forget about Gina.
Take the talisman.
Kill the bear!
Give me the talisman!
Talisman, Mr Hunter?
Hand it over.
No.
I said... hand it over.
Promise we can go in together.
Well, the thing about that, Bear,
is that Cabotos don't share!
(Chuckles)
An umbrella?
Not just any brolly.
The Windsorman Deluxe.
London's finest, Mr Hunter!
(Gasps)
Uh... Uh...
Apparently, they bought this plane
for the Pope's visit in 1985.
- It's got its MOT and everything?
- It's got a papal blessing.
(Rattling and beeping)
(Engine dies)
(Beeping)
(Engine starts)
- Look!
- What?
It's Paddington!
Bear!
Oh! Spiky Red One!
- Reverend Mother, can you land?
- It'll be tight.
Yes!
- Where are you, Bear?
- Oops!
- (Alarm beeping)
- The landing gear's jammed.
One of you will have to lift
that panel in the floor,
and turn the manual release.
It's all right, I'll do it.
(Mrs Brown) Go on, darling!
Ooh!
Any-anyone happen to have
a very large tumbler?
Come on, Henry!
(Sniffing)
I can smell the marmalade.
Oh! Hello.
Sorry, Mr Hunter!
(Both gasp)
Hurry up, lad!
We need those wheels out!
(Madison) 'Embrace the risk, Henry.'
Embrace the risk...
There you go.
(All) Dad!
- Be with you in a minute!
- Oh, my goodness!
- Let me take a photo!
- Forget the photo!
No, do it! Do it!
My gosh!
(Groaning)
- You did it!
- Oh!
- (Mrs Brown) Darling, well done!
- (Mr Brown) There you go.
Home sweet home.
That was amazing!
Well done, Mr Brown!
Nothing can go wrong now!
(Screaming)
Whoa... Oh!
Oh.
Oh!
- Whoa!
- Bear!
Huh?
(Screaming)
One of these must be
the windscreen wipers.
(Screaming)
- Stop pushing buttons!
- I've got an idea!
- (Mrs Brown) What?
- I'll need back-up.
- Oh! Oh...
- (Bleating)
Oh. Hello again.
- Bear!
- Oh, dear.
Erm... excuse me, Mr Llama,
could you please... giddy up?
- Give me the bracelet, Bear!
- Oh... erm... Ah!
Ma-llama-lade.
Hmm?
(Jonathan) Hold me up!
- Left a bit!
- Come on!
- No! My left!
- Which left?
- That left!
- That way?
This left!
Huh?
Yes! Here we go.
Thank you. And this way!
And I think it's up here.
Thank you.
- Just round this corner...
- I need that bracelet!
I'm coming, Aunt Lucy!
Huh? Not you again?
- Yes!
- (Screaming)
Well done!
Gangway!
(Sighs)
- That was close.
- (Cracking)
Oh...
Extremely close.
- Thank God!
- (Mr Brown) Well done, Jonathan!
- Here we go! Brace positions!
- Okay.
You really don't seem yourself,
Mr Hunter.
I am Gonzalo Caboto!
- And I want my...
- (Engine approaching)
♪ Onward Christian soldiers
- ♪ Marching as to war
- (Jonathan) Why's she singing?
- ♪ With the cross of Jesus... ♪
- (Screaming)
Oh, we've landed!
(All) Whoa!
(Groaning)
(All) Ooh...
(Gasps)
Hmm?
You looked like you enjoyed that!
Oh! Oh, it's just so nice to...
...all be on the same sofa again.
(Mrs Bird) Well done,
Reverend Mother.
Well done.
(Mr Brown) Right, come on.
Out you go.
We can all sing a hymn of thanks,
once we find Aunt Lucy.
- Paddington!
- Mrs Brown!
- Oh, Paddington!
- Paddington!
(Mr Brown) Oh!
- I'm so happy to see you all.
- Thank goodness you're all right.
- I knew this would come in handy.
- (Groaning)
I know where Aunt Lucy is.
She's somewhere behind this.
And I think I know how to open it.
Clever little bear.
I was rather hoping you would.
Reverend Mother?
Oh!
- What on earth are you doing?
- Why, same as everyone else, my dear.
Looking for gold.
So, thank you very much for leading me
straight to it, as I knew you would.
- This is a bit unchristian, isn't it?
- Well, it would be...
...if I were really a nun.
- Oh!
- Ooh! Oh, crikey.
(Hunter) Clarissa?
Cousin Clarissa?
But you are dead.
You died in the jungle.
- They're related?
- And you went to find yourself...?
No, I went to find gold!
'And I never stopped looking.
'And when I found out it had something
to do with bears, I did the obvious thing.
'I disguised myself as a nun, and got a job
at the Home for Retired Bears.'
Hello!
I'm your new Reverend Mother!
Not that obvious.
Years I was stuck there
with those mangy furbags.
How rude.
Until one day,
Aunt Lucy showed me that bracelet.
'And I knew that you would be the one
to lead me to El Dorado.'
- Why me?
- Oh, she never told you?
- It's your bracelet, Paddington.
- Oh?
It was round your ankle
when she pulled you out of that river.
Hmm...
I knew if anyone was gonna
show me the way, it would be you.
So, I lured you to Peru, and I arranged
for your aunt's disappearance.
(Gasps) Reverend Mother?
Reverend Mother, I can't see you.
I-I can't see anything!
(Reverend Mother) 'I knew you'd
never rest until you found Aunt Lucy.
'So, with a little help from me...
'"Dear Paddington.
'"I'm afraid I have some rather
worrying news about your Aunt Lucy.
'"Please don't mention that I wrote.
'"She wouldn't want you bothered
by such things."'
You led me right here.
So, please, give me that talisman.
Thank you.
Oh, I don't seem to have it.
- I really don't.
- Well, then, who has?
- Hand it over, or I shoot.
- With great-grandpa's musket?
That thing is over a hundred years old.
It won't even work.
Shall we put it to the test?
(All) Gina!
(Hunter gasps)
She means it.
And she's very strong for a nun.
She's not a nun!
The gold or your daughter?
You're all family.
Couldn't you just share the gold?
Cabotos don't share!
- Sorry, it was just a thought.
- It was a very good one.
Papa, please!
But I am so close.
I cannot lose it now.
I have been searching forever
in this... sweaty jungle,
and I am hot and flushed
and-and-and uncomfortable, and...
Why do I feel so...
...queasy?
It's called a hard stare, Mr Hunter.
And it's for when people have forgotten
their manners and the important things.
- Yeah...
- Gina's your treasure.
Don't lose her because of gold.
Gina will steal the gold for herself.
- Choose the gold!
- You can always get a new daughter.
Cabotos don't share!
I'm sorry, Gina.
All I can say is, er...
- ...boom.
- Boom?
Boom!
- Oh! (Giggling)
- Huh...
Oh, dear... What?
- No, no, no!
- Papa!
Here. Here...
You're free.
We are free.
Go... and find your Aunt Lucy.
You're not coming, Mr Hunter?
Mr Paddington, um...
...I've got all the treasure I need.
Thank you, Mr Hunter.
Oh, no... thank you.
Mmm...
Um... I'll just try that again.
(Blows)
- (Low rumbling)
- Huh?
- (Mrs Bird) What's happening?
- (Mrs Brown) Whoa!
- (Mrs Bird) It's opening! It's opening!
- What's happening? Oh, my goodness!
(Mrs Bird) Back! Back!
(Mrs Bird) Oh! Oh, my...
- Oh, it's the...
- It's... it's from the book, the weird...
- Yes, the "Espiritus del Bosque".
- (Judy) The forest spirits...
- (Mrs Brown) Yes.
- (Judy) They're real.
Oh!
- (Roaring)
- Oh!
They don't sound friendly.
Quite the opposite, Mr Brown.
That was my bear name.
Oh...
- They want us to go inside.
- Really?
Thank you. Afternoon.
Thank you so much.
Could this be...
could it be El Dorado?
Oranges.
Thousands of oranges.
Juicy ones, at that!
Oh... they're beautiful, perfect,
every one.
But what about the gold?
I think we're looking at it.
The gold is oranges.
El Dorado is an orange grove!
- Oh...
- Oh! Oh!
- Hello, again.
- Hello.
- (Mr Brown) Oh?
- (Mrs Brown) Oh, look!
(Growling)
- (Mr Brown) And...?
- Hi!
They're bears.
(Gasps)
(Roaring)
- (Answering roar)
- Oh!
Aunt Lucy!
Ooh! Paddington?
Oh, Paddington!
Aunt Lucy.
I always knew you'd come for me.
- You'll be needing these.
- Oh!
Oh... Oh, my, my...
Quite the rescue party!
We're so pleased you're safe.
All thanks to these bears.
They heard my roars and rescued me.
- Who are they, Aunt Lucy?
- And why do they dress up like... trees?
To stay hidden.
They are the secret guardians
of the El Dorado oranges.
They know my bear name.
And I've been dreaming
about that statue.
Help me up.
All those years ago, when Uncle Pastuzo
and I found you as a cub,
you told us you were orphaned.
But we always wanted to know
where you came from.
The answer was here all the time.
Your bracelet.
All the cubs here have them.
So, if they get lost...
They can find their way home.
(Aunt Lucy) They are your tribe.
You are an El Dorado bear.
I think... I remember.
Uh... argh!
(Screaming)
I got lost.
In finding me,
you have found yourself.
Oh...
(Soft growling)
What do you think they're saying?
I think they're just...
happy to have him home.
Would you mind taking these for me,
Mrs Brown?
There's something I think
my tribe might enjoy.
And I may need Jonathan's help.
With oranges this wonderful,
you have to make marmalade.
More sugar, please!
He looks so happy.
Like he never left.
Now, Mary...
It's all right...
it's how it's meant to be.
- Paddington belongs here.
- With his clan.
(Paddington) 'Hello.
Coming down in stair rods, isn't it?'
Good evening.
(Mrs Brown) I hope you don't mind me asking,
but shouldn't you be at home?
Oh, yes, I should, but I haven't quite
worked out how to find one.
I didn't realise it was this difficult.
Oh...
It's just what happens next.
This one's for you.
Thank you, Paddington. Gosh!
No... thank you for...
...well, for everything
you've done for me.
And, um...
...there's something I wanted to ask.
You were all so kind to take me in
all that time ago.
I know it couldn't have been easy,
and that I've sometimes been
a bit of a nuisance.
Sorry about that business with your pyjamas
in the paper shredder, Mr Brown.
That's all right, Paddington.
So, I wanted to ask,
if you didn't mind terribly...
...if, um...
...if I, um...
Yes, Paddington?
Um...
...if I could stay.
Mmm...
With you.
If I could come back home.
Come back home with...? Oh!
Yes, of course you can, Paddington!
You don't have to ask that.
Oh, I thought you were going
to ask to stay here.
Mrs Brown... they are my tribe.
But you are my family.
This is where I'm from,
but... you're where I belong.
- Oh.
- (Chuckling)
You think to press the red button?
Yeah... yes., that's right.
(Paddington) 'Dear Aunt Lucy.
'I hope you're still enjoying life
at the Home for Retired Bears.
'It seems a long time since our holiday
together in the valley,
'and everyone's lives
have changed so much.
'And it was nice of the church
to forgive Clarissa Cabot,
'providing she became a real nun...'
- Out.
- Are you sure this is the place?
(Paddington) '...and took a new posting.'
(Wailing)
'Hunter and Gina
have a new boat,
'thanks to Mr Brown
sorting the insurance for them.
'As for the Browns,
Jonathan has given up chillin',
'and is hardly ever in his room.
'He spends most of his time at trade fairs
doing something he calls hustlin'.
'The G is silent.'
The first day of our extremely
dangerous mission...
(Paddington) 'Mr Brown
has been promoted at work,
'and he is now Head of Calculated Risk.'
...finally, with the purple-kneed tarantula
on my face.
So, as you can see,
some risks are worth embracing.
But only if they're for the greater good,
and for the people you love.
- Thank you.
- Outstanding.
- Sensational.
- Awesome.
On that note, I will be doing
a sponsored BASE jump
for the Home for Retired Bears.
So, please chip in.
And remember, embrace the risk!
(Paddington) 'Mrs Brown started
a new art project called "Taking Flight".
'And despite her previous fears,
she's actually closer to Judy than ever.
'Judy's travelogue helped her
get into university,
'where she's already very busy
at the student newspaper.'
With a few changes,
this could make the front page.
Thank you.
Wait... changes?
(Paddington) 'I hope Mrs Bird
is enjoying her stay with you,
'and that she's ticked a few things
off her new to-do list.'
(♪ Jungle music playing)
The jungle is massive!
(Groans)
(Paddington) 'As for me...
'...I think I made the right decision.
'Mr Gruber was right when he said
you can have mixed feelings
'about where you're from.
'But maybe that's okay.
'Because I suppose
I am a bit of a mix.
'Part London, part Peru.
'A sprinkle of El Dorado.
'But most of all...
'...a whole lot of Brown.'
(Mrs Brown) Paddington, they're here!
(Paddington) 'Oh, must go.
My guests have arrived for their holiday.'
- (Footsteps)
- Hello, there!
- (Pot smashing)
- (Mr Brown) That was my mother's!
Oh, you've grown.
Come on, let's go and see London!
Oh, careful!
(Paddington) Sorry, Mr Brown!
'Love from Paddington.
'Also known as... (Roaring)
'...Brown.'
Look, over there!
And there!
Hello! Good morning!
(♪ "Paddington in Peru" playing
with Peruvian music arrangement)
(Low growling)
- And this is Euston.
- (Grunts)
- St Pancras.
- Waterloo, Piccadilly, Baker Street.
- (Grunting)
- High Barnet, Bromley-by-Bow.
- Leicester Square, Elephant and Castle.
- (Grunting)
- Clapham North, Clapham South.
- And Cutty Sark for Maritime Greenwich.
- (Low growl)
(Gasps) Hey...
Tell me this...
Do any of your friends
care for the theatre?
Perhaps some of them
like to perform?
As you know,
I am shortly to be released,
and I wonder...
red cape, flaxen wig, lights.
Phoenix Buchanan is... Goldilocks!
- (Grunting and growling)
- Yes?
- (Grunting)
- (Buchanan) Oh, yes, they like it.
- Who wants to be Daddy Bear? You!
- (Grunting)
- Mummy Bear, you!
- And Baby Bear, come hither.
- (Squealing)
Don't be frightened, come here.
Let's talk.
I am thinking the autumn, I am thinking
a small theatre, the Wyndham, the Duchess.
And I am thinking
we may need some money.
You who've been to El Dorado.
Did you, by any chance, find any?
- (Paddington) We found these...
- (All grunting)
Oranges?
That is disappointing.
What fun! What fun.
What a lovely bunch of...
...of-of... fur.