Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[MUFFLED "HYMN TO RED OCTOBER"
PLAYING WITH RUSSIAN LYRICS]
[SINGING GROWS LOUDER]
["HYMN TO RED OCTOBER"
CONTINUES AT FULL VOLUME]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[TRUCK ENGINE RUMBLING]
[HYDRAULICS HISSING]
SOLDIER 1: [IN RUSSIAN]
You have five minutes.
Relieve yourselves.
[IN RUSSIAN]
Where is 0864?
0864!
[SOLDIERS SPEAKING RUSSIAN
INDISTINCTLY]
SOLDIER 3: [IN RUSSIAN, LAUGHS]
Thought we'd leave without you?
You wouldn't
last an hour out here.
The wolves will eat you alive.
[CHAINS RATTLING]
["HYMN TO RED OCTOBER"
CONTINUES AT FULL VOLUME]
[MUFFLED CLAMORING
AND BANGING INSIDE]
-[LOUD CLAMORING]
-[BANGING]
[MEN SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN,
WHISTLING]
[SHOUTING AND BANGING CONTINUE]
-[BUZZER BLARES]
-[SONG ENDS]
[IN RUSSIAN]
I hate roommates.
[IN RUSSIAN] We have
something in common already.
Last guy made it a month.
I'll be here three days tops.
Everyone here is a lifer.
One minute longer,
you can take your best shot.
[CHUCKLES]
It's a deal.
Can I sit with you at lunch?
[IN ENGLISH] No.
["GRUPPA KROVI" PLAYING OVER
SPEAKERS WITH RUSSIAN LYRICS]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER
IN RUSSIAN]
[IN RUSSIAN]
This is a private area.
Fuck off.
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTS]
MAN 1: [IN RUSSIAN] Who the fuck
do you think you are, asshole?
[STRAINS]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[IN RUSSIAN]
Now it's open territory.
[GUARDS SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[IN RUSSIAN]
Boss wants to see you.
[IN RUSSIAN] So this is the man
my men want to kill.
Do you know who I am?
[IN RUSSIAN]
You're Semyon Chorney.
You run the Kirov Gang.
Your guns kill thousands of men,
women and kids
all over the world.
[CHUCKLES] You know me.
Who the hell are you?
Me?
I'm a hunter.
Mm. [CHUCKLES]
He's a hunter.
What do you hunt?
People like you.
The Hunter is a myth.
[DOOR BANGS SHUT]
Now you're trapped, hunter.
What's your name? Who sent you?
My name is...
[IN ENGLISH] Kraven.
[IN ENGLISH] Kraven?
KRAVEN: [IN RUSSIAN] But I'm
sure you won't tell anyone.
-[GRUNTING]
-[INMATE CRIES OUT]
[INMATE WHIMPERING]
[GRUNTING]
There's an ounce of truth
in every myth.
[IN ENGLISH] No.
-[GRUNTING VICIOUSLY]
-[CHOKING GASPS]
[GRUNTING FIERCELY]
-[GUARD YELLING]
-[GRUNTS]
GUARD: [SHOUTS IN RUSSIAN]
Prisoner escaping!
-[STRAINED GRUNTING]
-[ALARM BLARING]
Prisoner escaping!
[GUARDS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY
IN RUSSIAN]
[GUARD SPEAKING OVER PA
[ALARM CONTINUES BLARING]
[GUARD SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
[GUARDS CLAMORING IN RUSSIAN]
-[GUNFIRE]
-[GUARDS SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
[CHUCKLES]
[SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
Three days.
[GUARDS SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
-[GUNFIRE]
-[SHOUTING CONTINUES]
[GUARDS CONVERSING FRANTICALLY
IN RUSSIAN]
[IN RUSSIAN]
He's getting away!
-[PANTING]
-[SHOUTING IN DISTANCE]
-[STORM RUMBLING]
-[WIND HOWLING]
[WOLVES HOWLING]
[WOLF GROWLING]
[SNARLS]
[WHINES]
[GRUNTS]
[IN ENGLISH] Move! Move! Move!
PILOT: [OVER RADIO]
You were late.
Next time,
you break out of prison
and I fly this thing.
No, thanks.
So, how'd it go?
How it always goes.
Good for me...
bad for him.
[IN RUSSIAN]
We've got a body over here.
Have you identified him yet?
GUARD: Nyet.
It's prisoner 0864.
Then who the fuck
killed Chorney?
[ROARS]
[SEAGULLS SCREECHING]
[STUDENTS SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY, LAUGHING]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Kravinoff and Kravinoff!
Your father is coming
to pick you up.
What'd you do?
Me? Nothing.
I thought it was you.
No.
Where are we going, Papa?
We're in the middle of a term
at school.
Sergei...
Mom never made us
do shit like this.
Sergei...
Your mother is dead.
She took own life. She was weak.
Sick in her mind.
Was her choice.
Well, she died
because you sent her away.
No.
She gave up long ago.
You haven't even seen her
for two years.
Nothing will change for you.
-Or for you, Dmitri.
-Where are we going, Papa?
To the funeral?
If you take own life,
you do not
get honor of funeral.
So then,
where are you taking us?
We go to hunt.
There've been
new sightings of lion, Zar.
It would be good for you. Both.
To join men,
be one with nature.
Shoot to kill.
Fun.
WOMAN 1: Careful with those.
Put the cards away now, Calypso.
Your mum and dad
will be back soon.
And you know the way
they feel about all this.
It's just a game, Granny.
You think my cards
are just pretty pictures.
Think again, Calypso.
They show us the unseen road.
What? Like, predict the future?
Mm-hmm.
In the right hands.
Lay three cards down.
The first card is the subject.
The High Priestess?
You do come from a long line
of very powerful women.
The second card
is the situation.
The Tower.
There's going to be
a terrible accident.
The third card is the outcome.
Strength.
There is great danger
in that card.
I have something for you,
Calypso.
I was going to wait
until you were older,
but the cards have shown us
you will need it very soon.
What is it?
A potion.
The formula has been passed down
in our family for generations.
What does that symbol mean?
It's the sign
of the spirit Papa Legba.
He opens the gate
to the other side.
Protect it.
Very powerful.
Go ahead.
It will heal whoever drinks it
in undreamed-of ways.
The time is coming soon.
You'll know what to do with it.
Now, put those away
before your parents get back.
[GUNSHOT]
Well done, Nikolai!
Sergei.
You see?
So beautiful.
Never fear death.
They are prey.
We are predators.
Men should be
only animal that is threated.
Dmitri, don't look so weak.
Be a man.
SERGEI: You all right?
DMITRI: Yeah.
SERGEI: He shouldn't have
talked to you like that.
Yeah, well...
He's an asshole.
There's nothing
I can do about that.
He'll never respect me
like he respects you.
Wanna bet?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[SIGHS]
DMITRI: I miss Mom.
SERGEI: Me, too, Dima. Me, too.
[LION ROARING IN DISTANCE]
Is it the Zar?
Not even pussycat.
Perhaps it's the Zar's
illegitimate half-brother.
Like your Dmitri.
NIKOLAI: Leave the boy.
He carries no blame
for his father's wandering eye.
You will know Zar when you hear.
He sound like
thunder from mountain top.
You have seen this beast?
I have seen his work.
This cat has killed 2,000,
maybe 3,000, men.
Yes?
For as long as men like you
have been coming
down here to kill lions...
there have been legends
of the one who can't be killed.
NIKOLAI: Men like me.
But you still take my money,
don't you, Bahari?
A lion hunts for food.
Same as I do.
Why do you hunt, Nikolai?
You know this, Bahari.
Men who kill legend
becomes legend.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
-MAN 2: Nikolai...
-[STRAINING FOR BREATH]
we should talk.
No. Save your breath.
No, it's a condition.
I'll be okay,
as long as I take
a few breaks here and there.
One thing that you should
know about me is that
I'm always
thinking of the future.
I want you to be my partner.
What is your name?
I'm a guest here of Vladimir.
Aleksei Sytsevich.
No.
You do not have name.
In this world, you barely exist.
So, what can some no-name,
nonexistent,
condition-suffering fool,
offer up to the Kravinoffs?
Nothing.
I am here...
teaching my sons
the joy of stalking.
And you
and your imbecilic voice
are stalking me.
So, be quiet.
Hope Father gets him this time.
Why?
Well, because then
he'll become a legend,
and we don't
have to come here again.
A true legend would fight fair.
Not with a gun.
You would do it one-on-one
with only the tools
you were born with.
[LION GROWLING]
Dmitri,
get back.
[GROWLING SOFTLY]
[GUNSHOT]
[ROARS]
Dmitri! Move! Move!
-[ROARS]
-[EXCLAIMS]
Run!
[GUNSHOT]
[GASPING, SCREAMS]
NIKOLAI: [ECHOING] Sergei!
[LION GROWLING]
Sergei!
[CAMERA CLICKING]
Calypso! Look!
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
WOMAN 2: Come on, honey,
stand up.
Calypso?
Calypso!
[LOW GROWLING]
[SNARLS]
[DISTORTED GROWLING]
GRANDMOTHER: In the name
of all the spirits
and all the mysteries...
[ECHOING]
Help!
GRANDMOTHER:
...bring the power of the Earth.
[GRANDMOTHER'S VOICE ECHOING]
[HELICOPTER APPROACHING]
Wait.
GRANDMOTHER: Bring the power
of the stars.
[DISTORTED]
[HEART MONITOR FLATLINES]
DOCTOR 1: Everybody's clear.
Shocking now.
DOCTOR 2: Okay, team.
We've done all we can.
I'm going to call time of death.
6:51.
[FLATLINE CONTINUES]
[LOW GROWLING]
-[FLATLINE CONTINUES]
-[DISTORTED HOWLING]
[ROARS]
-[HEART MONITOR BEEPING]
-[INHALES]
DOCTOR 2: The EMTs found
that card in your pocket.
You are one very lucky boy.
Thank you for saving me.
I wish I could say I did.
But I didn't save you.
I don't understand.
That makes two of us.
First, we're going
to run some tests,
see if we can figure out
what happened.
Sergei.
Dima.
NIKOLAI: Why did you not shoot?
You must be Sergei's father.
Mr. Kravinoff.
I'm here to take him home.
He needs to stay here
and recover.
Clinically, he was dead
for more than three minutes.
He will be leaving with me.
SERGEI'S MOTHER: Sergei.
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
I am sorry we are not together,
but we will be soon.
You know this is not
what I would have ever wanted,
but it is the only choice
your father gave me.
You must promise me,
you will never
become a man like him.
NIKOLAI: Sergei! Come down here!
[IMITATING NIKOLAI]
Father is the only animal
that is threated.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
SERGEI: You're getting
too good at that.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
It'll be all right.
You almost
got your brother killed.
You almost got yourself killed.
Because you were afraid.
Fear will eat you.
It makes you weak.
Are you weak like your mother?
Crazy?
Or are you like me?
Because if you
show weakness to enemies,
it gives them an opening.
You are old enough
to understand.
You know my business. Yes?
One day, you will be in charge.
Dmitri, go.
Dmitri will go back
to school in New York
and you will stay here.
With me.
I think America
is making you soft.
It is for your own good.
Each of us have a path to walk.
Embrace who you really are
and you will
have the strength to walk it.
Come.
Come here.
I got you something.
You never
have to be afraid again.
He should have killed you!
What's going on with you?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Sergei, get back here!
[DOOR SLAMS]
[CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY]
Are you okay?
[TAPPING AT WINDOW]
-[HAWK TRILLS]
-[CONTINUES TAPPING AT WINDOW]
[HAWK TAKES OFF, SCREECHES]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[CRACKS]
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
Don't leave me with him.
I'm going.
-I have to.
-Why?
I can't explain it.
Something's happened to me.
What are you talking about?
Do you remember the place
we used to camp?
Where all you could hear
were the crickets and the owls?
And Mom used to
sing to us around the fire?
That land
is all I have left of her.
How does that make it okay?
Picture me there.
I'm sorry, Dima.
I am.
Just go if you're gonna go.
Go!
I won't be gone forever.
SAILOR: Where you headed?
SERGEI: Trying to get
outta England.
To Russia.
SAILOR: On this?
You know there's planes
and trains for that, don't you?
You on the run?
Yes.
I am.
Come on, then. Come on.
[SHIP HORN BLOWS]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[EARS RINGING]
[RUMBLING APPROACHES]
[RUMBLING INTENSIFIES]
[SNORTING]
[BELLOWING]
[SNORTS, LOWS]
[WOMAN SINGING
"BAYU BAYUSHKI BAYU" FAINTLY]
[SINGING GROWS LOUDER]
[DISTANT THUNDER RUMBLING]
[SINGING CONTINUES]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
NIKOLAI: She was weak.
Sick in her mind.
SERGEI: She died because
you sent her away.
Sergei!
-[ROARS]
-Run!
Sergei! [ECHOING]
NIKOLAI: Fear will eat you.
It makes you weak.
Each of us have a path to walk.
They are prey.
[HOOVES BEATING]
We are predators.
[BLOWS]
[LOWS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTS]
[LOWS]
[DISTANT GUNSHOT]
[FAINT AND DISTORTED SPEECH
IN RUSSIAN]
Just the horns. Leave the rest.
[GUN COCKS]
[IN RUSSIAN] You don't
belong here, kid. Go home.
[IN RUSSIAN] This is my home.
Is this yours?
Put it down!
Or you're dead.
-[ROARS]
-[GRUNTS]
-[DISTANT GRUNTING]
-[DISTANT BLOWS LANDING]
[WOMAN SINGING
"BAYU BAYUSHKI BAYU" FAINTLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[AIRCRAFT APPROACHING]
PILOT: Welcome home.
We stayed under the radar
as usual.
Call me when you need me again.
[VOICE MESSAGING BEEPS]
NIKOLAI: [ON PHONE]
Sergei, it is your father.
Come home. I miss you.
I am sorry for everything
that has happened.
[DMITRI LAUGHING]
DMITRI: [ON PHONE]
Just kidding. It's your brother.
I texted you.
Where have you been?
-[WATER SPLASHES]
-[GRUNTS]
You still hiding out
in the woods, huh?
Am I gonna see you
for my birthday?
Call me back.
[EXHALES]
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
[GUNSHOT]
[MEN CONVERSING IN RUSSIAN]
Get this shit on the truck!
Come on!
Let's get 'em up.
[IN RUSSIAN] Who is this?
[IN RUSSIAN]
This is private property.
So I was wondering
if you were going to lock up
before you leave.
MAN 4: [IN RUSSIAN] Move!
[IN ENGLISH] Move.
Why is it that
you kill the animal
and only take the horns?
Because we can.
[IN ENGLISH] "Because you can"?
Out of the way.
There's six of us
and only one of you.
There are six of you now.
Ain't got time for this.
I've got deadlines.
[SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
[MAN 5 SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
What the fuck?
-[GRUNTS]
-[EXCLAIMS]
-[GROWLS]
[IN ENGLISH] Go! Go!
Mr. Taglin.
I apologize.
This guy, he came outta nowhere.
A crazy local, or...
I don't know.
But I took care of it.
He won't be
bothering us anymore.
In a moment, you won't be
bothered by much of anything.
How did you...
Where's Mr. Taglin?
Oh, you're standing in him.
Found this. Interesting read.
You're a poacher.
Mr. Taglin, he hires poachers.
But these names...
-Drugs, weapons, trafficking...
-No, no, I, um--
What's your name?
Andre.
Andre who?
The men in that book,
they're the ones you want.
They're the ones in charge.
I can help you find them.
I don't need your help.
But I will be
adding these names to my list.
Andre who?
Lavigne.
Pretty low
on the pecking order, Andre.
Oh. Found you.
-[GRUNTS]
-[THUDS]
[SPITS]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
REPORTER: [ON VIDEO]
And now, today's headlines.
Crusading London prosecutor
Samantha Hodges
was gunned down last week
in broad daylight
following a string
of vicious attacks
targeting law enforcement
and the judiciary.
Memorial services
will be held later today.
-[RAIN PATTERING]
-CALYPSO: I met Samantha
when I first moved to London.
She was a mentor,
a dear friend
and one of the fiercest
fighters for justice
this city has ever known.
We all know who did this.
Samantha dared to stand
in Semyon Chorney's way
and hold him accountable.
And for that act of courage,
she lost her life.
[VOICE QUAVERING]
This system's broken.
-I'm sorry about your friend.
-Shit.
-I didn't mean to scare you.
-You did.
Sorry for your loss.
Did you know her well?
Actually,
I didn't know her at all.
Well then,
thank you for the condolences.
Calypso!
I think this belongs to you.
You're...
You're the boy.
But no. You were...
-You were...
-I was.
For three minutes.
Would have been longer
if you hadn't been there.
Those were
my grandmother's cards.
I actually still
carry the deck with me.
So, why'd you give it to me?
Guess I thought you needed it.
This all you had to go on?
How'd you find me?
Hunting people down
is sort of my thing.
Hunting?
You know who did this?
Yeah, I do.
They gonna get him?
Probably not.
What would you say
if I told you...
I already did?
A tiger's tooth?
I use whatever tools
are available.
Why would you do that?
Wasn't he responsible
for killing your friend?
Look. I've been trying to
find you for a very long time.
This is my way of saying
"thank you"
for saving my life.
I didn't ask you
to murder anyone. I'm a lawyer.
[SIGHS]
But that bastard
got what he deserved.
I know who your father is.
You're like him?
A gangster?
No.
I grew up watching my father
put evil into the world.
The old man
had it all figured out.
I was supposed
to follow in his footsteps
and take over
the family business.
But something happened to me
that day you found me.
So, I got as far away
from my father as I could.
And now I do what I can
to get rid of people like him.
So, you're the Hunter?
That's just what
they call me in the press.
I prefer Kraven.
Kraven?
Mmm. With a "K."
Hmm.
But the only people who have
heard that name are dead now.
Then I guess I'll just
have to watch my back.
[KRAVEN CHUCKLES]
So, do you live here?
I live about as far away
as you can possibly
get from this place.
But my brother does.
We, um...
I wasn't always there for him
so I check in when I can.
What about you?
How'd you end up here?
Some days, I'm not so sure.
Um...
My parents were lawyers,
so that's what I did.
I was in the DA's office
in New York for seven years
until I couldn't
take it anymore.
Well, sometimes, the law
can get in the way of justice.
It can.
Now, I'm in London
at one of the biggest law firms
in Europe.
I know where you work.
You're one of the best
investigative lawyers
in that place.
I also know
all your clients
aren't exactly angels.
That's true.
So, what are you really getting
done from behind that desk?
I have a list.
A list?
There are other ways to do
what you set out to do, Calypso.
Well, you're gonna
need a lawyer, or worse,
if you keep
messin' around in this world.
What about a partnership?
From inside that firm,
you can find people I can't.
-And then I could do what...
-Yeah, I get it.
I'll think about it.
Kraven.
And a little friendly advice?
If you keep going after
the names on that list,
people you care about
are gonna get hurt.
[ELEVATOR BELL RINGS]
ALEKSEI: Hey! Raja!
MAN 6: We need
to talk about this.
Yes. We go again?
-[RAJA PANTING]
-Go! Go!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Did you hear me?
Raja, come on, give it here.
Oh, you're going to make me beg?
You know I don't beg.
You think I'm weak?
-Give me that thing.
-[RAJA GROWLS]
-[SHOUTS] Raja!
-[RAJA WHIMPERS]
It's okay, Rajinka. Yes.
-You're my Ryazhuchka.
-[RAJA WHINES]
Papa loves you.
Papa forgives you.
One more thing.
Semyon Chorney
was killed in his prison cell.
Who got to him?
They're saying
it was the Hunter.
Faster than a cheetah,
cunning as a fox.
More ferocious than a tiger.
[CHUCKLES]
Tell me,
do you think
this Hunter actually exists?
Could be a load of bollocks.
But, then again,
I hear he's got a list.
And once you're on it,
you never come off.
And there's a good chance
you're on it.
If he is real,
he can be found.
I'll do some digging.
ALEKSEI: Wait.
Chorney's operations
are up for grabs, no?
Set a meet.
His top three guys.
[CAR DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
Your boss, Semyon Chorney,
is dead.
I intend to assume control
of his asset transactions.
One of you will be my partner.
Who's it going to be?
[CHUCKLES]
The best pitch wins.
[IN RUSSIAN]
He calls himself "Rhino".
He doesn't look
like a Rhino to me.
[IN ENGLISH]
But don't you want to know
why they call me the Rhino?
[IV DISCONNECTS]
Why do it to yourself?
They have to see
who they're dealing with.
[SKIN CRACKLING]
-[WINCES]
-[SKIN CONTINUES CRACKLING]
[IN RUSSIAN]
Get rid of him.
[WHINES]
Oh, it's okay, Raja.
It's okay.
[EXHALES]
[GRUNTS]
[BULLETS CLATTERING]
[IV CONNECTS]
[SIGHS IN RELIEF]
-[GUNSHOTS]
-[GRUNTING]
You can put your guns away.
If I want you dead,
I only have to raise my...
Don't!
When a rhino
sees his opportunity,
he doesn't hesitate.
He charges in and takes it.
So, I'll ask one more time.
Which one of you
is going to be my partner?
[GRUNTS]
Hell of a pitch.
We have a winner.
[CHUCKLES]
[PIANO PLAYING
"SIGN OF THE TIMES"]
[IMITATING HARRY STYLES]
Just stop your crying
It's a sign of the times
Welcome to the final show
Hope you're wearing
your best clothes
[SOFT CHATTER AND CONVERSATION]
You can't bribe the door
On your way to the sky
You look pretty good down here
But you ain't really good
[SOFT APPLAUSE]
My son Dmitri.
This next one's for you, Papa.
[PLAYING "THEY CAN'T
TAKE THAT AWAY FROM ME"]
[IMITATING TONY BENNETT]
The way you wear your hat...
He does for me.
He knows I like Tony Bennett.
Do you like Tony Bennett?
I don't trust anyone
who doesn't like Tony Bennett.
He can do anyone.
He's like chameleon.
They can't take that
away from me...
These assassins...
if they can
get your boss in cage...
I think we all
need to take precautions.
I understand.
Hmm. Come closer.
Chorney, he is gone.
That makes your operations
become vulnerable.
I can offer you security,
distribution
and most critically,
peace of mind.
Sounds good. I'm on board.
Just like that?
You don't
want to think about it?
-Order has to be restored.
-[CHUCKLES]
The sooner, the better.
You have already done deal.
Didn't you? Who with?
The Rhino sends his regards.
[GUNFIRE]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
-[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
-[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
[WHIMPERING]
[GUNFIRE AND SCREAMING RECEDE]
Get up.
[NIKOLAI EXHALES]
You're hit.
Are you all right, Papa?
[GULPS]
Look at what
they have done to my club.
I get attacked on my own ground.
And who do I have to defend me?
My son,
the piano player.
Go on. Hit me!
Fight me!
I need fighters, not coward.
You won't even defend yourself.
The Kravinoff hit failed.
All of our guys are dead.
[HISSES]
Nikolai is a tough old bear.
He won't go quietly, you know.
I found this
slipped under my door.
ALEKSEI:
Nikolai Kravinoff's son,
Sergei, is the Hunter?
But what is this Kraven?
MAN 6: Apparently, that's what
he calls himself.
This can't be real.
-Can it?
-Not sure.
Put the Foreigner on this.
He's a bit of a freak
but he's been obsessed
with the Hunter for years.
Maybe he can figure out
what the fuck is going on.
Hey!
[IN RUSSIAN]
What are you doing?
THE FOREIGNER:
[IN RUSSIAN] It's okay.
I'm looking for the prisoner who
killed Semyon Chorney.
Turn around.
You don't have access here!
They call me the Foreigner,
because I'm not from
around anywhere.
[IN ENGLISH] One.
Two.
Three.
[GUNSHOTS]
I'll be seeing ya.
[FAINT TRAFFIC IN BACKGROUND]
-[PEOPLE SPEAKING FAINTLY]
-[SIGHS]
MAN 7: That's great.
Is it down by the river there?
[SHOWER RUNNING]
[GRUNTS]
-KRAVEN: Surprise!
-[DMITRI SCREAMS]
-Jesus! Sergei!
-[LAUGHING]
[EXCLAIMS]
You scared the shit out of me!
Happy birthday, baby brother.
[KISSES]
I love you, man!
[CHUCKLES]
What are we gonna do, huh?
-Well, you're not wearing that.
-Great!
-Let's stay in.
-What?
It's my birthday.
On your birthday, we can...
go to the petting zoo
or wherever it is you let loose.
But, tonight, this.
You think
I can fit in that?
This is too big on me,
so this would be
perfect for you.
-Sorry.
-Thank you.
Pleasure.
Nice perfume, by the way.
Thanks, but I'm not
actually wearing any.
[UNDER BREATH] No.
She was gonna
find out soon enough.
DMITRI: Papa was sitting
right here.
It all happened so fast.
You find out what you're made of
in a moment like that.
I'm a coward.
Dima, you're not a coward.
It's natural to feel fear.
That's just
your instinct talking.
Why don't we get
to choose who we are?
Why do I have to be me?
I need to be strong, fearless.
I would run towards the bullets,
I won't crumble to the ground.
Why want to be
anybody but yourself?
So he'd respect me for once!
Papa's a criminal.
So, what good is his respect?
You act like
you don't care what he thinks.
That you're above it.
-That he can't touch you.
-Well, he can't.
He made you hate people.
I don't hate people.
I hate what people do.
But I don't hate people.
I guess then...
Papa was right about one thing.
Yeah? What's...
[IMITATING NIKOLAI]
"Men should be the only animal
that is threated."
NIKOLAI: I'm glad
I didn't miss the party.
[DMITRI CHUCKLES]
-How could I stay away...
-DMITRI: Papa!
...and miss the chance
and see both my sons?
Dmitri.
-For you.
-Oh.
I don't expect you
to give me a hug,
but a handshake?
Dasha.
I just came for one toast,
to honor Dmitri
on his big day.
Pour.
Pour for men, not for boys.
Come on, Sergei.
To the Kravinoffs.
May we learn someday
to forget the past
and imagine future
together...
as family.
[TOASTING IN RUSSIAN]
[SERGEI AND DMITRI
MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Down we go.
You okay?
Sergei.
Huh?
I know why you come every year.
'Cause you...
feel guilty...
for leaving me with him.
I forgive you...
for...
everything.
I'm sorry.
[WOMAN SINGING
"BAYU BAYUSHKI BAYU" FAINTLY]
[FAN RATTLING]
[SIGHS]
MOTHER: Sergei! Sergei!
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
They never want anything,
don't they?
Hold that, will ya?
Please? Buddy?
[ELEVATOR BELL RINGS]
[SIGHS]
Penthouse, please.
-I tried to hold it for you.
-No, you didn't.
This?
It's my travel knife.
Use it for work.
Ah.
What do you do for work,
exactly?
I hunt...
people.
[ELEVATOR BELL RINGS]
Dmitri?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
DMITRI: Please! Please! Let go!
[YELLS]
[GLASS AND METAL SHATTERS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Stop! Please, please!
Wait, wait, wait!
We can figure this out.
MAN 8: Put him under.
There he is.
Lose him!
KRAVEN: Get the fuck
out the way!
WOMAN 3: Watch it!
[TIRES SCREECH]
-[GRUNTS]
-[GLASS SHATTERS]
[CAR HORN HONKS]
[ROARS]
-[THUDS]
-[GRUNTS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Fuck!
Go!
[ENGINE REVVING]
Faster!
[KRAVEN YELLS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
[GRUNTS]
[TRAFFIC PASSING AND HONKING]
Dmitri!
-[GRUNTS]
-[GUNSHOT]
It's bulletproof, idiot!
Inside and out!
Get him off!
[GRUNTING]
[METAL CREAKING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[CAR HORN HONKING]
[GRUNTS]
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[GROANS]
[YELLS]
[ALARM BEEPING]
[ROARS]
[HELICOPTER ENGINE REVVING]
[GUNFIRE]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[GRUNTS]
-[ALARM BEEPING RAPIDLY]
-Go! Go!
[YELLS]
[ALARM CONTINUES BEEPING]
[GRUNTS]
[CLANGS]
[GASPING]
Dima!
MAN 10: Hello, sir.
Can I help you?
A towel, maybe?
CALYPSO: Thank you so much.
Appreciate it.
Sir. I think you left
your shoes in the lobby.
-I'm pretty sure I didn't.
-Why don't we go
and have a look?
Not enough volts
in there, friend.
Brian! Everything's fine.
He's a client.
What the hell, Sergei?
I told you I'd think
about your offer.
You cannot
come in here like this.
This is my place of business.
They got my brother.
-Who got your brother?
-There were four of them.
Took him from his place.
-So, you saw them?
-There was this one guy.
Dark hair, brown eyes.
He's got a scar under
his left eye. Sounded Turkish.
Jesus.
You spoke to them.
Not exactly.
But there was
some screaming involved.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
Let's get into it, then.
I should have
been there for him.
I couldn't sleep, so...
I left and went
for a walk and my...
We're gonna find him.
[SIGHS]
Okay?
I'm gonna do what I do,
get us a name.
And then,
you are going to do what you do.
And we will get him back.
I'm looking for a mercenary,
just ran a kidnapping op
in London.
Moon-shaped scar
under his left eye.
Smokes Turkish cigarettes,
probably a national.
Find him.
NIKOLAI: Sergei.
Who are they?
They would not say.
But you know, don't you?
My list of enemies is long.
Look what they did to him.
How much do they want?
20 million.
In 48 hours.
Pay them.
It is complicated.
No. It's not. It's very simple.
You have the money
and he's your son.
This is not about money.
This is about power.
If I pay,
I am weak.
If I show weakness,
I begin to lose everything
I've spent lifetime building.
A lifetime building what?
You're a drug dealer.
[GRUNTS]
You don't get
to do that anymore.
Dmitri is innocent.
You let him die,
his blood is on your hands.
On my hands?
My hands?
I did not abandon him.
You abandoned him.
You.
He was dead
the moment he was taken!
Whether I pay or not!
No, you...
You don't know that.
Yes. I know.
Because that is what I would do.
You're despicable.
Of course I want him back.
I want both my sons back.
Hmm.
Some legend you've become.
MAN 8: Wake up!
Take these.
Antibiotics. I can't
have you dying on me, can I?
[IMITATING MAN 8] "Can't have
you dying on me, can I?"
That's good. [SNIFFS]
[GRUNTS]
Ömer Ozdemir.
He's holed up in a monastery
in the outskirts of Ankara.
Thank you.
You can thank me
by never calling me again.
We'll see.
[FOOTSTEPS RECEDING]
THE FOREIGNER: How'd it go?
-She took it.
-Of course she took it.
But did she believe you?
Yeah. She trusts me.
Hmm.
Which is why I want double
what your boss promised.
Double?
Why not triple?
What game are you playing?
[CHUCKLES]
[VOICE DISTORTING] One.
Two.
Three.
-[PHONE RINGING]
-[GUNSHOT OVER PHONE]
It's done.
[SPEED DIAL CALLING]
Get ready.
The Hunter is on his way.
CALYPSO: [ON PHONE] Sergei,
the man you're looking for
is Ömer Ozdemir.
I found an old monastery
in his family name in Turkey.
And that is where
you'll find your brother.
Thank you for this.
All right, Ellie, let's go!
-[DART THWICKS]
-[GRUNTS]
[SOFTLY] Okay.
[DISTANT THUD]
[DART SWISHES]
[MEN CONVERSING IN TURKISH]
[DISTANT THUD]
[MEN CONTINUE CONVERSING
IN TURKISH]
[CONVERSATION RECEDING]
[MAN IN DISTANCE
SHOUTING IN TURKISH]
-[GRUNTS]
-[GUNSHOT]
[MEN EXCLAIM IN TURKISH]
[IN ENGLISH] It's him.
[GUNS COCKING]
[MAN SCREAMS]
-[GUN FIRES]
-[YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
[DISTANT GUNFIRE]
He's there.
Where's Dmitri?
-[KRAVEN YELLS]
-[GRUNTS]
Where is he?
Drop me and you'll never
find your brother...
Kraven.
-[EXPLOSION]
-[MAN 8 SCREAMING]
[THUDS]
[ROCKSLIDE RUMBLING]
How do you know my name?
Who set me up?
Who took my brother?
The Rhino.
He's killed us both now.
[KRAVEN EXCLAIMS]
[GRUNTS]
[FAINT CONVERSATION IN TURKISH]
MAN 11: [IN TURKISH]
Who are you?
[IN TURKISH] Does one of you
have an evidence bag?
I left mine in the car.
What's that?
[IN ENGLISH]
This is crushed rosary peas.
The man who did this
knows his toxins.
[VOICE DISTORTING] One.
Two.
Three.
[BLADE WITHDRAWS]
[IN ENGLISH] What are you doing?
-[SLICES]
-[GAGS]
Be seeing ya.
[RAJA BARKING]
-[SNAPS FINGERS]
-That's enough, Raja. Hmm.
I'm very sorry
about your finger.
Collateral damage.
Cut him free.
[BLADE FLICKS]
We met once...
on your father's hunting trip.
I, uh... don't remember.
No, you wouldn't.
My hair was different.
You were very young.
Me?
I never forgot.
So, have you spoken
to my father?
Has he agreed to pay?
No. [CHUCKLING]
Nikolai Kravinoff was never
going to hand over $20 million
to get his bastard son back.
You're an accident, Dmitri.
You came into this world
as an accident,
and you came into my possession
as an accident.
So, can I go?
Those men who took you,
they weren't there for you.
They were there
for your brother.
Sergei?
Both of you went in...
but when my guys got up there?
Poof!
He'd vanished.
As he always does.
So, I took you.
I got lucky.
Why would you ever want Sergei?
He never hurt anyone.
You really don't know, do you?
Know what?
ALEKSEI: Wait for the end.
That's the best part.
DMITRI: Kraven?
Apparently, that's
what he calls himself now.
You think my brother Sergei
is the Hunter?
The Hunter is a story.
A fable
to put fear into criminals.
Clearly, you didn't know
your brother very well.
What do you mean "didn't"?
Kraven had a list.
Once you're on it,
you never come off.
So, I went after him first.
[ROCK THUDS]
MAN 12: Let me record this.
We've got Kraven.
Eh, I don't know about that.
[GRUNTS, EXCLAIMS]
[NECK CRACKS]
-Hello?
-KRAVEN: Calypso, it's me.
The whole thing was a trap.
The Rhino,
he knows who I am.
He'll be after you next.
Sergei, what are you...
Shit!
There are five guys walking in
who do not look
like they belong here.
KRAVEN: You need
to get out of there now.
Get to the cargo terminal
at Stansted.
I'll have someone
meet you there.
I call this my feed bag.
It's a mixture of medications
to manage my condition.
What happened to you?
I was underestimated, too.
In and out of hospitals.
They never
quite knew what was wrong.
I knew I would never have
your father's respect...
or anyone else's...
until I was strong.
I tried everything.
And then,
I found someone.
In New York,
a biochemist,
a professor, Miles Warren.
He was developing a procedure
to increase strength
tenfold.
I signed up on the spot.
My skin, it started to harden.
I was...
indestructible,
[VOICE DEEPENS] like a rhino.
[IN NORMAL VOICE, GRIMACING]
But the pain,
it was too much.
[THUDS]
[IV CONNECTS]
[SIGHS]
I think there is an animal
in each one of us, Dmitri.
I'm taking over
your father's territory.
I want you to be my partner.
The Kravinoff name
still opens a lot of doors
and you'll finally get
the consideration you deserve.
You're right.
I have been underestimated...
my whole life.
But if you think
I'm gonna betray my family,
you're wrong.
MAN 6: Boss.
Our boys haven't checked in.
I can't reach 'em.
Kraven is alive.
Hey, Bert!
Alpha team, Bravo team.
He's here.
-[RAJA BARKS]
-[ELEVATOR BELL RINGS]
[ELEVATOR BELL
CONTINUES RINGING]
-[ELEVATOR BELL RINGS]
-[THE FOREIGNER WHISTLING]
Cute.
Will your trick still work
when I remove
your eyeballs from your head?
Relax.
[PLANE ENGINE WHIRRING]
I'm sorry I got you
wrapped up in all of this.
-Any word on Dmitri?
-Not yet.
Three of my sources
have gone offline
while tracking
the Rhino's plane.
I don't like
the feel of this at all.
So, what is this place?
My mother's family
used to own this property.
But it's really the only thing
I have left from her.
[SOFT RUSTLING]
What is happening right now?
We're being hunted.
By who?
-[SNARLS]
-[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLS, GRUNTS]
[GRUNTS]
You don't hunt me!
Yeah, get pissed.
What are you gonna do?
Come on, show me!
-[ROARS]
I've seen her around
since she was a cub,
but she's a lot bigger
than I remember.
You're a goddamn lunatic.
I swear.
You just figure that out now?
I know I hired you for the job.
ALEKSEI: But what is Kraven
to you? Why the obsession?
My mentor was one
of the greatest assassins
who ever lived.
He taught me everything I know.
He was like a brother to me.
Maybe you knew him?
Hmm. Of him.
He was murdered.
One man made it inside
and cut his throat.
Kraven?
So, I traveled the world,
followed him wherever he went.
But Kraven
is nature's perfect predator.
He has no known weaknesses.
[SIGHS]
But you found one.
And I know how to exploit it.
Get to the part
where I start to give a shit.
These are Eastern Siberian
rosary peas.
A rare species.
I found their residue
on a poison in the monastery.
These peas are only native
to a specific region in Siberia.
That's where we'll find him.
[CHUCKLES]
Whoa, careful with that.
Actually, I'm pretty good
with one of these things.
Archery at summer camp.
Figwort.
Wood avens.
Tribulus.
Mm-hmm.
Rosary peas?
You seem to know your stuff.
-They'll kill you.
-Or save you.
Nature's funny like that.
What are you trying to do here?
Tell me about this.
It was my grandmother's.
We were on safari
visiting her that day.
I've been trying to figure out
what was in here for years.
My grandmother was kind of a...
mystic.
She had
a lot of crazy stuff around.
My parents
didn't like to talk about it,
but she was
a very powerful woman.
She said it would heal
whoever drank it...
in undreamed-of ways.
I was just a kid.
I didn't know
what it would actually do.
This saved my life.
Did it?
Trust me. It changed me.
Exactly.
Look at what you became.
I need to know what was in here.
And if you can get any more.
No.
She died
not long after that trip
and I never saw her again.
I heard back
from one of my sources.
The Rhino is on the move.
We should know more very soon.
I knew you'd be good at this.
Sergei.
We're gonna get Dmitri back.
But is all of this
really worth it?
Calypso, I was made to do this.
I'm the greatest hunter
on this planet. It's undeniable.
There's nobody I can't
track down, nobody I can't beat.
There's nobody can even
touch me. So, no.
Why would I want to stop?
It's called karma.
She catches up to you.
Not me.
I'm faster than she is.
But Dmitri wasn't.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
Interesting piece.
It's gonna take more than a gun
to kill Kraven.
I find this formula
that was developed by MI6
to be particularly effective.
May I?
It first brings on
your darkest nightmares,
then paralysis
of your vital organs
before a most violent death.
[CHUCKLES]
I like your style.
[PHONE RINGING]
Only one person has this number.
-Dima, where are you?
-DMITRI: Sergei.
I'm sorry.
They made me call you.
KRAVEN: Dmitri.
I'm afraid not.
But now you know he is alive.
What do you want?
A life without
looking over my shoulder.
You have two choices.
I know you hate your father
as much as I do.
So, you and I,
and young Dmitri here,
we work together.
You could be my partners.
Or I kill you and--
Okay, then.
Now we go hunt the Hunter.
Spread out.
Bring me his body.
Or don't come back.
Raja.
Where is he?
[BARKS]
He's already here.
-[ROARS]
-[GUNSHOTS]
Oh, shit! Look out!
[GUNFIRE]
[EXCLAIMING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[CLICKS]
[YELLS]
[SCREAMS]
Amateurs.
So embarrassing for us.
Do it.
[RADIO BEEPS]
Start the run.
[GRUNTS]
[EXCLAIMS]
Fire in the hole.
You got to be kidding.
[EXPLOSIONS]
[GRUNTS]
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BIRDS CALLING]
[WINCES]
[STRAINING]
[MOANING GROGGILY]
[SPIDERS CHITTERING]
[EXCLAIMS]
[DISTORTED VOICES SINGING
IN RUSSIAN]
[KRAVEN HYPERVENTILATING]
[SERGEI'S MOTHER WHIMPERS]
[IN RUSSIAN] The spiders!
[KRAVEN SCREAMS]
[MOTHER'S SCREAMS ECHOING]
[SPIDERS CONTINUE CHITTERING]
[GROANS]
THE FOREIGNER: Hallucinations
are just the beginning.
[DISTORTING] Are you seeing
your worst nightmares?
One.
Two.
Three.
-[WINCING]
-[DARTS FIRE]
[GRUNTS]
As the poison makes its way
to your spinal cord,
you'll begin to lose
all motor functions.
Then asphyxiation. [ECHOING]
So, you're the legend.
The myth.
[GRUNTING]
But look at you now.
You're just a man.
[CHOKES, GRUNTS]
[KRAVEN BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
You give him hell, Kraven.
[GROANS]
[KRAVEN PANTING]
Honestly,
I thought that would be harder.
[STRAINS]
It's done.
But the brother's
still out there.
Go find him.
Let's go.
[VOICE DISTORTING] One.
Two.
-[BOLT FIRES]
-[GRUNTS]
Three, motherfucker.
Goodbye, Kraven the Hunter.
DMITRI: Sergei!
BERT: Can't catch a break,
can you, mate?
[SIGHS]
Legends don't die.
Now get the fuck up, Kraven.
[DISTORTED]
-[CALYPSO EXCLAIMS]
-[GASPS]
[COUGHS]
I knew you had more of that.
Well, forgive me
for not trusting a lunatic
with my family's deepest legacy.
Get up.
Okay.
[GROANS]
Well, that must be
some summer camp.
You're not the only one
with secrets.
Don't make me regret this.
BERT: It's over.
Kraven's dead.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
What a day. [TITTERS]
Put him in the car.
Who knows?
Maybe Nikolai will pay
now that he has
only one son left.
[RADIO BEEPS]
Does anyone else see
what I'm seeing here?
[RUMBLING APPROACHING]
-[RUMBLING]
-[LOWING LOUDLY]
[SKIN CRACKLING]
[WINCING]
[THUDS]
[MEN SCREAMING]
[YELLS]
[IN DEEP VOICE] Kraven!
-[RHINO ROARS]
-[KRAVEN GRUNTS]
[GROANS, STRAINING]
Gosh, you're really heavy.
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[THUDS]
[LOWS]
-[MAN SCREAMS]
-[LOWING LOUDLY]
[RUMBLING RECEDES]
Sergei.
[METAL CREAKING]
[RHINO YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
[KRAVEN GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[GROWLING]
[EXCLAIMS]
[GRUNTS]
[SPITS]
[RHINO YELLS]
[YELLS, GRUNTS]
[YELLS, CHOKES]
[CHOKING] My father
was right about one thing.
You are nothing.
[GROWLING]
[EXCLAIMS]
[GROANS]
[GAGS]
[RHINO ROARS]
[KRAVEN YELLS]
[LOWS]
[RHINO YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
[CHOKES]
The video of me,
how did you get it?
[COUGHING]
Who sent it?
[GROANS]
How is it
that even the great Hunter
can't see what was
always right in front of him?
[RHINO COUGHS]
[GUN COCKS]
No.
He deserves to die.
And he will.
But, Dmitri, that's not you.
[RHINO GROANING]
[IN NORMAL VOICE] I wish...
I wish I never met...
you Kravinoffs.
[EXHALES]
[TWIG SNAPS]
[UNZIPS TENT]
Sergei.
How did you find me?
I'm a hunter.
It's what we do.
You sent the video
and told the Rhino who I was.
Did you really think
father would not recognize
actions of his own son?
An assassin
who uses all the methods
of animals of the jungle?
You, of all people,
should recognize and appreciate
the beauty of the trap I set.
The Rhino was coming for you.
You weren't strong enough
to fight him off by yourself?
Exactly.
But my son...
My real son...
Kraven... [CHUCKLES]
No one is stronger.
And I knew
you would not go after him
for me.
So, I sent him after you.
Some trap.
I mean, Dmitri could have died,
but that's the price
-of doing business, right?
-No.
Because I know
you would not let anything
happen to our precious Dmitri.
KRAVEN: Hmm.
Our empire is secure.
So, what now?
Papa, do we...
forget about the past?
Imagine a future together?
As family.
[SIGHS]
Sergei!
Where are you going?
I could have come for you...
years ago.
But I didn't.
After everything you'd done...
All the pain
you put in the world,
you were my father.
I still am.
Sit.
"Never fear death."
Isn't that what you taught me?
[BEAR GROWLS IN DISTANCE]
[BEAR GROWLING]
[BULLETS CLATTER]
[GROWLING GROWS CLOSER]
-[BEAR ROARS]
-[NIKOLAI SCREAMS]
[BEAR SNARLING]
[PIANO PLAYING "CHANGES"
BY BLACK SABBATH]
DMITRI: [IMITATING OZZY
OSBOURNE] I feel unhappy
I feel so sad
[PIANO CONTINUES]
I've lost the best friend
That I ever had
I'm going through changes
[FAINT APPLAUSE]
KRAVEN: Happy Birthday, Dima.
It is a happy birthday.
First one in a long time.
That's thanks to you,
Sergei.
Aw, come on.
-Or Kraven, should I say.
-Nah.
What do I call you now?
Mr. Kraven?
You know who I am.
I know you.
That was, um... hell...
what I went through.
But it also
freed me.
I...
I feel almost, born again.
[CHUCKLES]
I found a doctor in New York.
A little unorthodox,
I must admit.
KRAVEN: Mm-hmm.
But he really helped me.
I mean...
changed me.
-How so?
-Hang on a sec.
Huh?
Mmm.
[DMITRI SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
Since when did you have
friends in the bratva, huh?
I have business
with lots of people.
Business? I thought you said
you wanted to sell Papa's assets
-and get out of the business.
-I changed my mind.
I didn't pull your ass
out of the fire
so you can become
like our father.
Are you serious?
You put my ass in that fire.
You're a man
just like our father.
No, I'm nothing like him.
I have a code.
-And you're different than him?
-I'm better than him.
You're not better than him.
You're worse.
How did Papa die again?
A hunting accident, was it?
Don't lie to me.
You think you have
some kind of honor, huh?
Some kind of code?
Bullshit.
You're just another man
hunting for a trophy.
KRAVEN: Hey!
Dmitri...
You should see
the look on your face.
Hey!
Dmitri.
You know me.
I've always been a chameleon.
It's the one thing
I was ever good at.
Who is this doctor?
What did he do to you?
You want me to be weak,
so that you can be strong.
But I'm strong now.
I can be whoever I want to be.
The Rhino is gone. Dad is gone.
It's all just there
for the taking.
I'm gonna take it.
You know
I can't let you do that.
Go home, Kraven.
Dad left you something.
NIKOLAI: Sergei...
each of us has path to walk.
Embrace who you really are
and you will have
the strength to walk it.
You are more than my child.
You are me...
and I am you.
We are hunters,
the greatest
the world has ever known.
[VOICES SINGING
TRADITIONAL MUSIC IN RUSSIAN]
[TRADITIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]