Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[HIP HOP MUSIC PLAYING]
-[TIRES SCREECHING]
-[MARCUS SCREAMING]
[GASPING]
Hey, slow down, Mike, okay?
You're making me sick.
I would slow down
if you hadn't already made us late.
We're... We're not late, okay?
You're just anxious.
No, I'm anxious
'cause you made us late.
I'm not doin' this with you
in the next phase of our lives.
You're gon' respect my time.
-[TIRES SCREECH]
-[MARCUS GROANS]
My stomach. My stomach.
Hey, Mike, look,
pull over at that store right there.
I need a ginger ale.
Look, we don't have no time
to get no ginger ale, man.
Come on, Mike, I'm sick.
You're freaking me out, okay?
I feel like I'm gonna throw...
[GULPS] throw up.
I dare you, Marcus.
[MARCUS GAGGING]
You got 90 seconds, all right?
Ginger ale and nothing else.
-I am a grown-ass man, okay?
-Mm-hmm.
Just be nice.
Oh. Okay. 85 seconds.
[EXCLAIMING]
[SIZZLING]
Are those dogs fresh?
I put 'em on yesterday.
Well, give me one and put some relish
and some mustard on that motherfucker.
Hook it up. Come on, hurry up.
No, that one right there.
Yeah. Yeah, that right there. Hurry up.
Gotta go, gotta go.
Don't be takin' your time.
Yeah, my man.
Oh!
MAN: Hey, open the register.
-No, no, no.
-Now!
Sir, today is not the day.
-[GUN COCKING]
-Shut the fuck up!
Look, if I'm not in that car in 15 seconds,
there's a very surly man that's comin' in here
and we both are fucked.
-Marcus.
-Hey, don't fuckin' move.
The fuck over there!
'Ey, Mike, I told this guy I had to go.
Mm-mm.
Is that Skittles on the counter, Marcus?
Well, he was takin' a long time
with the ginger ale.
That is incorrect. He grabbed that ginger ale
the second he came in here.
A hot dog, Marcus?
You're not supposed to be eatin' that shit.
-This is not mine, Mike.
-Yes, it is.
Mind your business with your tattletaling ass.
Everybody shut the fuck up!
Sir, I'm gonna need you
to lower your weapon.
Come take my weapon, then, motherfucker.
Don't antagonize him.
Marcus, get in the car.
Mike, he has a gun to my head.
Wanna deal with him,
you wanna deal with me?
Sorry, sir, but I gotta go.
[MAN SCREAMS IN PAIN]
You didn't have to shoot him, Mike.
Get in the car.
Call 911.
SHOPKEEPER: Aren't you the police?
CHRISTINE: Other people look at you
and see the tailored suits,
the cars, the watches.
I met you without any of that.
Stripped, basically naked...
-which is 90% of why I'm marrying you.
-[GUESTS LAUGHING]
[BOTH LAUGH]
I met you at your lowest.
You'd been shot.
But there was a fire in you that was...
...extraordinary.
And I vow to spend the rest of my life
fanning that flame.
CHAPLAIN: I now pronounce you...
husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Yes!
[GUESTS CHEERING]
-I love it.
-Oh.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
KELLY: You know, it kinda makes sense
that he married his therapist after he got shot.
I love that for him.
Mental health is super important.
Well, it was his physical therapist.
-Congratulations, Michael.
-Rita. Thank you, thank you.
Mr. Mayor.
Oh, not yet. Don't jinx it.
I'm still just a lowly US Attorney.
[LAUGHS]
I've been watching what you're doin'.
-You got my vote.
-Oh, thank you.
Congratulations to you.
I mean, the definition
of a power couple right there.
-I'll grab you a drink.
-Okay.
-Can I get you anything?
-No, I'm good, thank you.
And all this time,
I thought you were a terminal bachelor.
I... I... I even surprised myself with this one.
Yeah, I guess
you just hadn't met the right one.
I had some growing up to do.
You were 50.
-[GUESTS CHEERING, CLAPPING]
-MARCUS: Uh...
Okay. Uh...
I'm gonna pre-apologize
for whatever he says.
-[SNIFFLING]
-MIKE: Uh-uh...
-Mike.
-No, you know how it is.
-MIKE: Don't... Marcus!
-Marcus. Come...
-MARCUS: Let me get it out!
Come on, man.
-Everything you have been through, man.
-Okay.
The witch. The Bruja.
The prostitute.
My sister. 'Member?
You coulda told me about my sister, Mike.
You coulda told me that.
I would've embraced you,
if that's who she was feeling.
-I love you, Mike.
-MIKE: No doubt.
You know, Cap would've loved
to have been here to see this.
But you know what?
We got his daughter, Judy,
and his granddaughter, Callie.
She wants to say something.
Um...
My granddad loved you guys.
And if he were here,
he would have told you not to F this up.
[ALL LAUGHING]
That's what he would've said.
Yeah, he woulda said, "Don't fuck it up."
Exactly.
Oh, excuse me.
'Ey.
Mike, you been my partner a long time.
Yes, sir.
Now he's gonna be your partner, Christine.
[EXHALES]
To Mike and Christine Lowrey.
-For life!
-ALL: For life!
-[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
-[GUESTS CHEERING]
CROWD: [CHANTING] Go Marcus! Go Marcus!
Go Marcus! Go Marcus!
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
[HEART THUMPING]
[MUFFLED CHANTING]
MARCUS: Oh, shit.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
What happened? What happened?!
Marcus. Marcus!
What's the address?
Let me in, let me in, let me in. Back up.
This is Captain Rita Secada.
I have an officer in cardiac arrest.
[DISTORTED HEART BEATING]
-MIKE: Come on, man.
-[DEFIBRILLATOR CLACKS]
-[THUNDERCLAP]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[SQUAWKING]
It's not your time.
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
[ECG BEEPING STEADILY]
[UPBEAT LATIN MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Marcus!
Marc-- Marc--!
This guy.
[HORNS HONKING IN DISTANCE]
Hey, buddy.
What you doing?
I spent my whole life being scared, Mike.
I wasted so much time.
Why... Why... Why don't you, uh...
Why don't you just step back
from the edge a little bit, please?
What year is it?
It's Tuesday.
Same year your ass was wobbling in.
Oh, wow. Felt like it was five years.
I was in the basement of the ocean.
All my bullshit was gone.
Just freedom.
And full body love, Mike.
Full body love.
Okay.
Why... Why... Why don't you, uh...
...love your full body
back from the ledge, please?
MARCUS: Nothing to be scared of.
It's not my time, baby.
It's not my time.
-[DOOR OPENS]
-Mr. Burnett!
Hey, I got him.
He's just, um...
[SIGHS BLISSFULLY]
I don't know what the fuck he's doing. Uh...
But I got it. I got him.
We're good. We are good.
-We are great!
-'Ey...
-Miami!
-Whoa!
MIKE: 305 for life!
Kakow!
All right. Just stop. You gon' put
somebody's eye out with that thing, man.
-I'm bringing the thunder, Mike.
-I get it.
Bringing the thunder. [ROARS]
All right. There you go.
Oh, man. Bring it in.
Thought I lost you, brother.
Couldn't lose me if you tried.
You know your ass is out, right?
Everybody's ass is out, Mike.
Hey.
There's a storm coming.
No. Not that kind of storm.
You're gonna be tested.
Things are gonna get bad,
and you're gonna have to make
a really hard choice.
Just know you're good.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
This is my private time, Mr. McGrath.
How may I help you?
-I need you to move some money.
-Your money?
Your boss's, actually.
I need it to be cartel cash.
Just under 20 million.
Backdated series of transfers
beginning 2004, ending January 2020...
into...
...that account.
In the name
of the late Captain Conrad Howard.
I have people who can handle logistics.
I really just need your login credentials.
And why would I give you those?
Oh, my God! [CRYING]
[SHUSHING]
[CRYING SOFTLY]
MCGRATH: Come here, darling.
Come on.
[CONTINUES CRYING]
Come here.
You can't transfer funds from a phone.
Hey, honey, what's going on?
Do they know each other?
[SOBS]
Honey, who's there with you?
-All right, all right!
-Honey--?
Here we go.
They'll kill you for this.
They're not even gonna know
this happened.
Your girlfriend
heard you on the phone with your wife
and realized
you were never gonna divorce her.
And in a fit of passion, she shot you.
[WOMAN GASPS]
Your bodyguard tried to step in,
but he was too late.
[SOBBING]
And realizing the horror of her actions...
[CLICKS TONGUE]
she took her own life.
-[GASPS] No!
-[GUNSHOT]
THERESA: Honey, what are you doing?
-You had a heart attack two weeks ago.
-Exactly.
They call it a widow-maker for a reason.
You need to be in the hospital, baby.
Hey, I tried to told his ass, T.
Apparently, he's an adult.
He was allowed to sign hisself out.
Hey, babe. Look, come on.
I couldn't take one more second away from you.
All these stents in me got my blood flowing.
-I'm on D way.
-All right, now.
[GROWLING PLAYFULLY]
Ey. Ey. Come on, man.
That's my phone.
-I love you, Marcus.
-MIKE: We'll be there in 10.
All right, babe. All right. Love you.
Hey, Mike.
I wasn't even gonna tell you this...
but this ain't the first time we done this.
We ride together all the time,
what you mean?
No, I'm talking about our souls.
You know, we've ridden together,
but I saw it all, Mike.
We're bound.
And we have been for lifetimes.
We haven't always been Mike and Marcus,
but we've always been us.
Um...
What you talking 'bout?
We're soulmates.
[CHUCKLING]
-Yup.
-Yeah.
Naw.
Yeah, I kind of... I saw my soulmate
looking a little different than that.
See... See, Mike, you stuck in the physical.
Souls don't have dicks.
I'm pretty sure
my soul has a dick, Marcus.
See? That's that shit right there.
That's why we're stuck.
You know, I wasn't gonna tell you
this shit either,
but my soul
is more advanced than your soul.
MIKE: Mm. Mm-hmm.
It's not that your soul is stupid.
-Mm-hmm.
-You know?
It's just that you're more like a baby soul.
You know?
And I'm more like a mother soul.
And I just gotta suckle ya.
[CHUCKLES] You know? Put you on that titty.
[CHUCKLING] You know?
Hey. How long you think
your brain went without oxygen?
-MEGAN: Daddy!
-Daddy's home.
-Baby! Oh, baby, you're back.
-Where my family? My family.
Hey, baby.
[ALL CHATTER EXCITEDLY]
Oh! Little Marcus!
Say hi to Pop-pop.
Say hi to Granddad.
-Oh, I missed you so--!
-MARCUS: Look at you, woman.
No, come on, look at me, baby.
[MARCUS MOANING]
-We're gonna have to hose them down.
-CHRISTINE: Mm!
All right. All right, we get it. We get it.
Put some ice in your drawers or somethin'.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, that's funny.
Are you feeling good, Marcus?
I never felt better in my life.
Oh, Marcus, I missed you so much, honey,
but you need to get some rest.
Oh, no, baby, I need you.
-Just let me get some electrolytes.
-Okay, baby. Give me a kiss.
So, what's going on with my dad?
Um... Well, he was on the roof naked...
and he said he had been
at the basement of the ocean.
"Amazing Chickpeas"?
Oh, and he said I have a stupid baby soul
-with no penis.
-THERESA: Mm.
MIKE: Y'all need to talk to him.
-Hey, Reggie.
-Yes, sir.
-MARCUS: Did you eat my snacks?
-No, sir.
I was looking forward to my snacks, Reggie.
-THERESA: Honey.
-[GRUNTS DISMISSIVELY]
[GUNS FIRING OVER VIDEO GAME]
You know what? You need to get a job.
I'm a US Marine, sir.
Well, then you need to deploy.
You know, we just got back from Yemen.
Thank you for your service.
-You thought I was dead, didn't you?
-Dead?
One thing you don't know, Reggie.
I got a camera up in here. Yeah.
[OBJECTS CLATTERING ON VIDEO]
Theresa!
It's the doctor's orders, Marcus.
You're on a strict diet. No salt, no sugar, no fats.
No stress, no loud noises, no physical exertion.
Just sit your ass down somewhere, man.
Tell him, Mike.
And, honey, I'm doing it with you.
We're now vegetarians.
Vegetarians? Look at me.
Look at all this man, baby. I'm brand-new.
I need animal sugars to survive.
Well, baby...
I have a salad for you.
A salad?!
Hey, T, looks like you got this under control.
My tour of duty is done.
-Bye, Christine. Bye, Mike.
-Bye, guys.
MARCUS: Hey, Mike. Wait up.
Wait up, wait up.
What you about to do?
Can you run a quick-quick for me?
Yeah, what you need?
Um, I'll give you $1,000 for some Skittles.
Marcus, I am not buying your ass no candy, man.
Okay, $2,000, Mike, for some Ding Dongs.
And that's my final offer.
I think you're gonna be Ding Dong-less...
like my soul.
-[SOMBER INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
-[SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
MIKE: You always take whoever I love.
[HOWARD GRUNTS]
MIKE: This is Detective Mike Lowrey.
The Captain is down.
He's my son.
MARCUS: You got a fucked up family, Mike.
[GRUNTS]
[GASPING]
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
The Department of Justice has been investigating
the corruption in the Miami Police Department.
And we now have credible intelligence
that Captain Conrad Howard
was directing these elements
in coordination with the cartels.
[REPORTERS CLAMORING]
GRICE: No, I'm not interested
in approximately what time.
I need to know exactly what time,
do you understand?
You knew about this?
I found out two weeks ago.
A press conference. Really?
I'm sorry about the way
you had to find out.
-But given your closeness--
-Our closeness?
Neither one of y'all would have a job
if it wasn't for Captain Howard.
Rita, you know this is not true.
Honestly, I don't.
The investigation
has turned up new evidence.
Miami law enforcement's been
a leaky ship for years now.
Witnesses turn up dead, informants disappear.
Events appear random
until you aggregate them over a period of years.
Then a pattern emerges.
Who is this?
Bud Grice, FBI, heading up the JTF on this show.
That's who I am.
Now, we knew
someone was providing intelligence
to a cartel moving product
into South Florida.
We just didn't know who.
A cartel banker turned up dead two weeks ago,
shot by his girlfriend.
They found a phone with Howard's contact on it.
Years of communication with the cartel,
account references offshore.
Millions in Howard's name.
Final piece we needed
to nail that dirty motherfucker.
-LOCKWOOD: Grice!
-Oh, whoa. Hey, hey, let me holler at you.
Um, you know I was with him
when he went down, right?
Call him dirty one more time.
I dare you.
We know he had others who were with him.
We're gonna find them too.
I was with him.
-Put the cuffs on me right now. I was with him.
-Mike.
No, these motherfuckers think
that just 'cause he's dead and can't defend hisself,
they gon' dump all this shit on him,
burn his legacy.
Not on my watch.
This is Judy Howard, US Marshals.
I realize I have no jurisdiction here.
But as a professional courtesy,
I'd like to request visibility into the sources
of the allegations against my father.
Judy.
We're gonna figure this shit out, all right?
How's Callie?
How do you think, Mike?
We're on the same team here, Judy.
Like hell we are, Mike.
My dad would still be alive
if it weren't for your bastard son.
Judy...
If I ever catch him out on the street,
I swear on my father,
I will put him down.
MARCUS: Come on. Come on, man. Come on.
So, what's our next move?
They said he was working with the cartel.
Let's ask the cartel.
How you doin'?
It's prison.
MIKE: Yeah.
Look. We need your help.
They're saying
that Captain Howard was dirty.
Do you know anything about that?
-How much time I get off for this one?
-MIKE: I'm still working on that.
This is me telling you that I need you.
I need to know if Captain Howard
was working with the cartels.
No.
He was onto the ones that were.
So he got greenlit.
Wait, no.
No, Captain Howard was killed
because he was on your mother's hit list.
He was added to it.
Your people wanted it to look like us.
Your people wanted him dead.
Whatchu mean, "our people"?
You should be careful.
You're playing a game
and you don't even know the rules.
-There's dirty players on your side.
-That's bullshit.
Wait, who?
I saw him one time.
-Can you ID him?
-Sí.
Give me a name.
I don't know his name.
My mother.
She's the one who dealt with him.
[MARCUS SCOFFS]
I knew we should have kept
that damn witch alive.
Marcus.
May she rest in peace.
Dude.
LINTZ: Hey, boss.
Our man on the inside
got all of Howard's records in the JTF file.
Computers, phones, files, all of it.
Well, we know Howard was onto our operation.
We just don't know how much he had.
We need to make sure we got every trace.
That's beautiful.
Hey, boss.
It's all the paper files.
They're clean so far.
Two phones had nothing.
His office computer was empty.
-He was careful.
-But?
NICOLE: But his old personal laptop
had weak encryption.
Here we go.
-[BEEPS]
-Shit. We tripped a fail-safe.
The fuck you mean, "we"?
Something was sent.
To who?
NICOLE: Tracing the phone now.
[CELL PHONES BUZZES AND CHIMES]
What the hell?
He's texting us from the other side.
No, he's not, Marcus.
If you're seeing this...
I'm probably dead.
Fuck!
Fuck me.
Before I begin...
I wanna say one thing:
I'm putting you in mortal danger.
Boys...
we got rats in our walls.
But I gotta make sure you're my bad boys.
The Coke-bottle giant is the key.
What?
Don't trust anybody.
What's that? What does that mean?
"The Coke-bottle giant."
[SNAPPING FINGERS]
Fletcher.
Oh, shit.
NICOLE: These are the guys.
We should put a bullet in these motherfuckers.
Be done with it once and for all.
Lintz, I love you. I'd like nothing more
than to let you loose on them.
But extra dead cops
doesn't do us any favors here.
Keep them under constant surveillance
and see if they make a move.
Fletcher's warehouse
is right down that alley.
Mike, I wasn't even gonna tell you this.
Ugh. Then don't tell me.
No, you gotta hear this. This is big.
I can't die.
What?
I cannot die.
Motherfucker, you did a pretty good job of dying
at my wedding a couple weeks ago.
But I didn't.
Watch.
Hey, Marcus.
-Hey!
-WOMAN: Come on! Get out of the road!
Hey!
-[CARS HONKING]
-[TIRES SCREECHING]
Hey! Marcus!
Hey, stop, stop.
Hey, hey! Marcus!
MAN: What are you,
some kind of moron?!
MIKE: Stop, stop, stop.
Police! Stop!
-Hey!
-Bro!
Slow down!
Crosswalk!
Ah! Ha-ha!
Talk to me.
-You gotta trust, Mike.
-Mm-hmm.
Trust yourself. Trust the universe.
Stop that shit, Marcus.
It's not my time, Mike.
Oh, okay. So you're saying
that if I shoot you in your face,
you're saying that you won't die.
Fate dictates
that you won't shoot me in the face.
I'm saying... I'm...
I'm saying that you saying
that if I shoot you in your face,
are you saying you won't die?
Fate doesn't deal in hypotheticals, Mike.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
[IN ENGLISH] I'm gonna call the police.
They're already here, ma'am. Mind your business.
Just go to the beach.
Stop that shit, Marcus.
[MARCUS LAUGHS]
See? You're putting your gun away.
He's putting his gun away. [LAUGHS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Ooh, Mike.
Focus, man.
Yeah, I call this place, you know,
Creative Space for Black Imagination.
-You know that...
-MIKE: Fletcher.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
What the hell is this place?
This is my studio gallery. I'm an artiste now.
Please, you ain't no damn artist.
[INHALES, CLICKS TONGUE]
-What do you guys want?
-Captain Howard.
Yeah. I was sorry to hear what happened to him.
He helped turn my life around.
He told us to talk to you.
Okay. Talk to me.
-I just talked to you.
-Then say what you're supposed to say.
-I said what I'm supposed to say.
-You didn't.
-Then tell me what I'm supposed to say.
-I've said all I can say.
Fucking with us, beanstalk?!
Marcus! Come on!
Captain Howard saved my life.
I'm not messing this up.
I can't say what I supposed to say
until you say what you supposed to say.
Fletcher, just tell us
what you supposed to tell us.
Dumbasses. Look.
Captain Howard was onto something big.
He didn't trust that you dumb fucks
would figure it out, so he contacted me.
Because you're stupid,
and I'm a genius.
So I protected the information
in something.
In something beautiful.
[SIGHS IN EXASPERATION]
Flex your face one more time. Flex it again!
I will blow your fucking head off.
Would you stop?! Come on.
In something that will live forever.
-[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
-Did you shoot him?!
[SNIFFING] I don't think so.
[PEOPLE CLAMOURING]
Freeze!
Marcus. Marcus!
[SEDUCTIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SPITS]
[GROANS]
You hit?
Nah-ah.
Black jellybean. Nobody likes that shit.
[GUNSHOTS]
Whoa.
[SEDUCTIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey! Stop that stupid shit!
I'm not fucking with you! Stop!
[DISTORTED ROARING]
No! No, no! No! No!
[YELLING]
-[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
-[WOMAN SCREAMS]
I don't give a fuck!
Marcus! No! No!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
What are you doing?!
-I got this!
-But you don't, though.
No. No!
Marc--!
Let's go! Let's move!
Marcus!
Burnett and Lowrey are moving north on 11th.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[GUNSHOT]
[CARS HONKING]
[GRUNTING, YELLING]
Miami PD! Go!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
-What are you doing?!
-I'm fightin' crime, baby!
Freeze!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPING]
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[HEART THUMPING]
Mike!
[ENGINE ACCELERATING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Have you ever had a panic attack before?
What? Ain't nobody have no damn panic attack.
You're at 165 over 90. Sweaty. Nauseous.
There's no shame in getting counseling.
All right. Thank you. Appreciate you, brother.
Mike, let the man do his job.
Good job, man.
Hey, Mike.
What the hell you panicking about?
I'm not speaking to you.
What'd I do?
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
You two all right?
Mike had a panic attack.
He didn't. Mike is fine.
What happened?
Rita, you ain't gonna believe this shit.
But we got a text--
A tip. We got a tip
that Fletcher had violated his parole.
So we came down here
and obviously he was into some shit
he ain't have no business.
Is that true, Marcus?
Oh. Um...
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Well, you know I was with Mike.
How could you, of all people,
think Captain Howard was dirty?
I don't want this to be true.
But it would benefit all of us to do our jobs
and follow the evidence.
And you think he was stupid enough
to put accounts in his own name?
-He's being framed.
-By who?
That's what we're trying to find out.
Rita, come on, you're smarter than this.
Michael, please do not forget
you're talking to your boss.
I'm trying to protect you here.
I got no footage for a two-block radius.
What?
They must've killed all CCTV, all security cams.
I got nothing.
At least they ain't film your panic attack.
-[CHUCKLES]
-[LAUGHS SARCASTICALLY]
Hey, guys.
-You had a panic attack?
-MIKE: No.
-If you want, I can recommend a good counselor.
-I'm good, Dorn. Thanks.
Look, I shot this, went frame by frame.
Check it out.
All right. Not here.
-Dorn, shut it down.
-Yeah.
Hey. Let's go.
So, what is this?
MARCUS: We're not exactly sure.
MIKE: Whoa. Uh...
There you go. There you go.
All right, you fucks. Now that I know it's you...
here it is:
I don't know how high up it goes,
but there's corrupt officials on our side.
And they're working with the cartel.
-[DORN SIGHS]
-This all started smelling funny
about nine years ago.
That shipment of coke
we were about to raid went missing.
You know, I kept getting shut down
from above.
So I pulled Sanchez and Ruiz
outta retirement.
I had 'em working on the outside,
you know?
They were killed in a car crash
a week later.
That shook me up.
And it's why I never brought you two in.
Well, shame on me for worrying about your asses
when you coulda saved mine.
But now it's up to you.
Remember the bust back in 2003?
314 pounds of ecstasy?
Well, I held onto the storage unit,
off the books.
That's where the real files are.
Everything you need
to exterminate these rat fucks.
It's in there!
You're gonna have to finish
what I couldn't.
Please.
Please, boys.
You're my last hope.
[DORN EXHALES]
2003. Um...
That was the Haitians. Zoe Pound.
Where was their storage locker?
I have no idea.
All right. We need you guys to go down
to the station and pull our original case files.
That'll tell us where the locker is.
Do it quietly and be careful.
We don't know who we can trust.
DORN: Shit, this is heavy, man.
Um... [CLEARS THROAT]
I just got something important to say.
I'm just gonna come out with it. Clear the air.
Uh, the rat is not me.
Thanks for that, Dorn.
[EXHALES] I feel safer.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[GATE SQUEAKING]
[EXHALES]
[EXHALES, MUTTERS]
[ATTACKER 1 GRUNTING]
[ATTACKER 2 YELLS]
[PRISONERS EXCLAIM]
[PRISONERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[ATTACKER 3 GROANS]
[PRISONER SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
-[ALARM BLARING]
-[PRISONERS CLAMORING]
[GRUNTING]
MIKE: They just tried to kill my son.
Because Armando can prove
that Captain Howard was innocent.
Cap was onto these dirty players.
Armando told you that?
Yes. It's the reason
they wanted Captain Howard dead.
Armando can ID the guy
that ordered the hit on Cap.
He have a name?
No. But a face.
Listen, I know y'all can do this. All right?
Just transfer Armando. Get him to Miami.
Get him to a secure location.
We'll debrief him. We'll get his testimony.
We'll get some pictures in front of him.
But please do it now.
These guys are tryin' to cover their asses
and they are not gonna stop.
Do it for Captain Howard.
[SIGHS] Look, the evidence against
Captain Howard is overwhelming.
If I'm doing this, I'm doing it for you.
All right, let's transfer Aretas.
You'll accompany him,
get him to igloo here in Miami, do a debrief.
But I'm sticking my neck out
and I'm trusting you.
If he turns out to be bullshit,
then it's gonna be my ass.
So don't screw me, Mike.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Thank you.
Yeah?
DORN: [OVER PHONE]
We found Zoe Pound's storage unit.
We'll go get the files, then take them
to my houseboat for safekeeping.
All right, stay on it.
Let me know when you got it.
[SIREN WAILING]
Please surrender your firearms.
They will be returned to you upon touchdown.
You good?
Never been better.
It's about 45 minutes.
Mike, I wasn't even gonna tell you this...
-but in one of our previous lifetimes together...
-Mm-hmm.
...you were a donkey.
And I owned you.
[SCOFFING] You were a stubborn ass, Mike.
You used to bite and spit.
-You were nasty.
-Hmm.
But I was a terrible owner,
you know, because I used to beat you.
-Mm-hmm.
-Because you wouldn't listen for shit.
And maybe I beat
some kind of shame into you, Mike.
And now I realize
I was scarring your soul.
You miss your nap?
[SIGHS]
Mike, I'm trying to apologize to you.
We don't have your blankie,
but you could just rest your eyes.
-That's exactly how you was as a donkey.
-Mm-kay.
-That's that shit there.
-I get it.
You need some help with your seat belt?
No, Donkey.
Hey. Bryant, this is Bronson.
Other guys are on turnaround.
BRYANT: Take a seat.
MIKE: What's up?
MCGRATH: Read the lines.
"US Marshal flight 724,
we have an emergency.
Our prisoner has escaped custody
with the aid of Miami PD Lowrey and Burnett.
There are officers down.
Mayday, mayday.
They are coming for the cockpit.
I repeat, they are hijacking the CH-47.
All ground units please respond."
[CHOKING]
-MCGRATH: Give me Lowrey's gun.
-LINTZ: Copy.
[GRUNTS]
MCGRATH: Go, go!
Get Lowrey.
Let's go!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
[ALARM BEEPING]
[ALARM BLARING]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
We welcome the storm, motherfu--!
[GRUNTING]
[ALARM CONTINUES BLARING]
[SCREAMING]
[ALARM BEEPING]
[GROWLING]
[ARMANDO YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
[STRAINING]
Get me out of this fucking cage!
MIKE: Marcus!
[GROANS]
Mike!
[STRAINING, YELLING]
[YELLS]
[STRAINING]
MARCUS: It's too heavy!
MIKE: Don't let go!
[STRAINING]
[PANTING]
[GASPING]
[GROANING]
[STRAINING]
ARMANDO: Grab the stick!
-[ALARMS CONTINUE BEEPING]
-[YELLING]
Where the hell you learn how to fly?!
I'm a drug dealer, man. To the right!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[METAL CREAKING]
[GASPING]
Whoa!
[GROANS, BREATHING HEAVILY]
He was using my gun.
How the hell
did they get on a federal transport?
We need to split up.
We're gonna stay together.
Says who?
I'm not asking you.
I'm telling you. We're stayin' together.
Fuck outta my way.
-Hey. Where--?
-Get the fuck off me.
Hey! Hey!
Look.
You are the only person
who can identify whoever is doing this!
The only way that any of us stays alive
is if we get them before they get us.
There's no us! There is no us!
Damn.
That Lowrey DNA is a bitch.
Y'all some strong motherfuckers.
Okay. Now, look, everybody unflex.
On three.
One! Two!
There you go.
Captain Howard left us files
that's gonna tell us who's doin' this.
Dorn has 'em.
We just have to get back to Miami.
You better not slow me down.
Lose your phones.
You keep up with me
or I leave you in the dirt.
You're in my world now.
Hey, Mike.
Look, we gotta think about this.
I know you wanna move with him,
you know, because he's your "son."
Whoa, whoa. Don't air quote that.
No, I didn't. I'm just sayin'
I know why you tryin' to protect him.
'Cause he "family."
Hey. Movin' the air quotes down to your hips
doesn't un-air-quote them.
Just say he's my son.
-He's your son.
-No, no.
Palms up is like you tryin' to say,
oh, he's not really my son.
Oh. Well, your son's gettin' away.
MIKE: Shit.
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
If your men are on some kind of op,
you might wanna pull us in.
Otherwise, it doesn't look good for them.
Judy.
-You ID the bodies?
-MARSHAL: Roger. We got three unaccounted for.
Lowrey, Burnett and Aretas.
Motherfuckers. Fucking--!
Shit.
All right. Listen up!
We have three suspects,
armed and dangerous, out there.
And I want them back.
Let's go!
RITA: Hold on. Judy.
Three suspects?
What do you think is happening here?
What do you think?
Play the audio.
BRYANT: [OVER TAPE] US Marshal
flight 724, we have an emergency.
Our prisoner has escaped custody
with the aid of Miami PD Lowrey and Burnett.
There are officers down.
Mayday, mayday.
Come on, you can't possibly believe
Mike and Marcus would do this.
Nah, you said it. Lowrey was obsessed
with getting his son out of prison.
Slow down, Judy.
This isn't Miami, Secada.
These are my fugitives
and right now the whole world is my jurisdiction.
You've known them your whole life.
How can you even suggest--?
Do I think
that Mike and Marcus planned this?
Probably not.
But people do things
they wouldn't normally do when family's involved.
In my experience, innocent men don't run.
-Can we stop and think before--
-Are you capable of doing your job?
'Cause I need to move on.
They survived.
What the fuck you mean, they survived?
No bodies on site.
US Marshals are treating it as a manhunt.
These guys just refuse to die.
They're wanted men.
Law enforcement and media
are our friends now.
FEMALE REPORTER:
A manhunt for three fugitives
is sending shock waves across South Florida.
MALE REPORTER: Ballistic reports
have matched the bullets
recovered from the bodies...
Are you planning on dropping out
of the mayor's race in light of the recent events?
GRICE:
The manhunt is currently underway.
The FBI is assisting US Marshals
in bringing these men in.
Lowrey, Burnett and Aretas should be
considered armed and dangerous.
These are individuals who have killed
fellow law enforcement professionals.
If you see something, say something.
Put a bounty on the streets.
Get it to every gang in the city
and let them fight for it.
Five mil. [SUCKS TEETH]
Let's go get these motherfuckers.
MARCUS:
The universe is crazy, ain't it?
Look at us.
I bet none of us thought when we woke up today
this is where we'd be.
You outta jail.
We goin' to jail. [CHUCKLES]
This shit is special.
Mike?
Is there anything
you would like to say to Armando?
Fuck you talkin' to me like that? No.
Mike, this is a moment.
Express with your son.
I'm sorry.
That's what I'm talking about.
-For what?
-MIKE: For everything, man.
Seems like bad shit happens
to anybody I love, so...
Startin' to think maybe I'm cursed.
I just feel like...
maybe I cursed you.
You ain't fuckin' cursed me.
Bad shit happens to everybody.
Ain't always about you.
MARCUS: Hey, Armando.
I don't know if I told you this,
but I died a couple of weeks ago.
Sorry to hear about that.
Oh, no.
The best thing that ever happened to me.
Shit's wild.
But y'all?
Y'all the reason I came back.
Hey.
Everybody, bring it in.
Come on, bring it in. Come on.
ARMANDO: What?
MARCUS: There you go, Armando.
There you go. There you--
Y'all are some terrible fuckin' fugitives.
So, what are you, fuckin' Marcus Winfrey?
-What?
-Now, see?
You makin' us look soft,
like we don't know how to be on the run.
Better get you out of this.
Hey!
-That boy hardheaded.
-Chip off the old block.
[GUN COCKING]
Well, what we got here?
Hey, Cain, come take a look at this!
-[GUN COCKING]
-What are you boys doin'?
"Boys"?
-Are y'all stealing our clothes?
-Looks like it.
Fuckin' racism.
Y'all think just because we Black,
we stealin' your shit?
Now, these are my own Black clothes
that I put on today
from my own Black closet.
-Marcus!
-What?
Look at your shirt.
[MUTTERS, CHUCKLES]
How'd this get in my Black closet?
Why don't you boys
sing us a little Reba song.
[MEN LAUGHING]
-MARCUS: Reba?
-MIKE: Reba? Oh, yeah.
Oh, please. [BLOWS RASPBERRY]
That's-- 'Cause he put...
He put me on to Reb--
Which one? Which y'all--? Which one?
Sing your favorite.
-Oh, she got plenty of them.
-'Cause she got hits.
-Was it the up-tempo song? Or the slow jam?
-Yeah, yeah, remember the one?
-It was the slow one, nigga.
-Oh, okay.
[SINGING] You hurt me in the morning
Yes, 'cause she was hurt.
[SINGING] You hurt me at night
Yes, yes.
-But I've changed
-Changed
And I'm strong, I'm a woman
I'm a strong Black wom--
I'm a strong woman
Yeah, 'cause she's not Black.
[BOTH VOCALIZING]
And then...
[SINGING] What you gonna do?
What you gonna d--?
MIKE: Mmh-mmh.
That ain't no Reba song.
It's from her mixtape.
[BAD BOYS BY REBA MCENTIRE PLAYS]
[GASPS]
MAN: Goddamn it!
[GUNSHOTS]
We're sorry! We'll bring it back!
We're not stealing your shit
because we Black!
Did you ever love her?
What?
My mother. You ever love her?
[WHISPERING] He's expressing.
I definitely loved her.
And then you sold her out.
I made some mistakes.
Like me.
-You know that is not what I was trying--
-Now wait a damn minute, Armando.
He's trying to make up for it.
He don't owe you a damn thing.
All right, hold on. Hold on, Marcus.
You're just... You're being aggressive.
I've been a dad a long time.
He needs to hear this, Mike.
He needs some tough-ass love.
Armando.
Maybe he does owe you something. Okay?
Your mom being deceived by him.
You being born in prison,
in a web of lies
that turned your ass
into a stone-cold fuckin' killer.
Yeah. You're a killer.
[SCOFFS]
But this man, through it all,
has been nothing but solid.
That's some
father-of-the-year shit right there.
-Is it?
-[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
Your wack-ass parenting broke the truck.
My bad.
-[ENGINE STALLING]
-Yeah, nah, that's dead.
We're not far from Tabitha's.
No, Mike. You know that woman's crazy.
Yeah, but she likes me.
I don't think she likes you
as much as you think.
-The Pony's about two miles from here.
-What's The Pony?
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
WOMAN: I need my Instagram.
I need my Friendster. I need more sex.
I need more men in this club.
You all look beautiful.
Now get back to work.
[CLICKS TONGUE] Mike Lowrey. Damn.
What up, Tabitha?
So y'all in trouble, huh?
Yeah, we need some help. Um...
-We need some clothes.
-No shit.
A ride and some phones.
Yeah. Guns too.
Uh, that's my son. That's Armando.
You got you a little Spanish son?
Yeah, it's a long story.
Um, can you hook us up?
I mean, I got all that
but what you gonna do for me?
What you mean? We good for that.
You were.
But you guys
are men on the run now, so...
Well, what you need?
-What I need?
-MIKE: Mm-hmm.
I need you to eat this pussy.
Oh!
I'm not doin' that, all right?
Whoa, hold on, Mike, hold on.
Think about this.
-Now, you say guns and phones, right?
-Mm-hmm.
Okay, well, look,
you know Mike's a married man.
So?
So he's gonna need
some plausible deniability.
So I'mma have you lay down
and stick out your tongue.
And you gonna have to do the rest.
I can fuck with that.
-Oh, yeah, go on, baby.
-No, Marcus.
-All you gotta do is close your eyes, Mike.
-No!
I'mma need pictures.
You know how to take pictures, right?
Hey. We don't have a lot of time.
I need you to stop fuckin' around.
Oh, I'm not fuckin' around.
All right, hey, let's go.
Wait, hold up.
Sit your motherfuckin' ass down.
-Hey, Tabitha, what is you doin'?
-What is you doin'?!
Sit your married ass down!
You get y'all asses down too!
-Shit.
-Everybody sit down.
Hey, I got the bad boys right here.
Let's get that money.
-Hey, Tab.
-Shut the fuck up.
MARCUS: Hold up, I'm confused.
You didn't want him to licky-licky?
There's a $5 million bounty on your head.
I need that money. I was just stalling.
That's... That's cold. He almost did that shit.
He did not, Marcus.
-I told you she didn't like you.
-[GUNS COCKING]
Get the fuck up.
[MARCUS SIGHS]
The bounty is dead or alive.
Don't be stupid.
Hey, Armando.
If you live, I'll let you...
What?
I said if you live, motherfucker,
holler at me.
He was kinda cute.
[LAUGHING]
[CELL PHONE BEEPING]
JUDY: We got a tip.
Positive ID on our fugitives.
Let's do this.
[SIREN WAILING]
Ooh! Mike, I'm about to make my move.
No, the fuck you're not.
You about to go wherever these men are taking us.
Oh, I'm not goin'.
Now I'll take the three in the front,
you take the six in the back.
Marcus, we do not have any weapons.
In five... four... three...
-[GUNFIRE]
-MAN: Fuck!
[MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYING OVER CAR RADIO]
Ah, shit! This motherfucker.
[SINGING] Fuckboy, fuckboy
Whatcha gonna do?
Ayo, Mike!
Ain't no fun
when the rabbit got the gun, huh?
Wait, you know this guy?
Yeah, I hit him with a hammer
a couple years ago.
You think I forgot about that fucking ho shit
you pulled off at Manny's Prime Rib?
How the fuck
did I let you two catch me?
MANNY: Mike, I want my five million.
-[PANTING]
-MIKE: Marcus!
You see I got the fam with me.
The streets!
We could do this nice and easy
or we can go to war!
'Cause I'm fucking war-ready!
MIKE: What are you doing?!
MIKE: No!
[ENGINE REVVING]
[GROANING IN PAIN]
MIKE: Go, go, go, go!
Back up! Back up! Back up!
No! No!
Windshield wiper fluid is flammable!
How the hell am I supposed to know that?!
I ain't no damn scientist!
Everybody relax.
The fire's on the outside.
-Oh!
-MARCUS: Oh, shit!
Now it's on the inside!
MIKE: Shit!
Okay.
[GASPS] Okay.
[SIREN WAILING]
[GASPS]
Everybody out! Everybody out!
[ARMANDO GRUNTS]
[SIREN WAILING]
[MAN GRUNTING]
Shit.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
MARCUS: Open the damn door!
MIKE: We can feel you right there, boy.
Open the door.
Hey!
Open up, Muscle Milk.
Come on, man.
What the fuck is you doing?
Nothing. It's just not a great time
for me right now, guys.
It's not a great time for us either.
Okay, let's reconvene
in like an hour or so.
Babe, we're out of body wash.
-MIKE AND MARCUS: Oh!
-Whoa!
What the hell?
We found you guys.
We're in a relationship. Okay?
-Oh, okay.
-All right.
Sneaking around has been destroying me.
It started about a couple months ago.
It will not affect our professional lives.
Except for that one time in that van.
-I am not sorry.
-Nothing to be sorry about.
Yeah, you know.
I mean, people do that shit.
-Are you guys okay?
-MIKE: Yeah, we're good. I wanted to-- Oh.
-KELLY: What the fuck?!
-MIKE: Okay. Whoa, whoa.
Hey, Kelly. Kelly.
I asked you to wait outside for a second.
All right. Kelly, he's with us.
He can't be here.
This is my son, Armando.
I know who he is,
and that's why he can't be here.
I trust you with my life, Mike.
But I as sure as shit don't trust him.
I trust him.
Then take him to your house.
[CLEARS THROAT] Hey, Mike.
Uh, can I have a second with her, please?
Yeah, yeah. Please.
-Hey, sweetie.
-Relax. Relax.
DORN: Come here for a sec.
Come over here for a second.
KELLY: We could both end up in jail.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
-DORN: Give him a chance.
-Yeah, give him a chance to kill us all?
This is some dysfunctional shit.
-DORN: She's fine.
-MARCUS: She don't look fine.
-I'm fine.
-Yes, you are.
-The fuck you say?
-All right, all right.
-It's the language barrier.
-It was English.
It was definitely English.
Thanks for the drip.
Yeah. Okay, we're aggregating all the data.
There's over 100 hours of video,
200 units of audio.
We're indexing all audio, video
and geo-located IP network data
to create a sight picture
and develop a target package.
Basically, you sifting through all this shit
to find the guilty motherfucker.
Bingo.
Hey, Dorn.
Can you safely get me into my Ring app?
I wanna see my family.
Yeah, we got our own VPN and router.
What's your username?
-Marcus37.
-[TYPING]
And password?
Snickers89.
Almost home, baby.
Hey, let's get to work.
We got a lot to get through here.
So, what exactly are we looking for?
MIKE: We're looking for the guy
who ordered the hit on Cap.
Armando can ID him.
HOWARD: This fucking bastard
has been my white whale.
For the last nine years,
I've been trying to harpoon the son of a bitch.
But now it's up to you.
Ey-Ey-Ey. Do I walk into your house
and show you how to make cocaine?
Blow it up.
It's him.
You sure?
ARMANDO:
That's the guy that ordered the hit.
Bam. Got a name.
James McGrath.
Army Ranger School, counterintelligence.
Deployed in Mexico until 2005.
Worked with the DEA,
Defense Attache's office.
Oh, shit.
He was taken hostage
by your friends, the cartel.
He gave up his entire squad
"under duress."
It's called torture, man.
DORN: He was the only survivor.
MIKE:
Cap had him the whole time.
He just didn't know it.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hello.
Hey. It's me.
Damn it, Michael. Where are you?
Rita, we're coming in.
We got proof that Captain Howard is innocent.
What proof?
We got the guy
that had Captain Howard killed.
Armando ID'd him.
Same dude that attacked us
on the chopper. James McGrath.
Rita, we got ten years' worth of files.
Cap was investigating these dudes.
We got 'em all. It's a whole network.
We'll surrender to you tomorrow.
Hey, look, we gotta go.
Michael, what--? [SIGHS]
You okay?
Uh...
They're coming in.
What?
Michael says they have proof
that exonerates Howard...
explains everything.
Do you still love him?
What?
No.
But I believe him.
Just be careful, babe.
Still going to dinner?
Yeah.
MCGRATH: They have the files.
We need to make this look like cartel business.
Spanish only.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
WOMAN:
Ammo's ready to go. Let's go.
MAN: [IN SPANISH]
We only need one hostage.
DORN: [IN ENGLISH] Shit! Shit! Shit!
You guys! We got a problem.
DORN: Miami Central, Miami Central.
29 in progress.
MARCUS: Oh shit, that's my house.
DORN:
Please advise, MOS residence.
Respond forthwith.
Fuck.
Fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, no.
Come on, Christine.
[BUZZING]
-Shit.
-Get a unit over to my house.
Come on, Reggie! Pick up! Pick up.
DORN: Miami Central,
we have another 29 in progress.
Please send units
to Detective Lowrey's home address.
-[CELL PHONE RINGING]
-WOMAN: [ON VIDEO GAME] Enemy's down!
Reggie! You got incoming.
-Get the family to somewhere safe.
-What?
-Now!
-Yes, sir.
-THERESA: What's happening?
-MEGAN: What's going on?
REGGIE: There's people comin' in the house.
I gotta keep y'all safe.
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
Please be careful!
-Okay, Reggie, what's happening? Okay.
-Trust me. I love you.
Fuck! Fuck!
[BUZZING]
Behind you, Reg!
Oh, damn!
[MAN 1 GRUNTING]
-Who the fuck is this guy?!
-That's my boy! That's my boy!
Ooh.
Damn!
Come on, come on, come on.
[SCREAMING]
Ooh!
No, no, no!
-Whoo!
-DORN: Holy shit!
[MAN 2 GRUNTING]
Come on, come on!
DORN: Holy shit!
-[GUNSHOT]
-[BOTH SCREAM]
Oh! Chitty-Chitty-Bang-Bang, motherfuckers.
Me snacks is your snacks, Reggie.
REGGIE: All right, come on.
Mike, did you see that shit?
MIKE: Pick up the phone.
Whoa, Mike! Mike! Mike!
-[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
-[KNOCK ON DOOR]
CHRISTINE: One second.
Callie.
I saw it on TV.
My mom is after Uncle Mike.
There is no way
that he did everything that they're saying.
Sweetheart.
Everything is going to be okay.
Okay? Okay?
[CELL PHONE CONTINUES BUZZING]
-Hello?
-It's me. Get out of the house.
-I've got Callie with me.
-Take her and go! Get out now!
[MCGRATH WHISTLES]
CHRISTINE:
Callie, get behind me.
Mike.
[CALLIE YELPS]
Christine!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Mr. Lowrey.
Who am I speaking to?
I think you know who you're speaking to.
[OVER PHONE] I need your boy...
and whatever evidence
your beloved captain had squirreled away.
And for that, you can have your wife.
I'll call you back with instructions.
-[CALL DISCONNECTS]
-Aw, shit.
[GROANS] Goddamn it.
-I'll go.
-[MIKE GROANS IN PAIN]
Let my life be worth something.
Never.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Mike.
He knew.
What do you mean?
He knew we were comin' in.
He knew we had Captain Howard's files.
He knew we had ID'd him.
How?
Only person you spoke to was Rita.
It's not Rita.
Damn, she got bad taste in men.
-[CELL PHONE RINGING]
-REPORTER: Justice has been investigating
the corruption in the Miami Police Department...
...with reports suggesting
the late Captain Conrad Howard...
Hello?
...was directing these elements
in coordination with the cartels.
Allegations against Howard,
which allude to include Lowrey and Burnett,
and the operation range from helping cartels
move the product into the state of Florida
as well as giving up key witnesses,
destruction of evidence,
and even the murder of fellow officers.
-What's going on?
-I don't know.
There's been a breakthrough in the case.
I need to get down to the station.
I'm gonna head down there.
I'm coming with you.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Who are you texting?
Uh, just...
Just gotta get in touch with the office.
JTF.
Gotta let everybody know.
Hey. Honey. Come on.
Honey, what are you doing? Stop that.
What are you doing? Stop it.
-Let go of me.
-What are you doing?
Give it back to me. Give it back!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[RITA GRUNTS]
[RITA SCREAMING]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
KELLY: Fuck!
Hey, hey, come on.
You okay?
Look at the phone.
You know you done fucked up, right?
You all right?
[RITA SIGHS]
I'm sorry.
Ain't got nothing to be sorry for.
We'll find her, boss.
[SHIP HONKING IN DISTANCE]
I don't trust anybody
that's not standing right here, right now.
Every extra person that we involve
increases the likelihood
that they know we're coming,
which increases the likelihood
that Christine and Callie
don't make it out of there.
That means no SWAT,
no marshals, no backup.
It's just us.
[SIGHS]
I never meant for it to go this way.
How did you mean it to go?
After 9/11, nobody cared
about drugs coming into this country.
So to secure the borders
we started to work with the cartels.
And they kept us informed about
any terrorist activity coming our way.
And it worked.
We haven't had an attack since.
We were protecting this country.
You were killing cops
and getting rich putting drugs into this country.
-Rita.
-That's why you killed Howard.
He was onto you.
You wanted to cover your tracks.
No. That was McGrath.
He's out of control.
Rita. Just take a second.
I never meant
for any of this to go this way.
I guess I just need to know
if it was ever real.
It was always real.
I panicked. I lost control.
Did you love me?
Yes.
I swear.
Well, that means...
MIKE: We good. We got it.
99% voice match.
...absolutely nothing to me,
you piece of shit.
[MUFFLED SHOUTING]
MIKE: [IN LOCKWOOD'S VOICE] Hey. It's me.
What the hell's going on?
You screwed up is what's going on.
We've been compromised.
I'll explain when I get there.
We're moving the hostages.
Cuba. Long-term hold...
to keep Lowrey, Burnett and Aretas quiet
while we sort this out.
I'm bringing a seaplane.
I'll be there at first light.
All right, pack this place up.
All equipment and personnel
prepare to move.
We're moving the hostages
out of the country.
What happened to your hand?
They call that a Colombian manicure.
[CRUNCHING]
[SCREAMS IN PAIN]
What's so great about it
is it's the maximum amount of pain,
but you don't die.
So now you've decided
to be the one holding the pliers.
Everybody breaks.
Everyone.
Your husband...
is gonna kneel down in front of me...
and beg for your lives.
And then you're gonna watch me kill him.
You don't know my husband.
Well, not officially, but...
I look forward to seeing him again.
[MARCUS SINGING]
Bad boys Bad boys
Mmh-mmh.
Come on, Mike.
[SINGING] Bad boys, bad boys
Whatchu you gonna do
Yeah.
What you gonna do
When they come for you
[VOCALIZING]
That's enough, dawg. That's enough.
Okay, well,
we'll circle back on that one.
[BAD BOYS PLAYS]
All right. The plane is ready.
We roll in 20.
It's an abandoned amusement park.
There should be no civilians.
Plane is gonna land from the south.
On the one side.
Marcus and I will be on the plane.
Armando's gonna make
his way in the water. The two side.
Kelly, Rita.
This road is one way in, one way out.
You're holding that road.
Dorn, you're gonna control the air.
DORN: Drones in the air,
jamming is active, comms are secure.
As far as they know,
Lockwood is on his way with the plane
to move the hostages to Cuba.
The second they get close to the plane
with the hostages, it's quick kills.
Neutralize all threats.
These motherfuckers
killed a lot of good cops.
They have my wife, they have Callie.
They attacked our families.
We not losing today.
Hey.
We get on the ground, you even flinch,
you'll be dead in .24 seconds.
I concur.
PILOT: I got one lookout
on the platform outside.
I got one sniper on the roof of building two.
Tee those up.
Everybody keep moving.
-What are those?
-Gators.
I thought it was an abandoned gator park.
Abandoned by humans.
DORN:
It's actually an old amusement park.
It sat on 10 acres,
abandoned in 2017 after Hurricane Irma.
Their main attraction
was an albino alligator named Duke...
...who was 16 feet long, 900 pounds.
"And legend has it he's still there."
Fuck that.
Armando's at his QTH.
Hostages are coming out now.
McGrath plus three.
Everybody stay calm.
[MIKE BREATHING HEAVILY]
Mike.
Mike, do you have the shot?
MIKE: Negative. I do not have a shot.
I do not have a shot.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
-Mike, he's right there.
-I don't have it. I don't have it.
They stopped. Why'd they stop?
[FLOOR CREAKING]
Shit.
Let's go.
Armando, they're closing in on you.
-Do they see him?
-I don't know.
Mike, now. Your chance is now.
They can see him.
They know we're here.
[MIKE BREATHING SHAKILY]
I don't have it.
Negative. Negative. Negative.
You gotta take the fuckin' shot.
Armando's burnt.
-Shit.
-Full green. Engage.
Kelly, get us there. Go, go, go!
[GUNFIRE]
Contact, west dock side.
[YELPS]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
Dorn! Take out that sniper!
Sending the drone.
Got him.
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Not now, Mike!
Not now!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
It's okay.
Not your fault.
Cut that bitch-ass shit out, Mike.
I need Nasty Mike.
Nasty Mike!
Bad shit happens,
but that doesn't mean you're bad.
Do that donkey shit, a'ight?
-[MIKE GROWLS]
-That's what I'm talking about.
That shit right there.
That's that shit right there.
Bad boy. Bad boy.
Bad Boy Mike. All right?
[SINGING] You're the big bad wolf
in the neighborhood
Not bad meaning bad
but bad meaning good
[BOTH YELLING]
[GROANS, YELLS]
-MIKE: Dorn, take out the vehicles on the four side.
-DORN: Copy.
MAN: Go, go! Move it!
Sir! We're taking heavies.
We lost the trucks and three guys outside.
Goddamn it!
Set firing positions, both sides.
Let 'em in.
Go.
MAN: [OVER RADIO] Marshal Howard, heat signature
at the site of the AMMO van is showing explosions.
ETA 15 minutes.
MIKE: Dorn, we need cover
and we need eyes inside. Go, now.
Here comes the smoke.
I got your six.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
MAN 1: Shoot those motherfuckers!
-MAN 2: Get those drones down now!
-MAN 3: Go!
Move, move, move!
Eyes up!
Oh, shit!
It's like redneck Jurassic Park in here.
Let's get out of here, now.
Kelly, go.
Dorn, back up Kelly inside.
I'm going after Lockwood.
Babe, I'm comin'.
[GUNFIRE]
Armando, go for Callie!
[GUN FIRING]
CHRISTINE: Let go!
Mike!
MIKE: Marcus!
[SCREAMS]
[GROANS]
MIKE: Go!
I'm out!
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING, SCREAMING]
[CHRISTINE PANTING, GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS IN PAIN]
-Nice to meet you, Mr. Lowrey.
-[CHRISTINE SOBS]
Grenade!
Oh sh--!
[AIRPLANE WHIRRING]
LOCKWOOD: Holy shit!
PILOT: Hang on!
[LINTZ GROANS]
[GRUNTING]
[AIRPLANE WHIRRING]
[SCREAMING]
[MIKE GRUNTING, SCREAMING]
[BOTH PANTING]
CHRISTINE: Stop!
-MIKE: Christine!
-[CHRISTINE GRUNTS]
MIKE: Christine!
Shit.
[GRUNTING]
Oh sh--!
-Mike, I got this!
-No. No, no!
Here I come, baby! Here I come!
MIKE: No! No! No!
[YELPS]
[GASPING]
[WATER BUBBLING]
Marcus!
-What?
-Behind you.
Oh, shit.
[PANTING]
I got this, Mike.
It's just Dukey, baby.
Marcus, my gun. I dropped my gun
in the water. It's by your foot.
I don't need no gun, Mike.
Begone, gator.
-[LOW GROWLING]
-This is not your place, Duke.
I rebuke you!
See, Mike?
That's how you command the universe.
[MARCUS SCREAMING]
[MIKE GRUNTING]
-[GRUNTS]
-[SCREAMS IN PAIN]
-Where's the gun? Where's the gun?
-Oh, shit!
-[MARCUS PANTING]
-Go, go.
That motherfucker racist, Mike.
That motherfucker racist!
Mike sent me.
I need you to trust me.
[GRUNTS]
[CALLIE SCREAMS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Run.
Run!
[SCREAMING]
[GROANING]
[SCREAMS]
[THUDS]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Come on. Come on. Get up.
[MARCUS PANTING]
[GROANING IN PAIN]
CHRISTINE: Stop!
[CHRISTINE SCREAMS]
Go! I'll slow you down.
Eyes on location.
[GROANING]
Oh, shit.
You alive?
[GRUNTS]
-[GROANS IN PAIN]
-Shit.
Okay. Hey.
Rita, stop this.
You don't want to shoot me.
You're right.
[YELLS]
[SCREAMING]
[GASPING]
[SCREAMS]
-Ow! Ow!
-Come here. Okay. Okay. It's okay.
-I fuckin' hate politicians.
-[SHUSHING]
[SIREN WAILS]
-MARSHAL 1: Let's move!
-MARSHAL 2: Go, go!
MARSHAL 3: Fan out. Take the team upstairs.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
MARSHAL 4: No targets.
MARSHAL 5: Go topside!
CALLIE: Okay. Okay, here.
-ARMANDO: Put me down. It's okay.
-Okay.
-CALLIE: You okay?
-Yeah. Yeah.
Hey.
Thank you.
[BIRD SQUAWKING]
I've been here before.
[GUN CLICKS]
Oh, shit.
[CHRISTINE PANTING]
[MCGRATH WHISTLES]
MIKE:
How did you let him catch you?
He's sneaky as hell, Mike.
MCGRATH: Your wife and I
were having a debate.
She seems to have
an inflated impression of you.
-Mike.
-Hey, bae.
Nevertheless, this is the end of the road.
One of them is about to die.
-[CHRISTINE WHIMPERS]
-You choose.
What you don't know, Mr. McGrath...
is one of 'em can't die.
Who you talking 'bout?
A wise man told me
I was gonna have to make a hard choice.
You need to check with that motherfucker
before you out here choosing shit.
MCGRATH:
You have five seconds, Mr. Lowrey.
We gonna need some more time, sir.
Four... three...
Mike. Don't you do no dumb shit.
...two...
[MARCUS GROANS]
[MARCUS GROANING IN PAIN]
-Mike. Mike.
-Hey. Hey. I'm here.
Motherfucker done shot me.
Aw, damn.
-Here. Let me check it. Let me see.
-No, Mike. Your donkey ass shot me again.
-Let me look at it.
-Don't touch me with your donkey hooves, Mike.
Damn, man.
Listen. I had to fucking take the shot.
No, Mike. No.
Marcus. Let me take a look.
You see that shit, Christine?
-I shot you in your vest. Stop bitchin'.
-It don't matter. Okay?
You see what you done
devoted your life to, Christine?
JUDY: [OVER RADIO]
I've got eyes on Aretas. Moving in.
Shit. That's Judy.
Armando, do you copy?
[OVER RADIO] Armando, do you copy?
Oh, shit.
Mom. Mom, don't.
Get away from her.
-CALLIE: Mom.
-Now!
Mom, listen to me, you don't understand.
Callie, I need you to listen to me.
I want you to step slowly to your right
and walk towards me.
Mom. Mom, I'm fine, okay?
Callie, I need you to move out of the way.
Mom.
Mom, don't shoot, don't shoot!
Mom, he saved me. Stop!
Judy! Judy!
Back off, Mike! Put the gun down.
He saved my life.
Please, Mom.
[BREATH TREMBLING]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Mom. Mom.
Are you hit? Are you hit?
I'm good.
You good?
You did good. You did good.
MAN: [OVER RADIO]
Howard. Where are you?
Howard. Do you copy?
Howard, what's your location?
Go.
Before I change my mind.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Hey. You good? You good?
Hey.
Take this.
Head south. Don't look back.
Hey.
I got it.
Be good.
It's not up to you, detective.
[MOTOR WHIRRING]
Come on, come on.
We got injured cops here.
-I need you to bring the writ to me now.
-[DORN GROANING]
KELLY: I know, I know, I know.
-How is he?
-You know, he'll pull through.
DORN: Ow!
Don't kiss him, Christine.
Mike, in our next life,
you coming back as a pair of my shoes.
And I ain't gonna wear no socks.
And I'mma step in all kind of shit.
MALE NEWSREADER 1: Miami DA
and mayoral candidate Adam Lockwood
and former Army Ranger James McGrath
were killed this morning
in a firefight.
FEMALE NEWSREADER: It is believed that
Lockwood and McGrath were the key links
between Miami law enforcement
and cartels.
MALE NEWSREADER 2: The late
Captain Howard has been fully exonerated.
Co-conspirators are currently being
rounded up by the FBI and the Miami PD.
MALE NEWSREADER 3:The search for
convicted killer Armando Aretas continues.
The fugitive remains at large.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
MIKE:
Hey, hey, hey. My people.
-Where's Theresa?
-She's with Little Marcus by the swings.
Hey. I'm about you hook you all up.
-I'm about you hook you up.
-DORN: Please. We're starving.
Watch this.
Partner.
What's all this?
Why you got on an apron?
Work on my grill skills.
No, Mike, you gotta earn the grill.
This takes seasonings and temperatures.
You can't just be cooking on my grill.
Your grill? Joker, this is a public park.
You don't own every grill you see.
You know what, Mike? Why don't you
go make some potato salad and set the table?
Oh, you talking dirty.
Now, look. I don't...
I don't know what you got going on
with your barbeque dictatorship
in your mind, but I ain't the one.
I'm cooking on this grill
whether you like it or not.
-Hey, Mike--
-Excuse me, sirs.
What are you...
What you doin', Reggie?
Request permission to cook my chicken.
[MIKE AND MARCUS LAUGH]
Permission denied, Reggie.
Go ahead somewhere, man.
Take your smock off
and go play with the kids.
Listen, this is the man area
of the barbeque.
Look, you know what?
All due respect, we appreciate that
you did save people that we love.
-We appreciate that, right?
-Yeah, we appreciate that.
-We appreciate that from here, Reggie.
-Yeah.
-Now, back the fuck up.
All right, look.
I'm willing to compromise with you.
You can work that half of the grill.
It's small. And I'll work this half.
Is he still standing there?
Yes, he is.
Huh, that's weird.
Yeah.
He think he hard now.
You need to let that motherfucker know
he ain't cooking no chicken out here today.
Mike. He killed 15 people at the house.
So, you not gonna handle this shit?
Yeah, I'm gonna let
that motherfucker cook the chicken.
Yeah, there's something weird in his eyes.
So I'mma make the potato salad.
-I'mma set the table.
-Yeah.
Permission granted, Reggie.
There you go.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DONKEY BRAYING]
Come on. Bring your ass on.
It's too hot out here for this shit.
Wish I had a horse.
At least I could ride that motherfucker.
All this free air out here,
and I still smell your stinkin' ass.
[DONKEY SNORTS]
I curse you, donkey.
I curse you for all lifetimes.
-[DONKEY KICKS]
-Oh!
You mother--
MIKE: Fuck you, Marcus.