Yeah!
Hey, Ellian! Wait up!
It's Princess Ellian. Open the gates.
Yeah!
Ugh.
Oh, come on. No, not the flare.
Again? Ellian, you just got out here.
Sorry, guys.
- Duty calls.
- That's the glamorous life of a princess.
It's okay. We'll see you
tonight at your birthday party.
Last year's was epic.
Yeah.
This year it's gonna be just family.
You know, super caszh. Super small.
Really? That's not like you.
Well, I'm 15. I'm a real teenager now.
So I wanna spend
more time with my parents.
Well, if you want to hang out later,
we'll be down at the market.
- Bye, Ellian!
- Come on. Let's go!
Good girl.
Princess Ellian!
I know I promised
I wouldn't use the flare today, but...
Minister Nazara.
Huh?
Uh...
Your Highness.
The king and queen
are requesting an audience.
Like an "audience" audience?
Like, a big one.
Hanging out at the market with my friends?
That's what I should be doing.
But can I?
- Princess!
- No.
Come on, Flink.
Here we go again.
♪ This is my world ♪
♪ Welcome, I guess ♪
♪ Thanks to my parents
It's sort of a mess ♪
♪ They've been on edge ♪
♪ Stomping about ♪
♪ Try to approach 'em
They'll snarl or lash out ♪
♪ Sure, woo-hoo, I'm a princess ♪
♪ Still, my life's not ideal ♪
♪ There's a few flaws, mainly because
Both of my parents are monsters ♪
♪ Like, actual monsters ♪
♪ For real! ♪
Keeping this secret
is ruining my wardrobe.
Sorry, Minister Bolinar.
- Dad! Mom!
- No, please!
If this ever got out...
Bad king. Bad queen.
Don't worry. I'm on it.
That's it. Over here.
Good queen.
♪ Only last year ♪
♪ Things were less weird ♪
♪ Then out of nowhere
A darkness appeared ♪
♪ Suddenly, boom! ♪
♪ Something just burst ♪
♪ When it was over
My parents were cursed ♪
♪ As for how we can cure them ♪
♪ That's still under dispute ♪
♪ But it's been strange
Since the big change ♪
♪ Seeing my parents as monsters ♪
♪ Impossible monsters to boot ♪
♪ Now, you may think
That yours are high-strung ♪
♪ Thoughtless and rude ♪
♪ Overdramatic, erratic, unglued ♪
♪ Stubborn as mules ♪
♪ Pains in the rear ♪
♪ But mine are so far past the line ♪
♪ That sometimes
I could practically swear ♪
♪ They're hardly aware I'm here ♪
♪ Such a sweet girl ♪
♪ Such a hard lot ♪
♪ Still, she's been coping
Despite you-know-what ♪
♪ Never complains ♪
♪ Never upset ♪
♪ Under that smile, though
She's struggling, I'll bet ♪
♪ She's the calm and mature one ♪
♪ While her folks go berserk ♪
- ♪ Having their backs ♪
- ♪ Hiding their tracks ♪
♪ Knowing her parents are monsters ♪
♪ And covering for monsters ♪
♪ It's work ♪
♪ And meanwhile
There are papers to sign ♪
♪ Troops to inspect ♪
♪ Meetings galore to restore
What's been wrecked ♪
♪ People to help
Laws to decree ♪
♪ And true
There's tons I'd rather do ♪
♪ But someone's gotta answer the call ♪
♪ And "someone" is always me ♪
- Did you finish your homework?
- I'll do it when I get back.
You're ruining my life.
♪ It would be nice ♪
♪ For just a day ♪
♪ To deal with parents
Who are bossy or nosy ♪
♪ Strict would be fine ♪
♪ Annoying?
Sure, okay ♪
♪ But all that mine do for me
Is pretty much ignore me ♪
♪ And let me say
It's the worst ♪
♪ Anyway, this is my life ♪
♪ It has been all year ♪
♪ Under a shadow that won't disappear ♪
♪ Everyone's tense ♪
♪ Tempers are high ♪
♪ But I've been dealing
Well, leastways I try ♪
♪ It's my job to stay hopeful ♪
♪ Till we're through this somehow ♪
♪ Frankly, I know that even though
They are behaving like monsters ♪
♪ Angry and wild
Easily riled ♪
♪ Ranting and raving like monsters ♪
♪ Somewhere inside
Under that hide ♪
♪ Those are my parents
Not monsters ♪
♪ I'm sure they're not monsters ♪
♪ I know they're not monsters ♪
♪ But, boy, are they monsters ♪
♪ Right now ♪
- Open this door!
- Oh no.
It's General Cardona, again.
I want to see
the king and queen.
Open the door.
Mom, Dad, shush.
We can't hold her off forever.
I know. But think about
what she'd do if she found out.
- Let us in!
- She's not exactly the chill type.
- Open this door!
- But what can we say this time?
We've already used every possible excuse.
State visit.
Labor dispute.
Trade summit.
Uh... Allow me.
After all, I am the minister
of communications.
Master of the spoken word.
Colonoscopies.
Masterful.
I will be back tomorrow.
And this time,
I will see the king and queen.
- Sunshine, this can't go on.
- I know.
It's been a year,
and we still haven't figured out how...
How to break the spell. I know.
What are we gonna do?
Oh man. What now?
Presenting the royal postmaster.
I come with an update on your message
to the Oracles of the Sun and Moon.
Oh, did they respond?
Now, as you know, the oracles live
in the Dark Forest of Eternal Darkness,
the most treacherous place.
Therefore, I sent eight
of my best birds to ensure
the safe delivery of your message.
Great. Did they get it?
Upon entering the forest,
seven of the eight birds
consumed enchanted berries
of petrification
and were immediately turned to stone.
We honor them.
- Hmm. But the other...
- Simon.
Millie.
Cedric.
Cedric II.
Hannigan.
Ambrose.
Little Dorrit.
Gone but not forgotten.
So tragic.
But that still leaves one bird.
And I'm hoping it's this guy
who's carrying
a little, tiny scroll in his beak.
- Correct.
- Oh!
My bravest bird, Old Joe,
has returned with your reply,
forsaking all fear
of the Dark Forest of Eternal Darkness.
All the while limiting his
intake of enchanted berries
to the smaller, slower-acting variety.
Oh! Oh.
Uh...
He was a good bird.
He was like a son to me.
"Add water."
Huh?
Hey, wh... where's the message?
Where'd it go?
Flink, you little thief.
Did you put it in your cheek again?
Uh-uh.
Oh.
Ooh.
Greetings, Princess Ellian of Lumbria.
We are the Oracles of the Sun and Moon.
Moon. Moon. Moon.
Your unfortunate situation intrigues us.
Yet to rectify this problem,
we must observe it firsthand.
Hand. Hand. Hand.
Flink, they're coming here.
Therefore, expect us
to arrive in your kingdom
on the eve of the third moon
on the third day of the third month.
Munch. Munch. Munch.
Not "munch."
- Mon-th.
- Oh.
Month.
Third moon of the third day
of the third month?
That's my birthday.
That's tonight.
Oh! Happy birthday, Princess.
Didn't we agree to keep this whole thing
mysterious and low-grade spooky?
Oh. Yes, we did.
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
Anyway, we will be there soon.
Prepare for our arrival.
Yes!
No more monsters.
No more secrets.
Just normal parents and a normal life.
I need to tell Bolinar and Nazara.
They're gonna love this.
Oh, I hate this.
Look at the circles under my eyes.
What have we become?
I speak 17 languages.
I wrote our kingdom's constitution.
I am a mother-loving national treasure.
And this is how
I have to spend my morning,
designing a monster pooper-scooper.
We need a real leader.
This kingdom cannot hold itself together.
Uh, begging your ministers' pardon,
but birthday gifts are piling up,
and the reception room is slightly...
Damaged?
...not there anymore.
Bring them in here.
All righty.
Nazara, we can't keep
this secret much longer.
Whoopsie.
What will the people do
when they find out?
- Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
- I'm afraid to guess.
The king and queen were so beloved.
So beloved.
Then again, there is someone here
even more beloved.
Who? Me? Oh, you're too kind.
No, not you, you big man-boy.
The princess.
Do you realize how old she's going to be?
I haven't the faintest idea.
Thank you.
She's turning 15.
This could solve everything.
What are you talking about?
♪ As you know
Our status quo is quite unbearable ♪
♪ Half the castle's unrepairable ♪
♪ We're in total disarray ♪
♪ Where we once had charm
And style and grace and elegance ♪
♪ Now we're babysitting elephants ♪
♪ It's completely not okay ♪
♪ Don't you wish
That we could gussy up the place again? ♪
♪ Dress in satin, silk, and lace again ♪
♪ Like we did
When times were good ♪
♪ Just imagine entertaining VIPs again ♪
♪ Drinking wine and eating cheese again ♪
♪ Well, what if we really could? ♪
♪ It's never gonna happen ♪
- ♪ It can ♪
- ♪ It won't ♪
♪ It will ♪
♪ We have a chance
To get back in the dance
♪ But we can't just sit still ♪
♪ We need to step
Step in a new direction ♪
♪ Step towards a new perfection ♪
♪ Step after step
Until all our problems are gone ♪
♪ And step by step ♪
♪ If we keep stepping forward ♪
♪ Step without looking backward ♪
♪ So we can all move on ♪
But, wait, what are you proposing?
♪ Lucky us ♪
♪ Tonight the princess comes of age
At last ♪
♪ Meaning we can set the stage at last ♪
- ♪ For a brand-new queen to reign ♪
- That's good.
♪ And when she has put the palace
Once again at ease ♪
♪ We bring back the old amenities? ♪
♪ And we'll toast 'em with champagne ♪
I like it.
♪ Please, you love it ♪
♪ You're right
I think I do ♪
- ♪ With style ♪
- ♪ And with craft ♪
♪ We'll have choreographed
A benevolent coup ♪
♪ Let's take that step ♪
♪ Step in a new direction ♪
♪ Call it a course correction ♪
- ♪ Step after step ♪
- ♪ Until we can pass the baton ♪
♪ And step by step ♪
♪ As we keep stepping upward ♪
♪ No one will think it's awkward ♪
♪ When we at last move on ♪
♪ Step one
Ease the royals aside ♪
♪ Step two
We announce that they died ♪
♪ Step three
Once the teardrops have dried ♪
♪ The popular daughter steps in ♪
- ♪ Next step ♪
- ♪ Give the princess a crown ♪
- ♪ And a fabulous gown ♪
♪ Next step
Watch the girl take the town ♪
- ♪ So easy ♪
- ♪ A breeze ♪
♪ If the princess agrees
Then the dance can begin ♪
Ministers!
- Princess!
- I've got the answer.
- So do we.
- We're going to break the spell.
You're going to be the queen.
- Wait, what?
- What? How?
The oracles finally answered my letters.
They're going to break the spell.
Oh, well, that would be wonderful.
Of course. But if they can't,
your kingdom needs a real ruler.
- A queen.
- Wait. What about my parents?
We'll send them to the country
where they can run and be happy.
And you can visit them anytime you like.
All right. I'll agree.
But only if we try the oracles first.
Yeah, of course.
But after...
♪ The after part won't matter ♪
♪ The spell will be unbound ♪
- ♪ If not... ♪
- ♪ But it will ♪
- ♪ Yes, whatever ♪
- ♪ But still ♪
- ♪ You'll agree to be crowned? ♪
- ♪ Yes ♪
♪ It's time to step ♪
- ♪ Step, step, step, step, step ♪
- ♪ Step in a new direction ♪
- ♪ Back towards reconnection ♪
- ♪ Step, step, step, step ♪
♪ Step after step
And then all our woes will be gone ♪
♪ And step by step ♪
♪ After the celebration ♪
♪ After the coronation ♪
♪ Then we can all move on ♪
♪ Then we will all move on ♪
♪ Then we'll at last move on ♪
♪ Happy birthday
Princess Ellian ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- Happy birthday, Princess.
- Absolutely, sunshine.
Thank you all so much for this wonderful...
This way, Your Majesty. Over here.
- Mom! Dad!
- Attaboy.
If my wish comes true, we'll all have
something to celebrate tonight.
Yes. Here's to that.
Bolinar?
Uh, excuse me. Uh, pardon me.
Royal business to attend to.
Uh, one for me, please.
Look. Your Majesty, focus.
Oh!
Look at you two,
getting all dressed up for my birthday.
Very good.
- Hey!
- Chew away, sire.
Dad! Put him down.
Thank you, Princess.
Okay, not feeling the crown. I get it.
But the crown is kinda important
and valuable, so...
Uh, wait, where'd it go?
Flink!
Get back here.
Uh. No!
Ugh... Filthy purple rat.
My cake.
Gotta say, it suits you.
Honestly, Princess, I don't understand
your affection for this vile vermin.
Oh! Oh! It's them.
They're here.
Be cool.
Presenting sole architects of the known
and unknown universe,
the most powerful and enchanted beings
of all time,
the Oracles of the Sun and Moon.
Greetings, citizens of Lumbria.
Lumbria. Lumbria. Lumbria.
Excellent service, Lawrence.
I'm giving you five stars.
Oh.
Five stars? What, are you crazy?
It smelled like cooked cabbage in there.
Oh, I liked that.
I thought it added a homey touch.
Illustrious oracles,
on behalf of the Kingdom of Lumbria,
I thank you for your presence.
Ah. You must be Princess Ellian.
Oh! That's me, the one with the tiara.
The birthday girl.
Enchanted to meet you.
I am Luno.
And I'm Sunny.
- I have a good feeling about this.
- So let me see here.
In your letter, you said you're having
some trouble with your parents?
You think they are... Uh... Uh...
- What did she call them, Sunny?
- Monsters.
Right. Monsters.
And what makes you think
your parents are monsters?
Well... Hmm.
Wow, you ain't kidding.
Her parents are monsters.
Yes, I know. That's why I need your he...
Dad. Dad. No, no, no, no, no.
These are our guests. Oh.
Hey, Mom, you too.
Oh, I thought it was a metaphor.
I thought you were just being dramatic.
- Why would I do that?
- Because you're a teenager.
Oh. Uh... Uh... Who wants Squeaky?
Yeah, fetch!
Wait. Wait, sire.
Sorry about that. They can be a lot.
Princess, something tells me
your parents have been
in the Dark Forest of Eternal Darkness.
So dark they named it twice.
Well, yeah, they have.
But how did you know?
Because it's the only place
this sort of magic exists.
And don't kill the messenger,
but if they don't change back soon,
they'll be monsters forever.
What? No. Please, do something.
Of course. Of course.
We didn't travel all this way
in a frog's mouth for nothin'.
Hand me the wand.
Oh! Um...
- I don't have the wand.
- Are you kidding? Where's the wand?
I traded it in for an upgrade.
What? Why would you do that?
Well, we talked about this.
- We talked about this.
- What are you talking about?
- You never said this to me.
- Oh, but I have.
This is all-new information
I'm getting here.
Oh, I've said it so many times.
This is a fob.
It's like a universal wand.
Now, instead of needing
a bunch of different wands,
we have one fob that does everything.
What was wrong
with the six wands we already have?
They were taking up
the whole coffee table.
Argh.
- Just speak a command and press a button.
- Speak a command?
- You just have to...
- Go.
- You gotta just press...
- Go, go, fob.
- Just press and talk.
- Go!
I'm pressing
the living daylights out of it.
- You just have to...
- But nothing's coming out.
- Oh, give it to me.
- No, no, no. I got it.
Ah. Eh. Ah!
Play!
Shoo. Shoo. Shoo!
♪ You want to know the secret ♪
♪ Of how to stop the curse? ♪
♪ To take your monster problem ♪
♪ And put it in reverse? ♪
♪ Then come a little closer ♪
♪ And listen extra well ♪
♪ This is how to break the... ♪
Mom!
Oof!
- Oh no!
- Help!
- Get him away from me!
- This is why we never go out.
- No! Dad, stop!
- Ahh! Help!
We are never setting foot
in this castle again!
Lawrence! Help!
Wait! Please! Come back!
No. No. No!
Don't go!
What have you done?
That was our only chance
to break the spell.
Ellian.
Sunshine.
I'm so sorry.
Make the arrangements.
I'll become queen.
Mom?
Dad?
I'm sorry I got so mad.
You didn't know what you were doing.
Anyway, it's still my birthday.
Here. I, uh, brought cake.
I just really miss you both.
Mom?
♪ Shattered walls ♪
♪ Empty hallways ♪
♪ Is that all we left behind? ♪
♪ I recall how we used to be ♪
♪ I see each moment in my mind ♪
♪ Endless talks ♪
♪ Celebrations ♪
♪ Aimless walks
With our hands entwined ♪
♪ Most of all
There was love to spare ♪
♪ And magic everywhere ♪
♪ We breathed it in like air ♪
♪ But no one's there now ♪
♪ I wish I knew the way back
To the way it was before ♪
♪ With you there
In your old familiar place ♪
♪ Reliving every day
Back when my heart learned how to soar ♪
♪ Every smile ♪
♪ Each embrace ♪
♪ If I could find the way back
To the way it was before ♪
♪ And we could be together there
Right now ♪
♪ I'd run without delay
Back to the way it was before ♪
♪ Run like mad ♪
♪ To what we had ♪
♪ If only I knew how ♪
♪ With you here ♪
♪ I was fearless ♪
♪ Year by year
I grew sure and strong ♪
♪ Now it's clear
What I really need ♪
♪ Is what you gave me all along ♪
♪ The lessons that you taught me ♪
♪ And all the plans we laid ♪
♪ The winters by the fire ♪
♪ And the summers in the shade ♪
♪ The stars we used to wish on ♪
♪ And the wishes that we made ♪
♪ Things like that must live on ♪
♪ Can't we go to where they've gone? ♪
♪ There's got to be a way back
To the way it was before ♪
♪ To stand with you again
On solid ground ♪
♪ We'll spend one perfect day back
In the way it was before ♪
♪ Just one day ♪
♪ Then one more ♪
♪ Maybe three ♪
♪ Why keep score? ♪
♪ Let's just stay ♪
♪ The way it was ♪
♪ Before ♪
Oh no.
No.
I didn't lock the doors.
Oh no.
Monsters!
Monsters? In the kingdom?
- Where did they come from?
- I don't know.
Ready the battalion!
Mom! Dad! Stop!
This way.
No. No!
Seal off the plaza! Follow me!
- Your Highness. Stay here.
- What are you doing? No. Stop.
Don't do this.
Listen to me.
- Mom! Dad!
- Princess! No!
You don't understand.
These are my parents.
This is your king and queen.
General Cardona,
they were changed by a spell a year ago.
You should have told me.
Stop, please.
Get the nets!
- Princess!
- Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
- Their Majesties.
- That's the king and queen?
Perhaps at one time.
But not anymore.
- This is dark magic.
- How could this happen?
It turned the king
and queen into monsters.
- It could change us too.
- Hold on.
What should we do?
- We have to leave.
- But I can't leave my home.
- Where will we go?
- Listen, we... we... we have a plan.
- But who's in charge now?
- Yeah!
The princess will take the throne.
The princess?
I like the princess.
- Yes, but what of the monsters?
- Yeah!
The monsters?
Wait. No. No. No. No.
You... you don't understand.
Once Princess Ellian assumes the throne,
the monsters will be sent
to the far reaches of the world.
What? I... I... I never agreed to that.
General, we did not discuss this.
For the safety of the princess
and the kingdom, it must be done.
Have no fear.
You will never see the monsters again.
We are taking steps.
The monsters are being put into cages.
By first light, they will be gone.
Flink, we have to do something.
We have to get them out of here.
Hmm?
Flink, what do you have?
Give me.
I mean it.
Why does everybody
keep eating all the important stuff?
Hmm?
I can't find it. I can't find it anywhere.
The oracles!
Calm down. Calm down.
Just retrace your steps.
- Hello?
- Good idea. Uh...
- We caught a frog...
- Hello?!
Who's that?
Did you invite your mother again?
No. It's me, Princess Ellian.
I have your magic fob.
See? I told you I didn't lose it.
Listen, things have gotten
really bad here.
Please, I need you to come back.
Oh, no. We are not going
anywhere near that crazy place again.
- Luno, she's in trouble.
- What if I come to you?
Will you help me then?
Ooh, you're very pushy for a princess.
Oh, of course we will. Won't we?
Oh, fine. But good luck
finding a frog at this hour.
Use the fob, Princess.
It'll bring you directly to our home
in the Dark Forest of Eternal Darkness.
The order is given.
Move the monsters out.
Thank you both so much.
Soldiers!
- Put down your weapons.
- Princess?
I said drop 'em.
What the...?
- Ugh.
Guess we gotta be a bit more specific.
Uh... Take us to the oracles.
What's happening?
I was really hoping for more of
a "zing and you're there" type of thing.
- Hey! Wait for us!
- They're getting away!
We need something. Uh...
A... a carriage! A... a cart!
Uh, something.
Oh!
They're stealing our princess.
Hurry! Hurry!
Stop those monsters.
Soldiers, follow me.
Princess!
Flink, here. Stall them.
Whoa!
Hey!
- Wait!
- Hey!
Whoa!
Close the gates!
Oh no.
Flink, hold the gate!
Whoa!
Whoa.
Oh no.
Hey, look alive.
Heel.
Sit. Out of the...
Princess!
We're trying to rescue you!
No, thanks! I don't need to be rescued!
Why won't she listen?
Because she's a teenager.
Now, just get her!
Ah!
Flink?
Oh no.
Sorry, Bolinar!
Well, I should think so
after all you put me through.
Bolinar?
As your trusted counselor,
your esteemed mentor,
I implore you to... Whoa!
What's that hairy thing?
And that hairy thing?
No!
Oh, wait. If I'm in this body,
who's in my body?
Oh! No. No, no, no, no, no!
Ellian, you have to help me.
I'm a purple rat!
Not at the top of my to-do list.
Oh, what am I gonna do?
Get us out of here.
Whoa!
Huh?
Mom? Dad? You okay?
Well, I'm not.
Thank you for asking.
- We did it. We made it.
- Well, bully for us.
But meanwhile,
my body is back at the kingdom.
No! No! No! Please, don't eat me.
Don't worry, Bolinar.
The oracles will fix everything.
Well, how are supposed to find them?
Wait, stop. What is that?
I smell oregano.
A dash of basil.
A delicate sprinkling of rosemary.
Oh!
It's pasta fazool.
Come on. Who would be cooking pasta
in the middle of the Dark Forest?
Who? Who?
What do you think? Should we be
naughty and have garlic bread?
Well, we were eaten by a monster,
so I think we deserve it.
Yay! Because I put it
in the oven 20 minutes ago.
You're terrible.
Oh! Company!
Ah, you're finally here.
Ugh! She brought those monsters.
We told her to come.
It's not like she could
just hire a monster sitter.
Princess, you made it.
Whew. Barely.
But here we are.
And so sorry about the whole
"my mom eating you" situation.
It won't happen again. Will it, Mother?
So here's your fob.
Go ahead.
- Go ahead?
- Break the spell.
Oh! No, sorry.
The fob was just to get you here.
It can't change them back.
- What?
- But you can, right?
- I'm afraid it's not in our skill set.
- But you can change me back?
Nuh-uh. You're a body switch.
You're going to need
your other half to do anything.
Anyone you might know
who could help my parents?
Like a wizard or a sorcerer or a pixie?
A pixie? What,
you think we all know each other?
Like we're all part
of some sort of magical mafia?
Oh, sorry, I didn't mean...
Though to be fair, there is
that pixie couple we play pinochle with.
They're not very magical though.
They're not very good
pinochle players either.
Bless their hearts.
So you're telling me
there's no one who can break this spell?
We didn't say that.
Well, then who?
- Them.
Them? Are you cuckoo banana cakes?
Look at them.
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
So tell me what to do,
and I'll do it for them.
That's not how these things work.
Only they can break the spell.
How?
Together, they get to embark
on an invigorating quest
through the Dark Forest
of Eternal Darkness.
But there's no path.
There'll be lights to guide them.
Mmm, some of the time.
They're very fickle.
You're messing with us, right?
- Discover pathways through mountains.
- With lots of unstable cliffs.
- Ford new streams.
- Ha! More like deadly rapids.
Glide across deserts.
Oy, the heat. And it's not a dry heat.
Princess! Wait!
You didn't let us finish.
If what you're saying is true,
I'll never see my parents again.
It's... it's hopeless.
Great.
Oh, poor thing.
Princess, it's never hopeless.
♪ When you're in the dark ♪
♪ And lost ♪
♪ And life looks gray ♪
♪ Just a single drop ♪
♪ Of light ♪
♪ Can point the way ♪
♪ And so ♪
♪ If you can catch one glimmer
Tend to it well ♪
♪ Help it to swell and grow ♪
♪ Like so ♪
♪ Soon that little drop
Might just become a spark ♪
♪ One that lets you find more light
Within the dark ♪
♪ And soon
Those lights will start to shimmer ♪
♪ Making the gloom
Practically bloom and glow ♪
♪ Suddenly, boom
You know which way to go ♪
- ♪ Look for the light ♪
♪ And it will guide you ♪
♪ Look for the light ♪
♪ Keep it in sight ♪
♪ Close as can be ♪
♪ Follow its gleam
And it will seem ♪
♪ Somehow the dark's not as extreme ♪
♪ If you just look for the light
Well, you'll see ♪
Is it a metaphor?
Metaphor, shmetaphor.
What you need
is an actual drop of pure radiance.
I'm afraid he's right, Princess.
Your parents are monsters
because they've lost their light.
It needs to be replaced pronto.
♪ When somebody's spark goes out ♪
♪ The dark creeps in ♪
♪ Till they can't see
Who they are ♪
♪ Or where they've been ♪
♪ So go ♪
♪ Before the world grows dimmer ♪
♪ And you just might
Somehow ignite what's gone ♪
♪ One drop of light
Could turn it right back on ♪
♪ Look for the light ♪
♪ Just like the light burning inside you ♪
♪ Look for the light
Cling to it tight ♪
♪ Follow its lead ♪
♪ One little ray
Could be your way ♪
♪ Out of the night
To a new day ♪
♪ Where you will find
All the light that you need ♪
You see that?
High atop the last mountain,
it's the Lake of Light.
To restore your parents' humanity,
they must go into that lake.
But beware the darkness.
It feeds on dark feelings,
growing bigger and bigger
until you're lost.
Well, that's no problem.
I don't have any dark feelings.
Everyone has dark feelings.
It's how you deal with them that counts.
Got it.
Mom. Dad.
Follow me.
♪ Look for the light ♪
- ♪ This is it, the answer I needed ♪
- ♪ Steady and bright ♪
- ♪ My prayers have been heeded ♪
- ♪ You'll be all right ♪
♪ Now I'm on track to get my life back
To sorta normal again ♪
♪ Trust me, it's true ♪
- ♪ Up ahead, the pathway is glowing ♪
- ♪ And trust me too ♪
♪ So come on
It's time to get going ♪
- ♪ Gotta hurry, no time to worry ♪
- ♪ No need to worry ♪
- ♪ Come on, you know what to do ♪
- ♪ You know what to do ♪
♪ Simply look for
The light shining through ♪
♪ Just look for
♪ Look for the light shining through ♪
Garlic bread!
I don't know what you're so happy about.
Bolinar, all we have to do
is get my parents to the Lake of Light.
You heard the oracles.
Oh, I heard 'em all right.
They also said to beware the darkness.
And the cherry on top,
that it's drawn to dark feelings.
Oh, it's definitely coming for me first.
Look.
There's the next light beacon.
But I think that's our only way across.
They found us already!
Please spare me, great darkness.
I'm small and meaningless.
Relax, Bolinar.
We're traveling with two giant monsters.
Whatever the darkness is should be
more afraid of us than we are of it.
Oh yeah,
they're our big, brave protectors.
Mom, Dad, let's go. Come on.
- Soldiers.
- Yes.
Quick, everyone down there.
Shh.
Stop grunting.
Wait, where's Bolinar?
Help! Help!
Over here! It's me, Bolinar!
- It doesn't look like me, but it is me!
- Don't move.
- I'm with the princess! She's here!
- Bolinar!
- Help!
- Bolinar, stop it.
If they find us
before my parents change back,
they'll be banished. You know that.
They aren't your parents.
They aren't the king and queen.
Princess, Lumbria needs a true monarch.
Yes, and the best way to give Lumbria
a true monarch
is to break the spell and bring back
the king and queen.
Wait a second.
Where are the king and queen?
Mom! Dad!
Wait. Wait for me.
Huh?
Whoa.
Echo.
Hey, watch this.
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
Okay, Dad, you try.
Good one, Dad.
♪ La, la, la ♪
Whoa. Mom, that's great.
Your turn, Bolinar. Say something.
I wish I was dead.
Uh!
Shh!
No more angry noises.
Just stay nice.
They're just animals.
They don't know what you're saying.
They're my parents,
and they know what I'm saying.
No!
No. Lower your voices.
Stop!
Stop it.
- Mom, Dad, you're making it worse.
- They can't understand you, Princess.
- Your parents aren't in there anymore.
- Don't say that.
No, you're wrong.
They are in there. They have to be.
Wait.
- Stop it [grunts].
- Princess!
Why do they keep fighting?
Why can't I stop them?
The darkness, it's coming for me!
Wait. It's not coming for me.
It's coming for you, Princess.
I thought you said
you didn't have any dark feelings.
I didn't think I did.
Get out! Get out of there!
Get out of there!
Help!
Whoa!
G...
- G... G... G...
- G... G...
- Girl!
Mom! Dad! You can talk!
No, I cannot.
Well, Dad, you just did it again.
You said... [imitates king] "No, I cannot."
What is "no"?
What is "I"?
What is "cannot"?
Hey, I am saying things,
but I do not know what they mean
as they come out of my mouth.
Yeah, you are.
What about you, Mom?
Girl.
Yes. Yes!
I am a girl, your girl.
Girl, listen to me talk now.
I like the sound of my own voice.
You're my dad all right.
Girl.
Yes. Don't you remember
anything else about me?
Cake girl.
True. I guess I did bring you cake.
- You bring cake?
- Like cake.
- Wait.
- Have cake now?
- No. Listen.
- Cake.
Hello. If you have cake,
I definitely want a slice.
There is no cake.
Aw.
That doesn't matter.
You're talking!
There must be so much you wanna say to me.
I have to release liquid
from inside myself.
Well, they're a far cry
from their former selves.
Would it kill you
to look on the bright side?
Me? I'm the most positive person I know.
Look.
There's the next light beacon.
Hey! The liquid is outside of me now!
Congratulations.
Okay, you guys.
We need to start heading
in the direction of that light.
- Hey, quit it.
- You quit it.
- No, you quit it. No, you quit.
Hey! Knock it off, both of you.
Didn't you guys learn anything back there?
Fighting in this forest
makes bad stuff happen.
So, going forward, no more fighting. Okay?
- Okay.
Great. Now stay close and follow me.
Wait. Wait for me.
Wait for me. Wait! Wait!
Are we there yet?
We just started.
Whoa, I see sky balls.
What? Oh!
Those are clouds.
I like my word better.
I think I do too.
What is?
That is a rock.
Rock.
Pretty.
Like rocks. Ooh!
Big rock.
Shiny rock.
Itty-bitty, teeny-weeny rock.
Oh! Bird rocks.
Mom! Don't eat those berries.
Beautiful. What are they?
Butterflies.
Butterflies?
How can butter fly?
Did you just make a dad joke?
Dad! Wait up!
Oh, Bolinar, this is so wonderful.
My parents are coming back to me.
Oh, Princess, they're still just beasts
who can string together a few words.
They don't know who you are.
They don't know who I am.
- Me, their brilliant advisor.
- No, they know. You'll see.
They will remember me and you.
They won't. For all they know,
my name could be Lord Candy Pants.
- Lord Candy Pants.
- Lord Candy Pants. Lord Candy...
- Lord Candy Pants. Lord Candy Pants.
Why did I go with Candy Pants?
Is Lord Candy Pants tired?
Lord Candy Pants is fine.
Stop saying that.
- Is Lord Candy Pants upset?
- Lord Candy Pants is always upset.
I am not upset.
Come on, Bolinar. Lighten up.
The light. We did it. We made it. Oh.
Sweet sleep at last.
No. Bolinar, we can't rest.
We have to get to that next beacon.
Probably just takes a second.
And we're on to the next beacon.
Uh, beacon.
Show me the beacon.
Uh, bring me the beacon.
Beacon for four, please.
Can I get a beacon up in here?
Where is it?
What about my name?
Do you remember my name?
Mm.
I know.
Is it Cake Girl?
No, Dad. It's not Cake Girl.
Where is that light?
I see a light.
You do? Where? Where is it?
Those are stars, Mom.
Mm.
Pretty.
Yeah. They are, aren't they?
We used to look at them together.
♪ Do you remember
When we'd gaze at the stars? ♪
♪ And then you'd say ♪
♪ You'd love me till the stars ♪
♪ Turned cold and gray ♪
♪ I remember night sky ♪
Yes.
♪ I remember hush sounds ♪
Me too.
♪ Nestled in the warmth feel ♪
♪ Watching as the blink lights blaze ♪
♪ I'm not remembering ♪
♪ But sometimes pictures come
And catch my eye again ♪
Go on.
♪ Then they float on by again ♪
♪ And drift away ♪
- ♪ I remember laugh bells ♪
- ♪ Is that remembering? ♪
- ♪ I remember heart smiles ♪
- ♪ Pretty pictures ♪
- ♪ Safe beneath those blink lights ♪
- ♪ How they fill the air again ♪
- ♪ Blazing down as bright as day ♪
- ♪ Like I'm almost there again ♪
♪ But they won't stay ♪
- ♪ I remember joy glow ♪
- ♪ Yes, you remember ♪
- ♪ Filling me with proud beams ♪
- ♪ Don't let that feeling go astray ♪
- ♪ As the little blink lights ♪
- ♪ Don't let it die ♪
♪ Turn their shining eyes our way ♪
- ♪ Still not remembering ♪
- ♪ Try, please try to remember ♪
♪ I tell my eyes
To try and not forget again ♪
- ♪ It's okay, just try ♪
- ♪ But they just get wet again ♪
♪ It'll all come back ♪
- ♪ And won't obey ♪
- ♪ Someday ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ I'll keep remembering
Those stars, us, and everything ♪
♪ And, hey ♪
♪ I'm sure that you will too ♪
♪ Someday ♪
Ellian?
You know my name.
Mom.
They stopped here.
Looks like they spent the night.
Oh, I'm so worried about her, General.
We've got to find the princess.
And soon.
What is that noise?
Bolinar.
Now what are you eating?
That's disgusting.
Wait a minute.
It's a trail
of nuts.
Bolinar's found their trail.
Brilliant, Minister.
Scouts, I want
a thorough flyover of that area.
How do you make more money than me?
- Ellian.
Ellian.
I like this name, Ellian.
Okay, you got my name.
Great. Now listen.
You are my parents,
and I am your daughter.
You are my parents, and I am your dogger.
No, I'm your daughter.
Look! There it is!
Well, whose dogger am I?
No one's.
Oh.
- It's okay because you're my dad.
- And you are my dogger.
Yes, exactly.
And purple rat is my dogger.
No. Purple rat is not your daughter.
He's also not a purple rat.
- You rat.
- Huh?
- I am confused.
- You're breadcrumbing.
- You're leaving a trail.
- No, I'm not.
- You're gonna lead the soldiers to us.
- You really think so?
- Okay.
- No.
No more schemes. No more trails.
We are getting to that beacon.
The only question is
can I trust you to get there on your feet,
or am I going to have to
get Mom to carry you in her mouth?
- I choose mouth.
- You can trust me. I'm a team player.
Yeah, but which team?
- Wh... what's happening?
- We're sinking.
- I know we're sinking. Why are we sinking?
- Well, how should I know? Just save me.
I have sand
where there should not be sand.
That's why I like rocks.
Quick, Dad, get to a rock.
Oh.
Okay, here's the deal.
To get across this thing without drowning,
we need to stay in the light.
No. There are too many sky balls.
It's too dangerous.
We will go that way
on hard, safe green land.
Mom, that's so far.
No, we have to go straight.
Faster this way.
Right, Ellian?
It's a faster way to die.
Tell him, Ellian.
We won't die if we are fast.
Ellian, let's go.
Dad, we all have to agree on a plan.
- We did. Mine.
- Dad, would you just stop?
- Ellian agree with monster woman?
- I didn't say that.
You don't agree with me?
I didn't say that either.
- Ellian agree with me.
- Dad.
Why does Ellian agree with monster man?
- Wait, what?
- Ellian likes monster man more than Mom?
- Yes.
- No. Don't put me in the middle.
The darkness, it's coming!
- Oh no.
- They found us.
That's my armor.
That's my body.
That's my body in my armor.
- Come on.
- But... but... but my body!
- Why are you always right?
- Why do you never listen?
This isn't the time.
Move out!
- Ellian, tell her she's wrong.
- No, Ellian, tell him he's wrong.
Mom, Dad, this isn't fair.
Halt! Retreat to solid ground!
We'd be on the other side now
if we'd gone my way.
No, if we'd gone my way.
- This is your way.
- Why do you always do this?
- Ellian, tell her I'm right.
- Ellian would be safer my way.
No, Ellian would be safer with me.
- Don't make me choose between you.
- No, you...
Ellian would be safer my way.
- No, Ellian would be safer with...
- Dad! Dad!
- Can you get us over there?
- Huh?
Yes. Yes, I can do that.
Left. Left.
Whoa.
Oh no!
- Mom, can you carry me over there?
- You got it.
No!
We've gotta get there without being seen.
But how?
Take her. I'll hold them off.
No. She's safer with you.
I have an idea.
Wha...? Where did they go?
Nothing here, General.
Search the other side.
They can't have gone far.
Oh, wonderful.
There goes my body,
riding away with the army.
What if the oracles were wrong?
Or the lake doesn't work?
What if we're all stuck like this forever?
Oh, things couldn't get any worse.
My body.
My beautiful body.
Bolinar, are you still pouting?
- Yes.
- Well, come on.
Try to keep up.
We all have to get to the Lake of Light...
Wait.
Mom? Dad?
Oh no. We're lost.
- Princess, protect me.
- What?
Oh, they're flinks.
Maybe they can help us.
With what? Getting rabies?
Excuse me.
We're lost.
Can you help me find my parents?
They're sort of these big monsters.
No! No. They're nice monsters.
Oh, that's not good.
Please tell me those aren't graves.
What do you think they're saying?
Well, it's basic diplomacy.
Share a meal, gain their trust,
and in turn, they'll help us out.
Great. Then bottoms up.
Me? Why me?
Because you're a flink.
I am not a flink!
I'm a man of good taste and high breeding.
One who pampers his palate a lot.
True, I've done some adventurous eating.
But right there, that's a definite not!
♪ It's so disgusting ♪
♪ I mean disgusting ♪
♪ All crunchy crusting ♪
♪ And wriggling toes
It's too appalling ♪
♪ And, yes, I'm stalling ♪
♪ But if I must ♪
H... Here goes.
♪ I could get used to this ♪
♪ I could get used to this! ♪
♪ Somehow I find I don't quite mind
That I've been reduced to this ♪
♪ And while it's true
It's sticky as glue ♪
♪ Much like the goo
That someone might sneeze ♪
♪ Still, do I detect dill? ♪
♪ And are those notes
Of chocolate and cheese? ♪
♪ I'd be okay with this ♪
- ♪ Nearly gourmet with this ♪
- Hey, wait!
♪ Frankly, I swear that
I could pair a lovely rosé with this ♪
♪ Sure, it seems tough
To swallow this stuff ♪
♪ But swallow enough
It isn't so strange ♪
♪ Maybe I could get used to
My big change ♪
Bolinar, don't forget
to ask for directions!
I will, Princess.
Eventually.
♪ No, this isn't the life I expected ♪
♪ Still, it isn't so bad, I confess ♪
♪ Yes, I'm probably getting infected ♪
♪ But I think I'll survive nonetheless ♪
♪ What's more surprising ♪
♪ I'm not despising ♪
♪ This huge downsizing
Of my affairs ♪
♪ Call it revolting ♪
♪ The stench is jolting ♪
♪ But on the whole ♪
♪ Who cares? ♪
♪ I could get used to this ♪
♪ More than just used to this ♪
♪ How about a most wholehearted toast
With some kind of juice to this? ♪
♪ Gross, it may be
But snooty old me ♪
♪ Is finally free
From worries and strife ♪
♪ Looks like I could get used to
My new life ♪
Bolinar, what's gotten into you?
♪ I've gotta say
It's more than marvelous ♪
♪ How have I lived
My whole life larva-less? ♪
♪ The slop, the slime
The sludge, the rot ♪
♪ It's different, sure
But hey, so what? ♪
♪ I could get used to this ♪
♪ Really cut loose to this ♪
♪ Make no mistake, I'd proudly shake
My big fat caboose to this ♪
♪ And if a guy as stuffy as I
Can fall from so high ♪
♪ And still have a ball ♪
♪ Maybe any big change
Can soon feel small ♪
♪ And anyone could get used to anything ♪
♪ At all ♪
Mom! Dad!
I like this new Bolinar.
Oh!
Thank you!
Ooh.
Whoa.
Hey!
Mom, what are you... Uh...
Okay, okay, put me down.
Oh, you think you're tough, huh?
Come on. Show me what you got.
Hm?
She likes cake.
Yah!
Daughter.
Ellian
is my daughter.
Our daughter.
Mom. Dad.
Are you back?
- Oh, Ellian.
- You are our daughter.
Oh, you're back!
I missed you.
Oh, my little girl.
Ellian, my love.
Ellian, you were right.
They were in there all along.
Your Highnesses.
The princess never gave up on you.
How amazing you are.
The Lake of Light.
There it is.
Come on.
Yeah!
Whoo!
We made it.
We made it!
Come on in. The light is fine.
Huh?
You always have to
rehash everything.
No, it's you.
You never let anyone finish.
If I held my breath waiting for you
to get to a point, I would suffocate.
There you go again,
turning a disagreement into an insult.
Right, it's my fault.
It's never not my fault.
You always do this.
Oh.
So that's how it happened.
This is all our fault.
The anger.
We let it consume us.
Huh? What are they doing?
We stopped bringing out
the best in each other.
Hey! What are you waiting for?
Just get in.
What?
Ellian,
you remember how much
we used to argue, right?
All families fight.
Not like that.
It's the reason we became monsters.
Just step into the light.
I... it'll fix everything.
We can't.
What do you mean you can't?
Well, don't you wanna be human again?
Of course we want to be human.
We just don't want
to be those people again.
I don't understand.
Ellian,
we can't be together anymore.
We can't go back to the way it was before.
Ellian, just give us a minute.
Your mother and I, we need
to figure out what we're going to do.
Maybe we can find a way to work together.
What you're gonna do?
What you're gonna do?!
Ellian.
♪ You say you're done, finished, goodbye
What about me? ♪
Ellian, please.
♪ You say there's no reason to try?
What about me? ♪
♪ And after all I've gone through
Just held on through ♪
♪ All the things I've had to see ♪
♪ What about me? ♪
- Ellian, you have to under...
- No! Not anymore!
♪ I had to grow up on my own
What about that? ♪
♪ When I felt lost, scared, and alone
Where were you at? ♪
♪ Still I did all I had to
I was glad to ♪
♪ That's what love's supposed to be ♪
♪ So what about me? ♪
Ellian!
♪ What about the lonely days?
What about the sleepless nights? ♪
♪ What about the mess
The moods, the attitudes? ♪
♪ The constant fights? ♪
♪ What about the guilt
The stress, the helplessness? ♪
♪ The doubt, the shame, the fear? ♪
- Ellian!
- ♪ I played my part, I gave and gave ♪
♪ So good, so calm, so sweet, so brave ♪
♪ And now that your lives are all set
Look what you do ♪
♪ Think I'll forgive, smile, and forget?
Well, sorry, I'm through ♪
♪ You made your plans without me ♪
♪ You never cared about me ♪
♪ No! ♪
♪ It's always about you and you ♪
♪ Not about me ♪
Ellian!
♪ So what about me? ♪
Please talk to us.
♪ What about me? ♪
Whoa!
Ellian!
We love you.
Words! I don't believe you!
If you can fall out
of love with each other,
you can fall out of love with me!
She doesn't think we love her.
Oh no.
- Ellian!
- We got 'em!
- Move out! Move out!
Go! Go! Go!
Troops, don't let them escape!
Watch them!
Stand your ground.
- Back, beast!
- Hold them!
Keep your eye on them.
Take the beasts
where they will never be heard from again.
Where's the princess?
Bolinar, take the troops
and search the valley.
We'll double back and check the fields.
Ah!
Oh no.
Huh?
Flink, attack!
- Princess Ellian!
- Ellian!
Perhaps they found the princess.
- What's going on?
- We've been out-flinked!
Flink, old boy.
The king and queen need your help.
Charge!
He's letting the monsters go!
Stop him!
- Let's go!
- Come on!
Stop! Nazara, General, it's us.
Your queen and king.
- Your Majesties.
- Queen Ellsmere.
I'm so glad you're both back.
But we don't know where the princess is.
- Ellian is in that storm.
- We have to save her.
- We have to save our daughter.
- We're with you, sire.
Move out!
You knew they were in there all along?
Why didn't you tell me?
He was just at a loss for words, my dear.
- Ellian!
We can't go back
to the way it was before.
We can't go back to the way it was before.
Ellian!
We're losing our baby.
We have to do something.
The light.
Yes.
- Ellian.
- Are you hurt?
- We thought we lost you.
- Ellian, we're so sorry.
♪ Somehow we thought
This was just about us ♪
♪ Not about you ♪
♪ Got so distraught
We just thought about us ♪
♪ Not about you ♪
♪ We should have known ♪
♪ But instead ♪
♪ We did what we said we'd never do ♪
♪ We forgot about you ♪
You were right, Ellian.
We should've been better.
♪ We forgot to calm your fears ♪
♪ We forgot to feel your pain ♪
♪ We forgot to notice ♪
♪ You were under too much
Stress and strain ♪
♪ I don't know quite how
But we forgot ♪
♪ That you come first
No matter what ♪
♪ We forgot to say how much we love you ♪
♪ And that we always will ♪
♪ Till mountains fall and fade away ♪
♪ And all the stars turn cold and gray ♪
The best thing about us is you.
And it always has been.
We're so sorry
we made you feel like that wasn't true.
♪ I wish there was a way back
To the way it was before ♪
♪ But families don't all grow
In one straight line ♪
♪ And since we can't just stay back
Well, it's time to close that door ♪
♪ Don't be scared ♪
♪ We'll be fine ♪
♪ I know now we can't go back
And that things will have to change ♪
♪ We'll figure out
The three of us just how ♪
♪ We won't get that same glow back
And at first it might feel strange ♪
♪ But I love you ♪
♪ You love me ♪
♪ Evermore ♪
♪ Endlessly ♪
♪ Yes, that will be ♪
♪ The way it was ♪
♪ Before ♪
Mom!
Oh, my baby.
Dad!
Ellian, my love!
So things are really
different around here,
and, I'll admit, I had my doubts.
But, I gotta say,
my parents have worked hard,
and life has actually been pretty good.
Couple changes.
For starters,
my mom now lives in that house,
and my dad lives in that one.
And I don't clean my room
in either of them.
Well, they're always on my case about it,
which is actually kinda nice.
Oh no.
- Princess Ellian.
- Nazara!
I know I promised not
to use the flare today,
but the king and queen
are requesting an audience.
What?
Like, a big one.
Happy birthday!
Get on in there, sunshine.
- Got ya.
- Happy birthday!
- Just keeping it super caszh.
- Yeah. And obviously super small.
Give her the gift, Little Joe.
Whoa! Heel!
Princess, good tidings.
Archimedes! No!
Felicitations, Princess.
Flinky, my boy, I have something for you.
Oh, look at you, Flink.
- Greetings, Princess Ellian.
- Oracles!
We just have to say
we are so proud of you.
But if anybody else
in your life turns into a monster,
please don't
hesitate to call us.
- Coming through. Coming through.
- Happy birthday, sweetheart.
Mom! Dad!
We know you didn't get to fly
as much as you wanted to last year, and...
We just thought that this year,
you should fly in style.
This is the coolest saddle I've ever seen!
Guys, let's test this baby out.
- Ellian, be back by nine.
- Dad, it's my birthday.
Fine.
Ten.
I'll let you know when she gets home.
♪ This is my world ♪
- The fob!
- ♪ Sure, it's got quirks ♪
Oh no!
♪ But the new normal surprisingly works ♪
♪ As for my folks ♪
♪ Yes, they're apart ♪
♪ Still, we're a family
Entwined at the heart ♪
♪ No more stress
No more secrets ♪
♪ I can live like I should ♪
♪ Free to just be regular me
Now that my monsters are parents ♪
♪ Spreading my wings
Doing cool things ♪
♪ Happy my monsters are parents ♪
♪ Safe and secure
Ready to soar! ♪
♪ Knowing my monsters are parents ♪
♪ Incredible parents ♪
♪ And they'll be my parents ♪
♪ For good ♪
♪ Shattered walls ♪
♪ Empty hallways ♪
♪ Is that all we left behind? ♪
♪ I recall how we used to be ♪
♪ I see each moment in my mind ♪
♪ Endless talks ♪
♪ Celebrations ♪
♪ Aimless walks
With our hands entwined ♪
♪ Most of all ♪
♪ There was love to spare ♪
♪ And magic everywhere ♪
♪ We breathed it in like air ♪
♪ But no one's there now ♪
♪ I wish I knew the way back
To the way it was before ♪
♪ With you there
In your old familiar place ♪
♪ Reliving every day back
When my heart learned how to soar ♪
♪ Every smile ♪
♪ Each embrace ♪
♪ If I could find a way back
To the way it was before ♪
♪ And we could be together there
Right now ♪
♪ I'd run without delay back
To the way it was before ♪
♪ Run like mad ♪
♪ To what we had ♪
♪ If only I knew how ♪
♪ With you here ♪
♪ I was fearless ♪
♪ Year by year
I grew sure and strong ♪
♪ Now it's clear
What I really need ♪
♪ Is what you gave me all along ♪
♪ The lessons that you taught me ♪
♪ And all the plans we laid ♪
♪ The winters by the fire ♪
♪ And the summers in the shade ♪
♪ The stars we used to wish on ♪
♪ And the wishes that we made ♪
♪ Things like that must live on ♪
♪ Can't we go to where they've gone? ♪
♪ There's got to be a way back
To the way it was before ♪
♪ To stand with you again
On solid ground ♪
♪ We'll spend one perfect day back
In the way it was before ♪
♪ Just one day ♪
♪ Then one more ♪
♪ Maybe three ♪
♪ Why keep score? ♪
♪ Let's just stay ♪
♪ The way it was before ♪