Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
MCCLUSKEY HAWTHORNE CORPORATION
MINING VESSEL: 'BOREALIS'
CRYO SLEEP CYCLE
TIME REMAINING: 4 YEARS 2 MONTHS
Is he asleep? Where's Daddy? Is he asleep?
- Shall we wake him up?
- Yeah.
Wake up, Daddy!
- Let's wake him up.
- I see him!
- Wake up, Daddy.
Wake up!
Wake up, Daddy! Wake up.
- Shall we wake him up?
- Yeah.
Wait.
Don't go.
Warning. Catastrophic hull breach.
Personal survival system activated.
- What the hell?
- Please remain calm.
You are being fitted with a Mark IV
Lightweight Environmentally Optimized
Navigation and Reconnaissance Device...
- What are you doing?
- ...commonly known as a LEONARD.
Continue to remain calm
as your emergency launch suit is built.
No, wait, wait, wait.
What's happening?
Don't worry. I'll be with you
on your entire journey today.
Emergency launch initiated
in three, two, one.
What?
To avoid cranial injury,
please remain completely still.
No, no, no.
What? What the fuck? What? Come on.
Suit build complete.
If you need me, just say "LEONARD."
Can't breathe.
Understood. Stand by.
O2 regulator engaged.
Automated medical systems online.
We're currently moving
at 15,000 miles per hour.
Gravitational pull and trajectory
indicate that we are falling.
No shit.
Outside temperature
is 2,900 degrees Fahrenheit.
This is exceeding
the manufacturer's recommended...
Shut up!
What the hell?
Stabilization compromised.
Exceeding advised reentry speed.
Right rear stabilization thruster
depleted.
Terrain alert.
Please brace for impact.
Vitals erratic.
Please confirm consciousness.
- What?
- Confirmed.
I hate you.
Heart rate dangerously elevated.
Possible heart attack.
Preparing defibrillator.
No, no, no. Disengage.
- Three.
- No, no. Disengage!
- Two.
- Disengage!
Defibrillator deactivated.
Diminished neural activity
suggests possible stroke.
No, I'm not having a damn stroke.
I just fell from the sky,
and you're trying to kill me.
Administering suppository for nausea.
You put anything up my ass...
Deactivate personal assistant.
Sleep mode requested. Are you sure?
Never been more sure. Go away.
Have a great day.
Where the hell am I?
Open comms.
This is Andy Ramirez. Ident-number 0725-E.
Anyone out there?
Broadcasting on all frequencies.
It's Andy Ramirez. Ident-number 0725-E.
Anyone out there?
Warning. Underground fissure detected.
Terrain unstable.
Suggest you exit escape pod immediately.
Okay.
Okay. Don't panic. Come on, come on.
Don't panic, come on.
Seriously?
Thanks, guys.
Okay.
Think, Andy. Think.
Yeah, we're in a mix.
Yeah. Let's go.
That's better.
That's what I'm talking about, bro.
Warning. Suit breach detected.
Exterior atmosphere comprises
2% oxygen, 97% CO2,
1% nitrogen
and will not support human life.
- Shit!
- O2 levels dropping.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Fifty-nine.
- Come on.
- Fifty-one.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Forty-nine.
Forty- seven.
- Not gonna die.
- Forty-two.
Forty-two percent oxygen remaining.
You gotta be kidding.
I'm never trying to leave this pod again.
Ever.
Warning. Electrical fire detected.
Exit escape pod immediately.
Come on, come on.
Good news. I have located the Borealis.
- LEONARD.
- What can I help with?
Map up my flight path.
Where am I?
After departing Earth,
you traveled 2.48 trillion kilometers
before an unexpected collision
sent you to this unmapped system.
You have not reached
your target destination.
Records indicate you are the first human
to reach this unexplored planet
or asteroid.
You are legally entitled to name it.
Please enter now.
- No.
- Searching.
The name "No" is already in use.
- No. Not "No."
- Searching.
The name "No Not No"
is already in use.
Fuck off, LEONARD.
Searching. The name
"Fuck Off Leonard" is available.
Would you like to use it?
Yeah, sure. Why not?
Request confirmed.
Sending the name to the registry
of extrasolar bodies and planets.
Done. Congratulations on successfully
naming this extrasolar body or planet.
Deactivate personal assistant.
Have a great day.
You're the worst.
This is Andy Ramirez.
Ident-number 0725-E.
Is anyone out there?
This is Andy Ramirez.
Ident-number 0725-E.
Is anybody out there?
This is Andy Ramirez.
Ident-number 0725-E.
Broadcasting on all frequencies.
Is anybody out there?
Where the hell am I?
This is Andy Ramirez.
Broadcasting on all frequencies.
Any survivors out there?
Come on, people.
Somebody hit me.
Don't leave me hanging.
LEONARD.
- What can I help with?
- Scan for active trackers.
Scanning. One tracker located.
Hey, is anyone over there? You okay?
Hello?
Thank God.
No, don't do that. Don't puke. Don't...
LEONARD, plot a course
to that light source.
Plotted course
has a travel time of 48 minutes.
Oxygen level will be depleted by 2.5%.
There we go.
Hey. Hey!
Thank God. Thank God.
I thought I was alone out here. Look.
I need your help, man. I'm low on air.
Good to see another face.
At least one still attached to a body.
Name's Dwayne.
Andy.
So you saw that back there?
Yeah. Tends to happen
when you land face-first from orbit.
We should probably pack him up
for rations. Hand me that cable.
Rations?
You mean, like...
You mean like for eating him?
Closest burger joint
is about a trillion miles that way.
What kind of situation
you think we're in here, kid?
Right.
So, you have any idea where we are?
Before my pod launched,
I checked the nav history.
We were only three years and four months
into the cryo sleep cycle
when the company decides to take
a shortcut through an asteroid field
to save fuel. Boom.
Which means we ain't
where we're supposed to be.
What are all these things?
They're SOS lights.
Hold up. Wait, you a comms tech?
Nope.
I ran comms in the Corps.
Marine?
Semper fi, brother.
So, I stumbled upon
the right person, then.
You stumbled into the only person.
200 souls onboard,
and we're probably the only ones left.
Wait. So, when we set this all up, then...
Relay our position to Earth
so we can get a rescue party out here
before we get used to
drinking each other's urine.
Cool.
Cool. How long's that gonna take?
If I send a direct transmission,
it'll be, like, nine months.
But Dwayne...
found a killer shortcut.
Yeah.
I'm bouncing the signal
off the McCluskey Hawthorne INSs
to cut the time down...
to eight.
Okay. Okay, yeah, I could do eight months.
Well, they get the message
in eight months.
At which point, they'll send the RTS.
Fastest ship they got.
Sucker really flies.
Fast is good.
Barring any snafus, that'll put them here
in about a year and a half.
A year and a half?
Plus the eight months.
How is that fast?
Not too bad if you ask me.
That's terrible, Dwayne.
What are we gonna do here till then?
I don't know. Start drafting our
workman's comp claim? It's gonna be huge.
Yeah.
No!
We're gonna establish a base camp.
We're gonna survive.
We're gonna make this planet
our Shangri-la.
Okay.
Saw the front half of the Borealis
go down south of us.
Maybe some of the habitats are intact.
That's where we're going next.
Oh, God, no. That's horrible.
That's horrible.
That's never gonna work. We're gonna die.
Hey!
Dwayne doesn't die.
I spent two months
dissolving in an acid lake on Titan.
I've been sucked out
of an air lock in orbit, no suit.
I sewed my goddamn hand back on.
Twice.
Stay in line and you'll be fine.
- Hey!
- My bad. My bad.
Wanna stay here another six months?
- Come on. Plug it in.
- Look, I'm sorry, man.
Hey, I'm gonna have to tether into
your suit for some air, if that's cool.
Okay. There we go.
Dwayne?
Hey, come on, man. Stop messing with me.
Hey, this thing's working now.
Warning. Oxygen is now 36%.
Suggest you replenish your reserves
as soon as possible.
All right, man. I'm gonna send this thing.
It's working.
Oh, snap. Let's go.
I'm taking your gun.
Theft is a crime.
This violates the LEONARD terms of use.
Okay.
I am required to report this infraction,
which may result in loss of bonus,
jail time or dismissal from the company.
Are you sure you want to proceed?
Go ahead. Knock yourself out.
Seriously, Dwayne.
LEONARD.
What can I help with?
Just chart me a course to the Borealis
without talking.
There are 2,307 pieces of the Borealis
spread over a two-kilometer radius.
Well, just get me to the biggest one.
Recalculating.
Setting fastest route now.
Continue straight for five klicks.
Andy Ramirez coming at you live
from some busted-ass rock.
Anyone out there?
Come on. Don't leave me hanging.
This is Andy Ramirez.
Ident-number 0725-E.
LEONARD, what the hell, man?
This is the fastest route to the Borealis.
It's a damn cliff, bro.
I'm sorry.
I am part of a corporate-wide recall.
The update process
may cause me to short-circuit.
Please return me
to the McCluskey Hawthorne Corporation.
- Deactivate!
- Have a great day.
I'm gonna die out here.
I said, "Deactivate."
Is any... out there? Can anyone read me?
Anybody copy this?
- Hello?
- Hi. Anybody here?
What? I can't... Can you repeat?
Yes. Yeah, I can...
Damn it. Just keep talking, all right?
I'm gonna try to find a signal.
Just stay with me. Stay with me.
Can hear you. I br...
- Wait. Hold on. Can you hear me?
- No, I can...
- Can you hear me?
- No...
Keep talking. Just keep talking.
Okay, this is it.
- Can't hear...
- Stay with me. I gotta find a signal.
I'm gonna find a signal. Keep talking.
Please don't... Hello?
Just keep talking. Keep talking. Hello?
Naomi. It's Nao...
Okay.
My name is Naomi Calloway,
ident-number 0928-A. Do you copy?
- I copy.
- Thank God!
- My name's Andy.
- Ramirez, yeah.
Yeah, wait. How'd you know?
Because you broadcasted, like, 50 times.
Yeah, true. Yeah.
You couldn't hear me,
but I heard your voice and...
Look, everyone's trackers
are reading as dead.
I'm showing only three of us survived,
but the other guy that I've been
trying to get, he's not responding.
I met that guy. He's in his own world,
not gonna be much help.
Are you okay?
No, I'm stuck in my pod.
Leg's pinned. Can't really see it.
I think it could be broken.
- Damn.
- Yeah.
You have a comm request.
Wait. Hang on. I got some weird
friend request or something.
- Yeah, Andy, that's me.
- Oh, right.
If you accept,
you can plot a course to my location.
Okay.
LEONARD, plot a course
to ident-number 0928.
Calculating. Warning.
This destination may not be accessible.
Terrain: unstable. Visibility: low.
Estimated oxygen use: 30%.
Looks like you're 10.7 klicks out.
That's kinda far.
What do you mean, "That's kinda far"?
So here's the thing.
I'm low on air.
Yeah, I can see your vitals.
How have you already used up
two-thirds of your oxygen?
- I had a little mishap.
- A mishap?
Yeah, but it's cool though.
- I got 34% left, give or take.
- Oh, God.
Yeah, my definition of cool
is a lot different than yours.
Well, add it to the list of shit
that's gone wrong today.
Look, I hate to say this,
but I don't even know
if I can make it to you.
But you're gonna try, right?
I found an alternate route to the Borealis
at 8.4 klicks away.
Please proceed to this route instead
of hazard level red, Calloway, Naomi.
I don't know. My suit is saying
it's dangerous to get to you.
Hazard level red or something.
No, no. It's fine.
You can just override it.
I do not recommend this course of action.
No, no. That's just a liability thing.
They categorize anything unknown
as hazard level red
because they're afraid of getting sued,
which is ironic
because I'm definitely gonna sue.
User safety is my priority.
The chances of successfully reaching
hazard level red, Calloway, Naomi,
are dangerously low.
Andy?
Andy, I know
you're probably asking yourself,
"Why take the risk? It's just..."
I didn't say that, all right?
I'm thinking.
Thinking of the fastest way to get here?
Damn, girl, chill. Hold up.
Listen, I know you don't know me,
but you have got to trust me.
I have enough oxygen for the both of us,
and that'll buy us time to figure out
what to do next. Let's make a deal.
All right, fine.
Yeah? We have a deal?
We have a deal.
Thank you. I promise
I'll stay with you the entire time.
Feels like I came out
with the much harder part of the bargain.
I'd switch with you,
but I'm a little tied up at the moment.
Right, and I'm not crossing a planet
to find a girl I don't know.
Okay, well, what do you wanna know?
I'm an open book.
Everything. Where's that accent from?
We're going from the beginning. Okay.
Well, I was born in West London.
But actually my parents
are both South Asian.
And then I moved to East London,
which kinda sounds like the same thing,
but, actually,
they're very, very different.
My parents are actually
both dentists, so...
So, what division are you with?
Hydraulic engineering.
Was gonna spend a few years
flushing out drills
for a bunch of underpaid miners
and their overpaid asshole bosses.
You?
Drilling supervisor.
Yeah, so that makes me
one of the arsehole bosses, I believe.
No, that was before.
Before what?
Before I got to know you.
All right.
So, you were an engineer back home? Or...
Nah.
I taught music, PS 377 in Brooklyn.
I was gonna start my own school too.
Music for space, interesting career shift.
Hang on.
LEONARD.
What can I help with?
Scan the area.
I'm sorry. That feature is unavailable.
I am part of a corporate-wide recall.
The update...
- Deactivate.
- Have a nice evening.
Did you just say you have a LEONARD?
I thought they discontinued those things.
There were loads of lawsuits.
They kept on electrocuting people
and catching on fire and...
Yeah, well, I guess
it makes up for it in personality.
Yeah. Wait. Does it still have
that weird little jingle?
I wish I could say no, but yeah.
Yeah, that thing
always got stuck in my head.
How did it go? It was like...
I swear that is a song. What song is that?
- I know, right?
- Yeah.
Great. Now I'm stuck in a pod, and I have
that bloody jingle stuck in my head.
Just think about your mangled leg.
That'll get your mind off it.
It's not mangled. I hope.
I mean, that's just how I imagine it.
It's like a gross, half-eaten turkey leg.
Even if you imagine your supervisor's leg
as a half-eaten turkey leg,
you shouldn't tell them.
Yeah, with like a chancleta on,
like a flip-flop.
God, remember flip-flops?
Makes me think of home.
- Nice. You miss it?
- Not so much.
I wasn't so successful in relationships.
Got it.
Yeah, I mean, it's not as bad as it seems.
Actually, maybe it is.
I thought I knew what the rest
of my life would look like.
Went out for coffee one morning, came back
home and all his bags were packed.
Damn. Sorry.
Don't be.
I mean, all the signs were there.
Yeah, I should've known. I just...
I guess I couldn't stand being alone.
Which is ironic,
considering my current situation.
Anyways, I've done a lot of work
on my positive energy.
Well, there you go.
Yeah. I take all the things I'm feeling,
I bury them deep inside me
so that they never come out.
I don't know about that method.
That seems a little not healthy.
We're sort of like a self-selecting group,
you know what I mean?
You don't choose to go to sleep
for four years
and wake up
on the other side of the galaxy
if you have a healthy,
balanced Earth life, do you?
Are you okay? You just stopped.
What's going on?
Wait.
Andy?
- Andy, what's up?
- It was nothing. It's probably nothing.
Please proceed to destination.
Keep heading northwest 2 klicks.
So, if I didn't have any oxygen to share,
you wouldn't be helping me?
It's hard to say.
You got any snacks?
I'd save you for something salty.
Yeah, I'm neck-deep in Pringles.
Something tells me you're gonna
finish those by the time I get there.
Damn, girl. Chill. Hold Up.
What are you doing? What is that?
I'm imitating you.
No, that's not me.
That doesn't sound like me at all.
I told you, I'm from Brooklyn,
not New Jersey.
I think you sound like a mob guy
from the movies I used to watch.
You know, like,
where your best friend smiles
as he watches you dig your own grave
in the desert?
Is there anything else you wanna
share here before I risk my life?
Or should I just make my way
to the Borealis to meet with Dwayne?
Dwayne... Dwayne?
Oh, is that that crazy guy?
Yeah, I was helping him
send out a distress signal.
But then he split when I told him
I needed to borrow some air.
Borrow. Implies you're gonna give it back.
Maybe he just wasn't willing to share.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm better off on my own anyway.
I know I said that about myself,
but just to be clear,
you definitely aren't
better off on your own.
Please don't Dwayne me.
Yeah, all right.
You know, there's something
kind of relaxing
about watching your little blue dot
on my screen.
I'm glad you're relaxed
because what I'm doing right now is not
relaxing. It's dark as hell out here.
Are you afraid of the dark?
You know, it really doesn't bother me,
to be honest.
Yeah, I'm more afraid of depth.
Yeah, well, everyone's afraid of death.
No, no. Depth, like, depth.
You know, like, sea.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
I love to swim. I just...
I just hate the idea that I have no idea
what's underneath me.
My biggest fear is just being dropped
in the middle of the ocean,
my feet just dangling in the darkness,
and at any moment something
could just come up and eat you.
Just jump at you when you least expect it.
Hell no.
Nah, nope. No, I don't do webs.
What do you mean, "webs"?
I don't know, like some kind of alien
spider nest or something in a hole.
Well, did you check it out?
Hell no, yo. My wife kills the spiders.
- Wait. Should I be freaking out?
- No, don't freak out.
Forget it. It was probably nothing.
- Well, it doesn't sound like nothing.
- No, look. Nah.
I don't even know if I saw anything.
It's dark.
Could've been a shadow or something.
All right?
We good. Don't even trip.
Yeah, I'm definitely tripping.
In hindsight, my last mission was kinda
nice compared to this mess.
What about you?
You ever been to space before?
First time.
We've made a good first impression,
haven't we?
- Why'd you come up here anyway?
- What?
Why are you really here?
You waved goodbye to your entire life
to clean up mining waste
on another planet.
Don't tell me there's not a story there.
- I just like to switch it up sometimes.
- Switching up from what?
Are you running from something?
Wait. Did you do something really bad?
Why do you think I'm a criminal?
Because we just don't get a lot of happy,
well-adjusted applicants for this job.
Trust me.
Everybody's running from something.
- Dada!
- Are you sure?
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, so you don't want to talk about it.
So you said your wife kills the spiders?
You got any kids?
Yeah, a son.
How old is he, your son?
He's five.
Going on 25. I mean...
Stuff that comes out
of this kid's mouth is, like...
I don't know where he gets it from.
He's too damn smart, you know.
Smart guy.
Must have been hard to leave them.
They left me.
Sorry, I didn't...
Yeah, that sounds rough.
Yeah, I mean it's tough
when families split up, you know?
Someone always ends up getting hurt.
You must really miss him.
Every single day.
Warning. Current destination
of hazard level red, Calloway, Naomi,
may not be accessible.
Atmospheric pressure: falling.
Visibility: low.
Estimated oxygen use: 27%.
Temperature has dropped 42.2 degrees
Fahrenheit in the last five minutes.
- I do not recommend this course...
- Deactivate personal assistant.
Have a nice evening.
So, any advice for someone
stuck in a confined space
with claustrophobia setting in?
- Lights off.
- Lights off? No way.
Then I'd be claustrophobic
and in the dark.
This is weird.
Wait, Andy. Wait, what?
I'm picking up a bunch of trackers.
They're moving right towards you.
I'm trying to ping them now,
but they're not responding.
- For real?
- Yeah.
They're 100 meters ahead of you.
Can you not see them?
- I don't see anything.
- You sure?
- LEONARD.
- What can I help with?
- Link with approaching trackers.
- Okay, linking.
Something's not right.
Yeah, I agree this doesn't make any sense.
Their vitals are all reading as off-line
and...
Oh, my God.
Andy, I think they're all dead!
They're moving fast
right towards your location!
Thirty meters. Twenty-four...
Can you not...
Andy, they're right in front of you!
Andy, get out!
Mute comms.
Come on.
Come on! Don't look back!
Lights on.
Unmute comms.
Don't leave me out here.
Please don't leave me out here.
Oh, God. I almost...
Andy? Oh, my God. Where did you go?
You just stopped talking.
Look, if you're gonna bail on me,
I need to know because I can't...
I muted you. I was being chased.
- Why would you do that?
- I'm trying to explain.
Do you have any idea
how freaked out I was?
Just don't mute me again, okay?
- I almost died!
- What?
I almost died just now.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because you're not letting me talk.
And I don't wanna freak you out.
Wait. You're not making any sense.
That thing, it ate them.
The trackers were in its stomach.
What are you talking about? What ate them?
It was big, scary, crazy-ass teeth,
like, spider legs or something.
It was hunting me with a scorpion tail.
You're screaming.
I don't understand what...
I'm not screaming! I'm just reacting
like any normal human person would react
- if they saw what I just saw!
- Wait. Calm down. You're leaking...
No, you need to calm down!
You're acting mad crazy!
Andy, your suit, it's leaking air!
Warning. Suit breach detected.
O2 levels dropping.
Sixteen...
14.5...
13.
Andy? Hurry.
12.3.
Sealant depleted.
Okay, okay. You're stabilized.
Andy, talk to me.
I'm trying very hard
not to lose my shit right now!
I'm sorry, okay?
It's okay. I'm sorry too.
Just don't mute me, all right?
- I can help...
- Naomi, we're not alone here.
All right, just start walking.
We'll figure out how to deal with
those things when you get here.
Andy! I'm alive!
Oh, my God. Is that Dwayne?
- Come on! Help me!
- We read you. Hello?
- I can't fight these things forever.
- I don't see him.
Ramirez!
Okay, his locator is .05 kilometers
east of you. Go, go, go!
Hold up. No, I ain't going back
in that direction.
Andy, he's the only other survivor.
Nah. That thing is still out there.
I'm heading straight to you.
I'm crawling in your pod until
somebody comes to get us. Okay? I'm done.
Yeah, but that somebody
can only be Dwayne right now.
I shot one! It's very upset.
Andy, you've lost a ton of air.
I'm just being realistic.
This guy has 61% oxygen.
The drones are packing up rations
for the alpha. Big sucker!
Look, I can't even see my location!
My HUD's messed up!
It must've happened when I fell!
- I don't even know where I'm going!
- I'll guide you there.
I'll be with you every step of the way.
I'm with you.
- Andy, we have to find a weakness.
- No.
You desperately need oxygen.
Maybe he can help you.
Questionable.
We need all the help we can get, Andy.
All right?
We gotta stick together.
It could be our only chance for survival.
I'm a music teacher.
What am I doing? What am I doing here?
Listen to me, Andy. You got this.
Fine.
But for the record,
I am not happy about this at all.
I know.
Andy. Can you get your ass here?
This is some bullshit.
Dwayne! I'm coming!
Andy, hustle up.
These things are fucking hu...
What? I can't hear you, Dwayne!
Bastards. How about a mouthful of flare?
Come on...
Dwayne, listen, you're breaking up,
but Andy's almost there. Hang on.
I see him!
We can take them together.
Come on! I got a plan!
Come on, you ugly spider-looking...
Hang on! I'm almost there! I see you!
I know how to beat you.
Dwayne, come again? I'm here!
What's the plan?
Andy, I know how to beat the...
- Dwayne doesn't die!
- Lights off.
Andy, talk to me. What's happening?
Dwayne doesn't di...
Andy, are you all right? What's happening?
I'm in trouble. That thing's back.
You have to get out of there.
- Go!
- I can't!
Andy?
Andy, are you okay?
Andy, hang on.
I'm finding you another route.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God,
there's two of them.
Look. My map's showing you're surrounded
by wreckage right now.
- You're surrounded by bodies.
- Not helping.
No, no, no, it's okay. We can use this.
All right, let me try something. Hang on.
Okay, I almost got it.
I'm gonna create a distraction.
You just sit tight, all right?
You have a comm request.
You have a comm...
- Did it work?
- Kinda. But there's still one left.
- Okay, I found another body.
- They can hear us.
I'll ping it so you can get away,
all right?
- You have a comm request.
- Cancel it. Turn it off!
- Why?
- Because he's right next to me.
You have a comm request.
It's not accepting my commands.
Look, I've got an idea, all right?
Just get ready to run.
You have a comm request.
Incoming comms request.
- You have a comm request.
- Incoming comms request.
Okay, get ready to run in three, two, one.
Go, Andy! Andy, go, go, go!
Get out of there!
I hate this place!
Andy, what's happening? Hello?
Oh, my God.
They're not attacking.
What do you mean?
I don't know. They just stopped.
I don't know.
Okay. That's good. That's good, right?
Those things, they were communicating.
They hunt in packs, eating people
with their second mouth thing.
What? God.
Those things, they ripped through
the pods like tuna cans.
Andy, I'm in a pod.
Why would you say that?
- You gotta get out of there. Now!
- What? You know I can't. My leg...
I know your leg's wedged in,
but you gotta find a way. You're not safe.
Andy, I can't, okay?
God, I didn't wanna tell you this,
but I can't even feel my leg anymore.
- Isn't that better than it hurting?
- No, it's not better!
It means the tissue is dying,
which happens when a limb gets crushed.
First the tissue dies,
and then it spreads. And then you die.
Oh, God, I'm having a panic attack.
Okay. First up, how do you
even know all of that?
I'm a supervisor.
We had to go through
weeks of crisis training
and role-playing disaster responses.
Okay.
When that happened, what'd you do?
I don't know. You talk to them.
Try to keep them calm.
That's all you can really do.
Because you know they're gonna
die anyway, just like I am.
Oh, my God, I'm gonna die
in this little pod by myself.
I'm not gonna make it out.
There's no monsters in the cupboard
Or under the bed
What are you doing?
I sing to Caleb sometimes
to calm him down.
There's no monsters in the cupboard
Or under the bed
Daddy took a shovel and smashed their head
If there's monsters in the bathroom
Or behind the door
Daddy will slash off their limbs
And spill their guts on the floor
And if one monster still survives
We'll blow his guts out together
Just you and I
Naomi?
- Naomi, you okay?
- Lot of death and guts for a lullaby.
Yeah, well, Caleb, he likes it straight,
you know? So I just...
- I just tell it like it is.
- Yeah. I like that.
Hey, was that to keep me calm or you?
I guess...
- I guess a little bit of both.
- Right.
Hey, I'm looking on my screen.
It's just you and me now.
We're the only ones left.
Okay.
Okay, listen. You have 8% oxygen left.
I think maybe you should
go to the Borealis instead.
No, we had a deal, right?
I'll understand if you break it.
Too late. You ain't getting rid of me.
I was hoping you'd say that.
I wish you could see this.
It's actually kind of beautiful.
Wow. That is the first positive thing
you've said about this place.
There are these little
glowing firefly things around me.
All right. Is that good or bad?
I don't know.
Hey there, little buddy.
I think I'm catching the vibe of one.
Stop that! Get away from me!
Get away from me, you...
Okay, I'll take that as a bad.
Wait. Unless you're hallucinating.
Your O2's at 6%, but hallucination
shouldn't kick in till you're around 2.
I'm not making this up.
No, this shit's real. Trust.
Maybe that's why those scorpion things
didn't follow you in there.
The good news is
you're just one klick away.
So just avoid everything and hurry, okay?
Yeah.
Hold on.
Something's up.
What?
Something's definitely here.
I don't see anything,
but maybe they're back?
No.
No, it's something else.
Andy?
I'm being pulled into a mouth.
What do you mean? Are you okay?
No, I told you, I'm being pulled
into a mouth! I'm the opposite of okay!
Okay. Don't panic, okay?
What are you doing?
- Panicking.
- Oh, God.
I wish you found someone else.
- I'm not gonna make it.
- What are you talking about? No.
We're gonna figure this out, okay?
We'll figure it out together.
I'm sorry. You gotta find a way out.
No, no, no. Andy, stay with me.
Okay, something scary under the...
God, I can't remember the lyrics!
- Tell me about your son.
- Caleb.
Yeah. What's he into?
Comets. The stars. That's what he likes.
He can name all the planets.
That's why I'm here.
Okay. Listen to my voice, okay?
No matter what happens,
you keep listening, you don't stop.
Stay alive, understand?
Caleb needs you. I need you.
Oh, God, your vitals are crashing.
Can LEONARD do anything? Andy...
- LEONARD, you have to help me.
- What can I help with?
- I'm having a heart attack.
- Preparing defibrillator.
For your safety, please stand five feet
clear of Ramirez, Andy.
Three, two, one.
Defibrillation successful.
Recommend one week under medical review
for post-resuscitation care.
- Do you have time for a quick survey?
- Hell no, we ain't doing that again.
On a scale from one to ten,
how would you rate my performance?
One being the lowest,
ten being the highest.
Help!
"Help" is not an integer
between one and ten.
Possible answers are: one, two, three...
- Oh, no. Shit. Not again! No.
- ...four...
- No, I'm not doing that again.
- ...five,
- six, seven, eight...
- Get off! Get off me, man!
Shit.
I'll just mark you down for ten.
- ...you still need...
- Naomi!
Oh, my God, you're alive.
Oh, God, I thought I'd lost you.
Naomi, you saved my ass. You saved my ass.
It was like...
It was like I was gone.
And then I heard your voice.
You brought me back.
As much as I love what's happening here,
you're breathing fumes.
You need to move.
Based on your oxygen consumption,
you have a higher chance of reaching
the Borealis, destination 0.3 klicks,
but a much lower chance of reaching
hazard level red, Calloway, Naomi,
destination 0.8 klicks.
I don't care. Stay on course.
You don't have enough oxygen
to make it to me. Go to the Borealis.
Nah. I've come this far.
I'm not changing course now.
Got you.
Andy, you've got less than 1% left. Hurry.
I can see you. Hang on.
Hey.
Hi.
I should probably
get you out of here, right?
Okay.
No, no, no! No.
Sorry.
- I just gotta undo the one thing...
- O2 is almost out.
No. Oh, God. Sorry. Turn around.
Yeah.
- What do you need?
- Bum up? Okay. Nearly there.
- Yes!
- Okay. You're in.
- I can breathe.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Okay. You're welcome.
- Your turn. Let's get that leg.
- Thank you.
Leg press. Great.
- Do you want me to help you or not?
- Sorry.
- Carry on.
- Okay.
It's not gonna work.
Yeah, I gotta find something
to help me wedge it out.
Okay. All right.
Damn, you're stocked up.
Yeah. Try that.
- You ready?
- Yeah. Here we go.
- You okay?
- Yeah. I can feel it moving.
Let's go.
- We got it out. Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How's it feel?
It hurts. But I don't think it's broken.
Good.
- Hey, thanks for that.
- Oh, yeah.
It's weird, this glass thing.
Kinda like we're in prison, you know?
Yeah.
No, I don't.
Well, because of the glass between us.
You know, like...
- Oh, right.
- Yeah.
I got you. So it's like
I'm coming to visit you, right?
Right.
And tell you I'm gonna
wait for you on the outside.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I'd ask if you found
my buried money in the desert.
And tell you to stop
sleeping with my cousin Cleto.
First off, I would never
sleep with your cousin Cleto. Ever.
Second, I spent all the money
on shoes and shit, so...
Sorry.
- We should get moving, huh?
- Yeah.
Yeah, okay. Okay.
Here. You're gonna need that.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Okay. Yep. And I'm definitely
gonna need this.
All right. Here we go.
- All right. Grab my hand.
- Yeah.
Wow.
Okay.
- All right. You ready?
- Yep.
Come on. There we go.
All right.
I got you. You okay?
- Yeah. My leg.
- All right. All right, hold on.
It's definitely not broken.
It's just a sprain.
- Oh, God.
- All right. Okay.
- Shit.
- All right, I got you. Hold on.
Let me try something.
- How's that?
- Hey.
That actually feels oddly better.
I'm impressed. Where'd you learn that?
Caleb, he fell off a trampoline
when he was four.
Well, it works.
It says O2's at 59%,
so that's about 30 each.
Yeah.
- Whoa. Hold on.
- AMIE, administer morphine.
Wait, hold up.
Your suit's got pain reliever?
Administering five milligrams.
Yeah. I've been shooting myself up
ever since we crashed.
That's better.
So then you'll have AMIE
charter a path to the Borealis and...
Yeah, and hope the habitats
or life support systems have survived
or just find something we can salvage.
Is that a splitter?
- The grappling gun. Where'd you get it?
- It was Dwayne's.
I found it with all his stuff,
but it doesn't work.
I tried, so I just thought maybe
I could use it as a club or something.
Can I see it?
Here.
Be careful.
Look at that.
I'm forever fixing these things.
They're always jamming on us.
It's so annoying.
It's because they give us this cheap crap.
I mean...
Hey, Andy.
Thank you for saving me.
I didn't save you. I needed oxygen.
I saved myself.
Oh, God. What the hell are those things?
That's what's been chasing you?
Yes.
Run!
Hurry up!
Hurry!
AMIE, another shot of morphine, please.
Administering five milligrams.
- Is it working?
- Yeah. Much better.
- Good.
- Can't feel a thing.
We made it!
We made it.
We're not there yet. Go!
- Sorry.
- Go!
Keep going!
I'm tethered to you.
If I stopped, you'd notice.
- Did you see that?
- Holy shit! Oh, shit.
Go, go, go!
Why didn't you tell me
those things were this scary?
- I tried!
- You should've tried harder.
Come on!
Hurry. Go, go, go!
Go. Go!
Wait. Hold... Stop.
Okay.
- Dude, take your time!
- I'm sorry. Do you wanna do this?
Get off!
- Yo, any day now!
- Okay!
Got it!
Oh, my God.
What the fuck?
Yes! That's what I'm talking about!
That's how you kill a monster!
Let's go!
You finished?
Yeah.
Come on. Let's get outta here.
That should hold them off for a while.
Yeah. Assuming that's the only way in.
Ship's in rough shape.
Yeah. It wasn't exactly five stars
to begin with.
There's no way to the cargo hold.
Main deck collapsed right into operations.
Shall we go right?
I don't know.
I only been on this ship twice,
and one of those times I was sleeping.
How's your leg?
Brilliant.
Yeah, especially after that sprint.
At least the emergency lights
are still working.
The backup generators must've kicked in.
This place is banged up.
You're not gonna believe this.
That must be ten years' worth
of snacks up in there.
What? No.
The entire cargo hold
has a stabilized atmosphere.
Right.
- So that means...
- Yeah. It's livable.
Okay. So we gotta figure out
how to get in there.
Yep.
I don't wanna see where that goes.
What is that?
Something bad.
Lights off.
I'm gonna be sick.
Swallow it.
- It's gone. Go, it's gone.
- Okay.
It's gone. Go.
- We gotta get the hell outta here.
- How do we know there's not more?
I don't care. Let's just keep moving.
That's a new one.
- Go, go, go!
- Come on!
No, don't do that.
Door closing. Stand clear.
- No.
- What?
- You just locked us in here.
- How do you get out?
With the panel on the other side
of the door you just closed.
- There's gotta be another way out!
- It's an air lock. Key word, lock.
Stop.
Andy, just stop.
Andy, there's no way out.
It's over.
LEONARD, play memory bank.
February 15th.
Is he asleep? Where's Daddy? Is he asleep?
- Shall we wake him up?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Wake up, Daddy!
It was my birthday.
- We were on our way home...
- Say, "Happy birthday."
...and a truck ran a red light.
It should've been me.
Andy, I'm so sorry.
I can't even begin to understand. But...
it was an accident.
There's nothing you could've done.
No, it was more than that.
I lost more than that.
Man, I just kept on living. I just...
What kinda person does that?
What kinda person just keeps on going?
After they lost everything.
Huh?
I tried to run away,
but I brought it with me.
- Listen to me, stop. Stop!
- I can't...
Your family are not dead because of you.
But me...
You're the only reason I'm still alive.
I took this mission
because someone made me feel
like I couldn't trust anyone.
And so I ran away.
I began to think
maybe that's just how everyone is.
But what you did today,
you showed me that there are still
people you can believe in.
There are still people
who answer your call.
So no matter what happens,
I hope you know that.
Okay.
There's like a bulge of light
on your back.
What do you mean, "a bulge of light"?
I don't know.
It's a gross, glowy thing
full of bugs or something.
Fireflies. Grab it.
Warning.
Atmospheric depressurization detected.
- Grab the sack!
- I'm not grabbing that sack!
- Do it!
- Okay!
Throw it!
Evacuate the area.
Closing all air locks. Stand clear.
Oxygen levels dropping.
Warning.
Atmospheric depressurization detected.
- Hurry up! Andy, hurry.
- Go, go!
- Door closing. Stand clear.
- Just leave it.
Look out!
We gotta kill this thing.
Maybe we can use the mining drill.
No!
Naomi! Hang on. I'm coming for you.
No. You gotta figure out
how to kill this thing.
I got it. We'll crush it with a pod.
Buy me some time!
What? What are you talking about?
Stall that thing,
and bring it back when I tell you.
That's your plan?
It's part of one. I'm working on the rest.
- LEONARD.
- What can I help with?
- Find me a pod that will still launch.
- There is one two levels up,
but willful destruction
of company property is a crime.
Andy! Cut the lights!
What?
Remember, these things
are attracted to light!
Cut them quick!
Assuming I even make it.
Andy!
All right, come on. You got this.
Naomi, what's your management override?
It's "boss"!
Now's not the time to flex.
What's the code?
That's the code, "boss."
Two-six-seven-seven.
Naomi, hang on. Hang on.
LEONARD, you gotta
help me launch this pod.
I'm sorry, Andy. Function denied.
Power has been cut off.
Damn. Well, let's turn it back on.
Unfortunately,
power takes 15 minutes to cycle.
We don't have 15 minutes.
I gotta launch this thing now!
Then I'm afraid launching from inside
the pod may be your only option.
Okay.
Due to faulty hardware,
I am part of a corporate-wide recall.
Not now, LEONARD.
Just walk me through this.
Plugging me in will short my circuitry
and launch the pod.
Wait. What?
LEONARD will help to save Calloway, Naomi.
Okay.
I'm bringing this thing to you,
and it's really pissed off!
Andy, where are you?
There is no crash safety system
in operation on this pod.
I know.
Chances of survival on impact
are highly unlikely.
I know.
Preparing update.
I've really enjoyed
our time together, Andy.
Me too, LEONARD.
I'll count you down.
Thanks, buddy.
Ten, nine, eight...
seven, six...
five, four...
three, two, one.
Have a great day.
Andy.
Wake up.
Andy, please, wake up.
Wake up. Andy.
Please. Please, wake up.
Please, wake up. Wake up.
Wake up.
Wake up, please.
Please, Andy.
Please, don't leave me here alone.
I need you. I need you.
- Andy?
- Naomi?
Oh, my God.
Thank God.
Did we...
- Did we...
- Yeah.
Hey.
Congratulations.
What?
You just killed your first spider.
Okay. Let's get you up.
What's that?
Okay. Let's go.
Never when you need it, right?
How does a shower and a bed sound?
- Amazing!
- Yeah.
Wow.
You know, if you remove
the whole life-threatening part,
it's actually really beautiful.
Yeah.
And Dwayne said it'd be over a year
until a rescue team gets here.
I mean, that's assuming
the message even made it.
So, this might sound a little fast, but...
how would you feel
about moving in together?
For say, I don't know, 18 months?
Yeah, I'd be down for that.
Good.
Reboot successful.
LEONARD, you're back.
Welcome to the LEONARD Mark V.
It is Thursday, six minutes
after the second sunrise
- on this circumbinary planet or asteroid.
- LEONARD. Deactivate.
Have a great day, Andy.
Wait. That was the song.
Oh, my God. What is it?
- Wait. What...
- I just had it. It was...
- What song is that?
- That's gonna drive me crazy now.
- It's an old joint, isn't it?
- Yep, definitely old.
Like my grandmother used to play,
like that kinda old.
But they ripped it from somewhere,
didn't they?
Man, it was on the tip of my tongue.
Oh, well.
- Guess we'll have time to figure it out.
- Yeah.
I guess we do.