[nostalgic music playing]
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot.
Oh![both laugh]
[narrator] I remember
my mom always asked me
to tell her a story.
And I never knew why.
Maybe it was just
something to make her smile.
[laughing]
[narrator] To take
her away from it all.
[Dad] Here she comes! Aah!
Salute.
[narrator] It wasn'Őt until
much later that I realized
that these stories
she wanted me to tell
had nothing to
do with her at all.
When I realized that the most
important stories we have to tell...
are the ones we tell ourselves.
[blows]
Whoo!
Are you ready?
Whoa![Mom laughs]
[speaking indistinctly]
Shh.
Boo! Oh, my God!
That is so scary!
[Dad, child talking gibberish]
[imitating creature] Hey, Bear,
I'Őm having a conversation here.
Abracadabra!
Whoa! Bea, that'Ős amazing!
Bye, Grandma.Bye. Love you.
[door opens]
[Grandmother] I don'Őt know if
you saw him, honey. Come in.
He sometimes
helps me park the car.
We were lucky to get a park,
because often by
the late afternoon...
Whew!
There aren'Őt any. [chuckles]
And then I'Őve got to go round
and round the block... [pants]
and I'Őm very lucky if
I ever get one. Whew!
[grunts, pants]
Oh, my goodness.
[chuckles] Those stairs!
I mean... Oh. Right.
Well... here we are.
Well, come on in.
Yeah, come on in.
I mean, nothing much
has changed, I don'Őt think.
Except, um...
was that couch
here the last time?
I don'Őt think it was.
There we are.
Well, I don'Őt know
why I'Őm asking you that,
because you were just this high.
Right. Well, I did a bit
of a shop, because, um...
Well, are you... are you...
are you hungry at all?
I mean, if you...
Well, right. Well, you
just tell me if you do...
if you are hungry, because
the kitchen is through here.
[Grandmother
speaking indistinctly]
Right. Well...
[clicks tongue] And here...
we have some fresh sheets
and, of course, some, uh,
fresh towels there on the chair.
And over here,
you might remember
something a little bit special.
I kept every painting you
did that summer in here.
I mean, I-I could barely keep
up with everything that went on
in that little head of yours.
Oh, Grandma?
I'Őm twelve.
I don'Őt really do that anymore.
Of course.
I'Őm... I am just going to
put all of this
in here.
Right.
Done. Done.
Right, we better get going,
'Őcause your dad'Őll
be expecting you.
And, uh, you probably
want to eat with him.
You could have something here if
you like. Can I get you something?
Where are my keys?
I left them somewhere.
Oh, keys, keys, keys.
I'Őll be in in a minute.
[elevator dings]
[chattering]
[door opens]
[nurse] How are you
feeling?[Dad] Feel good.
I'Őll let the doctor know you'Őre here,
and he'Őll go over everything with you.
Yeah, let him know I'Őm
here. We'Őll go from there.
Whoa! How'Őd you
even get in here?
Sorry about her. [chuckles]
I'Őm in no state to
dance, that'Ős for sure.
But if we were to dance,
we'Őre gonna do it for real, okay?
You want to?
All right, she wants to go.
Let'Ős go. We'Őre gonna do it.
Two, three, four, five, six.
Yes, and you'Őve got it.
Go. Yes. Yes. This
is it.[nurse chuckles]
Oh, what?
Big finish, big
finish! Come on, girl!
We'Őve never rehearsed it.
Thank you, judges. Be
kind.[nurse chuckles] Yes!
It'Ős the applause that
keeps me young.Aw.
Bea, this is Janet. Janet,
this is my daughter, Bea.
[Janet] It'Ős lovely
to meet you, Bea.
Your father'Ős told me
so much about you.
Nice to meet you, too.
What are they
giving you? Oh, this?
[blows] Magic.
[chuckles] All right,
I'Őll let you two catch up.
Anything I could
get for you, Bea?
[Dad] Do you want
anything? I'Őm good, thanks.
Just a burger for me.
Extra cheese, bacon.
Cholesterol, really.
Dad. Yeah?
Okay. She'Ős right. Broccoli.
Just all broccoli.
Great. And a water maybe.
Sorry, she'Ős usually more fun.
[Janet chuckling]
So, how was the ride down?
I'Őm really sorry I couldn'Őt
be there to pick you up.
It was Harriet'Ős only
time she could rehearse,
and she'Ős a bit of a diva.Dad.
You really don'Őt
have to do this.
Do what?
Treat me like a kid.
Ah.
Sometimes life doesn'Őt
always have to be fun,
you know?
Well, that'Ős true.
Very true.
It doesn'Őt stop us
from trying though.
[chuckles]
But you know what?
You'Őre right. [sighs]
Sometimes life isn'Őt fun.
Like coming back here.
Reminds us of Mom all
over again, doesn'Őt it?
And maybe
even makes you worry
that that could happen again.
But the good news is...
I'Őm not Mom.
I'Őm not sick.
I'Őm just...
broken.
[chuckling]
And I can be fixed.
Look at me.
It'Ős a very simple surgery.
And I'Őm gonna be fine.
I promise.
Okay.
But you got to
promise me something.
That you will not
hang around here.
That you will get out there
and have some fun.
I mean, you got to admit,
one day it'Ős gonna
make a hell of a story.
What?
Living in New York?
[chuckles]
Being a kid.
[Veta, through TV] You and
I may take a little ride later.
[Elwood, through
TV] Oh, I'Őd like that.
It'Ős certainly been a long time
since we'Őve been for a drive.
You'Őre very sweet
and thoughtful, Veta.
[Veta] Don'Őt forget to wait for
me, Elwood. I'Őll be right back.
[Elwood] All right, well, make
yourself comfortable, Harvey.
[loud thump]
[Elwood] There. All right?
Veta wants to talk to us.
[TV continues, indistinct]
[door creaks]
[hatch shuts]
[radio host] ...skateboarded
across Canada in 11 months,
raising over $14 million
to fight heart disease.
He covered over 5,000 miles...
Hello?
What? What? Can you...
Oh, God.
[butterfly] Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
[footsteps running]
[butterfly] Not good.
Not good. Not good.
Oh, and she'Ős
following, she'Ős following.
Hey!
[butterfly] Oh, God, no.
No, no, no. No. Stay, stay!
[Bea] Wait![butterfly
panting] Oh, God.
So many stairs.
So... many... stairs.
[door opens, closes]
[butterfly] I think
she followed me.
[man upstairs] What do
you mean she followed you?
When?[butterfly] Just now.
[man upstairs] What
do you mean, "now"?
Right now. Now now.
Because I think she...
I think she saw me.[man
upstairs] What do you mean?
[butterfly] Right
in the eyes. Boom!
And then run, run, run.
And then stairs, stairs, stairs.
But then she'Ős there,
and she'Ős coming.
And she'Ős bigger,
and she'Ős faster.
And I think she... [man
upstairs] Shh, shh, shh.
[gasps]
Hello?
[man upstairs] Please go away.
I, um...
I was just trying to say
hello to your little girl.
[man upstairs] No little girl
here. Please go away, please!
Okay.
I just moved in downstairs...
and I don'Őt really
have anybody to talk to.
[door opens]
Who...
Who is that? I'Őm
sorry, I was just...
[neighbor] Oh, it'Ős you.
You'Őd better get
back downstairs.
It'Ős too late to be up here!
Yes, ma'Őam.
[Elwood, through TV] Harvey!
Harvey?
[patient] Hi!
Hi.
Those for me?
Uh, no, actually.
They'Őre for my dad.
Just kidding.
Oh! Want to play chess?
TV'Ős busted.
I'Őm sorry?
It'Ős okay. It'Ős
not your fault.
That'Ős why my mom got me chess.
Checkers.
What happened?
I fell.
I fall a lot.
This time I broke
my leg and my...
coxxyx?
Cozzyx? No, uh, my cowzyx?
Cozmokyx?
You know, I just broke my butt.
[chuckles]
And your arm, too?
What'Őd you fall from?
Oh, separate incidentses.
Got it.
I'Őm Benjamin, by the way.
I'Őm Bea. Cool!
What does B stand for?
Oh, nothing. My mom
just used to call me Bea.
I like it. Just B.
Well, it was really
nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
You know where to find me!
Oh, hello.
You have to stop.
Never.
[Bea singing along to "Better
Be Good to Me" over camcorder]
[singing continues]
[loud thump]
[butterfly] Oh, God.
So many stairs!
[footsteps running]
[butterfly] We'Őve got to go.
We'Őve got to go right now.
[man upstairs] I'Őm not going
anywhere. I just poured some...
[butterfly
whispering] It'Ős him.
[man upstairs] Oh,
God.[door closes]
[man upstairs] Honestly, this
is the last time I'Őm doing this.
Never again.
[butterfly] I'Őm sorry,
how is it my fault?
You leave the photos
out, he'Ős gonna find them.
[man upstairs] I didn'Őt...
I said it wasn'Őt your fault.
[butterfly] I'Őm not even
gonna listen to this.
[man upstairs] I'Őm sorry...
[butterfly] I would never have let him...
No, because, number one, he'Ős
too big. He'Ős just generally too big.
And secondly, everything else!
[man upstairs] He'Ős gigantic.
How did he get up there?
[butterfly] Beautiful house.
Oh! Imagine. One
day. Second floor.
[chattering]
Okay, you go around
there... All right.
Just go! You'Őre so rude.
[man upstairs straining]
[grunts]
[straining continues]
[thuds]
[panting]
[gasps]
[whispering] Blue!
Blue?
This is it.
I swear to God,
if you don'Őt answer
me right now,
disappearing will be the
least of... [toys squeaking]
Hi.
Well, lookee, lookee.
[chuckles] Okay, okay.
I know how it looks.
But the truth is,
she loves me!
We are doing great!
Really? I heard
she cried for an hour.
Oh, come on.
An hour seems like a little
bit of an embellishment.
Do you know how hard
it is to cry for an hour?
Grab your stuff. We'Őre leaving.
No, no, no!
You can'Őt take me
away. This is the one.
She is the perfect
fit. I promise.
Did you talk to her?
Well, no. It was hard
to with all the crying.
Exactly. That'Ős
not a good thing.
Did she even see
you? She was about to.
She was about to? Absolutely!
I can almost guarantee it.
I think.
What happened?
Well, she was putting
that creepy doll to sleep.
[shudders]
She stopped. She looked up.
She definitely felt something.
So I slowly walked over to her.
And as I got close, I...
[stifles sneeze]
Wait.I...
What are you
doing?[stifles sneeze]
No, no, no. No, don'Őt do this.
Hey. Don'Őt do this, okay?
[wheezing]Blue. Hey, hey.
[gulps]I swear to God, I
will never speak to you again
as long as I live if
you do this. Please.
[sniffs, gasps]Do not do that.
Please. No. No. No. No!
No, no. No. No. No. No. No!
[sneezes][man upstairs grunts]
[gasps]
[mechanical toys chittering]
[toy voice 1] Let'Ős play
again![toy voice 2] Great. Yeah!
[window squeaks]
Hi.
[body thuds]Oh, God.
["'ŐDeed I Do" playing
on phonograph]
Ooh, I wouldn'Őt do that.[gasps]
[man upstairs] What was that?
Just changing the record!
[scoffs] He just gets so cranky
when people touch his stuff.
[man upstairs]
Don'Őt touch anything!
[chuckles] See?
Who are you?
[chuckles] What do you
mean? I'Őm... I'Őm Blue!
But you'Őre purple.
Oh! Yeah, well, he
was color-blind, so...
Who was?
Well, my kid! Remember?
What?
[butterfly] Oh, for
God'Ős sake, Blue!
Of course she doesn'Őt remember.
She thinks you'Őre
gonna eat her.
[sighs] Apologies about him.
He'Ős the most
adorable train wreck,
but a train wreck nonetheless.
Thank you!
You'Őre welcome.
Now would you mind picking
our guest up off the floor, please?
That'Ős it. Big finger.
Lovely. Well done, Blue.
Now, let'Ős start over, shall
we? How do you like your tea?
I don'Őt drink tea.
[man upstairs] What kind
of girl doesn'Őt drink tea?
Not helping! [chuckles]
I'Őm Blossom, and
you'Őve clearly met Blue.
Me again.
And that is... She
knows who I am.
We'Őve, uh...
We'Őve met before.
Been a while since you...
since you been up here.
Yeah, last time I saw
you, you were, uh...
smaller.
What is going on?
Yeah, well, that'Ős a perfectly
understandable question,
given, um...
and, uh... Hey!
"Hey"? Yeah, hey.
What, we'Őre gonna
explain it all right here,
in a neat little pink package?
[Blossom] We'Őre
supposed to try.
Excuse me.
Will you stop poking her?
Sorry. Sorry. This
is just so exciting!
What is? That you'Őre back!
Blue! That'Ős enough. I mean...
What is that?
What part of "don'Őt touch my
stuff" do you not understand?
Come on! This was
all in alphabetical order!
Did you say your...
[man upstairs] And
color coordinated.
Kid? Oh, yeah.
His name is Jeremy.
God! Get to hear
more about Jeremy!
So that house
we were at tonight,
that was Jeremy'Ős?
Oh, no. That was different.
That was a potential match.
And one that could'Őve
been successful,
if it wasn'Őt for you know who.
All right, you know
what? Do it yourself.
Okay? I don'Őt need this.
I don'Őt need any of this.
Whew! [chuckles] Okay.
This has been
quite a day for him.
But you...
I'Őm sure you have questions.
So, are there more of you?
[man upstairs] Say no!
Yes. Oh, yeah! Lots more!
[chuckles] I mean, almost
every kid has one. Had one.
Had what?
A friend.
An imaginary friend?
IF. We say "IF."
[chuckles] Get it?
Imaginary. Friend.
But also like what IF?
Like, anything'Ős possible!
Ooh! Ouch! Okay, let'Ős... let'Ős
not get ahead of ourselves here.
Her eyes look like they
might melt out of her head.
So...
what was happening tonight?
Oh, that was a placement
attempt with a new kid.
We'Őve started a
fledgling little operation.
[man upstairs] Ugh! "We"?
He.What kind of operation?
Sort of a matchmaking agency.
To help IFs find new kids.
New kids?
But what happened to your kid?
Oh. He grew up.
He doesn'Őt need me
anymore.[Bea] He doesn'Őt?
That'Ős so sad.
Eh, more like
terrifying. [laughs]
Woo. [chuckles]Oh, no.
Because if he
doesn'Őt need me...
Blue... he can'Őt see me.
Blue, over here.
And if he can'Őt see
me... Look at me.
Then all that'Ős left is
to disappear!
[Blossom] Blue.[crying]
Happy place! Happy place!
[sobbing] Coffee and croissants.
Coffee and croissants.
Good, good.[Blue]
Coffee and
croissants.[Blossom] Okay.
Coffee and croissants.
This has all been a lot.
Yes! Yes, it is...
a lot.
For everyone. I think
we should call it a night.
I think she'Ős doing
quite well actually.
Thank you.[Blossom]
You'Őre welcome.
Well, I think it'Ős all too
much. Not to mention too late.
And I don'Őt think any of us
want to be on the
wrong side of that door
when that creepy
witch comes out.
You should go.
Aw, come on, Cal,
she'Ős just a kid.
I'Őm not a kid.
Well, that'Ős that.
Good night.
[gasps]
Oh! Oh, gosh, you gave
me a fright. [chuckles]
Good morning. Good morning.
Ah, you'Őre off.
I made pancakes.
Oh, God. They seem
to be stuck to the pan.
Um, I have some
cereal or some grapefruit.
I'Őm not that hungry.
Well, you'Őll let me know
if you need anything.
I will.Good.
Oh, God.
[sighs]
[chattering]
Is there any food?
Of course.
What do you feel
like? Real food?
Or junk food? Yeah.
There'Ős a vending machine
down the hall and to the right.
Oh!
[bell dings]
[elevator door opens]
[muffled sneeze]
Oh! Fancy seeing you here.
[whispering] What are
you doing? Get out of there!
I would love to, but I
cannot feel my legs.
Oh, my God.
Okay, give me your
hand.[Blue giggles]
Give me your hand. Your
hand. Give me your hand.
Come on. Okay, come on.
[grunts] Come
on.[laughs] No, don'Őt.
Come on, stand up. Okay,
wait, wait. Ow, ow, ow!
Okay.
You are strong!
Whoa!
[Blue shouts]
[grunts]
[wheezes, laughs]
Can we do it
again? Okay, get up.
Get up, get up.[Blue giggling]
Is this a hotel?
What are you doing here?
I'Őm visiting my dad!
Oh, yeah! Your dad
has a broken heart?
That must be scary.
What? No, it'Ős not.
What are you doing here? I
cannot be seen talking to you.
Ooh, why not?
Because there'Ős real people
here. I'Őm gonna look crazy!
[chuckles] Come
on. You'Őre just a kid.
[Benjamin] Hi!
Who are you talking to?
Okay... Oh... Whew! [groans]
Open up! All right.
Open up! I have your...
thing.
What are you anyway? An IF.
I know that. But what?
I don'Őt know.
Finally! Oh. It'Ős you.
Hello! I want it to stop.
Oh, that'Ős awful!
I'Őll make tea.
I think she was pretty
clear she doesn'Őt...
Whatever.
Make what stop?
All of it. I don'Őt need this.
Well, I don'Őt know
what to tell you,
but that'Ős not how this works.
That'Ős not how what works?
What is happening to me?
You are the chosen
one. Nope! Nope.
Let'Ős not give her a complex.
She'Ős already enough
of a spark plug as it is.
Chosen for what?
This whole thing is a
curse. Now you'Őre getting it.
No, no, no! You could
do so much good.
You could save all of us!
All of who?
And don'Őt say IFs.
[squeaking]
Um...
You should
probably let him say it
or I think his head
may actually explode.
[choking]Fine.
I-I-I-I-I-I-F-F-F-F-Fs.
Thank you.
How can I help them?
You can'Őt.Of course she can.
Look, there'Ős
nothing we want more
than to be with our own kids.
But our kids...
they'Őve forgotten about us.
So we need new ones.
You can help us find them.
Like I always say:
"Better to have a new kid
than not to... not to
have a... one... a kid."
He'Ős never said that.
[Blue sighs] Well, thought it.
So, I help you place
them with new kids,
and that'Ős it?
Everything goes back to normal?
Careful what you wish for.
Then I want to meet them. Who?
All the IFs you'Őve been
trying to match with them.
That'Ős impossible.
Why? Because... [laughs]
I can'Őt be seen
to take you to...
Where?
Nowhere.
You need help.
You have no idea how
true that statement is.
But not in the way
that you'Őre thinking.
After last night, you
clearly don'Őt know
how to make this whole
placement thing work.
[groans] Really?
I can help you.
How?
'ŐCause I'Őm a kid.
Well...
that'Ős that.
[Bea] Where are we going?
To get help. From who?
From somebody more qualified.
'ŐCause this is way
above my pay grade.
I think it'Ős really nice
of you, by the way.
What is?
That you'Őre helping
them all like this.
Oh, I don'Őt have
a choice, actually.
They never leave.
How long have you
been able to see them?
Oh, as long as I can remember.
Where do they live?
Well, "live," I think
that'Ős a relative term,
but normally anywhere
kids are, or have been.
Is it...
magical?
Hmm? What? Where we'Őre going.
Used to be.
This is us.
Wait, I'Őve been here before.
Really?
Yeah, my mom took me here once.
All coming back to you, is it?
Wait.
IFs live here?
Hope so.
But it'Ős locked.
I'Őm gonna give you a
minute to think about that one.
Stay here. I'Őm gonna slip
around back, grab us a key.
You'Őre leaving me alone?
You'Őre never really alone!
Thought that was obvious by now.
[groans]
You sure you want to do this?
Yeah.
Because there'Ős no telling
who'Ős behind that door today.
Are any of them scary?
Worse.
Desperate.
Ah, Vicki. How are you?
Is that a new
perfume? It smells, um...
Okay. Boundaries, of course.
Here to see Il Capitano.
Yeah, the ol'Ő spirit bear.
Okay. [knocks]
Look alive.
[Judge Judy, through TV] Was your
daughter living in her mother'Ős house?
That'Ős loud.
[Judge Judy] And you were
using her utilities accounts.
Your husband says that your
daughter was not living in...
[news program intro on TV]
[through TV] I'Őm Kurt Loder
with an MTV news brief.
[Cal] Hey!
Let'Ős go! Come on.
[crashes][Cal] Oh!
Why is this here?
Hi, Todd!
[squeaks]
[therapist] Okay. Let'Ős
start like we always do.
Big breath in. [inhales]
And out.
[exhales]
And in. [inhales]
And out. [exhales]
Beautiful.
Who'Őd like to start?
[sobbing] I'Őve been...
Last week I was
feeling pretty good,
and then this week, I
don'Őt know what happened!
It'Ős okay. I just
started falling apart!
Oh, here we go.
[chuckles] I mean, cue
the violins. Am I right, Terry?
Oh, come on. Ted,
you know she'Ős a viola!
Well, that'Ős not nice. That
doesn'Őt make anyone feel good.
Guys, guys.
We have to move
through this narrative
that our kids choose
to forget about us.
They all go through something
that makes them forget.
[sobbing] Oh, I wish I
could see him one more time.
I wish I could just
tell him I'Őm right here!
I'Őve always been right here!
Hey, hey, hey,
whoa! Not the cape.
That is toxic.
It'Ős okay. We'Őll get
someone to clean that up.
Listen, Doc. I'Őm
payin'Ő good cash,
and this slime ball'Ős
takin'Ő up all the time.
[IF] Doc, I got a question.
Is it possible that
kids are just the worst?
Oh, my God. Is that a kid?
What'Ős that? Oh, my God!
Uh, what does
the skin look like?
What does it feel like?
Is there light
reflecting off the skin?
Psst! Or is there none? Yeah.
[whispering] Hey. Uh,
Judith, you can cover up.
Let'Ős take five, everybody.
Hey, Cal. You still
owe me twenty bucks
from that foam party.
That'Ős right, yeah.
We said we were never
gonna talk about that with words.
Listen, I need to find somebody,
but I need to do it
on the quiet, okay?
Oh, hi.Hi.
Hi.
Is that... No.
Yes. Oh, boy.
I need to see Lewis.
Where is Lewis?
Yeah, sure. I think I saw him
heading down towards the pool.
The pool, okay. Go, go, go.
Yeah, yeah, sure. No
worries. Good luck! [chuckles]
Aw, come on, guys. We'Őve
been through this before.
It'Ős not snacks. It'Ős art.
How'Ős that feel?
Regret starting to
burble up in your throat?
Hey, Cal! Good God, Cos!
Who'Ős the girl? What
is wrong with you?
Hey, Tater Tot. She'Ős a friend!
What kind of friend? Hey!
You'Őre stronger
than you look. Hey!
You know I'Őll find out. Yeah?
[chuckles]
Whatever, man. Whoa!
Cloak-and-dagger!
[scoffs] Starting to
see why I live alone.
Keith!
What kind of a kid
creates an invisible IF?
Was he laying down? Who knows?
[instructor] Down and up, and
down and up, and down and up,
and down and up, and down.
Really bend those knees, ladies!
[Gummy Bear] Am
I looking red? Yes.
Oh, thank God!
Come on.
[birds singing]
Lewis? I have someone
I'Őd like you to meet.
Hello, Elizabeth.
It'Ős very nice to meet you.
Thank you.
So, did he give
you the grand tour?
Kind of.
And what'Őd you think?
Not quite what I expected.
Uh-huh.
She wants to help
with the placements.
Uh-huh.
Lewis here is 93.
He started this place.
He can teach you
everything you need to know.
Isn'Őt that right,
Lewis?[Lewis] Calvin.
[chuckles] You know,
he wasn'Őt always like this.
Oh, no? Nah.
Old Calvin here used to
be a clown. He tell you that?
No.
[Lewis chuckles] That'Ős right.
Before all this, his only job
in life was to make you smile.
Well, not anymore.
All right. [claps]
You guys seem to
have this under control.
He'Őll show you the ropes.
Probably have you
wax a car or something.
You know, if he'Ős not
gonna give you the grand tour,
why don'Őt you give it to him?
I'Őm sorry, what?
This place can be
anything you want it to be.
All you need is a
little imagination.
No. No.
No, no, no. Don'Őt do this.
Show us how it looked
in that head of yours.
[rumbling][grunts]
["Better Be Good to Me" playing]
[chuckles] That'Ős it.
No.
[panting]
What happened?
Nothing, Matt. Let'Ős just
get you back inside here.
There you go.[Blue giggles]
What are you doing,
Sneezy? Help me out here.
Something'Ős happening!
Nothing is happening!
[Blue giggles]
Yeah!
Get inside. No, no,
no! I want to see!
No, I want to
see, I want to see!
[Cal grunting] Get in![laughing]
Oh, wow![bell dings]
[sniffs] Mmm.
[laughs]
Whoo-hoo! Wow. Wow!
[grunting]
Oh, my gosh! It
looks like a dream!
[screams]
[sighs, gasps]
[grunts]
[roars]
[giggling]
Woo hoo!
Oh, my gosh! Is this the pool?
Oh, wow, nice. Whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
[gasping, panting]
Sorry.
[panting, grunting]
Cal?
Whoa! Are you all right?
Whoa! Hey, where'Őd
you come from?
No, no, no, not the fruit!
[rewinds]
A walking palette
approaches. Steady. Steady.
Good God, you
fool! Damn your eyes!
["Better Be Good to Me" playing]
[crowd cheering]
Where have you been? You were
supposed to be here five minutes ago!
You'Őre on! What do you mean?
Come on, get out there!
Oh, let'Ős go!
Let'Ős go!
[giggles]
Thanks.
And here we go.
[grunts]
Watch it!
Oh!
[exclaims]
Well, look who'Ős back.
Ooh! You'Őre
back. Is he all right?
Oh, that was fun![panting]
You look a mess.
Your tush okay, hon?
Did you say G-4? I have bingo!
Well, that was the
weirdest job interview
I'Őve ever been a part of.
[snickers]
Oh, good! Glad
you'Őre having fun.
So does this make us partners?
Let'Ős not get ahead
of ourselves, shall we?
Ooh!
Keith![chuckles]
See you tomorrow.
[seagulls cawing]
[dings]
You know what no one
tells you about hospitals?
There is nothing good to read.
How'Ős your story coming?
Oh, I don'Őt have time for that.
I got a job.
Okay.
I assume I'Őm allowed
to ask no questions.
Nope.[Dad] As you were.
[door closes]See?
We still have a chance.
[blowing]
Hi!
Whoa.
You got supersonic
hearing or something?
Nope. I was just
waiting for you.
Oh.
TV'Ős still busted.
They should
really get that fixed.
Honestly? I think my mom
has something to do with it.
Your mom? Yeah.
She says that screens
turn my brain into mush.
What if she broke it?
Guess what. I got a job.
Wow. Like, at an
ice cream store?
More like a matchmaking agency.
Well, whatever it is, I'Őm sure
you'Őre great at it. Good luck!
Thank you.
Hey. Yeah?
Have you ever had
an imaginary friend?
Nope.
Want one?
Sure!
Well, he'Ős about eight or nine,
so I think we prioritize by hobby.
Oh, boy. See if anybody
has any experience
in magic or fantasy.
Good luck, guys.
Hmm, fantasy'Ős a
bit of a Pandora'Ős box.
Maybe their person
liked superheroes.
Yeah. He does.
Or art.Yup. Love art.
Or TV.I'Őm not
gonna ask you again.
Put some pants on. You'Őre
freaking everyone out.
[chuckling] Pants.
How are we
feeling?[Bea] I feel good.
You feel good? Yeah.
As good as can be expected.
It'Ős your show. Here we go.
You can send them in.
Okay, so I just...
just put myself right
here? Got it right, okay.
Perfect. Hi.[all] Hi.
[giggling] Oh, hi! My gosh!
This is just so exciting!
So, what'Ős your name?
[chuckles] My name is Ally.
Sunny.
Andromedus the Third, son of...
Steven.
Pop.
Because, well, sometimes,
when I get nervous I...
Oh, dear God.
[chuckles]
Nothing to be nervous
about. You'Őre doing great.
[gasps] She'Ős so sweet.
My little girl'Ős
name was Tabitha.
Uh, she named me Uni,
because... because... [laughs]
because I'Őm a unicorn!
[laughing] Sorry.
Oh, I'Őm so nervous!
And where are you from?
Originally? Philadelphia.
DeKalb. Illinois.
Spokane.
New Jersey. Save
your comments, please.
Uh, mostly RadioShack.
Let'Ős see, we moved in 'Ő83.
Oh, no! 'Ő84? Yeah,
that was rough.
I mean, rough.
Poughkeepsie? Come on, Dad.
[chuckles] Might as well have
moved us to the moon, am I right?
[laughing][chuckles]
It'Ős not funny.
[mouthing words]
[triumphant music playing]
Are you ready?
For what?
Anything.
We used to put on
shows every day.
Sometimes multiple
shows! Look...
They kept building me and...
and rebuilding me.
You know what I mean?
But we never got lasers
to shoot out of my eyes!
I'Őm not gonna lie and say
the schedule wasn'Őt brutal,
because it was.
But at the end of the day,
to hear the roar
of that crowd. God!
The uncles... [chuckles]
the uncles were the best.
Okay, I got a whole
bunch of friends here.
You just let me know
which one you can see.
Sure.
[chuckles]
All right, can you see this guy?
[scatting]
Ta-da!
Nope.
Nothin'Ő?
No problem. Who is this kid?
You know, the hardest part
for me was maybe bedtime.
Look, Mom just
didn'Őt get it. I mean...
Okay, let me tell you
something about the dark, okay?
All kids are scared of
the dark. All of them!
Even if they don'Őt
admit it. And why?
'ŐCause those night-lights
don'Őt do anything! That'Ős why.
That'Ős why.
Like, sure, Mom, you got a job to do. You'Őre
doing great. But let me ask you something.
You put this kid to bed,
who'Ős gonna watch
over Poughkeepsie?
Can you see this guy?
Okay. Here we go!
Nope. What'Ős that?
[chuckling] Ask him again.
Ask him again.
Really?
Nope. That'Ős it. I got this.
Whoa! No, I got this!
And Mom said too much
candy isn'Őt good for your tummy,
but I said...
[flatulence]Oh, my God.
Wow. My eyes can taste it.
I'Őm so sorry.
You don'Őt taste
that in your eyeballs?
I can find anyone.
Anywhere![screams]
Don'Őt, don'Őt!
Okay, okay, okay.
But where are you from?
[chuckling] Like I
would ever tell you that.
Like he would
ever tell you that.
[Cal] All right, thank
you very much, sir.
Pretty but dim.
Uh, he'Ős in my...
He got in my mouth.
Look, you seem like a nice kid,
so I'Őm just gonna
shoot straight.
In the beginning, I thought,
what if he created me as
some kind of metaphor?
I mean, it'Ős possible
that he could be
like a legit genius,
right? Wrong.
It was Arizona, and he was
just thirsty. And here we are!
[whispering] Don'Őt, uh,
don'Őt look him in the eye.
Which one? You know
damn well which one.
And I just want to say,
thanks for doing this.
It really means a whole
lot to everybody! Oh!
[retches]
[Lewis chuckles][gags]
Nope.
I don'Őt think he
knows what he wants.
What the hell do you want?
Who'Ős next?
[thuds]
[Cal] Keith!
No.I agree.
Yeah, that one'Ős
just confusing.
Keith'Ős the worst.
Mmm. His favorite
snack was croissants.
Which was kind of cheating.
Because his parents owned
a bakery right downstairs.
[chuckling] So that
was convenient!
So we had a lot of croissants.
And bread. Carbs. Lotta carbs.
Not pasta. Which is interesting.
But everything
else they did make
was a delicious smell-fest.
Hey! Whoa, whoa,
whoa! No, no, no!
Hey, hey, hey!
Okay, you saw... Okay,
you saw this! You see this!
Because this is my
life in a nutshell, okay?
Nope.
[sneezes]
[crashing]
Any more?
No.
It didn'Őt work.
I'Őm sorry.
That'Ős okay. I still have you!
[seagulls squawking]
Being excited is exhausting!
Okay, let'Ős get you to bed.
So, how'Őd it go?
It didn'Őt work.
[chuckles] Well,
maybe it just wasn'Őt meant to.
All this time spent
trying to find new kids,
they stopped looking
for their old ones.
But their kids have grown up.
They don'Őt need them anymore.
[chuckles] All kids need
their imaginary friends.
Especially when they grow up.
But they'Őve forgotten.
Nothing you love
can ever be forgotten.
You can always go back.
How?
Memories.
They live forever.
Right there in your heart.
Sometimes you just need to
find a way to invite them out.
For me, it'Ős the smell
of the sea breeze.
Or the sound of footsteps
tapping on the boardwalk.
After that,
you just close your eyes,
and it all comes rushing back.
["L-O-V-E" playing]
Shall we?
Thought you'Őd never ask.
[Uni giggling] Wait
for me! Wait for me!
[song continues playing]
[chuckles] Hey!
Pretty good, huh?
[gasps] I love it.
Look at this. Oh, my gosh!
Wow, is that a
flower? It'Ős so cute.
[chuckles, snorts]
Ooh! Ooh, mine!
Mine! I want to try!
[Blue] Thank you, my good sir.
Look at this!
[chuckles] Oh, those look great.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[laughs] The best
night of my life!
Oh, wow! Look at me![laughing]
Onward, dear friends!
[Matt laughing] Fantastic!
Can I have one lick?
[song ends]
Lights out.
You should get some rest.
You got a big day tomorrow.
Why, what'Ős happening tomorrow?
[chuckles] You got to stop.
Never.
[chuckles]
[Grandmother] Because
there I was having my final swim
before getting to the airport.
Now, normally you just
go up like that, don'Őt you?
You just go
"Whump!" and legs up.
I could not do that,
because I had a broken leg.
[Bea giggles]
Now, do you want
some more of this?
Because I didn'Őt know
what flavor you like.
So I just got everything.
No, it was great.
You did great.
Good.
Right.
Grandma?
Can I ask you a question?
Of course. Anything.
What did you want to be
when you were a kid?
Well!
[both chuckling]
What? Gosh.
Well, that is a good question.
Yeah, um, well, I, um...
[both laughing]
I always dreamt
of being a dancer.
Really?
Excuse me, don'Őt
look so surprised.
Your grandfather thought
I was quite fetching.
So, he saw you dance?
Of course!
I'Őve got something here.
Oh, yeah. Oh, my goodness.
Oh.
[sighs] That'Ős
your grandmother.
You'Őre beautiful.
Yeah, well, he thought so.
[chuckles]
Actually, I was shaking
in my boots that day.
Or in my slippers.
You were? Yeah.
I mean, it was the most
important day of my life
because they only had...
I think six schools
were chosen to perform
across the river in just
this beautiful little theater.
And I still remember
the sound of the wood
on the floor creaking.
And the music just
tumbled from the orchestra,
just like a wave.
And how the dust
caught the light as it fell.
And it made me feel like
I was in a dream.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
So what happened?
Oh, my dear girl, I grew up.
Too tall.
Too awkward.
And too old.
I mean, let'Ős be honest,
who wants to see
an old woman dance?
Now,
can I get you some dessert?
I have some ice cream. Well,
I think I have some ice cream.
If it doesn'Őt have ice on top.
Why does ice form on
the top of ice cream?
["Dream a Little Dream of
Me" playing on phonograph]
Ooh! Miss us already?
Is she here?
Who? Blossom.
Oh, hi! I only made
enough for two.
I'Őll make more.
You'Őre hers.
Ooh, is this a
riddle? I love riddles.
My grandmother. You'Őre her IF.
Well, of course I am. [chuckles]
Devilish style, adorable accent.
I'Őm surprised it wasn'Őt
obvious, to be honest.
Then let'Ős go!
She'Ős right downstairs.
She won'Őt believe it.
Bea, it'Ős not
for lack of trying.
I'Őve been down there
with her every day.
I read with her, I
watch TV with her,
I even went through her
Pilates phase with her.
She couldn'Őt see me.
There'Ős nothing you can
do if they can'Őt remember.
["Dream A Little Dream
of Me" continues playing]
Then we have to help her.
[song ends]
[whispering] Elizabeth.
Bea! Shh!
What are you doing?
["Spartacus" playing]
What are we doing?
This is ridiculous!
What on earth are you up to?
Bea?
Huh.
[sighs]
[Bea] Oh, my God.
Where have you been?
This your room? I
like it. Old school.
I found him. Works in the city.
Told you I could find
anyone, anywhere! [laughs]
Good luck, Short
Stack. It'Ős all up to you.
Cloak-and-dagger!
Hope this works.
It says we should
be on the next block.
We got to hurry.
Okay, so... Okay,
so let'Ős recap this.
So we'Őre actually
going to see him?
Yes! Oh, okay.
Wow. Like, see him right now!
Not if you can help it.
Okay, but, you know,
how do we even know it'Ős
him? It'Ős all in the dossier.
[Blue] Yep, that'Ős him.
Ooh, boy.
[chuckles]
Wow. I am not ready for this.
I think I'Őm gonna be sick. Oh!
[Blue] What, you see him?
He'Ős on the move. Come on!
[Blue] Where?[Cal] Let'Ős
go, go, go. Double-time.
Oh, I should'Őve worn a suit!
[mumbling]
[barista] Next!
[glass squeaks]
[Blue sighs]
Oh, boy.
He looks...
great! [laughs]
Wow! Look at him!
So fit!
He used to look,
well, more like me.
Oh!
Looks like he'Ős done
something to his hair.
I think that'Ős sweat.
I am so emotional!
Now'Ős our chance.
[elevator music plays]
Okay. Got to go in there.
Wait, what?
I can'Őt go in there alone.
Then you go with him.
Oh, no, I'Őm afraid
that'Ős not on the menu.
Um, I wouldn'Őt say that public
bathrooms are my worst nightmare...
Oh, please!
But they'Őre definitely
up there in the top one.
And she'Ős breached.
Get on in there, come on.
[toilet flushes]
[sighs]
"20% of the third
quarter next year...
20% of the third
quarter next year.
How is that possible, you say.
How is that possible,
you may ask."
Come on, man, get it together.
"In the third quarter"...Go!
"of next year." This is it.
[Jeremy] "20% in the
third quarter of next year.
How do I know that'Ős possible?"
[mockingly] "How do I
know that'Ős possible?"
You got this.
Okay? You'Őre fine.
[breathing heavily]
Don'Őt you cry.
Please don'Őt you cry.
Come on. Look at me!
Don'Őt cry.
Come on.
Ah. Ah. Ah! Come
on, come on, come on.
[sneezes][metal creaks]
Oh, God.
How'Őd it go? Oh! Oh, my God!
Come on!
[sighs] I blew it.
Gross. Come on.
Oh, God, is this it?
Cal, am I disappearing?
Pretty sure that'Ős
not how this works.
Oh, boy! I think I
need to throw up.
Well...
gave it our best shot.
It didn'Őt work.
I don'Őt understand. They were
standing right next to each other.
Okay, yeah. I need to throw up.
Or I need a snack.
It'Ős one of the two.
Maybe the mood wasn'Őt right.
In fairness, the
music was terrible.
Yeah, I definitely
need to eat something.
I'Őm starving.
That'Ős it.
What'Ős it?
Don'Őt lose him.
Can I help you?
Yes.
I'Őm here for a delivery.
[crunches]
[sniffs]
[breathes deeply]
[mumbling]
Wow.
[receptionist] Mr. Griffith.
They'Őll see you now.
[exhales shakily]
[sniffles]
[gasps]
You'Őre okay.
Okay.
Hey, everyone. Thanks
for seeing me today.
I'Őm really excited to be here.
I think it'Ős gonna
be a good one.
[beeps]
Wow.
I mean, that was just...
I mean, that was just so...
[IFs cheering]
Oh. [chuckles]
[cheering]
[chuckles]
[Cal laughs]
Congratulations.
You did it.
We did it.
I think we make a pretty
good team, don'Őt we?
Yes, we do.
[Cal, Bea chattering]
Okay!
Did you do the bracelets?
Yes, of course! My whole
arm was covered in them.
Oh!
[gasps]
[gasps] Thank you very much.
Oh, where have you been?
Uh, sorry, I was just
out with some friends.
Come inside. Come
on, come inside.
It'Ős okay, Grandma.
I'Őm okay, I promise.
Not you.
Your father. I'Őm
sure he'Ős okay.
Just get whatever you need,
and we can talk in the car.
Keys, keys, where are my keys?
[knocking]
I can'Őt do it.
I just can'Őt do it.
It'Ős okay.
You'Őre okay.
I need you to help me.
Hey, I'Őm right
here.[inhales shakily]
I just can'Őt do it again.
You can'Őt do what?
Say goodbye.
Then don'Őt.
I don'Őt know what to say.
What do I tell him?
You just tell him a story.
[sniffles, sobs]
Thank you.
If you could just
wait here a moment.
Oh. I see. Thank you.
Bea.
Hey, your dad had a long day.
He just needs some rest.
[door closes]
Hi.
So...
I'Őve been working
on that story.
And I'Őm ready to tell you now.
It'Ős a story about...
a little girl.
A little girl who was so sad
and so scared
that she did everything she
could to block the world out...
so she'Őd never have
to feel anything again.
But she couldn'Őt.
She couldn'Őt because
she has this person...
this magical person...
that, no matter how hard
she tried to push away...
no matter how hard
she tried to grow up...
he wouldn'Őt let her.
[crying] He would just
keep holding on to her
tighter and tighter.
[sniffling]
And the funny thing is...
that'Ős the only place
she truly feels safe.
It'Ős the only place
she ever wants to be.
[crying]
So you can'Őt go anywhere.
I'Őm just a kid.
Please, Daddy, please.
Please.
[sobbing]
[whispering] That'Ős
a really good story.
What happens next?
I love you.
He'Ős awake! He'Ős awake.
Oh!
Hey.
Open the door.
Hello?
Who'Ős there?
Open the door.
[chuckles]
Are you trying to get in there?
Uh, yeah. My friend lives here.
Your friend?
He helped me, so I just
wanted to tell him thank you.
Oh, I'Őm so sorry.
[chuckling] There'Ős
no one in there.
All right.
I think that'Ős everything.
Hey, we can always come back.
Got everything? Mm-hmm.
All right, I'Őll be right back.
Oh, I was just coming
to say goodbye.
It was you.
It was always you.
And I'Őm so sorry that I
didn'Őt remember sooner.
You'Őre probably
thinking that...
I don'Őt need you anymore.
That I'Őve grown up.
So...
I just had to come tell you
that I'Őll always need you.
Especially when I grow up.
All I have to do
is close my eyes
and it all comes rushing back.
[grunts]
[both] Gross.
["Ooh La La" playing]
[Bea] When I was little,
I remember telling a story.
And as I get older, I often
find myself looking back,
questioning certain details.
But every time that happens,
I always remind myself
to take a breath...
and simply ask myself...
[sighs]
"What IF?"
They'Őll be fine.
She'Őll be fine.
So...
shall we go in?
Oh, God.
[song continues]
Danny, I'Őm back!
You look great. Love the
beard. How old are you?
[screams]Cloak-and-dagger!
[crashing]
Whatever.
Come on, let'Ős go.[song
continues playing]
You got this.
[gasps]
[chuckling] Let'Ős go, come on.
[chimes]
[song continues playing]
[chattering]
[Dragon grunting]
Hi.[grunts]
[Dad] Can I admit
something to you?
I'Őm not sure I even
know what a pizza roll is.
I should'Őve admitted
it earlier, but...
Hey, is that
heavy? A little bit.
Oh, it is? Okay, great.
Don'Őt worry, I got the rest of it.
Okay? Okay.
[squeaks][thuds]
[sighs] Hey, Keith.
One, two, three, four!