Power over Spice is power over all
Imperial Diary. Year 10,191.
Third comment.
The battle for Arrakis
took everyone by surprise.
There were no witnesses.
The Harkonnen operation
was perpetrated overnight,
without warning
or declaration of war.
By morning,
the Atreides were no more.
All died in the dark.
And the Emperor said...
nothing.
Since that night, my father
has not been the same.
Nor have I.
His inaction
is difficult for me to accept.
For, I know he loved
Duke Leto Atreides like a son.
But my father's
always been guided
by the calculus of power.
This would not be
the first time the Harkonnens
have done his dirty work.
In the shadows of Arrakis
lie many secrets...
but the darkest of them all
may remain.
The end of House Atreides.
Sister, Father is dead.
Shouldn't you go back
to the stars,
be with him?
I'm afraid I won't have
enough time to fix things
before your coming.
This world is beyond cruelty.
Enemy.
Stay here.
Down. Right.
They're close.
Do you hear that?
The rats are calling a worm.
Worms!
Unit, climb. Now!
Look for wormsign.
We're okay.
Shields!
No Shields!
I got you, rat.
Never stand with your back
towards the open.
How many times do I have
to tell you that, huh?
You okay?
- Yeah.
- How 'bout her?
She's fine.
They do not usually
venture this deep.
They wanna make sure
no Atreides escaped.
You think too much of yourself.
No, no,
we are in the deep desert.
Only Fremen can survive here.
They were here for us,
not for you.
Don't worry.
I'm taking you somewhere
they will never find us.
Filthy water.
It's full of chemicals,
but good enough
for cooling systems.
Don't let it out.
- You okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Don't let that out.
- Don't let it out!
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
Mm-hmm.
You fought well...
once you woke up.
I wasn't sleeping.
No, no, no. I'll do it.
Lor-- Lord Rabban.
Now that the spice fields
have been secured,
I strongly recommend bringing
all troops out
of Fremen territories.
We're losing too many men
to the desert.
Rats.
- I beg your pardon?
- We're losing men to rats.
Fremen!
I can't confirm, my Lord.
Communications are hectic
in the open sands.
Your orders were to control
the whole planet.
- We are.
- I see only half of it.
As you may recall,
the South is uninhabitable,
my Lord.
May I suggest
you get some rest?
- Rats! Hairy rats!
Kill them! Kill them!
Kill them all!
Rats!
He's asking why we're so late.
He thinks you're spies.
You're not welcome here.
He said--
- I got that.
- Thanks.
Stay close to me.
Hmm?
Sietch Tabr.
Jamis! Jamis!
You killed Jamis!
Spies!
Witch!
Stop! Stop!
They don't know what they're saying.
Lisan al-Gaib! Lisan al-Gaib!
Mahdi!
Lisan al-Gaib!
I need your guidance
with the two foreigners.
Give them back to the desert.
I saw the signs.
Again.
Stilgar, your faith is
playing tricks on you.
The Lisan al-Gaib has not
shown his face yet!
He killed Jamis in a fair fight.
He speaks our language.
He will quickly learn our ways.
I'm ready to pledge my life for him.
The desert will handle his fate.
What about the woman?
Look how your Bene Gesserit
propaganda has taken root.
Some of them already think
I'm their messiah.
Others...
false prophet.
I must sway the non-believers.
If they follow me,
we can disrupt
spice production.
That's the only way
I can get to the Emperor.
Your father didn't believe
in revenge.
Yeah, well, I do.
What is happening?
Too spicy for the foreigner?
What is it?
There is spice
in the food.
He'll look pretty with blue eyes.
Don't mock him.
He deserves our respect.
He's a good fighter.
Woman.
Come with me.
To the well, our water we return.
We bless our brother, Jamis.
Thirty-eight million
decaliters.
None of us,
even dying of thirst,
would ever drink this water.
This is...
sacred.
Jamis' water.
We have a thousand such places.
When we have enough water,
the Lisan al-Gaib will change
the face of Arrakis.
He will bring back the trees.
He will bring back...
a Green Paradise.
So many souls.
Never give your water away,
not even for the dead. Hmm?
Why are you showing me this?
Because you are Bene Gesserit.
Because you understand
the prophecies.
The mother of
the Lisan al-Gaib
will be a Reverend Mother.
Our Reverend Mother is dying.
You want me to take her place?
Yes, I do.
You believe in Paul?
There are signs.
Yes.
What if I would refuse?
Mmm.
Then, he's not Lisan al-Gaib,
and you have no purpose
to serve.
What else is left to do then
but to return your water
to the well?
Huh.
It's an honor, isn't it?
I think you should
feel honored.
Well, it was a choice
between this or death,
so, you know, forgive me
if I'm not flattered.
How does one become
a Reverend Mother?
It's different from one culture
to another.
Here on Arrakis,
I have no idea.
You're afraid.
Reverend Mothers are tasked
with holding the memories
of all the Reverend Mothers
that came before them,
so I'll be given centuries
of pain and sorrow.
Is it dangerous?
It's lethal for men.
That's for sure.
What are you guys
laughing about?
Don't bother.
You don't believe in all this?
No, we don't.
These are old Southern beliefs.
Southern beliefs?
Southern tribes believe
a messiah will come
to deliver us from evil.
You don't believe
in the Lisan al-Gaib?
We believe in Fremen.
Amen.
You want to control people,
you tell them
a messiah will come.
You want to control people,
you tell them
a messiah will come.
- Mm-hmm.
- Then they'll wait
for centuries.
Now, we must pray.
What about him?
Stilgar?
- Mm-hmm.
He's from the South.
You didn't notice his accent?
What'll happen to my mother?
She'll drink worm piss.
Not funny.
He's about to lose her.
If she's stupid enough to drink poison.
Shut up!
We are praying.
I must not fear.
Fear is the mind-killer.
Fear, the little death
that brings total obliteration.
I will face my fear. I will...
Here is the Water of Life.
It frees the soul.
If you drink...
you shall die.
you may see.
Drink!
What is it?
What have we done?
She is pregnant.
That was no miracle!
You saw it with your own eyes!
The Mother of the Lisan al-Gaib
shall survive the Holy Poison.
And She did.
As written!
Her people wrote that!
Blasphemy.
The prophecy has been accomplished.
The Mahdi must be Fremen!
Arrakis must be freed
by its own people!
She's right. She's right!
It's no miracle.
My mother was trained
to do that.
Poison transmutation
is something advanced
Bene Gesserit can do.
I'm not the Mahdi.
I'm not here to lead.
I'm here to learn your ways.
Let me fight beside you.
That's all I'm asking.
The Mahdi is too humble
to say He is the Mahdi.
Even more reason to know He is!
As written!
How are you?
Better.
How is she?
She was frightened,
but she's...
she's okay.
Paul.
She talks to me.
She believes in you.
She says...
Kwisatz Haderach, show us the way.
You're so close now.
Only one step remains
and you will become
the Kwisatz Haderach.
Only one step remains.
You must do what I did.
You must drink
the Water of Life.
And your mind,
it's gon-- it's gonna open
and you will see.
You will see!
The beauty and the horror!
If you wanna fight
with us, first thing,
you must learn
to be one with the desert.
So, here is a tent
and enough food.
I want you to cross
that small erg and come back.
Travel by night.
You know how to use
a paracompass?
- Yes.
- Oh.
Anything else I should know?
Uh, beside the worms
and the Harkonnens,
beware of the trapdoor spiders.
Centipedes are very nasty.
Not the big ones.
They are harmless.
But the little ones,
you have to worry about.
And... Oh!
Don't ever,
ever listen to the jinn.
- The jinn?
- Jinn.
Desert spirits.
They whisper at night.
They, they can possess you.
Really, be careful.
They are demons.
But it's true.
Don't listen to them.
He doesn't know how to cross.
Stilgar is going to get him killed.
What is he trying to prove?
What do you think?
"The Prophet shall know
the ways of the desert."
I think it's for the best.
What's this?
You care for him now?
He's not like the other strangers.
He's sincere.
Jamis.
You sandwalk
like a drunk lizard.
Yeah, I'm doing
pretty good so far.
Yeah, well, you're not even
in worm territory yet.
You have to break up
your rhythm.
Like this.
Now, that's interesting
because in the filmbooks
I've studied,
the anthropologists say,
in order to properly sandwalk,
you actually have--
Never mind. Please keep going.
You know, I'm the only one
who believes you're gonna
make it until summer?
Everyone else thinks
you won't make it two weeks.
If you wanna follow us
in the desert,
you need to know
how windtraps work.
So, listen to me.
They're simple,
but they require
constant attention.
Uh, this right here,
it captures the moisture
and then it carries it
into that pocket.
Uh, and these are the filters.
They need to be changed
every three days.
What?
Stop looking at me like that.
He's training with the Fremen.
He will be back soon.
Don't worry.
Mm-hmm.
You're right. If we want
to protect your brother,
we need all the Fremen
to believe in the prophecy.
We must convert
the non-believers one by one.
We need to start
with the weaker ones.
The vulnerable ones.
The ones who fear us.
Hey, get out of here. Go.
You okay?
Yeah.
Let's go! Move!
Load.
Chani!
Reload!
Ugh! Reload.
Oh, watch out!
Its shield will
only open when it fires.
I know that.
What do you think
I'm trying to do?
I'll trigger it.
On my signal. Be ready.
Go!
Ah, shit!
- Go! Go!
You saw what he did.
He saw it coming,
and he saved her life.
He saw it.
He can foresee.
Muad'Dib likes his smell.
Who taught you
to fight like that?
- My old masters.
- Hmm.
They were close friends.
They were massacred.
Alongside my father.
You've been fighting
the Harkonnens for decades.
My family's been fighting them
for centuries.
I know everything about them.
Their habits,
their ways of thinking.
You know everything
about the desert.
You harness
the very power of it.
We can stop them together,
bury them in the sand
where they belong.
So that this planet
can be yours once more.
What would you
have us do? Huh?
What would you do, Stilgar?
I? I would...
would strike
even further north.
Then I will go further north.
And the further north you go,
the more likely it is you die.
Then I'll die.
Maybe you will too.
But the others will keep going.
And they won't stop
until the Fremen are free.
He deserves to be Fedaykin.
He needs names, Stilgar.
He does!
I see strength in you.
Like Usul.
The base of the pillar.
Come, come.
You shall be know
among us as Usul.
Usul.
- Usul.
Usul. And now,
a Fedaykin is a fighter
and needs a war name.
You must choose.
How do you call the, uh...
The small desert mouse, again?
- Muad'Dib?
Muad'Dib.
No, no, no.
Muad'Dib is wise
in the ways of the desert.
Muad'Dib...
creates his own water.
The constellation that points
to the North Star,
we call Muad'Dib.
"The One Who Points the Way."
That is a powerful name.
Now you are our brother. Mmm.
Paul Muad'Dib Usul.
Muad'Dib Usul.
Muad'Dib Usul. Mm.
Muad'Dib.
Usul.
Hey! Stilgar!
Father, I found my way.
It's breathtaking.
Hmm.
Look. Right there. Spice.
Arrakis is so beautiful
when the sun is low.
Where you're from, does water
really fall from the sky?
Oh, hm, yes.
Sometimes it rains
for weeks on Caladan.
Where you see sand here,
imagine water.
Our castle stands on cliffs
high above the sea.
If you dive in,
you can't reach the bottom.
You dive in?
- Yes, it's called swimming.
I don't--
I don't believe you, Usul.
Usul.
What's your secret name?
Sihaya.
- Sihaya.
- Hmm.
What does that mean?
Means Desert Spring.
"Desert Spring."
- I love it.
- I hate it.
It's from some stupid prophecy.
I prefer Chani.
I prefer Chani, too, then.
Do you think Stilgar
would teach me?
To ride?
Yeah.
No. Only Fremen ride worms.
Well, I thought I'd become one,
didn't I?
By name, not by blood.
Your blood comes
from Dukes and Great Houses.
We don't have that here.
Here, we're equal,
men and women alike.
What we do,
we do for the benefit of all.
Well, I'd very much like
to be equal to you.
Paul Muad'Dib Usul...
maybe you could be Fremen.
Maybe I'll show you the way.
Rabban.
Fremen attacks on your watch.
Your orders were to restore
spice production
to full capacity.
Do you know
what it means if you fail?
The Emperor will take spice
out of our control.
Tighten your grip, Rabban.
Uncle.
Or feel mine on your neck.
Usul? Usul.
It's okay. It's okay.
Hey.
I'm here, I'm here.
It's been a while
since you've had
one of those nightmares.
Mm.
Tell me,
what was it about?
Nothing's clear.
It's only fragments.
I'm in the South,
and I'm following someone.
And it triggers a holy war.
Millions and millions of people
starving to death...
because of me.
You've been exposed
to spice for a long time.
It can create weird dreams.
It's a big day.
We can ask Stilgar
to call it off.
No. I'm fine.
Usul.
I tuned it myself.
- Here.
Thanks.
Don't try to impress anyone.
You are brave.
We all know that.
Heh? Be simple.
Be direct. Nothing fancy.
- Nothing fancy.
- Hey, I'm serious.
Nothing fancy or you will shame
my teaching.
I won't shame you.
I understand.
Shai-Hulud decides today
if you become Fremen,
or if you die.
Hey, Muad'Dib!
Don't embarrass us!
Call a big one!
Don't worry.
Stilgar taught him well.
Enough joking.
This is the final test.
Lower.
Okay. Okay.
Not that big.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Okay. Okay!
Come on!
Whoa!
You're a rider!
As written.
Reverend Mother!
Muad'Dib made peace with Shai-Hulud.
He called a grandfather worm.
The biggest ever seen.
As written!
Shai-Hulud shall bow
to the Boy from the Outer World.
Bless the Maker and His works.
Will not Shai-Hulud know the Mahdi
when He comes?
Then share the Word.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
I know they do.
Our task in the North
is nearly done.
They believe in Paul.
Now we go South.
There are millions
of fundamentalists there.
They will protect him
when he comes.
The Kwisatz Haderach
will be born in the South.
Will you always be with me?
As long as I breathe.
What's wrong?
Chani.
There will be trouble.
What are you talking about?
Chani, what do you mean?
The way they look at you.
They worship you now.
The Fedaykin,
they count your victories.
They say you
can see the future.
Whisper, " Lisan al-Gaib."
I'm no messiah.
I'm a Fedaykin of Sietch Tabr.
Yet, we have a Bene Gesserit
among us,
fanning the flames
of your legend,
saying you're the One.
Mm.
Reverend Mother!
Your palanquin is ready!
She says you should
be coming with us.
You know I can't.
She's asking why.
Because I must continue
fighting in the North,
to protect you down
there in the South.
She says she can tell
when you lie.
Tell her that's because
our mother keeps spreading
dangerous tales.
What is she saying now?
She says you're blinded
by love,
and she reminds you that
you must reserve your hand
for the most
strategic alliance.
She's also wondering
why you don't believe
in who you are.
I do believe.
I believe I matter
to these people.
And I believe I'm making
a difference in this war.
We're nearly
at the gates of the city.
- That's not what she means.
- I know what she means.
Do you not think I also feel
the weight of the prophecy?
It's not a prophecy.
It's a story that you
keep telling,
but it's not their story,
it's yours.
They deserve to be led
by one of their own.
What your people did
to this world is heartbreaking.
We gave them something
to hope for.
That's not hope!
Reverend Mother, we have to go!
I'll be waiting for you.
All of us.
Those storms look bad.
They're the Guardians of the South.
It's a hard crossing,
but Shai-Hulud is strong.
How much?
We lost...
eighty percent
of our last crop.
My Lord Rabban,
you should not leave
the security perimeter.
Security perimeter?
The rats are already inside.
The Fremen Demon
might be with them.
I hope so.
We're tracking them, my Lord.
Today, Muad'Dib dies!
The rats are travelling fast.
Move!
Where is he?
Still negative, my Lord.
Why do I have to do
everything myself?
Open range!
Range open.
Life. Delta, delta, delta.
I've lost them.
- Strike!
Yes, my Lord.
Muad'Dib!
Show yourself!
Muad'Dib! Muad'Dib! Muad'Dib!
For Muad'Dib!
Muad'Dib.
Some new Fremen prophet?
It's not the first time we've
had frictions with the Fremen.
None of this magnitude.
So, my dear daughter...
how would you deal
with this prophet?
If this Muad'Dib
is a religious figure,
you can't use direct force.
Repression only makes
a religion flourish.
You'll only end up
humiliating yourself.
You underestimate my Sardaukar.
You underestimate
the power of faith.
Her Highness proves
once again that she was
my most acute student.
- You'd send assassins?
No.
Prophets get stronger
when they die.
Let the conflict
on Arrakis turn into war.
You then bring peace.
As a savior.
You'd be a formidable empress.
Muad'Dib. The prophet.
The one who points the way.
These are our own
religious patterns,
aren't they?
This is our doing.
Muad'Dib means kangaroo mouse.
An unusual war name
for a Fremen.
- What if Paul Atreides
were still alive?
Enough!
This must not come out.
Even to your father's ears.
Understand?
I do, Reverend Mother.
If Paul is alive,
he likely knows the truth.
And should
the Great Houses learn
that your father was behind
the liquidation
of the Atreides,
your father will face war
and lose the throne.
Then what hope is there?
Hope?
We are Bene Gesserit.
We don't hope, we plan.
Paul is not our only prospect.
The Baron's youngest nephew,
Feyd-Rautha Harkonnen,
will inherit Arrakis.
He may be the answer.
Feyd-Rautha? He's psychotic.
That's irrelevant.
The question is,
can we control him?
And I intend to find out.
Would you like some fresh meat,
my darlings?
- Lungs? Or liver?
What would you like?
I hear they're big today.
Your new blades
for this very special day,
na-Baron, Feyd-Rautha.
A notch
off balance.
It's the tip.
Should be sharper.
Come.
I won't die like a fool.
Kill me now.
No drug for you today,
Atreides.
Under our glorious black sun,
we welcome to these special festivities
our beloved leader
Baron Vladimir Harkonnen.
His presence today, watching over
a spectacle of blood and honor,
marks the Holy Birthday
of our beloved na-Baron, Feyd-Rautha.
Welcome to Giedi Prime, sisters.
I hope your travels
were agreeable.
A long way to come
just to watch our prospect
risk his life, Lady Fenring.
No fear.
These fights are all for show.
But we'll get
a good look at him.
Feyd-Rautha! Feyd-Rautha!
In celebration of our
na-Baron Feyd-Rautha,
we present a special treat.
The last three specimens
of House Atreides.
That slave isn't drugged.
That bug is walking straight.
You should cancel the fight.
Don't spoil
my nephew's birthday.
Happy birthday, dear nephew.
Why do they not stop the fight?
Plans within plans.
Show me who you are.
There he is.
Back! Back!
Stay back!
You have fought
well, Atreides.
Hmm.
Feyd-Rautha! Feyd-Rautha!
He's impressive, indeed.
The slave wasn't drugged.
You tried to kill me.
This morning
you were a playboy,
feared and envied,
but tonight you're a hero.
My gift to you.
I ought to drown you
in that tub.
Don't be hasty.
I have another gift for you.
A bigger one.
Arrakis.
What about Rabban?
He has failed
to protect spice production.
Rabban will be reassigned.
Tame Arrakis, Feyd.
Free the spice.
I'll make you Emperor.
Emperor?
How?
The Emperor helped me
destroy the Atreides.
He lent his own army
to the cause.
A serious crime.
If it came to light,
the Great Houses would rise
against him.
And then...
who will sit on the throne?
Feyd-Rautha Harkonnen.
You're following me.
Am I?
I may have gotten lost.
Will you show me the way
out of this maze,
my Lord na-Baron?
We've met, haven't we?
I don't think so.
I'm Lady Margot Fenring.
I'm here to honor
your coming of age.
You're not allowed
in this section.
How did you get
past the guards?
The guards?
May I ask,
what are you doing here?
You're not taking part
in your own celebrations?
You're Bene Gesserit.
And what makes
you say that?
I remember now.
I dreamed about you last night.
A pleasant dream,
I hope.
Don't mock me, woman.
I wouldn't dare.
I know your
Bene Gesserit tricks.
And what do you know
about the Bene Gesserit?
Tell me.
Something wrong?
I don't recognize this place.
This is the guest wing.
Where are you going?
To my room.
Come. To. Me.
Kneel.
Put your right hand in the box.
A sociopath.
Of high intelligence.
Driven. Cruel.
But strongly motivated
by honor.
He yearns to be hurt.
He loves pain.
Can he be redeemed?
He can be controlled.
He's sexually vulnerable.
And?
The bloodline is secured.
Female, as you requested.
You did well, Margot.
Respectfully, why didn't you
test him yourself?
I'm a motherly figure.
And based on what happened
between him and his own mother,
I didn't expect
to be effective.
What happened between
him and his mother?
He murdered her.
Desire and humiliation.
Those are his levers.
If Feyd-Rautha
prevails on Arrakis,
we shall know
how to control him.
All hail na-Baron Feyd-Rautha!
The new Planetary
Governor of Arrakis!
Rid me of this Fremen Demon.
Feyd-Rautha! Feyd-Rautha!
Feyd-Rautha!
♪ Do away with these idiots ♪
♪ I blame ♪
♪ My stillsuit
Is full of piss ♪
♪ My hand is caked in sand ♪
♪ Save me from
These utter morons ♪
♪ Another world, another land ♪
We're in.
Juicy?
Juicy, juicy.
Well, it was nice
knowing ya.
Oh, yeah?
Radar's clear. We're clear.
Cooking time.
Juicy, juicy.
Yeah, I got a meter reading--
All right, guys,
worms are on their way.
Watch out
for abrasions.
Get ready to dock.
It's gonna get hot.
Crank 'em up!
Throw them up!
Hold!
Mine! Mine!
Get moving!
East! East!
Get clear!
Let's get out of here!
Incoming!
Don't run, fight!
We're in deep
Fremen shit.
Holy Mother.
Oh, fuck.
I recognized
your footsteps...
- old man.
No.
- You young pup.
You young pup!
Mmm.
After the Battle of Arrakeen,
I was able to negotiate a trip
back home for the survivors.
Thanks to these guys.
Why'd you stay?
Well, I wanted blood.
Rabban's head?
Mm-hmm.
Well, since Muad'Dib's
been driving Rabban crazy,
the smuggling business
has been quite profitable.
Gurney Halleck the smuggler.
Paul Muad'Dib.
I've heard many stories
about Muad'Dib.
None of them pretty.
You see the fear?
When our resources
are limited...
fear is all we have.
How many men with you?
- Two hundred.
- Two hundred?
Do you realize what you're able
to achieve with 200 men?
Incredible fighters.
Duncan said there
were millions of them.
In the Deep South, yes.
Well, what are you waiting for?
With thousands of these guys,
you could take control
of the entire planet.
It's your father's dream.
What are you afraid of?
Hey!
Worship, Gurney.
They used to be friends.
Now they're followers.
Muad'Dib, the Prophet.
Why is that a bad thing?
Use it.
It's not that simple.
You have the power to avenge
your father,
and you're afraid to use it?
Spice opened my mind, Gurney.
I can foresee things.
If I go South, all my visions
lead to horror.
Billions of corpses
scattered across the galaxy.
All dying because of me.
Because you lose control.
Because I gain it.
That's a lot of water.
Chani.
What?
Look at him, he's hopeless.
He's family.
Really?
What do you think of the outsider?
I think he's trouble.
No, I trust Usul.
No need to be a prophet
to see what's ahead.
Your path leads to war.
You know that.
So, war is coming.
What will you do when you feel
its breath upon your neck?
If you don't want to raise
an army in the South,
you may still have an option.
Fire power...
which you don't have.
And here I am.
I know where your father
hid the family atomics.
Every House possesses
an atomic arsenal.
I thought ours had been lost.
It's huge, Chani.
It could change everything.
I could aim the bombs
at the main spice fields.
He who can destroy a thing
has the real control of it.
So, you can control it
and not us?
You promised me
you didn't want power.
No matter what I do,
you still don't trust me.
'Cause you're a foreigner.
Like your friend.
I'm not a foreigner.
Not to me.
But to the desert, you are.
My allegiance is to you.
To the Fremen.
I'm doing this for all of us.
Do you believe me?
I'll talk to Stilgar.
There.
It's right under
everybody's noses.
Not clever.
That's the idea.
Nobody would ever look in there
because it's obvious.
- Not clever.
Did you find it?
- I didn't look for it.
How many heads exactly?
Enough to blow up
the whole planet.
It's a figure of speech.
You know what I mean.
Only with
your genetic heritage.
Your great-great-grandfather's
legacy.
The 92 original
Atreides family's
atomic warheads.
Now that, that is power.
Imperial Diary. Year 10,191.
Eighth comment.
Reports from
the south of Arrakis
arrive rarely.
These are barren, burnt lands
hidden by sandstorms
which stretch a thousand miles
across the equator.
Nothing can live there
without faith.
Which is why
our Bene Gesserit missionaries
have been so productive there.
Through them,
we are receiving reports
of a mysterious figure
taking grip
on the imaginations
of the Southern
fundamentalist tribes.
A new Reverend Mother
from the North...
spreading word
of the imminent arrival
of the Lisan al-Gaib,
"The Voice
from the Outer World."
With religious fervor
rising in the South,
and Muad'Dib
strangling spice production
in the North,
everything points
to the escalation of war.
Only one at a time...
or they fight each other to death.
How old?
Very young.
Hmm.
My daughter asks, how is it done?
Quiet.
The Water of Life.
Listen carefully.
Soon a man
is going to visit your temple
and he may want
you to perform the rites.
Reverend Mother,
it is forbidden.
You question the prophecy?
No man will survive.
Let him try!
What the hell?
Chani!
Chani.
Sietch Tabr.
Old fashioned artillery.
Genius.
We're literally melting rock
on their heads.
I want to go on the ground.
Prepare my troops.
My Lord. I would recommend
you stay inside.
There was--
Bring his body to my quarters.
My poor darlings are hungry.
There was no food
for them on the flight.
What are you doing here?
It's early morning.
Kiss my feet, brother.
I'm gonna eviscerate your--
You humiliated our family.
You humiliated me.
Kiss...
or die.
We're even now.
Embarrass our family
one more time...
it will be the last.
They're all dead!
I lost them all in the fire!
They didn't even
engage on the ground,
like honorable fighters.
The whole of the North has been hit.
There is a call for a war council
in the South.
Every leader must attend.
Muad'Dib, they're waiting for you.
Usul, in the South...
only leaders
are allowed to speak.
- You must take my place.
- I can't do that.
It is a good time
to cross blades with me.
I am weak.
I am an easy kill, Muad'Dib.
I'd rather cut off my own hand.
We need you.
We need the Lisan al-Gaib
to lead our people.
You know what I think
of all that, Stilgar.
I don't care what you believe.
I believe.
I didn't see it coming.
The Harkonnens
aren't done here.
They just went back to reload.
We're setting thumpers.
We're moving everyone
to the South.
I'll stay behind
and cover your retreat.
- What are you talking about?
- Chani, I can't go with you.
You know why.
I'll stay, too.
- Nobody stays but me.
Paul.
- That's an order,
Gurney Halleck! Go South!
Protect my mother.
- My Lord.
Muad'Dib.
None of these people
will leave without you.
I can't go South.
He's afraid
of the fundamentalists.
And he should be.
Don't resist.
Talk to me, Jamis.
You see only fragments.
You cannot see the future
without seeing the past.
To unlock your mind,
you need to drink
the Water of Life...
and you will see everything.
A good hunter
always climbs the highest dune
before his hunt.
He needs to see...
as far as he can see.
You need to see.
You must drink
the Water of Life.
Your mind, it's gonna open,
and you will see.
The world has made
choices for us.
If I go South,
I might lose you.
You will never lose me,
Paul Atreides.
Not as long
as you stay who you are.
I'll cross
the storms with you.
Go South.
Bring your people to safety.
And then I will do
what must be done.
Where?
Spy. Left behind.
No trace of the others.
They've gone South
to hide in the storms.
Send this message
to the Baron.
The North is liberated
and secured.
Harvest spice at will.
Yes, na-Baron.
You killed nine of my men
with one single blade.
She won't talk.
Tell her that's fine.
I already know
everything I need to know.
Only pleasure remains.
You're not allowed in here, stranger.
Leave or die.
I should be welcomed...
If you drink, you shall die.
If you drink, you may see.
Now that you can see our past,
you can see your future.
Oh, brother,
my dearest brother,
you are not prepared
for what is to come.
You'll now learn the truth
about our family.
And it will hurt you
to the core.
Paul...
Don't worry. I'm with you.
I love you.
Who knows about this?
Only you, Reverend Mother.
Good.
Where are the others?
They just arrived from the North.
Find them.
Paul?
Paul.
I'm here. I'm here. Hey.
What happened?
He's dead.
His vital signs are so low,
they can't be detected.
But he's alive.
What did you do to him?
No, not that.
Why would he do that?
Why would you do that?
Because He is the One.
The Lisan al-Gaib should find His way
to where no man has ever been.
You're insane!
Chani, his body
is fighting the poison
and he needs your help.
Chani, his body
is fighting the poison
and he needs your help.
You do it.
You did this to him.
You did this
to your own son!
You do it!
Fix it yourself.
Chani, you might not believe
in the prophecy,
but you're a part of it.
You're the poison.
You and your lies.
Why would you do this?
Do it.
He shall come back from the dead
with Desert Spring tears.
Bring me a drop of Water of Life.
As written.
Desert Spring tears.
Kwisatz Haderach,
climb up. Arise.
Usul, I'm here. I'm here.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Thanks to you.
I'm sorry about Chani.
She'll come to understand.
I've seen it.
You can see?
The visions are clear now.
I see possible futures.
All at once.
Our enemies are all around us.
And in so many futures,
they prevail.
But I do see a way.
There is a narrow way through.
I saw our bloodline, Mother.
Written across time.
You are the daughter
of Baron Vladimir Harkonnen.
Did my father know?
I didn't know myself,
until I took the worm's poison.
We're Harkonnens.
So this is how we'll survive.
By being Harkonnens.
We must talk.
Stilgar, you can stop this.
Do you hear me?
You have the power
to stop this.
Northern woman!
You are not allowed
to speak inside the circle.
If you want to speak,
you know what to do.
Stilgar, please.
For Arrakis' sake.
This prophecy
is how they enslave us!
How they dominate--
You'll get yourself
in trouble.
This is none
of your business.
Rabban Harkonnen himself
killed my family.
He gave me this scar
to remember him by.
This is all of my business.
Only tribe leaders can speak.
If you wish
to share your voice,
you must take his place
by defeating him
and returning his water
to the well.
You think I'm stupid enough
to deprive myself
of the best of us?
Do you smash a knife
before battle?
Take my life, Usul.
It is the only way.
I'm pointing the way!
Slow down.
There is no one in this room
who can stand against me!
Your mothers warned you
about my coming!
Fear the moment.
But you think
you could have a chance.
But you're afraid.
What if I could be the One?
This could be the moment you've been
praying for, all your life.
You're praying now,
to your grandmother.
She died nine moons ago.
She lost an eye.
A rock smashed her face
as she was crossing the Belt.
She was 12 when it happened.
At that time, this world
had a Fremen name.
Dune.
Lisan al-Gaib!
Lisan al-Gaib! Lisan al-Gaib!
In your nightmares,
you give water to the dead,
and it brings joy to your heart!
Muad'Dib!
Muad'Dib.
Mahdi, what do you foresee for us?
Green Paradise.
Lisan al-Gaib, show us the Way!
This is my father's
ducal signet.
I am
Paul Muad'Dib Atreides,
Duke of Arrakis.
The Hand of God be my witness!
I am the Voice from the Outer World!
I will lead you to paradise!
- Lisan al-Gaib!
Lisan al-Gaib! Lisan al-Gaib!
Lisan al-Gaib!
Paul Atreides
is still alive.
He challenges my father.
You've never been
on Arrakis.
It's quite impressive.
You'll see.
Was this all upon
your advice?
What?
Did you counsel my father
to exterminate the Atreides?
Of course I did. Why else
would it have happened?
You tried to sacrifice
an entire bloodline.
And I was right
to do it.
The Kwisatz Haderach
is a form of power
that our world
has not yet seen.
The ultimate power.
For ninety generations,
we have supervised
House Atreides.
They were promising,
but they were becoming
dangerously defiant.
Their bloodline
had to be terminated.
That is why we have put
many bloodlines at work.
Several prospects.
But it's backfired.
Paul is alive.
And if
he defeats Feyd-Rautha,
my father--
Your father
will lose the throne
no matter who prevails.
But there is one way
your family can remain
in power
and, through you,
the continuation
of our stewardship.
One. Way.
Are you prepared?
You've been preparing me
my whole life,
Reverend Mother.
You're heading north
with the others?
I'm Fedaykin.
I follow my leaders.
If fighting goes north,
I go north.
Paul didn't have
a choice, Chani.
I won't be fighting for him.
I'm fighting for my people.
I came to wish you
best of luck.
I'd wish you the same,
but it seems
you've won your battle.
He took the bait.
Oh, the Emperor's
very obliging.
He's right on time.
As you foresaw, Muad'Dib...
a great-grandmother of a storm.
What is he doing here?
I brought spice production
under control.
What do we do?
Send messages
to the Great Houses.
Tell them that Arrakis
is under Sardaukar attack.
Tell them, their future
hangs in the balance.
He brought his whole army.
When the storm
hits this ridge,
Gurney will open
the way for you, Stilgar,
so you can enter
the basin from the West
and distract
their defense systems.
Chani, I want you
and your Fedaykin
to then attack
from the East,
inside the basin.
I'll strike
from the North,
head on,
with the Fundamentalist troops.
And I'll serve Arrakeen
for dessert.
Remember,
I need the Emperor alive.
Long live the fighters.
Hm.
Baron,
do you have any idea
who this Muad'Dib could be?
Some fanatic, your Majesty.
That's all we know.
More. More. Give me more.
He's a madman!
- Mad?
- All Fremen are mad.
That's all you know?
Really?
Muad'Dib is dead.
Or he went hiding
in the Southern storms
which means the same thing.
They speak the truth.
Your Majesty,
the sand storm
that's approaching
threatens the integrity
of our shields.
We recommend
going back into orbit.
Well, the mountains
will protect us
from most of it,
your Majesty.
Baron, have you
ever investigated
the south regions
of Arrakis?
Well, the entire region
is uninhabitable.
It's well known,
your Majesty.
Your uninhabited South
exhibits evidence
of human activity.
I wasn't aware of this.
I swear to you,
I wasn't aware
of any of this.
Muad'Dib is alive.
I must find him.
Long live the fighters!
Fire!
Sardaukar! On guard!
Sardaukar!
Grandfather.
You die like an animal.
Muad'Dib.
Bring the prisoners to the Residency.
Kill the Sardaukar.
Give the Baron's body to the desert.
Rabban!
Look who's back from the dead.
For my Duke, and my friends.
Warships.
The Great Houses.
Gurney, it's time.
Bring the prisoners.
- My Lord.
This isn't over yet.
I want you to know...
I will love you
as long as I breathe.
There is a massed armada
in orbit.
You're facing
a full invasion, Fremen.
How can you
be so sure the Great Houses
are here for me?
They may be curious
to hear my side of the story,
don't you think?
I am Paul Atreides,
son of Leto Atreides,
Duke of Arrakis.
- Gurney.
- My Lord.
Send a warning to all ships.
If the Great Houses attack,
our atomics will obliterate
all spice fields.
- You're out of your mind.
- He's bluffing.
Consider what you're
about to do, Paul Atreides.
Silence!
Abomination.
Message sent, my Lord.
As a servant of the Imperium,
you will bow at my feet.
Your feet? You'll be lucky
to keep your head.
I'll take the hand
of your daughter.
She will remain safe.
And we will rule together
over the Empire.
But you...
You have to answer
for my father.
Do you know why I killed him?
Because he was a man
who believed
in the rules of the heart.
But the heart
is not meant to rule.
In other words...
your father was a weak man.
Stand or choose your champion.
I am here, Atreides.
I need a blade.
Accept mine.
Do not stain your hands
on this animal.
Let me deal with him.
It's my burden, Gurney.
Why does he take such risks?
Muad'Dib leads the way.
I'm happy
to finally meet you, cousin.
Cousin? Is that right?
Well, you wouldn't be
the first relative I've killed.
May thy knife chip and shatter.
- She's your pet?
Any special attention
for the pet?
You have fought well, Atreides.
Lisan al-Gaib!
Lisan al-Gaib! Lisan al-Gaib!
You should've believed.
You chose the wrong side.
Side?
You, of all people,
should know.
There are no sides...
Reverend Mother.
The life debt has been paid.
Spare my father now
and I will be
your willing bride.
The throne will be yours.
My Lord,
the Great Houses have answered.
They refuse
to honor your ascendancy.
We await your orders,
Lisan al-Gaib.
Lead them to Paradise.
Lisan al-Gaib!
Lisan al-Gaib! Lisan al-Gaib!
What is happening, Mother?
Your brother attacks
the Great Houses.
The Holy War begins.