Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
I appreciate
you coming, Mr. Snow.
As I finish my move from London
and settle into your town,
I need your help retrieving
one final and crucial item.
A large crate will be
arriving at the wharf
at 6:00 sharp this evening.
You will be there
upon its arrival
and immediately load
said crate into your truck.
Now, this crate is very heavy.
And what's inside is very old.
So, you must take care
as you move it.
It's one of a kind.
Do you understand me, Mr. Snow?
So far.
After you pick up the shipment,
you will then deliver it
to my new home
up there on the hill.
Do you know it?
Uh... Yeah.
Everybody knows
the Marsten House.
Once there, you are to open
the bulkhead on the side
of the Marsten House,
carry the crate
into the cellar,
past the stairs,
finally delivering it
to the back.
I'll be sure to leave
a clearing for you.
The documents
to secure the crate
can be found in this envelope,
as well as your fee, of course.
My grandma
used to tell us stories
about this place
just to set us straight.
She said Hubert Marsten
worshipped Satan.
That's why he shot his wife,
- and killed himself,
- They're just stories.
We need to bring it down there.
- In the cellar?
- That's what Mr. Straker said.
Fuck.
But I'm gonna
back the truck up
so we can get closer,
but you, uh...
You go open it up.
You want me to open it?
Fuck.
What'd you say
this was again?
Paper said dresser.
It must be
some fucking dresser.
Could we set it down now?
I can't see a goddamn thing,
and I'm starting
to lose my grip.
Shit.
Christ, Hank!
I can't see where I'm going!
It's packed with dirt.
Why would a dresser
be packed with dirt?
I don't want to know.
Uh...
Pick it up, bring it into
the back, all right? Let's go.
Jesus Christ.
Shit.
Pivot. Pivot.
All right. Set it down. Gently.
Royal.
Come closer.
Closer.
Join me.
Royal! You don't want
to know, remember?
Let's get the fuck out of here.
All right.
It's the first day of fall,
September 23rd, 1975,
and you're on the WVAB radio.
That was the latest from
from the Raspberry Brothers,
that's coming in at
number two
on our Top 25
best songs of fall.
Those boys will be playing
a Halloween special
down at Portland next month.
Be sure to get your tickets,
when they go on sale tomorrow.
Oh, Jesus!
You lost, son?
No, no. Um, sorry.
I'm just sightseeing.
I used to live around here.
Huh. Come back for a visit?
Yep.
What are you,
some kind of an author?
Yeah.
Do me a favor, would you?
Don't make any trouble
while you're here.
Trouble makes work for me.
I don't like to work.
You'll get no trouble from me.
Just here for
a little inspiration.
All right. You take care now.
Here's
last year's release from
Gordon Lightfoot
to bring a little sunset simmer
to your drive
on this gorgeous day.
♪ I can see her lyin' back
In her satin dress ♪
♪ In a room where you do
What you don't confess ♪
♪ Sundown
You better take care ♪
♪ If I find you been creepin'
'Round my back stairs ♪
♪ Sundown
You better take care ♪
♪ If I find you been creepin'
'Round my back stairs ♪
♪ She's been lookin' like
A queen in a sailor's dream ♪
♪ And she don't always say
What she really means ♪
♪ Sometimes
I think it's a shame ♪
♪ When I get feelin' better
When I'm feelin' no pain ♪
♪ Sometimes
I think it's a shame ♪
♪ When I get feelin' better
When I'm feelin' no pain ♪
See you, Robbie.
More coffee?
- Yeah, thanks.
- Here you are.
Hey, Ray.
Take a look at this.
♪ I can picture every move
That a man could make ♪
♪ Gettin' lost in her lovin'
Is your first mistake ♪
♪ Sundown
You better take care ♪
♪ If I find you been creepin'
'Round my back stairs ♪
♪ Sometimes
I think it's a sin ♪
♪ When I feel like I'm winnin'
When I'm losin' again ♪
I have all the paperwork
in order.
That's right. It's all here.
And then the last thing
left to do is for you to sign.
You look familiar.
Well, how's the book?
I'm at the point in the story
where the reader decides
whether or not
she'll ever finish it.
Uh-huh.
Can I help you with something?
Uh, a place for rent.
You know, if you've got it.
Just you?
- Yeah, it's just me.
-  Bye, bye now.
Are you sure
you want to be here?
Susan!
Who goes there? Oh!
Hello! Hey! Larry Crockett.
Nice to meet you.
Would you like some coffee?
Get a fresh pot
going there, Susie. Will you?
I have trained her
to make it just right.
Oh.
Uh, I'm okay on the coffee.
Thank you.
Uh, I was just gonna ask
your associate here--
Secretary.
Yeah, I think I saw someone
in the Marsten House
on the way in.
Is someone actually
living there now?
Oh. Well, if you know
about the Marsten House,
that should tell you
I can pretty much
sell anything.
It's been sitting vacant
for almost 40 years.
Who bought it?
Um, some European fella.
Wears these fancy suits.
He's the one opening up
that shop across the street.
How do you know
about the Marsten House?
Are you from around here?
I grew up here
till I was nine, yeah.
So maybe that's why
you look so familiar.
Uh, what'd you say
your name was?
Ben Mears.
No, doesn't spack.
Mr. Mears,
are you looking to buy?
Nope, just need
a place to rent.
Um, well, I'm sure
you're acquainted
with the beauty of Maine.
Perhaps, as an investment--
Eva Miller has
a couple rooms open.
She's over on Railroad Street.
Eva Miller. Railroad.
Got it.
Enjoy your book.
Yeah,
that went great, Susan.
Good going, Suz.
Yeah,
you just jiggle it a little
and it'll work.
I keep asking
Weasel to fix it.
Who knows, maybe
one of these days he will.
Don't count on it.
Here we are.
All right, I serve breakfast
at 7:00 sharp if you want it.
Dinner's usually
on the table by 6:00.
Your laundry day is Tuesday.
And no guests.
What is it you say
you were again?
Some kind of writer?
That's right. Yeah.
I'll take payment in advance.
Morning, Jim.
Morning.
-  Look at the new kid.
-  I think he's doing
a magic trick.
No way! There's no way.
Make it real tight.
Yeah, okay.
Ralph, I got it.
There's no way
he's gonna get out of that.
Get your watch ready.
Let me know when to start.
Is he gonna do it?
-  I don't think so.
-  No way.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
It's Richie Boddin.
- Here, let me help.
- No, don't. I can do this.
-  Come on, Mark!
- I got it.
Come on, man. Come on.
Jesus.
Welcome to the Lot, dillweed.
What are you looking at?
-  Did you see his face?
- No, stay down! Wait!
-  He's getting back up.
-  Don't do it!
No. Huh?
What is he doing?
Fucking goof!
Say "uncle."
Say "uncle" or I'll break it!
...are on different teams.
Fuck you!
These two rookies
don't know nothing...
...the kid got third
in MVP voting as a rookie.
Once more unto the breach.
Okay! Okay! Uncle!
Uncle, you win! Uncle.
Uncle, just get
the fuck off of me!
- Now say,
"I'm a big, ugly turd."
-  Okay.
Say it!
Go back to your corners.
Then, decide which one of you
is gonna tell me
how this started.
You better
watch your back.
He's new, Mr. Burke.
He doesn't know
to stay away from Richie.
Quite a way to make
a name for yourself,
Mr. Petrie.
We can walk him home later,
in case Richie
gets any ideas, sir.
Richie Boddin having an idea
is as likely as the Royal River
running backwards.
And you, Mr. Petrie,
next time you tell a man
to say uncle, and he does,
you let him go.
We take people at their word
here in the Lot.
Yes, sir.
And this will do nicely.
Come on, let's go!
He's the nice,
handsome man that comes
from a good family.
And I just don't understand
why you won't give him
another chance.
Because I didn't want
to give him
a first chance, Mother.
- Oh, but, Susan, honestly...
- Shh!
We're in a library.
Who are we discussing, ladies?
Floyd Tibbits perhaps?
Mind your business, Mabel.
You know,
he's right over there.
Floyd?
Ben Mears. The author.
You know, he actually
lived here as a boy.
I don't know
if you'll remember,
but there was that awful crash
on Halliwell Road
about 20 years ago.
Drunk driver.
Oh, what was the family name?
Anyway, it turns out,
the people that driver killed
were his parents.
Tragic. Who knows
why he'd want to come back.
But he's actually been
spending a lot of time here.
I'm pretty sure he's doing
research for his next book.
Wonder what he finds
so interesting about
a little town like Salem's Lot.
So, you ladies have
any big plans for the weekend?
Well, as a matter--
Tonight, I'm going
to the drive-in.
Shh, Susan.
Library, remember?
Now, what are you
going on about?
Mabel asked what we're
doing for the weekend.
And I said,
I'm going to the drive-in,
tonight.
By yourself?
Hmm.
I think
I should come with you.
I'm gonna come with you.
Mom, no.
Help!
Stay back, Monster!
Doesn't all this stuff
scare you?
I will fell you with
my mighty sword where you...
Stop, Ralph.
You'll break them.
It's okay.
They're pretty safe to touch
once the glue sets.
See? Take a look.
You're not afraid
of anything, huh?
Not even Richie Boddin.
Well,
I had to fight back.
Or else, he'd be on my case
for the rest of the year.
Yeah, but,
what happens
when he comes for you
with the big kids?
I hear his brother
has a switchblade.
If he comes at me again,
I'll fight back then too.
Running away makes it worse.
Oh, well, I hope
he doesn't kill you,
so we can hang out some more.
Come on. We should go.
It'll be getting dark soon,
and you know what that means.
What's it mean?
Ralphie's just scared
of the dark.
I am not.
Maybe I can help.
Here, take this.
If you blow on it,
it'll help with your breathing
and calm you down.
I learned that from Houdini.
He used to play one
to help strengthen his lungs.
Who was Houdini?
He was the most famous
and best magician of all time.
Neat!
♪ Clap for the Wolfman ♪
♪ He gonna
Rate your record high ♪
♪ Mmm... Yes, gracious! ♪
♪ Clap for the Wolfman ♪
♪ You gonna dig him
Till the day you die ♪
♪ Doo-Ron-Ron
And the Duke of Earl,
They were friends of mine... ♪
-  Come on out.
-  All right...
That's become like
a rite of passage here.
Happens every weekend.
Fancy seeing you here.
Hope you didn't pay full price.
You can only see
half the screen
from way over here.
You're practically in Yarmouth.
Yeah, I didn't think
it would be this full.
I haven't been here
since I was a kid.
Yeah, you can find
the whole town here
most nights it's open.
Probably find out more
about the town here
than down at the library.
Mabel told you about my...
My research?
Mabel tells everyone
everything.
Uh...
The sun's setting.
The show will be starting soon.
Um, I have a secret spot,
with a better view
if you want to join.
Best seats in the house.
Come on, I'll show you.
♪ ...you gonna dig him
Till the day you die ♪
♪ You might want to try
But I'm gonna keep em!♪
♪ Clap for the Wolfman... ♪
Greetings, young masters.
Are you lost?
Would you like a lift
to wherever it is
you're needed?
Uh...
Um... No, thank you.
Come on, Ralph.
Every car tells a story.
I'll catch you up.
See Mr. Zimmerman?
In the Caddy over there?
-  Yeah.
- That isn't Mrs. Zimmerman.
Over here,
Cory Bryant and Bonnie Sawyer.
Breaking up for the 10th time.
Oof.
That's Father Callahan
in the Ford,
in the corner.
Quietly getting blitzed.
Let's see,
- who else--
- What about you? What...
What's your story?
- There's no story here.
- Come on.
You're here. You work with
what's-his-name?
Only till I get
my real estate license.
Then I'm striking out
on my own.
See, that's...
That's something.
You'll run him
right out of town.
Larry?
No. He can have the Lot.
I plan on moving back
to Boston.
You were in Boston?
Yeah. Right after high school.
I only came back
to help my dad
when he got sick.
And then, he passed away
last year, and my mom
has just been
trying everything to make sure
that I do not leave her.
That's a sad story. I'm sorry.
Now you go.
Why did you come back?
Well, uh,
Mable was right.
I'm here for research.
What exactly, though,
are you researching here?
Me.
I don't really have
much of a story, either.
I've always just written
other people's stories.
Uh...
My parents died
in a car accident
when I was nine.
So, I left here to live
with extended family.
But it's always felt
like I ran away.
So...
My coming back
to Salem's Lot is like...
my way of reclaiming home.
You know?
Good evening,
folks, and welcome to
the Jerusalem's Lot Drive-In.
We want you have
the best experience
in modern cinema...
Will you stop with that?
It helps me.
I knew you'd get scared.
Why do we have to go
this way, anyway?
I told you,
I wanted to get away
from that strange man.
Ralph?
Ralph, stop!
Ralphie!
Ralph!
The master
needs a sacrifice
before he can begin
to transform your town
into his image.
It is a great honor that
I'm bestowing upon you.
Oh, Master Barlow!
Lord of Flies!
It is I, Straker!
Your devoted servant!
I have returned, master!
I bring you a sacrifice!
Ralph.
Let's feast.
Morning, Father.
Oh, well...
How bad did I get?
Three Hail Mary's.
You should be fine.
Look, I tried to take you back
to the rectory,
but you was bent on me
bringing you here.
You said it was...
Oh, hell, what did you say?
Atonement, probably.
Right, atonement.
Exactly.
Oh, thank God, I'm a Methodist.
Uh, your car is around back.
I had Nolly drive it in.
Oh, and, um...
You feeling up to it later,
you might want to
drop in on the Glicks.
The youngest boy is missing.
They're forming a search party.
Yeah. Yeah,
it's quite a world
we got here.
Only getting worse
if you ask me.
What are we supposed
to do about it, Constable?
Isn't that the question
we need to ask ourselves?
Mmm.
I ask myself plenty.
All answers
point to retirement.
It's just
the Methodist in you.
Only thing necessary
for the triumph of evil
is for good men to do nothing.
Well, you see, that's just it.
You see any good men
around here lately, Father?
Ralph?
Is Ralphie in there?
Anything?
Go back to New York, asshole.
Nobody wants your help here.
That's Floyd Tibbits.
He has a thing
for Susie Norton.
Word gets around quick here.
Matt Burke. School teacher.
You're Ben Mears, the author.
I've enjoyed your books.
They're better than
what some critics suggest.
You mind calling my publisher,
telling him that?
If you don't mind
coming around the school
and talking with the kids,
I know they'd love to meet
a real-life writer.
Sure, yeah.
Or maybe I could do some good,
push them into finance.
It's not just Floyd
with the funny looks, is it?
I mean, I wouldn't
blame 'em if they all
had a thing for Susan.
It's simple math.
You're new in town,
local boy
has just gone missing.
I'm surprised that Parkins
hasn't talked to you yet.
Well, he did.
But it was
a short conversation though,
considering I had someone
who could vouch
for my whereabouts,
at the time
of the disappearance.
Speaking of...
Hi.
I heard Parkins might
stop the search soon.
The cold reality
is settling in.
It's a shame the brother
doesn't remember anything.
Sometimes things happen
that are so terrible,
your brain won't
let you remember.
Not any time soon anyway.
Research tell you that
or experience?
Oh, my God.
So embarrassing.
Maybe she read my books.
It isn't you. It's...
Well, it is you.
But only because
you're an outsider.
She thinks that we will
run off together
or something,
and never look back.
Sounds kinda nice, actually.
Ralphie?
Ralphie!
Ralph?
Ralphie?
Danny?
I feel sick.
It's pernicious anemia.
It's a vitamin-B deficiency
that prohibits the body from
making more red blood cells.
Red cell count in
a boy Danny's age
should be around 80-85%.
Right now, Danny is at 40.
Even with the transfusions,
it's still going down.
All we can do is wait and see.
Danny! Danny, what is it?
Thirsty,
Thirsty? Thirsty. Good.
Yes. Okay.
Nurse! Nurse! Water!
My son, he's awake.
Mrs. Glick, what is it?
Oh, my God!
Go on, Mike.
Go.
Days like today are
where it's earned.
No sooner did they
lose one son, now this.
"Most merciful God whose wisdom
is beyond our understanding,
deal graciously with this
family in their time of grief."
"Surround them with your love,
so they may not be
overwhelmed by their loss,
but have confidence
in your goodness, and strength
in the days to come."
"We ask this in faith, Lord,
hear our prayer."
Oh, shit.
Oh, hell.
Help!
- Help, help!
- Oh, shit.
- Let me out!
Please! Let me out!
- Uh, hold on.
- Let me out, please! Help!
- Hold on. I'm coming, okay.
- I'm not dead, I'm alive.
Help me! Please!
- I'm coming. Hold on.
Okay.
We have time
for one last question.
Go ahead, Miss...
Becky Werts. Thank you.
So, are you
and Miss Norton dating?
Don't answer that.
I take it you're
Mabel's daughter?
Thanks, Ben.
I hope that didn't
hurt too much.
I have the sudden need to call
every teacher I ever had
and apologize.
How are the kids dealing
with the Glick news?
Same way the town is.
If they don't talk about it,
maybe it's not happening.
Here you go.
Mike?
Hey.
Mike.
You all right?
You don't look so good, Mike.
Uh...
Yeah, I think
I'm sick with something.
How long you been sick?
I'm not sure.
I passed out after a funeral,
and I'm not sure
how long I was out.
Danny Glick's funeral?
Yeah, I can't remember.
You can't remember anything?
Even the slightest of details?
I remember eyes.
Whose eyes?
What is it, Mike?
I'm real scared, Mr. Burke.
I don't want to go home.
Dr. Cody will be gone by now.
But I want to take you
to see her
in the morning, all right?
You can stay with me till then.
Sound good?
Thank you.
Thank you for inviting me over.
I feel better already.
Good.
Here.
Take these.
Oh.
Uh...
Where did you get
those marks, Mike?
On your neck.
I don't really know.
Is everything
all right, Mr. Burke?
Folks,
it's just about game time here
in the beautiful city
of Cincinnati, Ohio.
As the umpire takes the field,
we got Sammy McDonald
of the American League
behind the plate.
You're in
for a good one tonight.
This series is tied up
at two games apiece.
The Sox blew
the doors off of Cincinnati...
Let me in.
Yeah.
Yeah, just a minute.
Matt Burke is downstairs,
he's asking for you.
And he seems disturbed.
Okay. Um...
Yeah. I'll be right down.
Good evening, Susan.
Hi, Eva.
Matt?
Do you have a cross of any kind
or a Saint Christopher's
medallion?
What's going on, Matt?
I need you both to come
with me. We can talk about it
once we're there.
That's where I saw it go in.
The power must have gone out.
The lights were on when I left.
I know how it sounds.
The idea that Mike Ryerson is
some kind of, Jesus,
creature of the night.
It does sound...
Crazy?
Ben?
Mike?
I don't think he's breathing.
Shut the window.
Christ! He's cold.
They aren't there, are they?
The marks.
According to folklore,
they disappear after death,
and then the transformation
can take anywhere
from minutes to days.
What is it?
What do I do?
Let the machinery takeover.
Call Parkins. Tell him...
you saw Mike down at Dell's.
He didn't look so good.
So you brought him back here,
and he died in his sleep.
Just... don't say
a word about...
Vampires?
Well?
Well, he's definitely dead.
- Amen.
- Oh.
I knew Nolly'd be
good for something.
He's not much of a deputy,
but he's a hell
of an electrician.
What was it the Glick boy
died from again, Doctor?
Perspicuous...
It was Persimmons...
- Pernicious anemia.
- Yeah.
It's like when your body
can't make blood fast enough.
Something like that, isn't it?
Yeah, Matt.
Something like that.
Well, what do you...
You think it's some kind
of connection here?
I don't see why there would be.
It's not a disease
you can catch.
Huh.
What's your opinion, Doctor?
I'll let you know
when I have one.
Mark.
Let me in.
The window, Mark.
He commands it.
Open the window, Mark.
Master Barlow
wants to meet you, Mark.
I'll set you free, Danny.
You have my word.
Okay.
Crosses.
They can hypnotize.
No direct sunlight.
What else?
Let's see...
Have to stay in the shadows.
Guess I gotta go kill Barlow.
Mike?
Stop fighting and join us.
No.
Master Barlow wants
to meet you, Mr. Burke.
Mike, please.
I revoke my invitation!
Get out!
Hear the latest?
Try me.
That Glick kid? His mom was
found dead this morning.
Did they bring her here?
Brought her straight out
to Green's Mortuary.
All the way out there?
Why didn't they bring her
to Foreman's in town?
No one can
get a hold of Foreman.
It's been hard to
get a hold of anybody
over in the Lot these days.
Is Mike Ryerson's body
still downstairs?
Unless it got up
and walked out last night.
This is some shit.
Ah, for fuck's sake!
Matt! Hey! Hey! Matt?
Oh, Christ, my head.
No. Don't move yet.
We need to make sure
you're okay, then we can talk.
About what?
Marjorie Glick is dead
and Mike Ryerson's corpse
is missing.
You have any idea why?
The power of faith,
wooden stakes, crosses,
white roses, garlic,
all are supposed to be
deterrents for vampires.
Sounds like silly
superstitions to me.
Maybe.
Maybe so, but,
when I called Linda's Flowers
over in Cumberland earlier,
and asked for white roses,
they said they were
all sold out.
Said some well-dressed man
came in last week
and bought 'em all up.
Straker.
He must do Barlow's
bidding during the day.
And you think the Glick boys
are all caught up in this, too?
I think the first boy
was a sacrifice,
to consecrate the grounds
for Barlow's arrival.
The second boy...
Well, Mike made it sound
like he was attacked
after Danny's funeral.
There is one way
we can find out for certain
if Danny's still dead.
How?
You want to exhume Danny Glick?
Don't you?
No! No, I don't!
I don't want to do any of this.
You're sitting there
with a book about vampires
in your hand,
and the only evidence
I have is...
Is a missing body.
It's missing for a reason.
Mike Ryerson attacked me
here last night.
That's why he's missing,
because he's a fucking vampire!
What about the mother?
What mother?
Marjorie Glick. Danny's mother.
We don't need
to exhume the boy,
when the mother is laid up
over there at Green's Mortuary.
Maury said,
"Looks like she died
the same way as Danny."
We could pay her a visit.
And do what?
Wait till night comes.
We'll go.
You three go.
There's still some research
I need to do.
Wait. More research?
You seem to know
all that you need to
about vampires, Matt.
Yes, but I know very little
about Barlow and Straker.
I intend to remedy that.
So, when can I meet
this Mr. Barlow?
Ooh!
Out.
Now.
They got Danny.
I said I'd help him.
I gave my word.
Mr. Petrie, you have
no idea what you're
getting yourself into here.
Yes, I do.
They're vampires.
I can prove it.
You don't have to.
- You know?
- Yes.
Stay close.
We need another way
out of here.
Damn it! No way up.
No stairs!
- I'll boost you up.
Come on. Let's go.
- Okay.
- Higher. I can't reach it.
- Go.
Up.
Hurry up, Mark.
Door's locked.
It won't open.
Hurry! Mark,
the light, get the light.
Any...
Anything?
No.
I doubt if vampires rise
at almanac sunset anyway.
If vampires
exist at all, that is.
And what if she does rise?
What do you mean?
How will we protect ourselves?
-  Danny?
- Oh, hell!
- Danny, where are you?
- What do we do?
I'll make a cross
with these.
Danny?
It's not working.
Answer me.
This is not working!
Tape.
- Tape?
- To bind it.
- We need to bind the cross.
- In my bag.
There's some in there.
Danny, answer me.
In my bag!
-  Here. Let me see it!
- Here.
Oh, God.
-  Tape it!
- Susan, come on, hurry!
It's not working.
-  Tape it. Come on.
- It's not working!
-  Fuck.
-  Shit!
Bless it.
- What?
- I don't know!
You're the writer.
Think of something.
- Bless it!
- Uh... [sputtering] In...
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy--
Shit, it's glowing!
Bless this cross and... And...
- And...
- And?
The Lord. The Lord
is my Shepherd,
I shall not want.
He maketh me to lie down
in green pastures.
He leadeth me
beside the still waters.
He restoreth my soul.
He leadeth me in the paths
of righteousness!
Fuck!
Get her off!
Get off me! Get off!
The Lord
is my Shepherd.
I shall not want.
He restoreth my soul.
No!
No! Get her!
Get off! Get off of me!
Get off me!
Fuck! No!
Ben!
Oh, Jesus! There's no blood!
There is no blood!
There will be no one left!
Even now your circle
is smaller.
No!
Come on!
Come on, come on, come on.
Get my bag!
God!
Open that!
Here! Here!
- Okay. Come on.
-  What is it?
-  Here.
- It's a rabies shot.
A rabies shot?
It works for animal bites
if you do it quick.
Okay.
- Right here. See the vein? Go!
-  Yeah.
Get the cross.
Put it... Put the cross on me.
In the name of the Father,
the Son, the Holy Spirit,
bless this cross, and...
Thank God.
Tomorrow, we go
to the authorities.
- Parkins?
- No.
Father Callahan. The church.
Crosses, holy water, prayer...
he might be able to
help somehow.
But first, let's go find Matt.
Tell him he was right.
Stay in the car.
What? Why?
Because there are vampires
on the roof of Matt's house.
Look slowly.
What do we do?
Matt could be inside
and need our help.
We're too late.
They got him.
"Even now,
your circle is smaller."
That's what she meant.
Matt, Mike, The Glicks.
- Who knows how many others?
- Go.
Rise and shine,
young master!
There's much to celebrate.
Your town has been
most welcoming to us...
Just as Hubert Marsten
promised my Barlow long ago.
Oh, he looks forward
to meeting you tonight.
He's most capable of kindness.
It's only gonna be
a little sting and then...
nothing.
No.
No!
You do know lying
is a sin, right?
Haven't you noticed anything
out of the ordinary
in the Lot recently?
The mortality rate
has been rather high
in the Lot lately, Father.
Medically speaking, of course.
I'm in the business
of the supernatural.
In my youth, I had
my own unusual experiences.
So, you have to do a lot less
to convince someone like me.
You know, a younger priest
wouldn't have any issue
at all with this.
They view the trappings
of the church as symbolic,
rather than practical.
But I'm not young anymore.
And I am probably
a poor excuse for a priest
at this point.
But I still believe
in the awesome power
of the church.
It's a force.
And one does not
set that force
in motion lightly.
Yes?
Can I help you?
Mr. Burke.
He's one of them now.
I'm sorry, what?
One of who?
One of the vampires.
I'm gonna go after them.
I just need to get
some supplies.
Barlow, I think
he's the head vampire.
I didn't get him,
but I got his servant, Straker.
But you're, like, what? 11?
And three-quarters.
You killed Straker?
I had to.
It was the only way
I could get out.
Wait.
Show me where this happened.
Hello?
Son.
Where's the body?
Okay, fine. I'll go.
There's no stairs.
That's where I saw Barlow
get Mr. Burke.
There's a ladder outside.
Get your stakes
and crosses ready.
See anything?
Is anyone else
hearing this?
- Shit! I missed. Go! Run! Run!
-  Mark, go!
Come on. Go.
Barlow's coming for you,
your families, tonight!
Come sleep like the dead.
Ben!
Here. It has to be
through his heart.
I'm sorry, Matt.
Come on,
we need to go to Parkins.
See what he knows.
I don't expect him to help us,
but maybe he'll reach out
to someone who will.
My parents! Barlow's
coming for them tonight!
All right, we need to find them
somewhere safe.
The church.
Are they really
gonna believe what it is
we have to tell them?
Well, maybe they will
if it's coming from me.
I'll go with Mark
and we'll talk to them.
I need to warn my mom.
Get her to the church
before night comes.
Now that we know
Barlow's been watching us.
All right. I'll go with you.
Dr. Cody, you go see Parkins.
Okay.
Warn anyone else you see.
Wait. Shouldn't we all
stay together?
There's no time.
Half hour to sunset.
Oh, God! Well, let's make sure
we're all at the church
by sundown.
It's, uh...
It's protected soil.
We'll be safe there tonight.
Come on, let's go.
Ah! What's that?
- Where you going, Parkins?
- Out.
Out where?
Look, I don't want
to hear about it.
I don't want to hear any of it.
Hear what?
Vampires.
Like in all 'em comic books
down at Spencer's,
I don't want to hear it.
Well, you need to hear it
because something
needs to be done about it.
I am doing something.
I'm leaving the Lot.
And you should, too.
You coward!
This town is still alive
and you're running away.
You're supposed
to be protecting it.
It's not alive, Doctor.
That's why he came here.
Barlow.
It's dead. Just like him.
That's why he could
take over like that.
And the whole country's
going the same way, too.
You just watch.
You're giving up!
I'm surviving.
That's what I'm doing.
You'd better get going, Doc.
Things have gone bad
in the Lot now.
Mom! Mom, are you here?
- Susan?
- Mom?
- We need to leave.
- Oh, Susan.
Oh, I have
the most wonderful news.
I don't want him here.
Get him out of here now.
Okay, be quick.
What's the news, Mom?
I met an incredible man.
He promised he'd
take care of us, Susie,
and I said,
"I'd do whatever it takes."
He asked me to serve him,
and I promised to
- protect him during
the day while he sleeps.
- Mom.
- And he just--
- Who, Mom?
He owns the new
antique store in town.
Barlow.
I need you to listen to me.
We're in--
No! Susan!
You get your hands
off my daughter!
No! No! Don't leave!
Don't leave!
Bring her back!
You bring my daughter
back here!
I left a message
at the station.
He'll probably be here soon.
We need to get to the church.
Mark, go upstairs to your room.
Let the adults finish talking.
No, Dad, we need to leave.
- Mark!
- He's gonna come for you!
I understand how all of this
must sound to you.
He's gonna come for Mom,
for me, for everyone.
Mark, upstairs now!
There are others
that you can talk to,
who've seen the same things
that we've seen.
Dad, wait!
Enough, Mark.
Mr. Petrie?
No, Mr. Petrie, don't!
Don't go out there.
Who's there?
Mark.
Mom!
Oh, God! It's evil.
Help her!
No!
In the name of God,
I command you to--
Dad!
Oh, God.
Son!
Mark, run! Run! Run!
Get back!
I am a priest.
Are you?
Sad to see a man's faith fail.
Mark.
Play with us.
We just wanna play
with you, Mark.
Come on, Mark.
Let us in.
Come on, Mark. Let us in.
Mark, come play with us.
You can be just like us.
Mark!
Hang on, Susan.
Help her!
She's been bit.
God!
Get the shot!
It's okay, it's okay.
Hey, hey, hey!
You're gonna be okay.
Listen to me.
Susan, you're
gonna be all right.
Help her, goddamn it!
Get the shot!
- Susan!
- She's reacting to holy ground.
It's too late for her.
No, no, no! Help her!
It's okay. Hey, Susan.
Look at me. It's okay.
It's me.
There's only one way
to help her now, Ben.
What? What are you...
No!
No, are you fucking kidding me?
Just try, God damn it!
Just try!
Ben!
- Susan!
- No!
Ben, it's not safe!
No...
Here!
Catch!
Back off! Come on.
Back off!
Get back!
Come on.
You all right?
Susan's mom,
she's Barlow's new servant.
Mark? Father Callahan?
What about the sheriff?
He wasn't much help.
Jesus.
He left a note.
Mark?
At least, he's alive. For now.
What'd he say?
He's going to kill Barlow.
Ow.
I gave you my word, Danny.
Mark! Oh!
Are you okay?
Did you find him?
No.
Well, it looks like
you found some.
Just one.
And he found me.
Rest are all hiding.
I checked most everywhere.
Okay.
Okay, let's get out of here,
find somewhere safe.
No!
We need to fight back.
Barlow killed my parents.
He started with Salem's,
and then who knows?
If we don't do it now,
they'll come for us eventually.
Maybe they already moved on,
you said so yourself,
you couldn't find any--
No.
I don't think
it works that way.
They're here.
Somewhere.
Just has to be
a big enough place
for the whole town.
You two notice
anything else missing?
No cars.
How many of those
stakes you got?
You really think Barlow's here?
I think they're all here.
Ben, where you going?
It's gonna get dark soon!
Oh, sweet Jesus.
They're not cars,
they're coffins.
No, I can't do that.
It's not Susan, Ben.
It's just something
that looks like her.
I can do it
if it makes it easier.
Yeah.
No! Dr. Cody!
Get away from my daughter!
Run, let's go.
Barlow told me
you'd come for her.
Mark!
I'm okay! Go find Barlow!
Mark,
get to the sunlight!
Go, go, go!
No!
Mark, run!
Run, Mark, run!
You goddamn outsiders!
Thanks.
You okay?
No.
Are you?
Sun's almost down.
It's just you and me, Mark.
It's gonna be our last chance
to kill Barlow before
he moves on to another town.
There has to be somewhere
big enough for a coffin.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
Shadows, remember?
Here.
Here, let me help.
Get ready.
I got to find something
to open it with.
Ben!
Hurry!
Come on!
Fuck!
Come on. Come on.
No!
Susan.
- It's me.
- Let go, Ben.
Don't do this.
Good evening, folks,
and welcome to
the Jerusalem's Lot drive-in.
Grab those
last minute snacks
and refreshments.
Show time starts
in three minutes.
Ben! Help!
Ben!
Come here.
You think they're all dead?
Yeah.
What do we do now?
Best magician ever.
We make our escape.
♪ I can see her lyin' back
In her satin dress ♪
♪ In a room where you do
What you don't confess ♪
♪ Sundown
You better take care ♪
♪ If I find you been creepin'
'Round my back stairs ♪
♪ Sundown
You better take care ♪
♪ If I find you been creepin'
'Round my back stairs ♪
♪ I can picture every move
That a man could make ♪
♪ Gettin' lost in her lovin'
Is your first mistake ♪
♪ Sundown
You better take care ♪
♪ If I find you been creepin'
'Round my back stairs ♪
♪ Sometimes
I think it's a sin ♪
♪ When I feel like I'm winnin'
When I'm losin' again ♪