- [HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SINGER VOCALISING]
GARFIELD: Okay, time to eat.
Let's see... Open the app.
I'm gonna get
a double pepperoni pizza,
uh, order of bread sticks...
and, well, lasagne. Yeah.
Ooh! New item alert?
Jalapeño bread stick quick bites.
Huh. It might be nice to have
something in the salad family.
- [CHIMES]
- And do I want dessert? Ooh!
[CHUCKLES] I'm gonna be naughty,
butterscotch budino.
- Okay, I'm gonna have five.
- [CHIMING]
Delivery?
Goes without saying.
- Now, please.
- AUTOMATED VOICE: Mamma mia!
All right, that ought to hold me
till breakfast.
Oh, hey! Wait, are you guys
early or am I late?
No matter. I have got
a real treat for you today.
- [BARKING EXCITEDLY]
- No, not a treat for you.
- [WHIMPERING]
- [SIGHS IN EXASPERATION]
Okay.
[GROANS]
Anyway, about that treat.
Can I just say,
you will not be disappointed?
- It's a story about me...
- [DOORBELL RINGING]
...that no one's
ever heard before,
featuring someone in my life
you've never met.
I don't know about you,
but colour me intrigued.
[TRUMPETING]
Oh, yeah, drone delivery.
Welcome to the future.
You know, to really
understand everything,
I'm gonna have to take you back
to where it all began.
Mmm-hmm.
Don't want anything to take away
from the flavour of the cheese.
- [GULPS]
- [BELL DINGS]
And like every great story,
it all started...
[MAKES SUCKING NOISE]
On a dark and stormy night.
[IMITATES THUNDER]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Wait here, Junior.
I'll be right back.
[SOMBRE INSTRUMENTAL
PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUNDERCLAP]
[SOMBRE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [DOG BARKING AND GROWLING]
- [TYRES SCREECHING]
- [SIREN WAILS]
- [ENGINE ROARING]
[SNIFFING]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[ENGINE ROARING]
[HORNS HONKING]
CHORUS: ...moon hits your eye
like a big pizza pie
That's a more
- SINGER: That's a more
- When the world seems to shine
Like you've had too much wine
That's a more
-Bells will ring
- Ting-a-ling-a-ling
-Ting-a-ling-a-ling
- And you'll sing "vita Bella"
- Vita Bella, vita Bella
- [CLUCKING]
- Open wide, Jake.
- Hearts will play
Tippy-tippy-tay, tippy-tippy-tay
Like a gay tarantella
Lucky fella
[SIGHS]
- When the stars make you drool
- [GASPS]
Just like pasta fasul
Oh.
That's a more
Hi there, little buddy! Hi!
When you dance down the street
With a cloud at your feet
- You're in love
- GIRL: I'm so full.
- When you walk in a dream
- [CHUCKLES]
[PURRING]
But you know...
- You hungry, little guy?
- ...you're not dreaming, signore
- You want a little more?
- Scusami, but you see
Back in old Napoli
Oh! You are a hungry little guy.
- That's a more
- [GASPS]
That was a quick dinner,
Signore Jon.
You must have been very hungry.
Can I bring you anything else?
Uh, yes.
MAN: Grazie, grazie.
Thank you very much.
Some... lasagne?
- Si, lasagne for one.
- Uh, yeah.
You know what, no.
- Make it family-style.
- Very good.
- To go, please, Vito.
- MAN: Okay, everybody!
- What? Where'd he go?
- You all know this one!
ALL: Hey!
MAN: Stand up and sing.
Join with us!
- Oh, no! Hey!
- [MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, no, I'm dancing.
Excuse me, pardon me.
I hate this. What? Hey! Oh, no.
[CROWD CHEERING]
- CROWD: Hey!
- [GASPS]
[CROWD VOCALISING AND CHEERING]
Hey!
- [GASPS]
- WOMAN: Jon! Takeout for Jon!
- CROWD: Hey!
- Your takeout is ready,
- Signore Jon.
- Yes.
One famiglia style lasagne,
to go.
[JON EXCLAIMING]
- You eat alone too much, Jon.
- Yeah.
You should get on
the dating apps.
- There's Bumble, Tinder...
- I'm good, thanks.
Gluten-Free Singles...
- Hot Sauce Passions.
- No, I could never...
And you should spend serious
money on premium memberships.
Bye! [SIGHS]
- [SQUEAKS]
- Huh?
Oh, hey! [CHUCKLES]
Well, that was
an interesting dinner...
that you had.
Well, I guess, um...
this is where we say goodbye.
[SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, you're really cute
but I can't have pets
in my apartment.
So, I'll see you around. Okay?
Go on.
No. No, don't cry, don't cry.
Oh! Oh!
No, no, no! No. Oh, no. Oh, no.
[GASPS] Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
[SOMBRE INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
You don't have a home, do you?
SINGER: Scusami, but you see
Back in old Napoli
- That's a more
- CHORUS: Amore
That's a more
And that's how I adopted Jon.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
GARFIELD: So, I moved Jon
out of his apartment...
to this nice little two-bed,
two-bath in the suburbs.
As soon as he understood
the ground rules,
well, let's just say...
we were living the dream.
And once we were settled in,
I even let Jon get a pet.
[ODIE BARKING]
[SLURPING]
Odie became
my most trusted ally.
He was kind, gentle...
and most importantly,
my unpaid intern.
[ODIE GROANS]
Huh?
- Mmm.
- [BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[ODIE GRUNTING]
Oh, yeah, as you can see,
life here is
pretty near perfect.
Mmm. Well, yeah, except for...
Time to go to the vet!
[MICROPHONE FEEDBACK]
We're gonna need the big scale!
Does she need to announce it
to the whole office?
[GASPS]
No! Please, no! Ow! It's so hot,
it's really hurting!
Ow! Ow! Ow! [GRINDS TEETH]
[SNARLS]
And that's why we should go from
Sunday to Tuesday.
Okay. Where were we?
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Wakey, wakey, eggs and bakey.
Good morning!
[BARKING]
[MOTOR WHIRRING]
[GASPS]
What?
Where'd you get that chair?
- [PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
- Huh?
Ha!
WOMAN: I think I was meant
to be here tonight
because I was meant to meet you.
-I think we were meant to be.
- That's what I meant to say.
You had me at the word, "meant."
[KISSING]
[ODIE AND JON SOBBING]
TRAINER: We're gonna ride
like the wind!
Faster! Harder! More insane!
[GRUNTS]
Odie?
Yeah, can you put this
back to normal?
There you go,
just let the pepperoni's
healing powers work its magic.
[YIPS]
[SNORING]
You saw nothing.
[GARFIELD SIGHS]
Up until that moment,
my life was a perfect soufflé.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Little did I know
it was all about to collapse.
MAN ON HEADPHONES:
imagine yourself drifting away
on a sea of tranquillity.
There are no pets to bother you,
distract you
or max out your credit card
by excessively placing
online food orders.
[SNORING]
- [STOMACH RUMBLES]
- [GROANS]
Yeah... Sorry...
Huh? What? Who said that?
Huh? Odie, Odie? Odie!
It's time for
our midnight snack.
[GROANING]
Thank you, good sir,
your kindness will be rewarded.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[YAWNS AND GROANS]
What are we feeling
like today, huh? French?
Italian? Chinese? Cupcakes?
- [RUMBLES]
- Chinese it is.
Odie, shape everything
from the bottom two shelves
into a dumpling.
[CLANGING]
- Huh?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUNDERCLAP]
[ANIMAL SNARLING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROWLING]
[BRITISH ACCENT]
Late night snackin'.
Not good for digestion!
Odie, I'm dreamin' again.
Slap me across the face.
[ROARS]
Nope. Still dreamin'.
I must be really deep
in this one.
[THUNDERCLAP]
GARFIELD: [STAMMERING]
What do you guys...
You want money?
I don't have any money, okay?
Who carries cash any more?
I've got Jon's
credit card number memorised...
Five-5-5-2-3-8-5-7-5-5-2-1.
Did you write that down?
- Expiration code is 5-5-5.
- The cat is out of the bag!
[LAUGHS]
- [ODIE GRUNTS]
- [CHUCKLES]
I really hope
this kidnapping plan works
- or she'll put us down...
- [GASPING]
...with her insults
and cutting observations.
[GASPS] I think this is a case
of mistaken identity.
You must be looking for another
gorgeous, lovable
kitty cat, right?
[SHUDDERS]
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, where're you going?
No, no, come back, come back!
[SHUDDERING]
[BARKING]
Odie? I'll handle this.
All right, you guys.
I'm giving you
to the count of three
to get back here
and let us down.
One, two, three!
Four, five...
I am not kidding here!
[PLAYING SAD HARMONICA MUSIC]
Three hundred and eight,
309, 300...
Yeah, they're not comin'.
[GROANS] It's over.
[MUSIC ENDS]
- MYSTERIOUS VOICE: Psst.
- [GASPS]
- [ENLIGHTENING MUSIC PLAYING]
- GARFIELD: Huh?
- [HARMONICA SQUEALS]
- Am I dead?
Are you an angel?
Please, take me.
I am ready to go to that...
to that all-you-can-eat
buffet in the sky.
What? Listen, I'm going
to swing you out,
cut your ropes and drop you
safely to that landing below.
Wait, what?
That seems a tad risky.
Is there another plan
that doesn't involve
cutting a rope
over a 40-foot drop?
No time. We gotta get outta here
before they come back.
[ODIE YIPS]
[GROANS]
We need to go. Come on, Junior!
Wait here, Junior.
I'll be right back.
[THUNDERCLAP]
[GASPS]
- You!
- Hey! Junior.
Huh?
"Who is he?"
This is Vic. My "father."
Look, Junior,
I know how you might be upset.
Upset? Why would I be upset?
You only abandoned me
in an alley as a kitten.
I'm probably just overreacting!
- [BOTH GASP]
- [EERIE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREECHING]
Oh, no, not her.
- Okay, follow me, Junior.
- Oh, no, no, no.
You lost the privilege
of telling me
what to do a long time ago.
- Hello, Vic.
- [BOTH SHRIEK]
Dang it!
Scare cam! Oh, you should've
seen your faces!
[GASPS AND LAUGHS]
Okay, boys, show me!
Hello, Vic.
- [BOTH SHRIEK]
- Dang...
[LAUGHS] Post that ASAP!
[CACKLES]
Wha... [CHUCKLES]
What? Hey, Jinx!
I haven't seen you since...
Well, no hard feelings
though, right?
Oh, I don't think so.
I'm a hugger!
Part of me
wants to be mad at her
for kidnapping us,
but you gotta love her energy.
[GASPS] Where are my manners?
Chop-chop, gentlemen!
Look alive!
[GLASS CLINKS]
[GARGLING]
Mwah! Perfection.
You know, I was so delighted
that you accepted
my invitation here tonight.
Well, throwing us
in a burlap sack
wasn't exactly an Evite.
Vic, you're so quiet.
Are you feline sad?
Cat got your tongue?
Would you prefer a mew-mosa?
Excuse me,
how do you two know each other?
- Let me handle this, Junior.
- Oh, don't "Junior" me.
You may call me Garfield,
Mr Garfield, or G-Money.
- [SCOFFS]
- Okay, whatever, no G-Money.
Anyway, can somebody
please tell me what is going on?
We really don't need
to get into...
Uh, zip! I'll take this one.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[PLAYING PIANO]
- What?
- [GRUNTS]
I'm from a small town
outside London
that you've probably
never heard of.
Oh, I scratched and clawed
my way through hard times...
to come here with one dream.
- [PEOPLE CHATTERING]
- [CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
I wanted to be seen.
- I wanted to matter.
- [AUDIENCE GASPS]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
- But I was a failure.
- [TUBA BLOWING]
ANNOUNCER: The winner!
[AUDIENCE CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING]
[CHEERING FADES]
And then I met Vic and his crew.
They were outcasts,
losers, thugs.
We didn't have much,
but we had each other.
We became a real family.
[SCOFFS] Vic and family?
I know where this is goin'.
Excuse me,
garçon, uh,
when might we expect appetisers?
- Perhaps an amuse-bouche?
- And then one night...
We were about to make
our biggest score.
Enough milk
to last us for weeks.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS] Vic!
Vic!
Jinx, I tried to come back
for you.
You have to know that.
- Yes, you get an "A" for effort.
- So, what happened next?
Imagine Alcatraz...
but smellier.
- [RETCHES]
- It was cold. And lonely.
And stinky. So very stinky.
I can't overstate that enough.
But it gave me purpose.
I needed to get out.
I just needed help.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[PURRS]
[CACKLING]
So, your purpose
was to escape jail
and get involved with charities?
No. My purpose was...
revenge.
[GULPS]
Oh, I see,
I went the other way with it.
I'm kidding.
Another cat
would be bent on revenge,
but I'm... Ooh,
how would you put it?
Evolved, compassionate,
- and incredibly self-actualised.
- Bingo! [CHUCKLES]
I had such trouble finding him
and when I discovered
you were his son,
I had no choice but to kidnap
you to lure him here.
No, listen, I totally get it.
It's all part of bein'
associated with Vic.
So, what do you need from him
to make this right?
I simply want him to pay back
the quart of milk
I lost that night
- and we'll call it even.
- I can do that.
What he can't do
is raise a child.
- Just one quart.
- Done.
For every day
I was in the pound.
- What now?
- Nice twist. Well played.
How long were you
in the pound again?
Four years,
seven months and two days.
Oh! That long?
All right, I'm gonna do
the math here
in my brain.
Uh, the way you do that is...
- [CLEARS THROAT] Odie?
- [YIPS]
1,675 quarts of milk.
Exactly right, Odie.
We both came up with it
at the exact same time.
Where am I gonna find
that much milk?
Well, I suggest
you go back to the place
you double-crossed me.
- Lactose Farms.
- Wow. Well, good luck, Vic!
[CHUCKLES]
I'll leave you two to work out
the fine print.
We'll just see ourselves out.
Odie?
Uh, no.
You're all going to do this.
What? Wait, why me?
He's the one who abandoned you.
Yes, but this is more
than a one-cat job.
Yeah, but I'm sure
Vic has a whole crew
of low-life cat burglars
he could ask.
Oh, I'm sure he does.
But if I'm being
completely honest,
seeing how miserable
you make one another
brings me endless satisfaction.
Oh, well, thank you
for your honesty.
And if I don't go?
You can stay and have a playdate
with Roland and Nolan.
Okay, boys... go play!
[BOTH GROWLING]
Ma'am, I think
this is an opportunity
to take a deep,
cleansing breath...
and repeat your
anger management mantra.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Anyone else have any objections?
[GULPS] Nope, I'm good.
Thanks for the opportunity.
Excellent!
Now, you boys have 72 hours.
[GULPING]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- Or else...
I can't believe
this is happening!
I don't see you for years
and when I do,
you pull me into
a life of crime!
I had this reunion playing
differently in my head too.
Well, that's the difference
between us,
because I never wanted
to see you again!
Now, I totally
understand your anger.
But if you give me
a chance to explain
you'll see I'm not the bad guy
you think I am.
A good guy doesn't leave
his kid in an alley!
- It wasn't like that.
- It was exactly like that!
No, it wasn't.
- Let me tell you what, Junior...
- No, no!
I don't wanna hear it!
This whole thing with Jinx?
This is your mess, not mine.
Come on, Odie.
Can't let you do that.
We'll be watching you.
Like a hawk.
[HAWK SCREECHES]
[SHRIEKS]
[GROANS]
Is today a Monday?
Because it feels
an awful lot like a Monday.
It's Thursday.
- Not to me, it's not!
- Look, I know this isn't ideal,
but we have to do this.
So, let's just try and make
- the best of our time together.
- Our time together?
What are you talkin' about?
Once we get this milk,
I want you out of my life.
Forever!
All right, just relax.
Lactose Farms ain't nothing
but a sleepy little
mom-and-pop dairy.
This will be a quick
grab and go.
You'll be back home
before you know it.
[CHUCKLES]
So, how do we even
get to Lactose Farms?
It's way out in the country.
You ever jumped a train?
I've never jumped.
Look, if jump in' a train
is too hard, just say it.
- How hard could it be?
- Exactly!
- [BELL DINGING]
- Ha-ha! This is gonna be fun.
JON: [YAWNS] Garfield?
Odie? Hello?
Garfield, how many times
have I told you
to close the refrigerator door?
Ga...
Wait, there's food on the floor.
[GASPS]
He's never left food
on the floor. Garfield?
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Garfield?
Garfield? Garfield?
[TRAIN HORN BLOWING]
[GARFIELD GRUNTING]
Our best shot at jumping
on the train is here.
Hold on a sec. I'm just
taking in the wind speed,
the direction of the sun,
and various angles.
Yes, I say we jump the train
from right here.
Didn't I just say that?
I've seen it on television
a million times.
- We'll need a 100 feet of rope.
- Uh-huh, rope. Yeah, okay.
- Great idea.
- Yep.
We'll throw the rope
over that branch
- right there.
- Over the branch. Got it.
Can you follow me? All right.
And then timing it just right,
we swing over
as the train passes by
and land on top of the car.
- Boom!
- Or, we can do this!
- Odie, jump, boy!
- [YIPS]
Huh?
- [BELL DINGS]
- Uh-oh!
[YELLS]
Whoa!
[GRUNTING]
[GARFIELD MEOWING URGENTLY]
Part of me wants to help him.
No. This is how he learns.
[GARFIELD GRUNTING]
[CHUCKLES]
[GASPS AND GRUNTS]
I don't know,
it's kind of pricey.
How does it handle?
- [YELLS]
- [LAUGHS]
I'll take it!
[YELLING]
[GRUNTING]
See? I told you
this was gonna be fun.
You and I have
different definitions of fun.
- MAN: Hello?
- Oh, finally! Hello!
You've reached Find My Pet.
If your pet is lost,
we're here to help.
Hi, yes! Great, okay.
My orange tabby and my dog
are both missing
and I need your help.
Please listen carefully
as our menu options
have changed.
- Okay.
- if you'd like to hear
this call in Spanish...
- ...oprima número dos.
- What?
For Pig Latin,
ess-pray even-say.
For gibberish...
Come on. What do I press
to talk to a real person?
Your call is
very important to us.
There are 1,346 people
ahead of you.
What?
Garfield, where are you?
[TRAIN HORN BLOWING]
Okay, Vic,
you gotta figure this out.
Jinx can't be trusted
and you gotta keep Junior safe!
You just gotta figure out a way
- to get him outta this.
- [GARFIELD STRAINING]
Tell me, is it a burr? It hurts.
Ah! You pulled my hair.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
- [GROANS]
- Is it a gnat? Is it a bug?
A bug?
[SHRIEKING]
- Ow! Ow!
- Hmm?
GARFIELD: Odie, Odie!
[SHRIEKING]
Okay.
Hmm.
[CHUCKLES]
You know what, Junior?
- This is gonna be good for you.
- What'll be good for me?
What we're doing.
We're about to steal
a truck full of milk
from a dairy to pay back
a deranged cat.
What part of that is going to be
good for me?
All of it!
You can't even imagine
the life lessons
you're gonna learn.
Oh, yeah? Name one.
Well, for starters,
you already know
how to get on a moving train.
[LAUGHS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
I found it funny.
All I'm ea yin'
is that to break into a dairy,
it's going to
take a few skills...
I'm guessing a rounded,
mush-filled,
overly pampered indoor cat
like you...
doesn't have.
So, we need to toughen you up.
Toughen me up?
Hey, I know tough, Vic.
You've obviously never been
in an Olive Garden
that's run out of bread sticks.
Anyway, I'm never gonna
need those skills
- you're talking about.
- But you'll have them.
I'm never gonna
break into a dairy
or anything else, ever again.
You are missing the point.
You're going to learn
to improvise,
think on your feet,
develop moves
that'll come in handy
out there in the real world!
I wouldn't be
in the "real world"
if it wasn't for you!
True. You'd still be hanging
upside down in the mall.
- No, I would be asleep at home!
- Missing out on life altogether.
Look, I'm just a dad trying to
teach his son some skills.
Uh, no, no, no.
You can't make up for five years
- of not being around.
- Uh, yes, I can.
- No, you can't.
- I think I can.
- In fact, you can't.
- Yes, I can!
- You really can't!
- With your attitude, I can.
[GROANS] Okay, whatever, "Dad."
Wow. Great lesson. Ugh!
I'm done talking to you.
You do not know me,
you don't know
the first thing about me.
I am not pampered.
I'm not anything you think I am!
Okay. I'm just gonna say
that blanket
is not the best idea.
Ah! Fantastic, thank you.
I'll take it from here.
[GARFIELD GASPING]
Get them off! Get them off!
Get them off me!
What are you doin'?
[GASPS AND SPITS]
- What did you do?
- Cedar chips.
Spiders hate 'em.
See? Another life skill learned.
[STAMMERING] I...
I think the words
you're looking for are...
"Thank you, Pops."
No, the word
I'm looking for is...
- Ah! Here's our stop!
- Really? Where?
- [YELLING]
- [LAUGHS]
Ooh, Odie, you think
he'd see that coming.
[YELLS IN DELIGHT]
- [UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
- Take your picture.
- Yeah!
Cheese!
Yeah!
- Here you go!
- Yay!
[GRUNTING]
Quaint. Just a simple little
"grab and go."
Okay. Okay, so they've done
a few upgrades
since I was last here.
Why being so dramatic?
All we have to do
is climb the fence...
- [ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
- [SHRIEKING]
[GRUNTS]
[MUMBLING]
[GASPS] Wait. Is that Otto?
- Who?
- Otto!
Of "Otto and Ethel."
Uh... No clue
who you're talkin' about.
He's one of the mascots
of Lactose Farms.
See? On the side of the barn?
I'll bet he knows
how to get into that place.
VIC: Leave him alone.
Seems to be in a period
of meditation... or depression.
Yes, he does.
Hmm.
This calls for tact,
sensitivity, and diplomacy.
Yeah? And where are we
supposed to get that?
I have it. In spades.
Watch!
Maybe you'll learn somethin'.
Excuse me, you're Otto, right?
[GRUNTS]
[CLEARS THROAT] I'm Garfield.
- A pleasure.
- Go away.
I just wanted to say
I am a huge fan.
I have eaten everything
that has a picture
of your face on it.
I'm not that guy any more.
I even loved that recalled
provolone from a few years back.
- Junior, no.
- Yeah.
Anyways, here's the thing.
Me and my crew back there,
we're in a bit of a bind.
Got ourselves in a situation.
Long story short,
we could use your help.
[GRUMBLES] Hmm.
- You're a fan, huh?
- [CHUCKLES]
- Oh, yes! Big time.
- Then sing the jingle.
Well, I don't really
sing on command.
I'm not a circus animal.
- Sing it.
- Really?
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- Lactose Farms, Lactose Farms
We've got milks, butters
creams and cheeses
- More spirit.
- Much as you want
- As much as it pleases...
- Livelier!
Come and take a look
and see what we got
'Cause what we got
is a whole lotta lot
[SCATTING]
[HISSES]
Tasty goodness is our motto
brought to you
By Ethel and Otto!
[GRUNTS]
What was that for?
I hate that jingle.
[GROANING] You could've just
told me to stop.
Mmm.
[PEOPLE CHEERING
AND CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[SOMBRE INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
Hmm.
MAN: Let's go.
Kids are waiting.
[SIGHS]
[ODIE WHIMPERING]
Odie, come back!
Leave him alone!
He might punch you!
[SOMBRE INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC CONTINUES]
Was that Ethel?
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[ODIE WHIMPERS]
A few years back,
Old Man Lactose
was forced out of business.
The corporation that took over
separated me from my Ethel.
[DOOR SLAMS]
- Ethel!
- ETHEL: You are my day!
OTTO: You are my night!
I was put out to pasture.
[KIDS LAUGHING]
She was put on display
as part of the tour.
I tried to get in there
to break Ethel free...
but they stop me every time.
Now, I only see her six seconds,
twice a day.
We... We feel you, Otto.
Come on, let's go, Junior.
We'll find another way
to break in there.
What... What could you possibly
want from that place?
You know,
a couple quarts of milk.
Couple thousand quarts.
Mmm. Good luck.
We'll take any helpful hints
you have.
Pass.
I'm telling you,
it's a life-or-death situation.
Then I hope you've notified
your next of kin.
What if we can get Ethel out?
Or get you a commemorative pin?
Where are we gonna find
a commemorative pin?
- [DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- Now, pay attention.
Here's the perimeter
of the plant.
And here are the two places
you need to go.
First, the truck
with your milk is back here.
[BELL DINGS]
And this delicate buttercup
is my Ethel.
My North Star,
and reason for living
is being kept by those
barbarians in... a petting zoo.
Located here.
- This cricket...
- [SQUEALS]
...represents
the electrical room...
this snail,
the refrigeration room...
this toadstool
is the loading dock
where you'll find the keys
to the trucks.
Wait, what's the pine cone?
The pine cone is the cheese
and butter room.
Ooh, cheese is my love language.
Now, for this briefing,
I've done a quick reading
of your personalities
and have chosen tokens
to represent each of you.
- Oh!
- You are the majestic bullfrog.
[CROAKS]
Oh, yeah, that feels right.
You are the curious
and clever chipmunk.
- And you...
- Wait for it...
...are roadkill.
Huh? What?
Oh. [CHUCKLES]
No, I get it.
That's a good one, Otto!
Giving your new
best friend roadkill.
Seriously, though,
what's my real token?
That is your real token.
Now, if you have any chance
of succeeding...
Wait, can I... Excuse me, can I
switch to something living?
- Like the snail or the cricket?
- You should've spoken up sooner.
At this point, it would be
too confusing to switch.
Sooner? But you just told me
this five seconds ago.
- Come on, Roadkill, focus.
- Really?
You give Vic
the majestic bullfrog.
You give Odie the curious
and clever chipmunk...
and then you give me,
your new bff, roadkill?
I mean, it feels disrespectful,
not gonna lie.
What makes you think he's dead?
My eyes.
I have eyes and can see.
It's a possum.
They're masters at playing dead.
Well then,
little Daniel Day-Possum here
should do Shakespeare
in the Park!
Things aren't always
what they seem.
You're right.
But in this case, they are.
What's the big deal?
Possums play dead.
Do they, Otto?
Do they play dead?
Do possums play possum,
is that what they do?
Yes. Possums are very clever.
Yeah, I'm sure he was
until the day
he ate a pick-up truck!
Uh, just ignore him.
Please, continue.
I'll just put this back
where you had it.
The straightest line
to the loading dock
is through the snail here,
then the cricket, there,
cut through the toadstool
and onto the rock.
Each of these rooms
have their own set
- of unique challenges.
- Well, why can't we just go
straight through the pine cone?
You don't want to
go through the pine cone.
Looks like the straightest shot
is through the pine cone.
You like walking
with those feet, do you?
You a fan of unimaginable
pain and misery?
Then go through the pine cone.
Stay away from the pine cone.
Got it.
Once you're inside
the facility...
[SPY MUSIC PLAYING]
You will enter
the electrical room.
There you will locate
the air vent.
Pop the grate and climb up.
Then, you'll crawl through
a maze of vents and drop down...
[CROAKING]
...to the refrigeration room.
Next, you will need
to hurl your body
over a 30-foot drop...
to a series of hand rungs.
You'll propel yourselves
hand-over-hand...
and drop down
directly into a loading dock.
From there, you'll locate
the keys to the milk truck.
Drive that truck to the west
pasture of the complex,
cut the lock on the gate.
And find the closest thing
we have
to an angel here on earth.
You'll escort my sweet Ethel
onto the truck
and drive her to freedom.
[MUSIC ENDS]
It's going to take mad skills
to get that milk,
and free my dear, sweet Ethel.
Clearly, this one is qualified
for the mission.
But I have some serious doubts
here about all of... this.
- He's pointing to you, Roadkill.
- Hmm.
- Let's get to work.
- [ODIE GRUNTS]
Stupid roadkill.
Hey! I'm workin' here!
Ugh. Definitely a Monday.
MAN ON PHONE: Your call is
fairly important to us.
If you've lost a cat,
please press one.
- If your cat is orange...
- Yeah.
...please press two.
This doesn't really
accomplish anything...
- [GASPS]
- but gives you the false sense
that we're engaged with you.
[WHIMPERING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
OTTO: All right, gentlemen,
I've made a list of skills...
that you'll need
to master in order
to break into Lactose Farms.
Number one,
develop lightning-fast reflexes.
You tell Garfield
there's a plate of pasta
on the other side of that wall
and you will see
lightning reflexes.
Yeah, no, no, no.
Depends what kind of pasta.
This pebble represents danger
you may encounter.
You need to grab it,
before it grabs you.
[SCOFFS] It grabs me?
Snatch the pebble from my hand.
- Too slow!
- Ow!
What was that for?
Being able to grab
the pebble could be
the difference
between life and death.
All right,
let me try that again.
[STRAINING] Ha! Got it!
[GRUNTS]
Now what was that for?
It's never
just about the pebble.
Come on, Junior,
everyone knows that.
Your head's got to be
on a swivel at all times.
Gotta be ready for anything.
I was ready.
He changed the game.
Sounds like
someone's making excuses!
[CLANGING]
And what was that
about being ready for anything?
You were distracting me!
Might I suggest putting
your head on a swivel?
You should have
seen that coming.
Toes on the line!
Guard your grill!
Cover your stomach!
There are surprises
around every corner
at Lactose Farms.
You need to stay alert!
Too slow! A baby could have
seen that coming!
Too slow! Too slow!
[SODA CAN POPS]
Too slow!
You'll never make it
through Lactose Farms
if you can't survive
this training!
Are you for real?
What kinda dairy is this?
The kind of dairy that requires
teamwork to survive!
Danger could be
anywhere, gentlemen!
[GRUNTS]
You've got to be ready
to outrun it.
[BOTH YELL]
[GASPING AND GRUNTING]
- [TRAIN HORN BLOWING]
- Here comes the pain!
- Left, right, left, right.
- You're confusing me!
[BOTH GASPING AND GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
[SHUSHES]
[CRASHING]
[BOTH GROANING]
I think I'm gonna need rehab.
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS WEARILY]
If this is going to work,
these two have to be
on the same page.
I'm out of ideas.
You got any?
Can't believe I'm out
in the middle of nowhere
getting beaten up
against my will
by a former celebrity steer.
Odie? Will you tell my son
to please stop whining?
Odie, can you tell Vic
that I collapsed
on this tree first
and that he needs
to find another one?
Odie, can you tell my son
that I will gladly
find another one
when I get the feeling
back in my legs?
Odie, can you tell my father
that he wouldn't be
lying in pain
if he led a better life
and didn't create
problems for himself?
Could you please
inform my son
that he should focus
on fixing his own issues?
Odie? What?
- Odie? What'd you do?
- [SCOFFS]
After all
I've let you do for me.
Ooh. What is this?
Hey, watch it!
[SNICKERS]
What's the problem, Vic?
Is this bothering you?
[GRUNTS]
[STRAINING] No.
In fact, I don't mind it at all!
I don't mind it either.
- [STRAINING]
- Ow!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
I could watch this all day.
- Stop pulling.
- I'm not, you're pulling!
If I was pulling,
you would know it!
Why does everything you do
always end up hurting me?
Hurt you?
All I ever did
was try to help you.
You sure?
'Cause every time you're around,
it ends up with me in pain. Ow!
Odie! These ropes
are not funny any more! Ow!
[LAUGHS]
Maybe, if you were a little more
open to seeing me,
things might be
better between us.
You do remember you were the one
who left me in an alley, right?
You don't know
what you're talkin' about.
Then please, enlighten me.
[SIGHS WEARILY]
This is about to get real.
Oh, that's right.
You're normally never around
to actually defend yourself.
No back door
to slink out of this time.
First, you abandon me,
then years later,
you pull me
into a life of crime.
Well, classic "Father of
the Year" stuff, "Dad."
You know,
why would I ever think
that seeing you
could be anything
other than a train wreck?
I did not leave you
in that alley!
Oh, you did!
You told me you'd come
right back. You never did!
No. That is not what happened.
Oh, please! You were probably
on the run from someone
- like Jinx and I was in the way.
- No.
No, that, that night...
[SIGHS]
That night was different.
[SLOW PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
- [PEOPLE CHATTERING]
[STOMACH RUMBLES]
WOMAN: Hey! Shoo, shoo!
Get outta here!
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROWLING]
[VIC SHRIEKS]
[DOG BARKING]
[DOOR OPENS]
Wait here, Junior.
I'll be right back.
Oh! Hey, get outta here.
Hey, how you doing? Yeah.
I had to shoo a cat.
Yeah, yeah,
diggin' in the trash. Yeah.
So, what'cha up to now, huh?
Still takin' it easy?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, no, you're kiddin'. Really?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's been raining here
for a while now. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah! I'll see you then.
Okay, bye.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Subtitle | www.movieddl.me
- [PEOPLE SINGING AND CHEERING]
- [GASPS]
[PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SAD INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I...
I never knew.
I know, how could you?
Why didn't you ever come
visit me?
I did. [CHUCKLES]
Million times I...
came to knock on your door
and I'd see what a great life
you had with Jon.
So, I just...
thought it was better
if I kept my distance.
I sense a positive breakthrough
in your relationship.
Am I wrong?
Good.
After an extensive evaluation,
I have concluded
that you two are,
in fact, ready to move forward
- with this mission.
- VIC: We are?
GARFIELD: How is that
even possible?
Mathematically, it isn't.
But given your present levels
of incompetence
and overall lack
of basic skills,
I have determined
it would take roughly...
seventeen years to get you both
properly ready for this job.
And since we have...
less than 48 hours,
you've passed.
Congratulations.
[ODIE GRUNTS AND YIPS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[JINX HUMMING "ALOUETTE"]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[CACKLING]
ROLAND: Um...
She's really losin' it.
Ugh!
[SIGHS IN EXASPERATION]
Yes, what is it?
They're ready to rob the dairy.
Perfect.
Oh, everything is going to plan.
Now, it's time to make a call.
Excuse me, you keep that thing
in your folds?
That is so disgusting.
You. You dial the number
and put me on speaker!
- [BEEPING]
- [LINE RINGING]
WOMAN: Hello?
- Hello? Lactose Farms?
- How may I help you?
It's come to my attention
that there'll be
an attempt to rob
one of your
dairy trucks tomorrow.
It's not important who I am
or how I came to know this.
Just think of me
as a concerned citizen
intent on fulfilling
my civic responsibility
as well as...
Miaow, miaow, miaow.
[MIAOWING CONTINUES]
Uh, Chief?
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- We may have a situation.
- Well, okay then.
Let's go have a look-see.
JINX: Miaow, miaow, miaow.
[CONTINUES MIAOWING]
This is the third time
they've called.
It just sounds like some cat
prank callin' us.
If it were a dog barking,
I'd be on board for a prank.
Them dogs are born for mischief,
they just are.
Not cats. Oh, no.
Cats mean business.
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEEPING]
JINX: Miaow, miaow, miaow.
[DISTORTED VOICE] "I repeat,
there will be an attempt
"to make off with one of your
milk trucks tomorrow.
"I suggest you take
appropriate measures
"to prevent this brazen thievery
from occurring.
"Okay, I'm done.
Hang up the phone.
"Ha, ha.
What an evil genius I am."
[CALL ENDS]
Well, then, still seem
like a prank to ya?
- That last part did a little.
- What's our next move, Chief?
Our next move is for me
to go back to my office
and formulate an ingenious plan.
And you go get my car waxed.
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, well, well,
would you look at that,
Margie Malone?
We're having company tomorrow.
I guess I better take out
my finest china
to serve a heapin' plate...
of justice.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
What are those for?
For us to communicate
once you're inside...
the belly of the beast.
- [SNARLS]
- Uh...
Okay. Don't we need something
more like radio headsets?
[SCOFFS] Indoor cat.
These are better.
It just feels like Bluetooth
would be better.
These are better than Bluetooth.
These, these are better
than Bluetooth?
They're equal.
And I don't have to pay
for the brand.
[STATIC CRACKLES]
Gold Eagle to Chipmunk.
Do you copy?
[YIPS]
Of course, you can hear him.
He's standing
three feet away from you.
Oh, I see you sprung
for the binoculars.
Now, we just need to find...
a way in.
Anyone ever told you
that you take
a lot of dramatic pauses
when you speak?
Yes.
[GROANS]
- [PEOPLE CHATTERING]
- [HORN HONKING]
Hey, wait up!
- GIRL: Look at that!
- Bingo.
[TRUMPET BLOWING]
Hello, everyone!
And welcome to the one
and only Lactose Farms!
If you will all
gather around me,
we'll begin our tour
and head into the heart
of the farm.
MARGE: I know you're here.
I can feel it.
Show yourself.
WOMAN: Today you will discover
the answers
to all of your
dairy questions,
including the most asked
dairy question of all time,
are curds the whey?
[PEOPLE LAUGHING]
OTTO: Bullfrog, Chipmunk,
Roadkill, do you copy?
Are you kidding me?
They actually work?
You should take this to
Shark Tank.
Now, remember,
the only way to get the keys
to the milk truck
and free Ethel undetected
is by sticking to the path
I mapped out for you.
If you deviate from that path,
you will trigger security
and all bets are off.
Understood?
All right, look alive.
The electrical access door
should be coming up
on your left.
WOMAN: Okay, this way! [LAUGHS]
Hey, hey, look! There it is!
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, we're in.
Continue through
and locate the air vent
at the end of the hallway.
That will take you
to the refrigeration room.
WOMAN ON PA: Factory workers,
your 15-minute break begins now.
[ALL SQUEAL]
- [BUZZER SOUNDS]
- [CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[WHISTLING]
Ugh! Oh, your feet
need a deep rinse.
[YIPS]
[GARFIELD STRAINING]
- What's the hold up, Junior?
- How do you get through this?
You're bigger than me.
[STOMACH RUMBLES] Am I?
- Yes!
- Well, the vent doesn't agree.
- Try sucking in your gut.
- I am.
Try sucking in your butt
and your gut.
[ALL YELLING]
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
[ODIE YIPS]
Bullfrog, what's happening now?
[BOTH PANTING]
We fell out of a vent...
into a room that looks like
- it's full of heavy machinery.
- OTTO: Son of a cud.
You're in the pine cone.
Jiminy Davis!
The perp is a cat!
And this one looks like it could
eat us out of business.
Oh, Vic, Vic!
Look, there's the loading dock.
- No! Junior! Don't move.
- What? Why?
We're in the middle
of the pine cone!
Otto told us
to stay out of the pine cone.
Oh, stop. There's no pine cone.
Otto's a bit of a worrywart.
I can walk to the loading dock
from here.
- [GASPS]
- VIC: No...
Junior!
[MUNCHING]
Mmm! Oh!
Cheddar.
Probably one of my top 26
favourite cheeses.
GARFIELD: Mmm-mmm.
What do you think happens
when that gets to zero?
[ALARM BUZZING]
[GASPS]
OTTO OVER HEADSET: Bullfrog,
what's happening now?
Roadkill got carried away
into the pine cone!
Listen to me.
You have to carry on
with the mission.
Get to the loading dock
before the workers
return from their break
or you'll miss your only chance
to get that truck.
- [GASPS]
- [YELLS]
No, no, no.
No, no, no!
[SHRIEKS]
WOMAN OVER PA:
Shred sequence initiated.
[GASPS]
[ODIE BARKING]
Odie! Oh, thanks, buddy,
but I'm pretty full
from the cheddar.
- [YIPPING]
- Oh? Jump off.
Yeah, yeah, good idea.
[GRUNTS]
Oh, good. He's safe.
Oh, hang on. Wait.
Where am I going?
Fondue. Fondue!
[SHRIEKING]
[BARKING]
[GRUNTS AND GASPS]
[SHRIEKING]
[GASPS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[BARKING]
[SCREAMING]
[GASPS AND SCREAMS]
VIC: Junior.
[GASPING] Hot, hot, hot!
Hot, hot, hot! Hot!
[BOTH SHRIEK]
[YELLING] Junior!
[GROANS]
[SIGHS IN RELIEF]
Whoa-oh!
That was too close even for me.
[PANTS]
Thanks.
I couldn't let you
have all the fun.
- WOMAN OVER PA: Workers...
- What?
...your break ends
in five minutes.
Okay, Otto,
we're in the loading dock.
Where are the keys?
OTTO: They should be hanging
on a pegboard on the far wall.
[BARKS]
What do you mean
we have a problem?
- [BARKS]
- Ah!
- GARFIELD: Pegboard's empty!
- Empty?
Now would you look at this?
Three misguided stray pets
trying to steal a truck o' milk.
Never a dull moment
at this dairy, is there, Margie?
Well, you're looking for these,
aren't ya?
Well, here you go then.
So, how's this
gonna play out, fellas?
The easy way or the hard way?
And just so you know,
I'm up for either.
- Follow my lead.
- Huh? What?
[ENTHRALLING INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANS]
[NECK CRACKING] Who's next then?
- [YELLS]
- [BOTH SHRIEK]
Otto, a security guard
has the truck keys!
Crazy eyes?
Tragic sense of fashion?
Yeah. How did you know?
Marge Malone.
-Ethel!
- Otto!
She's not just my nemesis,
she's also my enemy.
Love to hear about it,
but right now,
- what do we do?
- Get those keys.
I'll create a distraction
so you can get out of there.
- Come here, you!
- [GASPING]
[ODIE WHIMPERS]
Did you see that?
That's indoor cat style!
[GRUNTS]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[SHRIEKS]
[GRUNTS]
MARGE: No, no, no.
You're not getting away.
I've already called the pound.
Your days of thievery end today.
[BUZZER SOUNDING]
WOMAN OVER PA:
Attempted perimeter breach.
Otto.
- Junior, sorry about this.
- Sorry? For what?
[ALL GRUNT]
[GRUNTS]
Vic?
What are you doing?
Vic! Don't you go.
Vic!
Please!
Send security
- to the loading dock.
- [STATIC BUZZES]
[ENTHRALLING
INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[YELLS]
[GASPS]
Otto!
[TYRES SCREECH]
You do not want to try me
today, mister.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROARING]
[OTTO YELLING]
Get him!
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[TYRES SCREECH]
[PANTING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[ENTHRALLING
INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[ALARM BUZZING]
- [YELLING]
- [TYRES SCREECHING]
Phew!
Welcome back... Victor.
Hey, Jinx.
Why are you here?
I... I was bringing this to you.
Were you? Really?
Yeah, of course I was.
That's what we agreed to, right?
Mmm.
[VIC SIGHS]
- So, you and me square now?
- [CHUCKLES] Not quite.
There's still the matter
of those five years
I lost because of you.
What?
But I thought this settled that.
[LAUGHING]
It was never about the milk.
It was about you getting caught
trying to steal it
and being sent to the pound
like I was.
You see, Vic,
I needed you to suffer
like I did.
Oh.
I see.
And I'm guessing
you have an idea
about how that should happen.
As a matter of fact, I do.
I can't believe he did that.
He ran out, and he left me.
Again.
I thought he'd changed,
but it was...
it was a lie.
All of it.
- [MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SIGHS]
How could I have been so stupid?
[SIGHS]
MAURICE: Oh, come on, kid.
Don't beat yourself up.
Vic, man,
we've all been burned by Vic.
ALL: Yeah, that's right.
Burned every cat I know.
[ALL CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Oh, yeah, the one thing
about Vic you can count on
- is that you can't count on him.
- Tell me about it.
CAT: Yeah.
MAURICE: Yeah,
I'll tell you about it.
Long story short, we all used
to run in a pack
until we had to kick him
out the crew.
[CATS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Like I said,
couldn't count on him.
Sounds about right.
He'd leave
in the middle of a job
just to go see his kid.
Yeah, he said
he wanted to check up on him.
Make sure he was doing okay.
But get this,
he'd never actually visit.
He'd just sit across the street
from his kid's house
in a giant oak tree.
- That never happened.
- He'd watch that kid eat...
- and eat and eat...
- ALL: ...and eat...
- He put a notch in the bark...
- ...and eat, and eat, and eat.
- ...every time he was there.
- Yeah. Sure, he did.
He'd go every Sunday night,
rain or shine.
Said that it was his kid's...
ALL: ...family dinner night.
[CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Okay, hate to tell you guys...
I guarantee
that never happened. Okay?
You all fell for another one of
Vic's lies. We all have.
Because that's
what he does best.
[ODIE BARKING]
Odie? Odie!
How did you get out?
Quick, pick the lock on my cage.
- Garfield, there you are!
- [GASPS]
Jon! Oh! Take me away
from all this.
You can't imagine
what I've been through.
- You want this one too?
- Oh, yes, I do.
- I was hung upside down.
- You sure he's yours?
He didn't have a tag.
- I jumped a train.
- Yeah. He has a tag.
Huh? I have a collar and a tag?
How long have I had those?
Okay. I'm just gonna
need you to hold.
I will not hold!
I am done holding!
The Jon who was on hold is dead.
Do you understand?
[UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
That's right. I'm back, baby!
I was just talking about you,
wasn't I?
Oh! I've missed you too.
WOMAN ON TV:
Coochie coochie coo!
Pooky!
I have a lot to tell you.
You're never gonna believe it.
Crazy stuff happened.
I slept outside, twice!
I know. Me.
Oh! And I got you
this commemorative pin.
- JON: Dinner time!
- [GASPS]
Talk later.
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ah!
JON: Say when.
Never, Jon.
Bury me in cheese.
JON: I have two more
in the freezer.
- Let me know when you want 'em.
- [BELL DINGS]
I'm gonna go check on dessert.
Oh, I apologise in advance.
The eating you're about to see
will not be pretty
and if you have
young children,
this would be a good time
for them to leave the room.
Mmm-hmm!
[SLOW INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
CAT: He yd just sit across
the street from his kid's house
in a giant oak tree.
[STOMACH RUMBLING]
I know, I know.
We're coming back.
I just need to check
something out first.
[SLOW INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TYRES SCREECHING]
CAT: He put a notch
in the bark...
every time he was there.
[GRUNTS]
[STRAINING]
"He left a notch."
[SIGHS]
Yeah, right.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING]
He was here.
He saw me grow up.
[ODIE BARKS]
Oh! Ow!
Wow, that really stings.
I don't know
why I didn't think it would.
Give me a second.
[PANTS]
Vic loves us!
Me first, of course,
but then you too!
But me, a lot, and first!
[SCOFFS]
Wait, but if he loves me, us,
why would he let me, us,
get captured at the dairy?
Unless... [GASPS] He wanted
- us to get captured!
- WOMAN: Hey!
- Yes!
- Hey, watch it!
He knew that Jinx wasn't gonna
let him off the hook.
But if we got caught,
- we'd get sent to the pound...
- [HONKS]
...and Jon would come to get us!
Don't you see, Odie?
- He was trying to save us!
- MAN: Losers!
We have to go save my dad.
And here's
your favourite dessert,
Mount Candy-toa!
Uh, guys?
[RUMBLING]
- [EXPLODING]
- [GRUNTS]
Oh! Come on!
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
What is this?
[BOTH GASPING]
[GASPS] Half a star
for Mamma Leoni's?
[GROWLS] She's a monster.
[YIPS]
She's gonna tie him up...
take him on a train...
- [JINX CACKLING]
- [GASPS]
She's going to throw him off
the Mile High Bridge!
We're gonna need help.
Who can we call?
Hmm!
- Ah!
- [GASPS]
Ugh! You've got
a lot of waxy build-up.
What's your Q-tip routine?
- [GROANS]
- You're right, you're right.
We can deal
with that situation later.
Hello? Hello?
Is anyone there? Hello?
[GROANS]
OTTO: Get off the line.
This acorn
is for emergency use only.
Otto! Otto, please, listen.
I wanna make good
on our original deal,
but...
but I need a favour first.
Otto, are you still there
or are you taking
a dramatic pause?
I'm listening.
[TRAIN HORN BLARING]
Hmm.
You know, Vic,
you only have yourself to blame
for this.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Right. Look,
there's got to be some way
for me to make this right.
I mean, I know
we can think of somethin'.
Oh, there is, and you will.
[MUSIC INCREASES IN TEMPO]
[THUNDERCLAP]
[HORN BLARING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
So, once I get on the train...
I untie Vic and we jump off
right as
the train gets to the bridge.
Correct. Chipmunk
will be waiting for you.
[OVER RADIO]
Confirm your status, Chipmunk.
[BARKS]
If you don't jump right as
the train gets to the bridge,
you'll miss the net.
Got it. It's getting close.
Have you considered
throwing a rope over a branch
and just swinging
onto the passing train instead?
You watch too much TV.
I've never watched TV.
Well, this way is much better
than your rope idea.
Better than the versatile,
reliable rope?
Look, I've studied the science.
I know what I'm doing.
And you think you can battle
these villains on your own?
Oh yeah. I have a plan. Odie?
Make the order.
[YIPS]
[BEEPS]
Now get ready to fling me
in the direction
of that moving train.
[GRUNTS]
- Get ready.
- [HORN BLARING]
If I don't make it back...
tell my story. Now!
Roadkill! You're too high!
You're gonna miss it!
No, no, this is how you do it!
It's called
the ricochet approach!
Ooh! [LAUGHS WICKEDLY]
It won't be long now.
I can't tell you
how excited I am
for what's about to happen next.
[GRUNTING]
Dad! I'm here to rescue you!
No, no, no, Junior!
- Get outta here!
- I'm gonna untie you,
and we're gonna
jump off the train!
- No! Just leave me and go!
- I didn't come this far...
just to turn around,
let me untie you!
- You're ruining everything!
- [GASPS]
Quick, this way!
[JINX YELLING]
Oh, you half-wit! Get them!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNARLS]
[GRUNTING]
[STRAINING]
[BOTH GASPING]
The bridge is comin' up!
We gotta get to the caboose now!
- What? Why?
- Just follow my lead!
Wow!
- Ha! [LAUGHS]
- [BOTH GASP]
Oi, kitty cat!
Did you expect
to take us on all by yourself?
No. I brought... takeout.
- [DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Huh?
Huh?
[HEROIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[HISSES]
Ah-ha!
[GRUNTS]
I never understood
the purpose of salad
until this exact moment!
[GRUNTING]
- [DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GASPS]
Go, go! Now!
Get after him!
[SNARLS]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS] Huh?
[CHUCKLES]
Ow!
Yeah, in case
you were wonderin',
I do my own stunts.
Me...
and Tom Cruise.
[SNARLING]
Junior!
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHS]
JINX: Stop him!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
Now that's amazing!
I can't feel my tongue.
OTTO: Roadkill!
Are you at the caboose,
ready to jump?
[GASPS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Dad! Dad!
Jump, Junior! I'll catch you!
[YELLING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLING]
[BOTH GASP]
[HORN BLARING]
[GASPS]
What do we do now?
We do this!
[YELLING]
[GASPS]
See ya, everyone.
The net's too tight!
Roadkill, the net is too tight!
I heard!
- [SHRIEKS]
- [YELLING]
Hello again, welcome back!
Now, where were we?
[VIC GRUNTS]
No, no!
Don't throw them over just yet.
- No!
- [STRAINING]
I want to find the perfect place
for them
to make the biggest splat.
Hey, hey! Junior!
Junior, Junior.
Get ready! Almost there!
I'm sorry
my rescue didn't work out.
- No, you gave me another chance.
- [SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
That's all that matters.
Now, now! Drop them now!
Huh?
What are you waiting for?
Their love for one another
indicates that
despite their
current circumstance,
they are at peace.
- Because they are together.
- So?
If the point of your revenge
was to hurt them,
it has done the opposite.
It's actually textbook irony!
And we're no longer
comfortable with your plan.
[GRUNTS]
You two
are still as weak as you were
when I found you
snivelling in the pound.
"Ooh, no one will adopt us.
"I never grew into my folds.
"I hide behind them
because I'm socially awkward.
"Please, somebody love me
"even though I can't sit still
for more than ten seconds
and have the attention span
of a bloody goldfish!"
We did everything
you ever asked of us.
I even spoke
with this ridiculous accent
to make you feel more at home.
But no more!
[NEW YORK ACCENT]
I'm New York, loud and proud!
I love myself the way I am
and I'm a big, brave, boy, baby!
And I've been
working on my attention span.
[GASPS] Is that
a hot-air balloon?
[GROANS] You two...
are...
Worthless!
[YELLING]
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[GRUNTS AND SCREAMS]
[ALL YELLING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [GASPS]
[ALL GASPING]
Might I just say as someone else
with a zaftig figure,
you have a beautiful body, sir.
[ALL GASP]
Oh, dear!
[ALL YELLING]
Rope. Versatile. Reliable.
There's something
about your cadence
that really throws me,
but thank you.
[JINX YELLING]
[JINX MIAOWS]
[GRUNTS]
[STRAINING]
[LAUGHING]
Tee-hee!
Tossing me off the train?
Did not see that coming.
Well, when you live in the wild,
you gotta keep your head
on a swivel.
Right.
It's basic Outdoor Cat 101.
And that had bird poop on it.
Hey. You good, Roadkill?
Not quite.
There's one last thing
to take care of.
Cut to...
[TYPEWRITER CLACKING]
GARFIELD: It was
a dark and foggy night.
The air was damp
and heavier than a broken heart.
On nights like this,
you can't swing a cat
without hittin' shady characters
makin' shady deals
all over town.
Oh, but this night
was going to be... different.
Justice was about to be served.
With a helping
of retribution on the side.
Is that... [CLEARS THROAT]
the package?
[ELECTRONICALLY ALTERED VOICE]
It is.
Then we have a deal.
[WHISTLES]
No one will come
looking for her?
Nope. I did what you said.
I burned her paperwork.
And then shredded it
and burned it some more.
It's like she never existed.
Except for the image of her face
on millions of dairy products.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[BELL DINGING]
[IN NORMAL VOICE] This...
[RASPY VOICE]
never happened.
Agreed.
- [GROWLS]
- Oh, save it, Cat Fancy.
I know you planned
the milk truck heist...
and then tried to throw those
innocent cats off a train
to cover it up.
The boys told me everything.
[GASPS]
Mmm-mmm-mmm.
[GROWLS]
Oh! [GASPS]
Otto! Oh!
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
You are my day.
You are my night.
["LET'S GET IT ON" PLAYING]
[MOOING]
[SLOW INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh...
[SIGHS] Well, this is us.
Right. You're home.
- Hey, listen, I'm sorry.
- I just want to say I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
For misjudging you.
Oh.
Well. Thanks.
Well, I just wanted to
apologise to you for...
Everything bad that happened
to us the last three days?
You know, you had your hand in
a few bad decisions
back there too, but...
[SIGHS]
Yeah, I'm sorry for
dragging you into my world.
This is where you belong,
here with Jon and...
What's your name again? Odor?
Huh? [SNARLS]
[YIPS]
- So... uh, yeah, I should go.
- Yeah, yeah.
I mean, unless...
you'd want to come in?
Nah. No, no.
I don't think that would work.
- You know, I'm an outdoor cat.
- Right. Sure. Sure.
- No, I just... I figured that...
- No, no, no, I get it.
But, you know what?
I got this thing on the other
side of town I gotta go do so...
No. I'm very busy too. Yeah.
See you around then?
You know where to find me.
- In the kitchen.
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, take care.
And remember,
[IMITATING OTTO]
"stay out of the pine cone."
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[BARKS AND GRUNTS]
What? You heard him.
It's for the best.
Mmm-mmm.
- [GASPS AND GRUNTS]
- [YIPS]
[JON GASPS]
You're back?
What is going on? Are you okay?
I was so worried!
You know, I was gonna
add more locks to the door,
you know, try to keep you in,
but then I thought, "Well,
"what if they wanted
to be outdoor pets?"
Do you wanna be free-range?
[BOTH GRUNT]
I really missed you guys.
And I gotta say...
it's great to be together again,
the whole entire family.
You have no idea what the last
few days have been like.
Phone calls,
and hold times and tears.
- [YIPS]
- And more tears.
Don't give me that,
I asked him to stay.
- Mmm-mmm!
- He wanted to leave!
You heard him,
he said he had to...
- [GROWLS]
- Well, I...
- A family should consist...
- Fine. I'll be right back!
Wait, wait, what?
Ah! Am I using trigger words
that I'm not aware of?
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
So, you coming in or do we have
to bring food up there to you?
I'll come to you.
I just need to finish
something up here.
[EXHILARATING
INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, those notches
show how much you love me.
Is that
what you think they mean?
Yeah.
Nah, I was just counting
how many slices of lasagne
you ate.
[ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING]
GARFIELD: My medium
is cuisine...
my colours are flavours...
my palette is my palate...
if you will.
[SNIFFS] Ah!
[DINGS]
Dinner is served!
Wow, son,
I didn't know you could cook.
Ah, yes, pasta
is my paint, and...
the dinner plate
my... [GRUNTS] canvas.
Oh! That's where that went.
I've had worse. [LAUGHS]
Thank you, Garfield.
[MUNCHING]
Is he gonna be coming around
for dinner often?
Yeah, he's family.
[BARKS]
- [ALL LAUGH]
- [PHONE BEEPS]
What?
Why do I have a takeout bill
for 6,000 drone deliveries?
Shh!
[POP MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEEPING]
[BELL DINGS]
[ODIE WHOOPS]
[SHRIEKING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[POP MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC ENDS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
JINX: [SINGING] This is
just what I had planned
Though I'm thrilled to meet you
I'm just a minx of English brand
Dreamed of the cat show
Till one night in the street
'Twas my chance I would meet
A miaow so discreet
We had the world on a string
Till he cut town
and left me empty-handed
[MIAOWS]
I'm back
And I'm on the prowl
Revenge would taste
so sweet right now
- I'm back
- CHORUS: She's back
JINX: It's time for war
Watch me scratch, hear me roar
CHORUS: She's a cat on the prowl
Got a mighty miaow
She's the queen of the streets
Her name is Jinx
JINX: That's me
I'm back
I can't believe
he double-crossed me
That really was so mean
We were friends from the start
A real work of art
The thickest of feline thieves
He came up with a scheme
To steal all the cream
But I was the only one caught
I was locked in a cage
Where my heart filled with rage
And I developed
this maniacal scream
[LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
ROLAND: Ay, yo.
It's doggy-diggity-
diggity-diggity-D
I'm bringing the
biggity-biggity-biggity-beats
- Don't you...
- JINX: No, no, no. Shush.
In case you hadn't noticed...
I'm back and I'm on the prowl
Revenge would taste
so sweet right now
- Well, I'm back
- CHORUS: She's back
JINX: And it's time for war
Watch me scratch, hear me roar
CHORUS: She's a cat on the prowl
Got a mighty miaow
She's the queen of the streets
-My name is Jinx
- Her name is Jinx
JINX: That's me
-I'm back
- She's back, she's back
JINX: I'm a cat on the prowl
CHORUS: She's back, she's back
JINX: A mighty miaow
CHORUS: She's back
Her name is Jinx
JINX: That's me
I'm back
She's biggity, biggity,
biggity, bigitty back
I'm back
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]