(HORNS HONKING IN DISTANCE)
(FAINT SIRENS WAILING)
(TRAFFIC HUM INCREASES)
(NOISES BLENDING,
INCREASING IN VOLUME)
(SOUND CUTS OUT)
(MAN) Sam?
Sam?
Why don't you go ahead?
(YAWNING)
I'm gonna share a poem
I've been working on.
I don't want to, but Reuben
said I had to, so...
I didn't say you had to.
It's called
"This Place is Shit."
Oh, good.
(SAM RECITING)
"This place is shit.
This place smells like shit.
Betsy's voice sounds like shit.
Cancer is shit.
Oscar does that stupid walk
When he wants to hide
he shit his pants.
And Milton has
shit taste in music."
- It's not finished.
- (CAT PURRING)
That was great.
That was great. Let's...
- I'm gonna clap for that.
- (SAM) Don't clap for it.
- I'm gonna clap for it.
- (CLAPPING)
Clap for it.
(ALL APPLAUDING WEAKLY)
(LANGUID JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALARM BLARING)
(WOMAN) I smell smoke.
(NURSE) It's okay, everyone.
- (REUBEN) How's your pain?
- Great.
Thanks for sharing today. Uh...
Lot of profanity, but I, um,
I didn't appreciate the comment
- about Oscar's poop-walk.
- (ALARM STOPS)
- Oscar thought it was funny.
- It was funny,
- but it was still mean.
- I'm a very mean person.
- That's a very open realization.
- I've known that for a while.
Hey! We're going to a show.
Half an hour.
Oh, see,
I might be dead by then.
Oh, yeah, you might.
But if you're not dead,
it's short
and it's in the city.
When's the last time
you were in the city?
Last time was supposed
to be the last time.
Well, here's another time.
I'll go if we get pizza.
Didn't we have pizza
yesterday?
- Did you eat it?
- No.
That wasn't pizza.
Okay, well, then, yeah, we'll
get pizza on the way back.
In the city.
- I'll go get changed.
- All right.
(REUBEN) Let Katie know
if you need help!
(SAM) Yeah.
(MEOWS)
(LEASH CLICKING)
- (MEOWS)
- Quiet.
You're getting fat.
(WINDOWS RATTLING)
(JETS ROARING)
- (DOORS SCREECHING OPEN)
- (REUBEN) Thank you so much.
All right, guys,
this is a little bit steep.
So grab onto the railing
if you need help.
(HORN HONKING)
Um, and remember,
go bad leg first.
(SAM) It's a puppet show.
(REUBEN) It's a marionette show.
We are the marionette club.
- (SAM) You lied.
- I don't know if I lied.
You could've checked
the schedule.
You tricked.
Oh, yeah,
I tricked you for sure.
(MAN) Marionettes have
a fascinating history.
The word's actually
a reference to the Virgin Mary.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Osa.
- (WHISPERS) Sorry about that.
- It's fine.
This is Frodo.
(SOFTLY) Hi, Frodo.
(SOFT LAUGHTER)
(FANFARE PLAYING)
(MOTHER) Osa, turn around.
(APPLAUSE, CHEERING)
(APPLAUSE SUBSIDES)
(SUITCASE THUDS)
(LILTING MELODY PLAYING)
(CHILDREN MURMURING)
Hi!
(GASPING)
(AUDIENCE GASPS)
- (LOUD POP)
- (AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
- (SIRENS WHOOPING)
- (OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
- (HORN PLAYING NEARBY)
- (INDISTINCT VOICE OVER P.A.)
(HELICOPTER THRUMMING OVERHEAD)
(COUPLE CHATTING ANIMATEDLY)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(HORN MUSIC CONTINUES FAINTLY)
- (CLERK) Just this?
- (SAM) Just this.
- How much do I owe you?
- (LOUD SIRENS)
(HEAVY VEHICLES RUMBLING)
Hey. How much?
It's four dollars.
And you can't
have a cat in here.
It's a service cat.
(HORN BLARING)
No, I hear you.
I'll gather them all up
and get them on the bus
as soon as I can.
- Hello?
- (APPROACHING SIRENS)
Hello? Shit!
You okay?
- (HELICOPTER FLYING OVERHEAD)
- Oh. Yeah. Um...
Yeah, I just...
How's your pain?
- Three?
- Okay.
So, listen, uh,
we have to head back now.
Why?
Something's happening
in the city
and they want us back ASAP.
But we're
getting pizza first.
No, we're gonna have to
rain check the pizza.
They can wait,
it's just pizza.
Sam, we'll get pizza
another day, okay?
We're already in the city.
Well, then we'll
order it tonight.
- Just get it in the city.
- What?
We're getting pizza in the city
and then we'll go back.
- No, we're not getting pizza.
- Yes, we are getting pizza.
- Okay, you got to calm down.
- Don't tell me to calm down.
I don't want to argue with you.
I'm your friend, okay?
You're not my friend.
You're a nurse.
(CHATTER, TRAFFIC INTENSIFYING)
- I'm getting on the bus.
- Yeah, get on the bus.
(EXHALES)
I'm s--
(HELICOPTERS FLYING OVERHEAD)
(OVERLAPPING SIRENS ECHOING)
(REUBEN) Use that one.
Good leg goes up.
(BUS BRAKES HISSING)
(CIVIL DEFENSE SIREN
WAILING IN DISTANCE)
(BRAKES SQUEAKING)
(DISTANT, THUDDING IMPACTS)
(FAINT, BOOMING EXPLOSIONS)
(POWERFUL BOOM)
(DEFENSE SIREN FADING)
(HIGH-PITCHED WHISTLING)
(SAM PANTING)
(GASPING LIGHTLY)
(DISTANT BANGING, RATTLING)
(DEEP, HEAVY BOOMS)
(SAM GASPS)
(SHAKY BREATHS)
(GASPING)
(FAINT, PERSISTENT RUMBLING)
(MAN) Can you walk?
- (MAN 2) I got you. I got you.
- (WOMAN CRYING)
(MAN 3) It was like
a flash and then--
(SCREAMING)
(TERRIFIED GASPING)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING FAINTLY)
- (DISTANT BOOMING)
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(WOMAN) Ma'am! Ma'am!
Take cover! Now!
(SOLDIER OVER RADIO)
They're fucking everywhere!
(GUTTURAL ROAR)
(FAINT, THROATY WHICKERING)
(SHATTERING GLASS)
(FAINT SCREAMS)
(RASPING BREATHS)
(GUTTURAL WHICKERING)
(HEAVY, ORGANIC SQUELCHING)
(SOFT CHITTERING)
- Run! Run!
- (MONSTER SHRIEKING)
(SCREAM, QUICKLY FADING)
(SAM PANTING)
(SIREN APPROACHING)
- (GUTTURAL SHRIEK)
- (POWERFUL BOOM)
(SILENCE)
(GASPS, COUGHS)
- (MAN) Shh! Shh!
- (STIFLED GRUNT)
(INHALES)
(GENTLY SHUSHING)
(QUIET MUTTERING)
(STIFLED MOAN)
(SOB, SHARP SNIFFLE)
(SHUDDERING)
(REUBEN BREATHING DEEPLY)
(SOFT, SHUDDERING BREATHS)
(MUFFLED KISSES)
(HELICOPTERS APPROACHING)
(MAN OVER LOUDSPEAKER)
Shelter in place.
- Remain silent.
- (HELICOPTERS THUNDERING)
Attackers are deadly.
- Make no sound.
- (HELICOPTERS RECEDING)
(VOICE FADING) Wait for
further instructions.
- (THUNDERING FOOTSTEPS ABOVE)
- (PRIMAL SHRIEKING)
(GALLOPING FOOTFALLS)
(LOUD CRUNCH)
(FAINT CHITTERING)
(SOFT MEOW)
(RESPONSIVE CLICKING)
(CHITTERING PAUSES)
(HEAVY, THUDDING FOOTFALLS)
(CHITTERING RESUMES)
(HEAVY, GUTTURAL CHITTERING)
(DEEP, RASPING BREATH)
(JINGLING)
(HEAVY GRUNTING)
(ROARING)
(GUTTURAL WHICKERING)
(HEAVY CLICKING)
(REUBEN BREATHING FAINTLY)
(FOOT THUDS)
(TRILLING SNORT)
(RUMBLING GROWL)
(SHORT, TREMBLING BREATHS)
(HISSING EXHALE)
(MAN OVER LOUDSPEAKER)
Attackers are deadly.
Remain silent.
(HELICOPTER THUNDERING)
(HEAVY THUDDING)
(THUNDERING HERD CRASHING)
(STAMPEDE RECEDING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(PANTING)
(FAUCET SQUEAKS)
(PEN SCRIBBLING ON PAPER)
(RADIO STATIC BUZZING FAINTLY)
(WOMAN OVER RADIO)
Minus 73.949708 west.
I repeat. Minus 73.949708 west.
- (GASPS)
- Evacuate the area.
- (WHISPERS) Sorry.
- I repeat.
Remain silent
and evacuate the area.
This is not a drill.
Evacuate immediately.
At 2100 hours,
all civilians
on Manhattan bridges
will be in active--
(LOUD BOOM)
(DUST SETTLING)
(DEEP BOOM)
(MUFFLED EXPLOSION)
(JET ENGINES ROARING)
(JET NOISE CONTINUES)
(PAINED GASPING)
(JETS ROARING OVERHEAD)
(SHALLOW PANTING)
(JET NOISE FADES)
(WIND BLOWING)
(JETS APPROACHING)
(METAL SNAPPING, GROANING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
What's happening?
We're trapped. We're trapped!
(SHUSHING)
- We're all gonna die--
- Shh!
(MUFFLED YELLING)
(CREATURE ROARING LOUDLY NEARBY)
- (GRUNTING)
- Shh!
(MUFFLED YELLING)
Shh!
- (CONTINUES YELLING, MUFFLED)
- Shh!
(MUFFLED)
Look what they're doing!
(WHISPERS) Stop.
(MUFFLED)
Look what they're doing!
- (LOUDLY) We're all gonna die!
- (HEAD THUDDING)
(WIND BLOWING)
(SHUDDERING BREATHS)
(WHISPERING) I'm sorry.
(MUFFLED, DISTANT EXPLOSIONS)
(WHISPERING) No.
(WHISPERING) I'm going.
(ECHOING THUD)
(GAS GENERATOR STARTS)
(WHISPERING) Stay. Stay.
- (VALVE SQUEAKS)
- (GENERATOR SHUTS OFF)
(SOFT, RELIEVED CHUCKLE)
(LOUD RIP)
(SOFT CLICKING)
(POWERFUL ROAR)
(MUFFLED CRY)
(WIND BLOWING SOFTLY)
(FLAMES CRACKLING)
(WATER FLOWING)
(CLICKS LOUDLY)
(LID PEELING OFF SLOWLY)
(SOFT CLICK)
(SOFT CHITTERING)
(HELICOPTER APPROACHING)
(FAINT VOICE OVER LOUDSPEAKER)
(MAN ON P.A.) Boat evacuations
are beginning now
at the South Street Seaport.
Travel south
with extreme caution.
(MOUTHING) Come with me.
You have to be very quiet,
okay? Come on.
(MAN ON P.A.) This is
a mandatory evacuation order.
We remain under attack.
Seek shelter on water.
The attackers cannot swim.
Boat evacuations
are beginning now
at the South Street Seaport.
(CREATURES THUNDERING)
(LOUD CLATTERING, IMPACTS)
(FOOTFALLS RECEDING)
(ALIEN SCREECHING)
- (GLASS TINKLING)
- (SAM GASPS)
(FAINT CLICKING)
(HEAVY FOOTFALL)
(GUTTURAL CLICKING)
(LOUD RASPING HISS)
(THROATY WHICKERING)
(SAM BREATHING TENSELY)
(ALIEN GROWLS SOFTLY,
RECEDING)
(WIND BLOWS SOFTLY)
(WHISPERS) Go.
(SOFT FOOTFALLS)
(FEET SCUFFING AND SCRAPING)
(MUFFLED THUD)
(MAN COUGHING)
- (INCREASING FOOTFALLS)
- (LOW MURMURING)
(FEET CRUNCHING SOFTLY)
(SOFT CLATTERING)
(GLASS CLINKS)
(SOFT METALLIC CLANK)
(CHAIR RATTLING)
(METALLIC CLANGING)
(LOW RUMBLING)
(RUMBLING INTENSIFIES)
(ROARING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
- (HEAVY THUDDING)
- (ALL YELLING)
- (ROARING)
- (CAR ALARM WAILING)
(SCREAMING)
(CHAOTIC SCREAMS, SHOUTING)
(GRUNTS)
- (GLASS SHATTERING)
- (PEOPLE WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMING)
(BREATHING TIGHTLY)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(MAN SCREAMING)
Please! Please!
- Please! Help me!
- Shh!
Help! Help me!
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(AIR HISSING)
(METAL CREAKING)
(GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
(CAR THUDS)
(MUFFLED, CHAOTIC SCREAMING)
(MAN PANTING)
(PEOPLE WHIMPERING)
(WOMAN)
Jonathan? Jonathan!
- (CREATURE SNARLS)
- (WOMAN SCREAMS)
- (HEAVY THUD)
- (GLASS SHATTERING)
(WHEEZING)
(WIND BLOWING SOFTLY)
(GASPING)
(PANTING HEAVILY)
(PURRING SOFTLY)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
(MOUTHING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(RAIN DRUMMING ON CARS)
(SOBBING QUIETLY)
(MUFFLED WHIMPERING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(RAIN POURING ON METAL)
(WHISPERS) Hey.
Hey.
What's your name?
(SOFTLY) Talk under
the rain. What's your name?
Eric.
Eric? Okay, Eric.
You need to go
to the South Street Seaport.
There are boats there, okay?
Okay.
(UNDER BREATH) Okay. Okay.
- Eric?
- Okay.
- Hey.
You need to stop
following me, okay?
Okay.
- That way?
- Yeah.
Okay.
(EXHALES SHAKILY)
Okay. Okay. Okay.
I'm really scared.
I don't want to die here.
Okay.
Look.
Let's just get out
of the rain, okay?
Okay.
Come on.
(EXHALES)
(THUNDER PEALING)
(THUNDERCLAP)
- (ERIC) Is this your place?
- Yeah.
Kick it down.
Kick it down with
your foot.
- (INHALES SHARPLY)
- Wait.
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(GROANS)
(SIGHS)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(THUNDER PEALING)
(RAINFALL CONTINUES)
- What are you doing?
- I'm looking for my meds.
Why are you looking
for your meds?
Because every muscle
in my body is on fire!
(WHISPERING) Eric,
do you have family here?
Why?
Don't you have
anywhere you can go?
No.
My parents are in Kent.
In England.
I came here for law school.
That was the one thing
I was supposed to do.
You got to get to the water
and get out of the city.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going to get pizza.
Where?
Patsy's up in Harlem.
I think the world
might be ending.
And I think there's
a slice of Patsy's
sitting up there that's
the last that'll ever exist.
And I'm gonna get it.
Okay.
Okay, what?
Okay, let's get pizza.
No, I'm getting pizza.
- Did you write this?
- Yeah.
You're a poet?
Not anymore.
Who's that?
That's my dad.
He played piano?
He played
beautiful piano.
This wasn't part
of the plan.
(THUNDER RUMBLING SOFTLY)
Please, can I come
and get pizza with you?
Read this.
"Bad Math.'
You said one to two years.
And it has been two.
You said four to six months,
And it has been six.
And Mrs. Friedlander taught
Me subtraction,
And the corner store
Taught me addition,
And I used only simple maths
All my life.
And I never needed more
Than more,
And less.
To four.
To three.
To smaller
And smaller.
Until months,
To days.
To hours,
To seconds.
But to not now.'"
(THUNDER BOOMING)
- (LOUD THUNDERCLAP)
- (SCREAMING)
(THUNDER FADES)
- (THUNDER CRASHES)
- (SCREAMING)
(HORNS HONKING FAINTLY)
(ROAR, ECHOING)
(IMPACT ECHOING)
(FAINT CLICKING)
(HEAVY CLICKING)
(OVERLAPPING CLICKS)
(ALIENS CHITTERING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(DISTANT SHRIEKING)
(SOFT THUD)
(LEATHER CREAKING)
(LOUD THUMP)
- (CLICKING)
- (GLASS BREAKING)
(ROARING)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(GUTTURAL ROAR)
(ALIEN SHRIEKING)
(HEAVY IMPACTS)
(CLICKING LOUDLY)
(CAR ALARM WAILING)
(GRUNTING)
(CAR ALARM CONTINUES)
- (FAINT CRASHING)
- (CAR ALARM STOPS)
(RAPID CLICKING)
(CLICKING FADES)
(FAINT CLATTERING)
(SOFT THUMP NEARBY)
(FAINT SQUEAK)
(HEAVY IMPACT)
(DEEP, RESONANT CLICKING)
(HEAVY, RHYTHMIC WARBLING)
- (CLICKING)
- (HEAVY FOOTFALL)
(WARBLING CONTINUES)
(WATER TRICKLING)
(CLICKING RESUMES NEARBY)
(FAINT, RASPING BREATH)
(SLOW, GUTTURAL SNORTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SHIVERING BREATHS)
(GASPING LIGHTLY)
(SHUDDERING GASP)
(SHUSHING SOFTLY)
(WHISPERING)
You're good. You're good.
(GASPS)
(CLICKING)
(WHISPERING) Hey...
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay?
(STIFLED SOB)
(WHISPERING) It's okay.
It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's fine.
(BREATHING STEADIES)
- (MOANS)
- (CREATURE ROARING)
(GASPING)
(INHALES, GROANS)
(BOOMING GROWL)
(THUDDING FOOTSTEPS)
(ERIC GRUNTING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
- (CREATURE ROARS)
- (LOUD BANGING)
(MUFFLED SCREECH)
(DESPERATE, MUFFLED GROWLING)
(WATER RUSHING)
(SAM GASPING)
(GASPING, CHOKING)
(ERIC GRUNTING)
(WATER RUSHING FAINTLY)
(PRIEST MURMURING IN LATIN)
(MURMURING CONTINUES)
(LOW RUMBLING)
(SAM RETCHING)
(EXHALES WEAKLY)
(PEN SCRATCHING ON PAPER)
(WIND BLOWING SOFTLY)
(FAINT METALLIC SQUEAKING)
(LEAVES RUSTLING IN BREEZE)
(SWITCH CLICKS FAINTLY)
(SOFT THUMP)
(PANTING)
No, no, no.
(TENSE EXHALE)
(IMPACT ECHOING)
(CREATURE PANTING)
(FUNGUS SPORES HISSING)
(CREATURE BREATHING SOFTLY)
- (HEAVY THUD)
- (CREATURE CLICKING)
(SHORT, BARKING GRUNTS)
(PANTING SOFTLY)
- (HAND SCRAPES METAL)
- (HEAVY GROWL)
(DISTORTED, REVERBERATING
AMBIENT NOISE)
(WRAPPER TEARING)
(BREATHING DEEPENS)
(WHISPERING) I'm here.
I'm here.
(RECITING) My father
played beautiful piano.
I loved...
when he took me
to see him play.
At a jazz club
by Patsy's.
Then after,
we'd get pizza.
(MURMURING) Pizza.
(SOFT CHUCKLE)
What happened to him?
He died.
Like I am now.
Not before we get pizza.
(SHARP EXHALE)
(CRYING SOFTLY)
(FIRE BURNING)
(FLAMES CRACKLING)
(WHISPERING) Where did
your dad play piano?
(MOUTHING)
(LIGHT GASP)
(BOAT HORN BLOWING)
(CREATURES SNARLING NEARBY)
(HORN BLOWING)
(ALIENS CLICKING)
(FAINT CLICKING)
(STEAM HISSING)
(SCRAPING LIGHTLY)
(SOFT CLICKING NEARBY)
(HORN BLOWING)
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
(SNORTING)
(GROWLS)
(BREATHING SHARPLY)
(ALIENS CONTINUE GROWLING)
(WHISPERING) Breathe.
(SHARP GROWLING)
- (PURRING SOFTLY)
- (SAM KISSES FRODO)
Run.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
- (WINDOW SHATTERS)
- (ALARM WAILING)
- (ALARM BLARING)
- (HORN HONKING)
(SCREECHING)
(GROWLING)
Stop the boat.
Stop the boat!
- (CREATURES THUNDERING)
- (CAR ALARMS CONTINUE)
(GASPS)
(HEAVY IMPACTS)
(ALARM WAILING)
(ALARM FALTERS)
(CAN CLATTERING)
(PANTING LOUDLY)
(SHRIEKING)
(GASPING FOR AIR)
(ALL SNARLING)
(WOMAN) You can do it! Come on!
(GASPING)
(SCATTERED YELLS
OF ENCOURAGEMENT)
(FRODO MEOWS)
(VOICES MUTED)
You're safe.
Safe.
(PURRING)
(SNIFFLES)
(CRYING SOFTLY)
(SAM) Eric,
you better take care of my cat.
Don't rub his belly.
He doesn't like that.
And don't feed him too much.
He'll get fat.
And thank you.
Thank you for bringing me home.
Thank you for helping me
live again.
I had forgotten
how the city sings.
You can hear it
when you're quiet.
(WIND BLOWING SOFTLY)
("I'M FEELING GOOD" BY
NINA SIMONE PLAYING IN EARBUDS)
♪ It's a new dawn
It's a new day ♪
♪ It's a new life for me
Yeah ♪
♪ It's a new dawn
It's a new day ♪
(SAM) It's good
to have been back.
(OVER SPEAKERS)
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh... ♪
♪ And I'm feeling good ♪
♪ Fish in the sea
You know how I feel ♪
♪ River running free
♪ Blossom on the tree
You know how I feel ♪
♪ It's a new dawn
It's a new day ♪
♪ It's a new life for me ♪
♪ And I'm feeling good ♪
♪ Dragonfly out in the sun ♪
♪ You know what I mean
Don't you know? ♪
♪ Butterflies all havin' fun ♪
♪ You know what I mean ♪
♪ Sleep in peace
When day is done ♪
♪ That's what I mean ♪
♪ And this old world
Is a new world ♪
♪ And a bold world, for me ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Stars when you shine
You know how I feel ♪
♪ Scent of the pine
♪ Oh, freedom is mine ♪
♪ And I know how I feel ♪
♪ It's a new dawn
It's a new day ♪
♪ It's a new life for me ♪
(SCATTING)
♪ Oh, I'm feeling good ♪
(SONG ENDS)