Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
This is an emergency meeting
of top-level leadership.
Highest priority.
The Central Home Minister and
the Chief of RAW will also be joining us.
Subject, sir?
I believe it’s about Yethi.
As you know, we’re hosting
the Cricket World Cup this year.
The opening ceremony is next month.
Twelve teams
and leaders from three countries
will be our prestigious guests.
But…
there’s also trouble on the horizon.
The gangster brothers, Daya and Yethi.
Last month, Daya's account in Dubai
received funds
from various Arab countries.
Large amounts.
Daya and Yethi are plotting something
major at our event next month.
Intelligence indicates a severe threat.
Daya isn’t on our radar.
All his operations here
are controlled by his brother, Yethi.
We need to apprehend Yethi immediately.
Sir, Shivam is the task force head.
- Sir!
- He's been monitoring
Yethi's operations
for the past three years.
So, Shivam, what information
do you have on Yethi?
To be honest… nothing, sir.
I almost arrested Yethi three times
in the past three years,
but each time I received orders
from above that he shouldn’t be touched.
No, no.
This isn’t the time for blame games.
Sorry, sir.
I’m granting you complete authority,
effective immediately. Go and get him.
For the past two months, none of his
gang members have surfaced, sir.
They may have gone underground
due to this operation.
- Something has to be done immediately.
- Sir!
The event is next month.
We must catch Yethi before then,
or we’ll have to call off the event!
When we had Yethi in our hands,
we let him slip away.
Now we don’t even know his whereabouts.
Can’t we track down
at least one of his gang members?
We have a chance.
Yethi gang's number two. Rane!
He has a girlfriend.
They were meeting regularly in Mahim
before he went underground.
If we can get to her,
we might be able to locate him.
Would he show up?
There's a girl involved.
He might take a chance.
Can we trust the girl?
We assured her safety if she cooperates.
He will definitely come.
There he is.
Hi, baby!
- Now you remember me!
- Oh, my wild one!
- Do you miss me?
- Yeah.
Rane!
Shoot on the legs.
Come on, shoot on the legs, boys.
Tell us where Yethi is.
Tell us.
Tell us, I say.
Hey!
Where is Yethi?
I don't know.
Since he won't open
his mouth about Yethi…
his tongue is of no use.
Speak up!
If we cut it off…
I will at least have some satisfaction.
- Tell me.
- He's gone to the South.
Near the Andhra, Tamil Nadu border…
There is a place called Ratnagiri.
There is a guy… Muruga,
a small-time smuggler.
He can transport goods not only
from the port but directly from the sea.
Three months ago,
Yethi went there.
Tell us!
He has not returned since then.
We have no information
on his whereabouts.
DSP Tulasi?
Please sit.
My name is Danny.
I am a Mumbai-based smuggler.
We are expecting a consignment by the sea.
We cannot receive it at the port.
We heard a smuggler called Muruga,
can bring in goods from the sea,
so, we came for him.
But when we reached here,
they said he was no more.
When we inquired about his inner circle,
we were told this area's DSP, Tulasi,
supported Muruga a lot.
You have earned quite a lot.
I want the same help
you extended to Muruga.
Quote your price.
Goods from the sea are neither brought
by Muruga…
nor me.
On the mountain that you see in the East,
there are four villages.
Those four villages together
are called the Red Sea.
They are the ones who actually bring
in goods from these waters.
Who do I meet there?
Bhaira.
I am also a cop.
You think I cannot recognize a fellow cop?
One more thing…
Be careful with the Red Sea people.
Who are you? What do you need?
I need to meet Bhaira.
We are here from Mumbai on a job.
A job only you are capable of doing.
We have a delivery coming
from another country on a ship.
Mumbai is too challenging
to unload the cargo.
The ship will pass through
this area tomorrow night.
I know you can go into the sea
and unload the cargo discreetly.
We quit doing such jobs a long time ago.
That means you did it in the past.
So, start again.
I will pay you beyond your imagination.
I will cover your mountain in gold.
Listen to me
and go back to where you came from.
What's the matter?
Are you misinterpreting
my requests for pleading?
You are far away from civilization.
If I kill you right here, it will be ages
before the world learns about your death.
Before I see your blood,
just follow my orders.
Take what I give you.
You come to the Red Sea,
and threaten me of bloodshed?
Are you teaching us
about the dangers of death?
They definitely know about Yethi.
I have to find someone
who can give us the information.
You came to the mountain
and tried to scare them?
Who are you?
Singappa.
I live on the East side of the mountain
you just climbed down.
I have come here on a job.
You look like an elder.
Can you talk them into doing it?
Come.
Take the boat out, Naga.
What's the big deal
in knocking off some cargo?
This sea route is like a path
to a diamond mine.
Am I a fool to believe
you gave up everything?
Quote what you want
and how much you want.
I will give it to you.
You should convince them to do it.
What do you say?
You want it?
This is a very expensive diamond.
If you do as I say,
many such diamonds will be yours.
Check it out.
Sir…
Down there! Down there!
- Down there.
- What's down there, sir?
What's there, sir?
Could you find the diamond ring?
You saw something
terrifying in the sea,
that made you forget the ring.
It is out of this fright,
that no matter how many of you show up
and how much you tempt us,
the locals from here
won't meddle with the sea.
With my eyes closed or open,
I cannot unsee
what I saw in the sea.
Who were they?
Who is responsible for all this?
It's quite a long story, sir.
It's the story of a sea
turning red with blood.
Whose story is it?
The story of the rough waters
of the mighty sea…
on which he stood unshaken.
It's the story of our beloved "Devara."
To overcome fear,
you should listen to the story of God.
To understand fear, you should listen
to the story of Devara.
Many years ago,
behind that mountain,
existed a kingdom.
To conquer that kingdom,
the sea had to be crossed.
But a huge army was stationed
on the mountain.
A dynamic force specially chosen
by the king from across the country.
They had no caste. No religion.
They never knew fear.
Their God was their weapon.
And their weapon was courage.
Day and night, they were
watching the sea from the mountain.
As a testimony to the sea
reddened hundreds of times
with the blood of the enemies…
this place came to be known
as the Red Sea.
Ages passed.
Kingdoms disappeared.
When the white folks from
far-off lands were looting
and carrying our wealth away
across the ocean,
the army couldn't simply watch
and do nothing.
It's the story of that army ready
to do anything for our country, sir.
They ventured into the sea,
looted the ships,
and distributed the loot
back on this land.
After the British left,
the country didn't need the brave warriors
from the mountain anymore.
There was nobody
to care for them.
These keen warriors…
became an opportunity
for someone.
To use their strength
in fearlessly taming the sea,
a few had flocked to our mountain.
Very unlikely of you
to be worried sick like this.
What's up, Muruga?
It's a full moon night, Tulasi.
The sea is raging.
I am worried if they can make it…
Whether the sea
is calm or raging,
when we have a brave warrior
ready to confront it,
why should you worry, Muruga?
Devara! Devara!
Hello, sir!
Indian Coast Guard,
Eastern Regional Officer, Irfan.
Ethan's Captain, John.
Warrant to search the ship.
We have information
that some illegal weapons
and ammunition
are coming from Russia.
Help us to search your vessel.
I see our cargo. Let's go.
Sugar, sir.
Why are the locks open?
All in all,
there must be ten officers, Devara.
There is no other way.
The smuggler gangs
from foreign countries,
who found it difficult to get
their cargo through the port,
knew the strength of these men and
used them to get it directly from the sea.
Every village had
its unique strength.
All the four villages got together
and challenging the Red Sea itself,
took up this dangerous mission.
Kids shouldn't be
involved in this job.
Devara has addressed this
with you on several occasions, Bhaira.
My land, my people, and my rules.
I have made this clear just
as many times, Rayappa.
- Count it.
- It must be right.
If you eat at this hour of the day,
how will the food nourish you?
Forget that.
If you stay up so late,
don't you see how unhealthy that is?
I have seen it all.
That's why I can't sleep unless I see you.
With these eyes,
I witnessed my father's death.
I saw your father's passing too.
I watched my siblings die…
and the death of
all my close ones.
How unlucky I am!
I spent all my life
closely watching death.
I can't do this anymore, son.
Either you should
see my death next…
or I should get to see you every day.
Now that I've seen you,
I can sleep peacefully.
Is Vara asleep?
Your mom doesn't fall asleep
until she catches a glimpse of you.
Vara won't sleep until he
hears a story from you, will he?
It was raining very
heavily that day.
The British ransacked
all our treasures
and were getting away in a ship.
My father…
Your grandfather…
- gathered all our people in a ship…
- Oh, my!
Stop it, Father.
You always narrate your
father's or his father's story.
I want to know
my father's story.
Tell me Devara's story.
Your father's story is not worth sharing
with the next generation.
My father's is a story of valor
and honor, of a fight for our country.
Ours…
are dark stories that
cannot be shared.
Yes, we are barely living.
Whether our lives
will change enough
to become great stories
for future generations,
is something even I don't know.
How are you, son?
Yes, I am good. How are you?
I am fine.
Greetings, Devara.
Hey, how are studies going?
I am studying well, Devara.
I will be done in two years.
Then I will return
and start teaching here, Devara.
Please take this.
We have a lot of help from
you already. I can't accept this.
Don't call this help, Ademma.
This is our responsibility.
Your husband was
one of us on the sea.
We lost him to the same sea.
His family is now our family.
Please accept this.
After his father passed,
though he was keen on venturing
into the sea with you,
I disapproved
and sent him out to study instead.
For understanding me, helping me out,
and being a great support,
I'm much obliged, Devara.
He is your son, Ademma.
He should become
what you want him to.
He will be exactly that.
It's Ayudha puja tomorrow.
I wonder who will win
the competition this time,
and take home the weapons.
Devara will win again if he wishes to
or he will voluntarily lose
if he wants someone else to win.
You can root for
whoever you want,
but it's my father,
Bhaira who will triumph.
This time the weapons
shall come to our village.
If Devara wants the weapons
to go to your village,
only then will Bhaira win.
Is that so?
Let's find out the winner right away.
Come on, Vara.
Go on, Vara.
You show him who
Devara really is. Go.
Come on, you.
Pasura, knock him down.
- Hit him, Vara.
- Hit him!
Strike at him. Pound him.
- Hit him well, Pasura.
- Go for it, Vara.
Yes, Pasura, that's right.
Hit him hard.
Knock him down, Pasura.
Strike at him.
- Pasura, pin him down.
- Hit him, Vara.
- Hit him, Vara. Go for it.
- Knock him down.
Pasura, that's right. Hit him hard.
Just like that, strike at him, Pasura.
Hit him hard. Knock him down, Pasura.
Beat him. Yes, take him down.
Didn't I tell you?
No matter who is in the arena,
the winner will be Bhaira.
What happened?
Devara is here.
The Red Sea swells up
And gets boisterous with a roar
The warriors of the land
Celebrate their valor today
The waves of blood from clanging swords
Pounce like a tempest off our legion
Hey, the salty air
Has turned burning hot
Hey, the sound of drums rent the skies
The tiger's heirs
Sway like possessed
As the rebellious land
Rises in a dance of ecstasy
Today is the day
To worship the weapons we wield
Let us tap our shoulders
And celebrate the fair
It's a fete of warring brave hearts
Let's give them a welcome…
With warm blood coursing through
March ahead, our warrior
- This is a tradition
- Breaching it is desecration
- It's a family for whom war is life
- The sea and the time stand witness
The sacrifices by our mothers
Are the breast milk that blesses us
Making this body shape into a weapon
Self-esteem that refuses to surrender
Dictates the boundaries
The chronicles of our ancestors
Are radiant like a glorious history
This day that comes
Every year is meant for us
The stroking of our mustache
Is our message to the world
Today is the day
To worship the weapons we wield
Let us tap our shoulders
And celebrate the fair
It's a fete of warring brave hearts
Let's give them a welcome
With warm blood coursing through
March ahead, our warrior
The Red Sea swells up
And gets boisterous with a roar
The warriors of the land
Celebrate their valor today
The waves of blood from clanging swords
Pounce like a tempest off our legion
It's time for the battle.
Women and kids should leave.
All of us know the village that wins
the battle gets the ancestral weapons.
They have been in Devara's
possession for a long time.
Let us see who gets them this year.
Let me remind you of
the battle rules once again.
Only two warriors from each
village can get into the arena.
The last man standing
shall be the winner.
Are you ready?
We are just four villages.
Instead of this contest,
why don't we allow each village to
possess the weapons each year?
Rayappa's village hasn't
seen weapons for years now.
I would like them to get
the weapons this time.
Do you think our ancestors were fools
to introduce this custom, Devara?
For our ancestors,
war was a livelihood.
They introduced such customs to
intensify the spirit of fighting, Bhaira.
It has been a long-standing tradition.
We must go for the battle.
What about Rayappa's village that
can only row boats and not fight battles?
If the weapons go
to their village at least once,
they too will be benefited, Bhaira.
Winning has become a habit for you,
so if it bothers you so much,
win them again
and give them to Rayappa, Devara.
Let's begin.
Sura! Sura!
- Sura! Sura!
- Dega!
- Dega! Dega!
- Sura! Sura!
- Hit him hard.
- Dega! Dega!
Dega! Dega!
One man down from the West side.
Kunjara! Kunjara!
Kunjara!
One man down
from the North side.
Bhaira! Bhaira!
Hit him!
Knock him down!
Bhaira! Bhaira!
Come on!
Kunjara!
Both the contenders
from the West side have now lost.
- Bhaira! Bhaira!
- Devara! Devara!
Bhaira!
- Bhaira! Bhaira!
Along with the four villages,
maybe even the sun was curious to see
which of these two warriors
would emerge as the winner.
By the time the crimson sun rose,
the two had turned red from blood.
- Bhaira!
- Devara! Devara!
Devara! Devara!
If Devara requests you,
it means he has ordered you.
Rayappa…
I had a nightmare last night, Jogula.
The sea had gone red again
turning into an actual Red Sea.
And it was I who made it so.
The days to come are
not auspicious, Devara.
Not everybody you think
is yours is trustworthy.
You must be all eyes
and be very cautious, Devara.
I went home for Ayudha puja.
- I'm returning to college now.
- Oh, is it?
How did the ritual go?
It was good.
My Sivudu is no more, Devara.
He was on his way to the town
when they blew up
the bus he was on.
I thought he would come back
after finishing his studies.
This is how he came back.
Instead of going away to study,
had he followed his heart
and took to the sea with you,
he'd still be alive.
I am the reason
for my son's death.
We must have some
past-life connection.
Because of your association with me,
my business is booming.
That's why it's about
time you increase the pay.
Two bags for each village.
Have I ever denied your request?
In two days' time,
the ship with our cargo
is crossing the Red Sea.
Those goods are highly valuable.
The coast guard has tightened
the security on the sea.
We somehow managed to escape
the last time.
It's best we take a break for a while.
Is this really Devara talking?
How come you are scared, Devara?
I am not scared.
I am saying we
need to be cautious.
The ship has already set sail, Devara.
How can you refuse to go now?
It would be dangerous if all of us got
caught with the consignment, Muruga.
We already know it is dangerous
but we do it anyway.
What is this strange talk, Devara?
If something happens to one person,
the rest of us will stand by his family.
But if it turns out bad for all of us…
who will stand with our families, Bhaira?
In that case,
we will go this time, Devara.
If something happens to us,
you will protect this mountain, won't you?
Let's go, guys.
Send us a note with details of the ship
and the arrangement of its cargo, Muruga.
Though you have objected,
they seem ready to get into the sea.
But if you come along,
we know we all will return safely.
Give it a thought, Devara.
Come on!
Where are you coming
from at this hour?
We went hunting, sir.
To hunt fish, sir.
All the heroes went together
yet not much of a catch today.
I mean, the fish.
We went in a
different direction.
We couldn't catch much.
It's already quite late, sir.
It's the usual time for sharks to come.
We better leave.
You should too.
Sir, there are bigger fish in here.
Illegal weapons, grenades,
and material to make bombs.
This is what you are
transporting over the Red Sea.
Do you have any idea where it
goes and how many lives are lost?
This sea is a border
to our country.
Whenever there was danger
across this sea, for our land,
your ancestors struck
it down making this sea
red and I grew up listening
to their stories.
But today the country faces danger
from you, who are their descendants
and from this Red Sea.
It's not like
I am unaware of your heists.
It's the tale of your forefathers
guarding the sea that has inspired me
to take up this job
of watching over the sea.
Considering you're their clan resorting
to petty thefts for your survival
I remained silent,
which was my biggest mistake.
Do you know how many hands
your smuggled
goods change,
and how many lives they take?
Had I managed to stop you
two months ago,
I would've saved hundreds of lives
lost because of that consignment.
Even a kid from your own village
lost his life there.
This is what I feel when I look at you.
The stories we heard
of those great warriors
were either made up
or you are not
from their bloodline.
Guard your tongue, sir.
Not tongue.
I am saying our country should be guarded.
Okay, sir. Okay, copy that.
Sir, we've just received a message.
You have been blessed with a daughter.
A fresh life might have arrived
in this place full of monsters.
But I am not sure
how long it will survive.
Unless these beasts are
locked up permanently,
human beings cannot survive.
Devara…
Hey…
Stop it.
Let's go, guys.
Take the cargo along with you.
Keep breathing, sir.
You have to go see your child.
You said your baby will not survive
in this land of beasts.
I swear on the weapons
that we worship…
I will let no harm from
the Red Sea reach any child.
This is Devara's promise. Trust me.
Believe me.
What happened?
It is not my blood.
But someone else's.
Hey, Devara.
Did Devara also
go with you guys?
I knew you were all on one team.
Do your counting
and pick up your cargo, Muruga.
What's inside, Muruga?
Hand it to me.
What's inside?
That's one question I told
you not to ask me, Devara.
Weapons.
Just like the weapons you have.
But the latest ones.
Load the goods.
You will not move the goods.
Hey, what's wrong, Devara?
What is it?
Do you want more money?
I will pay you double
if that's what you want.
What do you mean we
can't move the goods?
We brought the goods
that killed our boy.
How many more kids
might we have killed?
You said there are weapons
in this like the ones we have.
Our weapons were made
to protect good from evil.
These weapons have been made
to kill the innocent.
You are talking too much.
Load the goods in the vehicle
and go to your wife and kids.
Forget about the goods
and you go do the same!
All these years,
I gave them whatever they asked for.
Now he is taking me for granted. Yes?
From now on, we are going
to get huge shipments, Devara.
Be frank and ask me what you want.
If your men or you approach
us for this work again,
even your dead bodies
will not leave this mountain.
This is Devara's word.
If it's all about your words,
then what about ours, Devara?
Just because the coast guard
blabbered something,
are we going to give up our work?
We must go into the sea.
We must conquer the sea.
I have told you already, Muruga.
Whether anyone likes it or not…
Whether they participate or not…
This line of work will not stop.
You said you will bring
much bigger consignments.
Even if it means people
dying because of them,
or killing a number
of people to get them…
This mountain is always ready.
Despite knowing what we do is wrong,
I believed that we did it only
to make our ends meet.
But I just realized
that these wrongdoings
have strongly seeped into our blood.
We should get rid
of this filthy blood!
We must know
how dishonorable this work is!
All that a man needs is
enough courage to live.
Not the courage to kill.
If you disregard my word
and still choose to gather that courage,
I will become a terror
that kills that courage.
If Devara requests you,
it means he has ordered you.
And if he actually orders you…
All hail!
From today, we will go into the sea
only for fishing.
It's the great ocean
The other side…
Burst into flames
The expansive sky
Atrocities come
To a halt…
Fizzled out, the evil adamance
On the path of war
The chief marches forward
Teaching fear…
He draws a line for his army
O' courage, ready to leap! Careful!
Don't you dare…
Don't you dare come face to face
What are you before Devara?
Hide yourself…
Time has faltered
The swelling tides have paused
Lives have run helter-skelter
And vanished into burrows
O' courage, ready to leap! Careful!
All hail! All hail the tiger!
What are you before Devara?
Oh, hail him! Devara!
If your son had stayed with Devara,
you said he would still be alive.
You sent him far from here
and blamed yourself for his death.
The explosives that killed your son
were brought by us from the Red Sea.
You were not responsible for his death.
It was me.
I don't have the courage
to look into your eyes and say this.
Hence, I am looking down at your feet.
I cannot fix my mistake
and bring your son back to life but…
I will make sure nobody
faces such loss again.
All hail!
Why harm the world?
Why face Devara's wrath?
When he comes down as war
It's all destruction
A miracle invisible to the eye
Acts as the guardian of the sea
When you defy destiny, it's a tragedy
Hey, the waters in red wash his feet
His very arrival like a deluge
Is a proclamation in itself
Devara's silence is a
Warning unamendable
His burning anger
Makes even death sweat in fear
O, courage, ready to leap! Careful!
Don't you dare…
Don't you dare come face to face
What are you before Devara?
Hide yourself…
Time has faltered
The swelling tides have paused
Lives have run helter-skelter
And vanished into burrows
O, courage, ready to leap! Careful!
All hail! All hail the tiger!
What are you before Devara?
All hail the king…
To face Devara, who was preventing
wrongful activities on the sea,
Bhaira found a solution in the sea itself.
Why did you do such a thing?
Did I not come across
your mind even once?
When I hear about how much you
struggle to get this blind sister married,
I am not able to live with it, brother.
If I am dead,
you may grieve me for a few days.
But I won't be a burden
to you anymore, brother.
How can you be a burden to me?
I will take care
of you all my life…
We will take care of her, Rayappa.
I want to get your sister married
to my younger brother.
Bhaira…
Are you serious?
Your family is my family too, Rayappa.
Without further delay,
make the arrangements, Rayappa.
What Devara did on the mountain
is still driving us mad!
And here you are negotiating a
wedding and celebrating it, Bhaira!
We will not be able
to stand Devara at the wedding.
We have tolerated him all this while.
Won't you at least
have a last look at him?
In fact, true celebrations will begin
with his death at this wedding.
You want to confront Devara and kill him?
Even before he could
get a proper mustache,
Devara ripped apart
a shark in the sea
and dragged it to the shore.
As long as he is conscious,
no one would dare
go near and touch him, Bhaira.
Oh! Rayappa!
Come in.
My younger sister's wedding
has been fixed, Devara.
You mean Padma's?
Who is the groom?
Bhaira's brother.
He was generous enough
to come home with the proposal.
You have come bearing
such great news, Rayappa!
When is the wedding?
We are planning it
for the day after tomorrow.
She holds you
in higher regard than me.
Don't worry about Bhaira.
All of you should come.
She is like a sister to me, Rayappa.
Don't be so formal
with your invitation.
I will be there
to send her off heartily.
Devara?
- They look good as a couple.
- Yes.
They complement each other, right?
What's up, Thanga?
What are you looking at?
Do you want to get married too?
There are many suitable matches
for you around here.
Let us know if you like somebody.
I will marry you off on the same stage.
With so many suitors around,
why are you eyeing my husband?
What is this? What's with the distance?
Devara came as soon as I invited him.
He came in the end
like a distant relative.
Kept himself distant too.
We considered you family
and came early.
We have downed three pots already.
Whatever I did is
for our own good.
This is not our only way to live.
If we put our heads together,
we will find ample other ways.
Please listen to me
this one time, Bhaira.
As long as you live,
this mountain shall obey
only your orders, Devara.
It's a promise from me.
Devara is dancing at
your wedding, Padma.
Devara…
How many outsiders are expected?
Apparently up to fifty.
Since it's Devara…
Do you think they can do it?
Hey, Devara is completely drunk.
You don't need
to fight him to kill.
Once he gets intoxicated
and collapses, just kill him.
Bhaira, what's going on?
I heard them say wicked things.
He is the one
with wicked words and wicked actions.
This is not right, Kunjara.
It's our Devara.
As long as I am alive,
I won't let this happen.
If this wedding is called off,
your sister won't stay alive.
Devara's life…
or your sister's life?
If you remain silent
just for tonight,
tomorrow… you can cry
over his corpse for a while.
Or your sister will die and you will
end up crying every day, Rayappa.
Tell him that a gang at Mandapala shore
is secretly setting out to loot.
Make sure he leaves from here.
Hey, Rayappa. Come and join me.
Why the tears, Rayappa?
You must bid goodbye
to your sister with happiness.
Isn't this what we have
all been waiting for?
With the wedding happening here,
some of our men are ready to venture
into the sea without being noticed.
They are setting out
from the Mandapala shore.
The sea is full of blood
It's his Red Sea
All hail! All hail the tiger!
The sea is full of blood
It's his Red Sea
All hail! All hail the tiger!
You never touch the sea
You never play with me
I'll never show you mercy
I'll never…
I had a nightmare last night, Jogula.
The sea had gone red again
turning into an actual Red Sea.
And it was I who made it so.
The sea is full of blood
It's his Red Sea
All hail! All hail the tiger!
The sea is full of blood
It's his Red Sea
All hail! All hail the tiger!
Eyes that knew
nothing but courage,
for the first time ever,
were filled with fear.
Were those the dead bodies
that I saw in the sea?
Dear…
Get up.
Oh, my…
Dear…
Kora…
Has Devara killed them?
Has he killed them all?
I thought I could reform
you with my words.
But now I see that you have turned into
fearless and uncontrollable beasts.
You won't even fear God or the devil
if he's visible every day.
So, just like them, I choose to be
an invisible fear from today.
If you forget fear and go into
the sea on your crooked jobs again,
I will lay you down on
the shore just like this.
It had been two years since
Devara set off into the sea.
The stillness and silence
had somehow reduced the fear.
They had lived like sharks.
Their pride stood in the way
of turning into fishermen.
But on Bhaira's assurance,
a few did venture
into the sea again.
Like a tempest born out of the sea,
Devara had probably pounced upon them.
Watching the half-dead
come afloat to the shores,
the mountain had
its heart in its mouth.
They took to the sea again.
However, this time
it wasn't for a heist.
It was for sustenance.
Fishing became their livelihood.
Meanwhile, the women in his family
kept waiting for Devara, counting minutes.
Adamantly trying to make Devara appear,
in the Ayudha puja
conducted every year,
Bhaira killed two people
from Devara's village…
- Bhaira… Bhaira…
and made a couple
more bedridden.
Since that year, the celebrated fight at
the Ayudha puja has also been stopped.
But Devara didn't return
to the mountain.
To put an end to Devara
and the fear he infused,
taking a few kids
of the mountain under his wing,
Bhaira wanted to mold a generation
into a fearless army.
Twelve long years had passed.
Bhaira ingrained the minds
of his young army with the belief
that Devara was their only target.
As per your instructions,
I saw Devara in him every minute
and spilled his blood, Bhaira.
When you are in the arena,
you must see Devara
in your opponent
and make him shed blood.
How many times
have I told you that?
He dropped to the ground so…
Also he grew up with me, Bhaira.
He only grew up with you.
But he was raised by me.
Samara born to Kunjara,
the dead leader of the West,
grew up only waiting for Devara,
who caused his father's death.
Every day he would go to Devara's
home to check on his old mother
because some day
the lady would die of old age and
Devara would come
to see her one last time.
And finally, Devara would
come under his knife.
Why didn't you come
to collect the money this month?
When will you stop going
to Devara's house?
When you send us
to the sea to kill Devara.
In order to kill Devara,
not only do we
need perfect timing,
but also a perfect weapon.
While coming from Hawk Mountain,
we had this shark attacking our boat.
No matter how much we tried
we couldn't subdue it.
Vara jumped into the sea, held it down,
and fought it till it died.
Just like Devara, Vara killed
that shark and pulled it ashore.
What are you all looking at?
Are you in shock
at how Vara killed the shark?
Once I jumped into the sea,
I could see nothing except
this aggressive shark.
I tore apart its fins,
punched through its ribs,
and pulled away its jaws.
Slowly it breathed
its last in my hands.
What are you staring at?
You think I found a
dead shark on some shore
tied it to my boat and brought it here?
Believe it or not. I don't care.
What a guy!
He couldn't hold up
and blurted out the truth.
Devara's son
should be a warrior.
How can Vara be so useless?
Did they ask you about it?
Why were they staring at me as
if I was incapable of killing a shark?
Of course.
Knowing you too well, they would.
You were so eager to tell them you
brought a dead shark from another shore
even before they asked you.
- Move it now.
- Hey, Vara!
I saw the ladies of your house
on the Pearl shore.
They were talking to someone who
claimed he saw Devara's belongings.
Hey, we heard you say that you saw
Devara in the Shell Mountain last night.
Did you see him for sure?
I went to that mountain
this morning to collect wood.
There were traces
of cooking in one spot.
Devara was probably
there in the night…
What else did you see?
Tell us the truth.
Did you see Devara?
No, my lady.
There were human footprints though.
No one would dare
to go there at that hour.
- I am quite certain it was Devara
- You mean…
- who spent the night there.
- Yesterday night…
Let's go home.
- Last night…
- Let's just go home.
Come in.
Everybody in the village thinks
you guys are mad.
Do you think your son has gone missing?
You are searching for him
as if you lost him in a fair!
If he had left for a job,
he would have returned once it was done.
Your son left because
he was hell-bent upon his vow.
He will not…
Don't say that he will not return.
This body will drop dead right now.
Every single day,
I survive in the hope
that he would return.
Even the sea that your son ventured into
hits the shore every day.
Years have passed.
Has he come even once to visit?
He visits me in my dreams every night.
Crossing over them someday,
won't he stand right before my eyes?
He will return.
He will return for sure.
I can understand where Grandma's
coming from. What's wrong with you?
Are you not yet done with somebody
who has abandoned his family?
Devara didn't abandon his family
when he left.
He left because he felt that these
four villages were his family.
Just like the sons of Kunjara and Devara,
even Bhaira's son, Pasura,
grew up to be a man.
I will come back next month.
You are not letting go of Chandrakala.
Are you going to be
with her forever, Pasura?
No way!
This is only until I get
Rayappa's daughter, Thangam.
I can't wait till she is mine.
Hey, Seenappa.
Heard your girl got a marriage alliance?
I wanted to talk to Thanga
regarding this matter.
Why should you talk to Thanga about it?
Did she find you the match?
Find the match?
Well, she ruined it.
My would-be son-in-law was at the tailor's
yesterday and saw your daughter, Thanga.
She looked at him coyly,
blushed, and smiled.
Assuming Thanga likes him,
he wants us to postpone tomorrow's event
of fixing the wedding day.
I need to find out what all this is about.
Call her out.
This is something the ladies
should discuss and resolve.
Let's get out of here.
I can sort this out myself.
Thanga… Thanga!
You have wrecked my daughter's life,
and you are happily washing your hair?
I didn't wreck her life.
In fact, I saved her from misery.
My smile made him drool and he asked you
to stop the wedding with your daughter.
Just imagine…
Had he seen me like this,
he would have left her
even after marriage.
How is he a good match?
Please go and explain this
to your daughter clearly.
I don't think she will let any girl
of her age get married.
Keep her under control
or this will cause a lot of problems.
Thanga, how many will you try this on?
What will you get out of ruining
everybody's alliance?
Mom! What do our girls
from the village actually want?
Everybody wants a simple
and uncomplicated husband.
But I want a macho man for myself.
Thanga wants a warrior
who will make her erupt.
If I miss someone like that
and he becomes someone else's
what would happen to me?
If the other girls wait
till I find my man,
what do they have to lose?
Why are the fruits so spoilt?
You hit me because my hand touched you?
It's because you laid your hand on me.
It will be my hands on you
someday anyway.
How many times do I tell you, Seenu?
I will consider you
only if I don't get Vara.
Can you not wait a bit for me?
His family is pressuring him
to marry his cousin.
Once he is clear about you,
he can give her some clarity too.
Yes!
Hey, Metta!
With the sun kissing my hair every day
on the sea, my hair has turned red.
Does it look fine?
You should be turning red
with smooches from girls,
but here you are talking about the sun
or the moon kissing!
What nonsense is this?
What are you mad about?
What happened?
Why are you angry?
- Nothing new.
- Uncle, one tea.
He saw Valli
and went to fool around with her.
She said she won't decide
until things get clear from your end.
Come to a conclusion
about that girl, Thanga
so that our lives will get some clarity.
Till then Valli will have her eyes on you.
Knowing she likes me,
how can you marry her, man?
She only has her eyes on you.
She is not on you, right?
Yuck! Disgusting fellow!
What is disgusting about being romantic?
Hey, Chennamma!
Hasn't your grandson recovered yet?
Are you still using medication?
If the bad omen on this village is lifted,
there will be no more illness.
Medicine is not going to help.
Without using medicines,
why carry such stupid superstitions?
What did I say?
Why did the old lady glare at me?
If Devara were here,
he would win the Ayudha puja fight,
carry the weapons
on his head,
and cleanse the hamlet
of its bad omen and bewitchment.
That's her belief.
Someone born of such noble blood
is ignorant of the value of our weapons.
It's our misfortune…
That's what her look says.
If the West side dwellers come,
give them the boat and collect the money.
I heard Chitranga made a big ruckus.
Strangely, instead of marrying Vara,
you are looking everywhere else.
He only got his dad's looks.
Not his courage.
Oh, really?
He is always so naive and timid.
How can I get along with him?
When I see my man even from a distance,
- Thanga's heart, from deep inside, must…
- Erupt and overflow.
Thanga, if you don't decide about Vara,
things will get complicated.
That guy Metta Seenu is fiddling with me
wherever he finds me.
Why didn't you slap him?
How could I slap him?
If she suddenly takes a fancy to Vara
and takes off with him,
Seenu will be my only option.
Then you should give him your consent.
How could I?
If she ends up disliking Vara,
won't he fall between the cracks?
Damn! How disgusting!
If she turns down Vara,
you want to go ahead with him.
If she accepts Vara,
Seenu is waiting to warm up to you.
- Oh, God!
- How would you understand this, sister?
Just a year after you came of age,
you were married off.
You can afford to say anything.
We are in our youth
but sadly with no companion.
Two days ago, when they were returning
from fishing on the sea,
a shark had leaped onto their boat,
and Vara apparently jumped into the sea
and killed it with his bare hands.
Who? Was it our Vara?
Yes! Seemingly, he also dragged
the dead shark to the shore himself.
He has it in him.
He definitely has it in him.
I know!
He does have something.
I have known him since we were kids.
He has it in him.
Oh, my goodness!
Watch him walk like a champion.
I am thrilled and enthralled from within.
Hi, Thanga, how are you?
I heard you jumped into the sea,
killed a shark with your bare hands,
and dragged it to the shore.
Your vigor, your valor…
I know about it.
What you saw is nothing.
There is a lot more to see.
Looks like they both are a thing.
It's just the two of us now.
I wanted to gift that boat
to my future husband.
I finished building it today.
Do you like it?
Sure, it looks nice.
How come… you've shown up here?
I could have come, had you called me.
I have come for Rayappa.
My goodness!
Have you gone to the extent
of talking to my father about us?
- Take this.
- Okay, Rayappa.
What brings you here, Vara?
Ayudha puja is upon us.
I wanted to speak to you about it.
What are you implying by that?
Oh, my goodness!
I might run out of breath today.
My knight is getting ready
for Ayudha puja.
- Are you planning to fight in the arena?
- What are you saying?
Have you got drunk in the morning?
Why will I get into the arena?
They will kill me.
That's what I thought.
Hey, Thangam…
Oh, no!
What happened, Thanga?
Remove your hand.
Go away.
Damn, you!
Everybody is sad that our village hasn't
received the weapons for a long time.
Maybe we should go to Bhaira
and plead with him…
to give us the weapons
without a contest this time.
I am too scared to go to him alone.
I was hoping you would accompany me.
We can go.
- Remove your hand.
- Why is that?
The link is broken there.
Let me not break my slipper.
I knew it.
I knew he didn't have it in him.
I knew he wasn't right for me
ever since we were kids.
I knew there was nothing in him.
What is he staring at, Rayappa?
Is he thinking about how these trees
grew from the water?
What made you come here, Rayappa?
That too with a cub for company.
It's been years since the weapons
have reached their village.
They are sad that nothing good
is happening there.
You know that Ayudha puja is upon us.
If you can hand us the weapons this year,
we will keep them in our village,
and give them back.
Whichever village wanted the weapons,
Devara would represent that village,
fight, and win the weapons for them.
You are his son
and you are begging for the weapons?
How many times have I told you?
I am not like him.
Please accept me as I am.
Am I not one of you?
I request you to give us the weapons
just this one time.
We were inside for nine minutes.
Instead of coming to me,
go to the sea…
and say, "Our village has no hero
or a valiant man. So, please, come."
Bellow and call him.
Maybe that will make your father
enter the arena for your sake.
Are we ending this with a celebration
like every year…
or is there going to be a fight?
If the ladies and children leave,
we are ready to fight.
Get the arena ready, guys.
Hey, wait up.
Ranga! Ranga!
Vara! Vara!
- Vara! Vara!
- Vara!
- Garuda!
Vara! Vara!
Hit him hard.
Come on.
- We are done with both the contenders
- Hit him!
from the West side.
Hey…
I will see to it that he is no more.
Is it enough to knock him down…
or should I bury him?
Defeat is worse than death.
His cry of pain due to defeat
should reach Devara all the way.
- Sena! Sena!
Strike him down!
Come!
Sena! Sena!
Vara!
We have finished two per village, Bhaira.
We are done with the fight.
The weapons will remain
in front of your house.
Watching them might help you
to get up and walk soon, Varada.
Have you heard what happened, Rayappa?
Vara drugged everyone
at the Ayudha puja
and won the competition.
When we know it all, why are we
still having this discussion?
Permit me.
I will go to his village, knock him down,
and bring back the weapons.
Tell me what we should do to him, Rayappa.
It's better to forget it
as if nothing happened, Bhaira.
If they fell because they were drugged,
they should have been sober
by morning.
But they aren't able to get up
from their beds.
During the Ayudha puja,
you only saw timidness in his eyes.
But I saw the technique in his fists.
I saw Devara-like strength in him.
Unaware of his own strength,
he tried to win by drugging everyone
because of his innocence.
In a way, that's the best-case scenario
for all of you.
There is already one Devara in the sea.
Creating another Devara on the mountain…
will not be good for you, Bhaira.
Husband and liquor have
a special connection.
I just don't understand.
How can he win by sedating everyone?
Sister, I imagined my husband
to be as mighty as the sea.
This guy…
seems like a small wave
that touches the shore.
I am your senior with a lot of experience.
Take my advice.
Every woman has a heartthrob,
different from the one she marries.
If you can see your heartthrob
in the man you marry
and save your marriage,
life can get surprisingly pleasant.
How is that possible?
When Thanga looks at her man,
she should erupt
- and overflow from inside.
- What nonsense!
Stop it right there.
Leave him alone, if you don't like him.
- I will take care of him.
- Hey!
Somehow, I still feel
hopeful about him.
What are you hoping for?
You want someone like Devara
and he doesn't exist on this mountain.
Should I just wait till Devara returns
and marry him?
Hey, have you lost your mind?
What do I do then?
My dear Thanga,
we don't get whatever we want.
We must mold whatever we get
and hone it to perfection.
Unless you ignite a desire in him
to marry you,
why would he try to be
your knight or warrior?
What is Thangam?
How great is her beauty?
He should see it…
and get tantalized.
Look at her yap!
Encompasses me like a fond guest
Your mischievous gaze
It doesn't stay still even for a moment
All the time, I am lost in your world
If you can, please, do stop me
Come, the comfort of my sleep
I have given it away to your dreams
I wait for you on the threshold
Of my youth
Come! I have gathered all my hopes
And stamped them on your heart
I have set the stage for your arrival
For some reason it is born
This fascination for you is born
And with it is born my madness for you
Naming itself after you
Allure has dressed itself in a half-sari
With hands colored in henna
Making vows to my lord
Encompasses me like a fond guest
It does encompass me
This mischievous gaze
It doesn't stay still even for a moment
Casts me a net of intoxication
Your chivalrous charisma
Why don't you come closer
And cuddle me?
I have nurtured this priceless charm
In all symmetry
Take possession of it little by little
Invade me with your kisses
For your mischief is most welcome
Why don't you touch me at least once
Even if by mistake?
Hey, come!
This necklace of gold
Doesn't please me at all
Deck me up with your hugs
Oh, come!
No lullaby by the full moon
Is able to put me to sleep
Consider my pain a little
For some reason it is born
This fascination for you is born
And with it is born my madness for you
Naming itself after you
Allure has dressed itself in a half-sari
With hands colored in henna
Making vows to my lord
Encompasses me like a fond guest
It does encompass me
This mischievous gaze
It doesn't stay still even for a moment
If everyone is sharpening their weapons,
I guess it's time
to put them to use.
We've been anxiously waiting
for your approval, Bhaira.
Are we going to the sea to fight him
anytime soon?
Bhaira…
The coast guard authorities
have opened up jobs
for expert swimmers
to help them in the sea.
I heard the pay is excellent too.
We could make good use of the training
you gave us all these years.
If you say yes, all of us
will find jobs on the sea, Bhaira.
Were all these years of my teaching
and practice meant for this…
or for Devara?
When we get busy with our jobs,
Devara will have no job to do, Bhaira.
Think it over until tomorrow.
How can you give in to his words, Bhaira?
I have kept him with me
since he was a kid.
I wanted him to reach my level,
but time and again,
I see more and more traits
of Devara in him.
Where did I fall short?
You gave us everything.
You are everything to us.
We are just like you, Bhaira.
He did grow up with us,
but for a while, we could only see
Devara in him, Bhaira.
How are you, Bhaira?
How come you called for me
after a long time?
It's time to get into the sea again.
The army I have raised over the years
is ready to enter the sea,
quell any level of danger,
and carry the cargo to the shore.
- What about Devara?
- Along with your consignment,
his head will be brought too.
Bhaira, Bhaira…
I cannot dare to do that
as long as Devara is alive.
If something goes wrong,
I will lose my consignment.
There is a good chance
he will end my life too.
Unless we get into the sea for the cargo,
why would Devara show up?
How will they kill him?
Could be true…
But I am not taking that chance.
Draw Devara out somehow
and send me word
that you got rid of him, Bhaira.
I will get a new consignment every week
and bring glory back to this mountain.
But only if you kill Devara.
Muruga said he will not procure shipments
unless Devara is dead.
For that to happen,
Devara must be brought out.
Hence Bhaira spread a rumor about it.
Everybody in our village thinks
Devara is not alive anymore.
I heard about it too.
Nobody has seen him till now.
Even his family hasn't seen his face.
It seems quite true.
The West and the East dwellers say
Devara is no more.
Is that true?
The North side and some of our own
are saying the same.
Even I doubt if Devara is alive.
Having heard what she feared most
all her life,
his mother's health deteriorated
and they took her
to Jogulamma's for treatment.
It is not medicine
that will cure her, Vara.
This is the angst of a mother.
She cannot fully recover
unless she sees her son Devara.
Knowing too well
that Devara would turn up
before his sick mom's health got worse,
Bhaira surrounded Jogulamma's house
day and night along with his men.
We have been waiting for him
for the past three nights.
Do you think he will show up, Bhaira?
He has to come at least for his mother.
Devara…
Did you have food?
- Hey!
- Bhaira!
Devara was here.
We must finish him before
he leaves the mountain.
There he is!
Hey!
Everybody on the mountain got to know
that Devara had paid a visit.
How is he doing?
Good as always.
His hair has slightly gone gray.
That's all.
Why do we care?
Why should we care how he is?
Are you still not through with him
after all these years?
He came to see the old lady as a formality
not out of his love for us.
When will you understand that
he will not return for you and me?
Damn it!
Bhaira, who was fuming because Devara
was almost under his sword
but got away again,
had another opportunity
knocking at his door.
When Devara, who should have charged
at you the moment he saw you, instead
sneaked away from you, it became
obvious that he had lost his vigor.
A ship containing our consignment
will pass by the Red Sea this coming week.
Are you and your troops
ready for this, Bhaira?
As you promised,
along with the shipment, make sure
you bring Devara's head too, Bhaira.
Coming Saturday, Bhaira.
Bhaira was elated to enter
the sea after many years…
but no one could have imagined
the event that followed.
What happened?
What's wrong, Bhaira?
What happened to your hand?
Out of fear of fighting
with Bhaira in the sea,
Devara must have done this.
His plan better not work, Bhaira.
Last night,
I know it was you who did this.
Bhaira…
Though you lost your father,
I treated you like my own son.
How dare you!
As a kid, since the moment
I saw my dad's body lying on the shore,
I haven't had a good sleep.
I have been hankering to kill him,
wash my hair with his blood,
and get my revenge!
But if you get into the sea
and face Devara,
his death will be on your plate.
The one who killed Kunjara
should be killed by this son of Kunjara's.
If that should happen,
you must refrain from coming.
In order to kill Devara,
it is not strength that you need Bhaira.
This is good enough.
Every one of us going there
has more than we need.
The coming week,
when we venture into the sea,
even if we see Devara from a
mile away, we shall kill him and return.
What happened, Uma?
I am scared, Mom.
Uma?
I went into the forest for henna,
and Bhaira's men stopped me
on my way back.
Hey!
Move aside.
How brave!
Not a trace of fear in your voice.
Is it because you are Devara's daughter?
They said, "Your dad,
Devara, will be dead soon.
Once he is dead, one of us
will take you each day."
We shall take out all our pent-up anger
on your mother and you each night.
There is surely a man in your house.
But no way he can save you.
"It is beyond your brother's ability
to protect you.
Neither can the locals do anything."
They were talking all this rubbish.
I feel like dying, Mom.
Nobody from this mountain
will ever dare touch Devara's daughter.
But if it does happen,
like you suggested,
we will all drink poison and die.
What's up, Vara?
Why are you here?
Did your sister come
and complain to you?
I wish she told me.
But she went crying to my mother
and told her.
She didn't consider me man enough
to tell her problems to.
You are a coward who can't win a contest
without sedating others!
Why will they consider you a man
or a hero?
Even I am drunk right now.
For the spite in me to thrash you,
why don't you see whether my intoxication
helps it or hinders it?
Rayappa…
Vara knocked up Bhaira's men
at the toddy shop.
What happened?
Bhaira's men troubled Vara's sister
when she was returning from the forest.
Vara smacked them down
when he got to know about this.
- Vara? Really?
- Yes.
How did he do it?
Has anybody seen him do it?
People at the toddy shop said
he beat them till they bled.
Oh, my goodness!
I knew it.
I knew that he had it in him
since we were kids.
He will not tolerate any advances
made towards me or his sister.
I knew it, Dad! I knew it!
I knew it. I did!
O' luscious murrel
I shall make a curry of you
The spices on the stove
Are boiling to stew
Your cute crony
Shall offer you her youth
And give you a passionate maiden feast
Your sidelong glances act
Like incense of moonlight
Girl, you have put me
On a winged horse
The prime of youth lures the hungry lion
Let me put the dark night to sleep
Look at your waist
Thin as a wasp's
How you chiseled it to a smooth finish
Cut the distance
With spirits soaring high
Surrender to the cupid for you
Are caught for good
Vara is here, Singappa!
What were you up to last night?
Bhaira's men were troubling my sister.
I drank some to build courage
and bashed them up.
Hey!
Yes, I got drunk and beat them.
What about it?
They are dead from your beating.
How can they be dead?
It wasn't me, Singappa.
We have been oblivious
to your strength just like you.
You lived as a coward around us.
But we should have known
that you are Devara's blood.
Since you thrashed
the people from that village,
Bhaira's men are about to charge on us!
If you take the lead we are ready
to kill them all, Vara.
Have you gone mad?
Keep calm and get to work.
I will go and explain myself to Bhaira.
Go!
I really don't know
how they died, Bhaira.
If I said that I am capable of killing,
would you believe it?
I dragged a dead shark to the shore…
Such is my courage.
I spiked everybody's drink
and won the weapons.
Such is my strength.
At least you should wonder
how I could do this, Bhaira.
He misbehaved with my sister
so I got angry and slapped him.
But how can you hold me responsible
for his death?
You must convince everyone
that I am one of you, Bhaira.
Though you are Devara's son,
you are not his man.
For everyone to believe
that you are one of us,
you must join hands with our people
and do what they do.
After many years,
your peers are venturing
into the sea tonight.
They are going to fight your dad
and bring the consignment.
Vara…
If you join them, then from tomorrow
you will become one of us and stay safe.
You want to go to the waters
guarded by Devara.
If something goes wrong,
I will not be able to handle it, son.
I thought you were feeding me out of love.
Is it out of fear of my death
that you are overfilling my plate?
You are all praise about the man
who killed your husband!
Was I born to Kunjara or Devara?
You seem to be in quite a good mood today.
Oh, I heard you are setting out
to the sea tomorrow.
If Devara does something to you,
we cannot meet again. Is that the reason?
Nobody's happy that Vara, who killed
our men, is accompanying us, Bhaira.
It wasn't Vara who killed him.
It was me.
Without me,
it is not as easy as Kunjara's son
thinks it is to kill Devara.
With Vara being a part of this team,
Devara will be caught in a moment
of doubt and confusion.
It is for this reason
that I killed our guy last night
and brought Vara to his knees before me.
What are you worried about?
Are you stressed about
what to do if your dad shows up?
Hold this.
In case you happen to face Devara,
this will come in handy.
Why would I need this?
I don't want it.
Are you confident that you will kill him
without using this?
Come on, Devara.
Hey!
Hang on, guys.
It's not Devara,
it's a shark.
Devara is here.
Tonight, we will head back only
with Devara's head in our hands.
Come on!
Singappa!
Along with the sons of Kunjara and Bhaira,
Vara has secretly gone
to the sea on a heist.
They are defying Devara, Singappa.
They must have influenced my son.
And believing them like a lamb,
he must have joined their herd.
Please do something
and stop him, Singappa.
You know my husband, Devara,
better than I do.
Will he spare a wrongdoer
even if it is his own son?
In spite of my incessant pleading,
why doesn't anyone say a word?
Have you also joined hands with them?
While acting like our own,
are you also trying to kill Devara?
All of you who are resorting
to forbidden activities,
including Vara, his own son,
will not be spared by my husband, Devara.
Your husband left all of us
a long time ago, dear.
Our Devara left us
and went to God long ago.
Guarding the sea all these years
and forbidding everyone
from committing a crime…
isn't your husband, Devara.
It is your son, Vara.
The sea is blue
But it's his Red Sea
All hail!
He grew up listening
to the stories from Devara.
To uphold fear in this mountain,
he scripted a very big story
that Devara is alive.
All hail!
Did you think that
under the influence of those beasts,
he followed them like a lamb?
That's not true.
Those who took him
as their pawn are the lambs.
By now, your son must be
hunting them down
like a monster in the sea!
Since you don't know him,
it might seem like
he has gone into the sea.
But to us who have been
watching him for years,
he himself appears to be a mighty sea.
Not them.
Go kill your dad, Devara,
and bring him here!
Who? Me?
Yes!
Now that you have heard of Devara's death,
I can imagine your anguish tonight.
But your son's dance of fury
on the Red Sea
to keep Devara's promise…
will make you forget your pain.
All hail!
O' courage, ready to leap! Careful!
Don't you dare…
Don't you dare come face to face
What are you before Devara?
Hide yourself…
All hail!
All hail! All hail the tiger!
All hail…
O' courage, ready to leap! Careful!
Don't you dare…
Don't you dare come face to face
What are you before Devara?
Hide yourself…
Twelve long years ago,
on the same shore,
watching people hanging from a boat,
a generation had discovered fear
and stopped their activities.
Now finding these men on this boat,
another generation
will come to a standstill.
Do you think the next generation will
grow up without fear, Singappa?
Even if somebody thinks
of entering the sea again,
it would remain a dream.
The waves that saw your play,
will testify to it, Vara.
I went with them to confront Devara.
To keep the story I wrote "alive."
What are you saying, Vara?
You want me to drive this weapon into you
and watch your blood flow?
To do that and to watch it…
This old heart is too weak
to bear the pain.
This weapon is
the God we worship, Singappa.
Do it for the sake of the mountain.
Do it.
I cannot do this, Vara.
Singappa…
Singappa!
Don't worry about
the pain in my eyes, Singappa.
Just focus on the fear
in everyone else’s eyes tomorrow.
The sea, which had only witnessed
weapons and blood,
probably broke into tears
over what Vara did.
It reached out to touch his feet that day.
Who was capable of killing Devara?
Who could have driven a knife
through Devara?