[wind whooshing gently]
[eerie music playing]
[insects trilling]
[Samuel] First, it came to Momma
as a snake...
[frog croaking]
then it took other forms
to torment her.
But Momma was a good little girl,
she listened to her parents
and always stayed on the rope
so The Evil couldn't touch her
outside the house.
Because if The Evil touches you,
it makes you do bad things.
[tense music sting]
- [screams]
- [gasps, pants]
[Momma] O blessed house of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
We'll keep you bright and never roam.
Heaven is here within our home.
- [doorknob clacks]
- [door creaks]
- [frog croaking]
- [insects trilling]
[door creaks]
[owl hoots]
- [animal whooshes]
- [door thuds]
[frog croaking]
[floorboard creaking]
- [frog croaking]
- [owl hooting]
[croaking continues]
[croaking intensifies]
- [grunting in distance]
- [gasps]
[shuddering breaths]
[growling]
[groaning, growling]
- [growling]
- [gasps]
[growling stops]
[door thuds]
- [Momma sighs deeply]
- [door creaks]
[clanking]
[exhales]
[footsteps thudding]
[door creaking]
[snoring]
- [Koda breathing rapidly]
- [snoring continues]
Samuel, Nolan.
Ten-minute warning, boys.
[Koda whines]
[footsteps receding]
Nine-minute warning, Nolan.
- [bed creaking]
- [bell jingling]
[Samuel] Momma says
there's only love inside of us.
That's why The Evil wants us so badly.
He wants to destroy this love,
- make us turn against each other...
- [Koda whines]
kill each other...
like he made the people in the world do.
[footsteps receding]
[bell jingling]
[Samuel] All it needs is one touch
without the rope on.
And then, not even the house can save you.
[ominous music playing]
[fire crackling]
[utensils and plates clinking]
[footsteps tapping]
[Koda whines]
[Nolan sighing]
[Momma] Eat it. Get it.
There you go.
Frogs sang loud last night.
- Spring is coming.
- We'll be ready.
It's a good day for a good day.
[Koda grunts]
Don't feed the dog.
We're not the only ones starving.
- And I don't need to eat as much as you.
- [Momma sighs]
Momma?
Momma, can we listen to it tonight'?
- It's not a new moon.
- I'm asking Momma.
We should wait.
It won't be special if we don't.
Told ya.
[Nolan grunting softly]
[sighs deeply]
You'll grow into 'em.
[door creaking]
[all] The Evil can't touch me here.
Dawn to night and year to year.
The forest where this thing is bound,
wrapped up tight and safe and sound.
- [wind whooshing gently]
- [leaves rustling]
[Koda whines]
[Koda panting]
[eerie music sting]
Do you see it?
Go get him, Koda.
Bring us a big, fat rabbit.
[Momma] Y'all ready?
Never let go.
[dark music playing]
[Samuel] Momma told us that even before
The Evil possessed everyone,
the world was already bad.
[creaking]
And that's Why it came.
The people opened their door for it,
whether they knew it or not.
[indistinct voices]
[voice] Let them go...
[Samuel] But Grandma knew it,
and Grandpa was the only one
to believe her.
He was a good man
and built this place for her,
a blessed house where The Evil
wouldn't be able to come in,
a place to raise a family far away
from the darkness of the world.
It was a good life.
But after a while, Grandma started to feel
a presence lurking in the woods,
something evil getting stronger.
She refused to leave the house anymore.
So Grandpa figured out how to tie the rope
to the foundation of the house
so she could finally go outside.
[ominous music plays]
[exhales, grunts]
[ominous breathing]
[wind whooshing]
[voice] Let them go, Junebug.
[bird caws]
[squeaking]
[thudding]
[grunts]
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
[whimsical music playing]
[panting, grunting]
[frog croaking]
[crunching]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[effort grunting]
Nolan.
What are you doing?
Making some slack so I can grab this egg.
Don't.
Could be a trick.
I could grab it. It's right there.
Give me your machete.
No.
We'll let Momma decide.
She can tie the ropes together.
[blows]
[leaves rustle]
I wasn't gonna let go.
We didn't get this far
just to die of hunger.
How can you be so sure of everything?
[Samuel] Because I'm older than you.
[Nolan] Yeah, by three minutes.
[Samuel] She loves me more.
What?
[ominous music plays]
- What?
- What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
[ominous music buildup]
[yells, grunts]
Sam!
- [cracks]
- [yells]
Sam! [whistle blowing]
[gasps]
Sam!
- [whistle blowing]
- [grunting]
Nolan!
Samuel!
[groaning]
[whistle blowing]
[Nolan] Sam!
My rope.
- [gasps]
- [groans]
[cracking, rustling]
- [Samuel grunting]
- [rattling]
[Nolan] Samuel!
[rattling intensifies]
Sam!
Sam! [grunting]
Samuel!
- [whimpering]
- Sam!
[panting]
Nolan!
No!
- Get back on the rope!
- [Nolan grunting]
[grunting]
[effort grunting, panting]
[growls, hisses]
[Samuel groaning]
[growling]
- [knife clinks]
- [growling]
- [grunting]
- [growling, hissing]
No!
No! No! No! No!
[grunting]
[hissing]
[panting]
- [panting]
- [groaning]
Did it touch you? Huh?
- [panting]
- [groaning]
Did it touch you, Nolan?
I don't... I don't think so.
[growling]
[Momma] Hold on to the rope.
[hissing]
[Nolan] What do you see?
Momma, what is it?
- [grunting]
- Breathe. Just breathe.
[breathing shakily]
[gurgling, hissing]
- [Samuel grunting]
- [Momma] Breathe. Breathe.
It's okay. It's okay. Just breathe.
Just breathe.
[shuddering, breathing heavily]
[Samuel grunting]
[Momma] On your knees. I need to be sure.
[clinks]
Don't look at me. Touch the wood!
Hands on the cellar.
Say it.
Say it!
[both] O blessed house of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
We'll keep you bright and never roam.
Heaven is here within our home.
Okay, get up.
- [Samuel groaning]
- [grunting]
- [Momma] What happened?
- [Nolan] I didn't mean to.
- I stepped on his rope...
- Have you lost your mind?
- It's all right, Momma. He didn't...
- Quiet!
One more second
and it would've all been over
for all of us!
That rope is your lifeline.
- [Nolan] I'm sorry.
- I don't need you to be sorry!
I need you to use your head!
[groaning, panting]
- [shoe thuds]
- [exhales sharply]
Oh...
Can you move it?
[Samuel groans]
I think it's broke.
[jars clinking]
Don't just stand there.
Get me a splint for his ankle.
[footsteps receding]
[groaning]
- I know, I know.
- [whimpering]
Come on. Come on.
- It's okay.
- [groaning]
What'd it look like this time?
Like my Momma.
It's trying to scare me...
like it tried to scare my Momma before.
[chair creaking]
[ominous music playing]
[rustling]
[hissing]
[Momma] That's all we got today.
Don't eat too fast.
Sure is good.
[sighs]
[Momma] I used to be thankful
that The Evil didn't show itself to you.
And then, I figured out what it was doing.
I never told y'all this.
But one time,
it came to me as a little girl,
crying out for help.
She was just at my rope's limit.
She got her foot stuck in a gopher hole.
She was howling, screaming.
[screaming]
I saw the bone
sticking out.
I had to keep telling myself
that it wasn't real.
But the screams went on for days.
So every morning, I went out to check...
to see if The Evil had given up.
But she was still there.
Her skin turned blue and gray.
[flies buzzing]
The smell...
[ominous music sting]
I wondered why she was still out there.
Why?
Because it wanted me
to go see about that girl.
It wanted me to doubt myself.
To lure me off the rope.
The Evil is clever
and patient.
It's like the snake
you've seen in the woods.
Evil can wear many, many skins.
And the greatest trick of all
is playing on you, boys.
And when enough time goes by,
you're gonna forget it's even there.
You're gonna let your guard down.
- And it's gonna get you!
- [gasps]
One touch
without a rope on
is all it takes to possess one of us
and get inside the house.
Never...
let go.
- Never let go.
[floorboard creaking]
[breathing shakily]
[door creaks, opens]
How long?
About an hour.
Felt longer tonight.
Did you imagine it?
Yes.
Tell us about it.
I imagined it was all gone.
You...
Sam...
Koda.
The house.
All I had left was the darkness.
And then what?
I thought about our birth in the house
and how safe it keeps us every day.
And I felt the darkness float away.
Look around.
Look how lucky you are.
All your dreams came true.
The Evil can't touch you here.
Samuel, your turn.
Time to clean your soul.
Remember, lose us completely
and then find us again.
Fill the cellar up with all your love.
You remind the house
Why we deserve its protection.
[door closes]
- [thunder rumbling
- [rain pattering]
[Samuel] Can I move yet?
[Nolan] Nope.
Nolan, I got an itch.
I said, "Don't move."
It's just one itch.
Okay.
That should do it.
Wow. Are those owl wings?
Uh-huh.
I can fly anywhere I want.
And eat whatever you want.
Once upon a time,
there was a boy who could fly
and catch all the squirrels in the trees.
[hooting]
[both chuckling]
Hey, Sam.
After your rope broke,
did you notice anything?
Like what?
Anything strange.
That was the first time we ever let go.
And nothing changed.
'Cause it didn't get us.
Yeah.
If it did...
do you think Momma woulda killed us?
Like she killed Poppa?
Like she killed Grandma and Grandpa?
The Evil touched them.
She was protecting us.
I know that.
[book thuds]
[thunder rumbling]
What?
Nothing.
You ever wish you could run free
like Koda?
Without a rope around your chest?
But Koda's a dog.
The Evil doesn't care about animals.
[thunder crashing]
[thunder rumbling]
You ever wish you could see what she sees?
Just once?
I felt something getting closer today.
You were just scared.
Why are you asking all these questions?
Momma never lied to us.
[thunder rumbling]
"She loves me more."
That's what I heard you say
before I stepped on your rope.
I didn't say that.
I didn't mean for what happened.
I know.
[thunder rumbling]
[blade clinking]
[chair creaking]
[rustling]
[man] O blessed house...
of ancient wood.
Home...
to my runaway wife.
Hey, Junebug.
What's wrong?
June!
June, it's me.
It's been a while.
God, have I missed you.
You think I can see 'em?
Oh, you ain't told 'em the truth
about their father.
I get it.
'Cause then you got to tell 'em
who you really are.
Ain't that right, my little Junebug?
I'm not her no more.
You know you loved it.
- What's your plan?
- [door creaks]
I know ya.
You ain't got no plan.
You might as well give 'em to me.
Or would you rather watch them starve?
I came so close today.
Sooner or later...
you're gonna let go.
And when you do...
I'm gonna... [distorted]
make you eat your babies.
June!
- [distorted] June!
- [door slams]
Careful now. Don't break those roots.
You think it'll get better?
Hard to say.
The winter did a number on us.
All we can do now is hope.
What?
Nothing.
The snake on your back...
You said you got it
when you were in the city.
But you also said The Evil
was already there, killing everybody.
- I don't understand...
- I got it before it all started.
When I met your Poppa.
I was a different person back then.
Does it still scare you?
Not anymore. I like it now.
Why?
Because it's from your life before.
In the old world.
A world full of pain and suffering?
What's to like about that?
Huh?
Don't know.
When I was your age,
asking questions like you do...
I didn't really believe my Momma, either.
- That's why you left?
- Mm-hmm.
Never thought I'd come back here.
But it's the only place
I could keep y'all safe.
But what if The Evil did, touch one of us
and come in the house?
What would happen?
It would make us kill each other.
That's how the world ended.
But how do you know we're alone?
Maybe our house isn't the only one
that's protected.
Would that make you feel better?
We wouldn't be alone
for the rest of our lives.
We're not alone, Nolan.
We have each other.
And that's everything.
There's nobody else out there, baby.
We're the world now.
[uneasy music playing]
[Momma] "Once upon a time,
there dwelt near a large wood
a poor woodcutter,
with his wife and two children...
a little boy called Hansel
and a girl called Gretel.
Once, when there was a great famine
in the land,
he could not procure
even his daily bread."
[grunts]
"As they lay there thinking
in the bed one evening,
rolling about for trouble...
he sighed and said to his wife,
'What will become of us?
How will I feed my children
when we have no more
that we can eat ourselves?'
'Know, then, my husband, ' answered she,
'we will lead them away,
quite early in the morning
into the thickest part of the woods.
And there make them a fire
and give them each
a little piece of bread.'
[effort grunting, yelling]
'And then we will go to our work
and leave them alone.
They will not find a way home again.
And we shall be freed from them.
- [Nolan] It's new.
- [Samuel] You sure?
You got eyes, don't you?
It's a new moon. Right, Momma?
Can we listen to it tonight?
[whirring]
["The Big Rock Candy Mountain"
by Van Hunt playing]
[Koda whines]
[Nolan chuckles]
Come on, Momma.
[song continues playing]
[song muffles, fades]
[unsettling music playing]
[breathing heavily]
- [exhales]
- [floorboard creaks]
[ominous music playing]
Nolan?
Nolan.
[water splashes]
Are you still asleep?
Nolan.
There you go.
[grunts] You forgot your bell again.
[bell jingling]
- [rain pattering]
- [thunder rumbling]
[grunts gently]
[stream flowing]
[wind whooshing gently]
[sighs]
[grunts]
[raven cawing]
[cawing]
[cawing, munching]
[gasps]
[raven caws]
[cawing]
- [cracks]
- [caws]
[breathing heavily]
[screams]
- [thudding]
- [breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[uneasy music playing]
It's better with sap.
Yeah. That'll make it
taste less like a tree.
[Momma] We're doing the best we can.
Eat.
[rustling]
[blade clinks, thuds]
[bell jingles]
Momma?
Sam?
[bell jingles]
[rustling]
[grunts, screams]
No!
No! [grunting]
No! No!
- [insects trilling]
- [gasping]
[bell jingles]
[breathing shakily]
- [animal growls]
- [frog croaks]
[rustling]
[breathing heavily]
Koda.
[door thuds]
[floorboard thudding]
[Momma] Touch the wood.
Say it!
O blessed house of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
We'll keep you bright and never roam.
Heaven is here within our home.
[Momma] Say it again.
O blessed house of ancient wood...
Again!
- O blessed house of ancient wood.
- Louder!
Shelter to the pure and good!
[bell jingling]
[Nolan whimpers] Momma...
Momma!
I have to pee, Momma!
Did you feel the darkness go away?
[creaking]
[owl hooting]
[uneasy music playing]
Sam...
You awake?
[Samuel] No.
Sam.
Sam!
Yes?
We need to leave the house.
Goodnight, Nolan.
I'm serious.
- Sam!
- [shushes]
How do you wanna leave?
The Evil will catch us
as soon as we take off the rope.
We know the forest.
If we look after each other,
we might have a chance to outrun it.
What about Momma?
We'll come back for her
once we find something to eat.
Momma knows what's right for us.
I don't think she does anymore.
Did you see her?
She's starving too.
[Samuel] She always figures something out.
[Nolan] For once, we have to help her.
[Samuel] By disobeying her?
Will you really let go of the rope?
I can let go of the rope,
but I can't let go of my brother.
It's too dangerous.
I'm sorry.
[distant crunching sound]
- [hisses]
- [tense music sting]
[Koda barks, pants]
[soft music plays]
[grunting]
[sniffles]
[exhales sharply]
This is a very special tool.
It's called a camera.
What does it do'?
Takes pictures.
It captures what it sees
with this little eye.
You aim it,
then you push
this button right here, and...
[whooshing]
A real-life picture comes out.
Like this one.
This was me...
from the old world.
Is that really you?
- [grunts]
- Hey, hey, careful.
I was a different person back then.
Or this one.
I took it outside on the porch.
Sam.
- This is us?
- Mm-hmm.
And this is Koda.
- [whines]
- [Momma] Yep.
You can take a picture
of anything you want.
But a good picture shows more
than what the camera's looking at.
It shows a special moment, frozen in time.
They can even show a feeling.
Like love.
Where's Poppa?
He was holding the camera.
Do you have a picture of him?
Mm-mm.
These are the only two I chose to keep.
And there's one more in there too.
I've been saving it.
For when?
Look for the right moment.
Maybe you'll find one that reminds us
What we're living for.
Even if it's something small.
'Cause some moments in life are hard.
But when we remember why we're holding on,
we get strong again.
This right here
is about to be one of those hard moments.
We've been through some brutal,
brutal winters, haven't we?
But nothing like this one.
Everything in the garden, gone.
The roots are waterlogged.
The animals, they ain't come back yet.
We got water.
But that'll last us, maybe...
a couple weeks.
Maybe a month.
But soon...
our bodies...
are gonna start shutting down.
And we're gonna die.
So we only got one option.
And that's Koda.
What?
We can salt the meat.
Maybe it'll last us a month or so
and before it's spoiled...
No!
I know you love him. We all do.
But he nearing the end of his life,
and he...
- he ain't caught us nothing in months.
- We can eat more frogs.
That's not gonna be enough.
I'll eat the bark, the bugs.
I don't mind it, Momma. I swear.
- Nolan.
- Maybe it's safe to leave.
I was out there without a rope on.
The Evil coulda touched me, but it didn't.
'Cause it chose not to.
It wants you to doubt me.
And look...
- that's exactly what you're doing.
- What if you're wrong?
What if the world is still out there?
This is the world!
There's nothing out there!
[slams table]
It's either the house or The Evil.
That's it!
No. This is evil.
Eating family is evil!
If we can't feed ourselves,
how are we gonna feed the dog?
- You wanna die?
- I don't wanna die,
but I don't wanna see my friend die!
But this is not fair!
All he's done is protect us!
Let's ask Samuel.
Of course he'll do what you say.
He can talk for hisself.
Samuel?
We have to.
I hate you!
I hate both of you! I hate this house!
I hate this house!
Come on, Koda.
[door slams]
Momma, I can do it if you want.
No.
[door opens, creaks]
[footsteps approaching]
[Koda whines]
[Nolan] No.
- No!
- [Koda whimpers]
No. No!
No! No! No!
Koda! Koda!
No!
No! Momma, please!
Please, no!
Koda!
Please!
[cries]
You're a good dog.
[voice breaking] I thank you
for taking good care of us.
[Koda whimpers]
[sobbing]
[kisses, sobs] You're a good dog.
[crossbow clacks]
[breathes deeply]
[Koda whimpers, pants]
- [Koda whimpers]
- [groans]
[sobs, exhales deeply]
[Koda whimpers]
Momma.
[gasps]
- Nolan.
- It's not real.
Listen to me.
You need to see.
You need to see
there's nothing to be scared of!
That's what it wants you to think, baby.
Don't do it! No! Don't do it. No!
- Nolan! Open this door. Nolan!
- [bangs door]
Open the door.
- Nolan!
- [bangs door]
Nolan, I-I lied.
I didn't tell you everything.
I brought The Evil here.
The Evil is real!
And if it touches me
and gets inside the house,
it's gonna make me kill you!
Open the door.
Please!
[screams] Open the fucking door!
[grunting]
Nolan!
- [Samuel roars]
- [grunts]
[both grunting]
[grunting]
- [Grandma] Bad little goat.
- [Momma panting]
- [gasps]
- Bad little goat.
Bad little goat...
[distorted] caught sitting in my chair.
Let's see that tushy, and I'll make it
so you can't sit anywhere.
It's here!
- [grunting]
- It's here!
- Momma!
- [grunting]
[shakily] It's here.
[bleating] Bad!
Bad!
Bad little goat,
putting poison in my food.
Bad little goat.
[distorted bleating] Bad!
I told you, I'm gonna make you
eat your baby.
You'll never get in.
No!
[squelching, gurgling]
[glass thuds]
- [gasps]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
Momma!
Momma?
Wake up, Momma.
Momma, wake up!
It's okay, Momma.
I'm tying the ropes together.
It's okay, Momma. It's okay.
Momma, please.
O blessed house of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
We'll keep you bright and never roam.
Heaven is here within our home.
Momma, please.
The house has us now, Momma.
You can wake up. Please, Momma, wake up.
I need you.
Please, Momma.
[sobbing, sniffling]
O blessed house of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
We'll keep you bright and never roam.
Heaven is here within our home.
Momma, please.
Please, Momma.
[Samuel sobbing]
["Our Love" by Starr Sisters playing]
- [thudding]
- [song fading]
[wind whooshing gently]
Koda!
[panting]
[Nolan] Koda!
Koda! Come back!
[whimpers]
Koda!
[blowing]
[door creaks]
I made some pine needle tea.
It'll help with your hunger.
Was that you out there?
Out where?
I saw you
in the woods
laughing at me
for not being able to save her.
[coughs]
I think you were dreaming.
Touch the wood.
Touch it.
[both] O blessed house of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
We'll keep you bright and never roam.
Heaven is here within our home.
Okay. Now drink.
We need some air.
[groaning]
I won't let you die.
[uneasy music playing]
[rustling]
[insects trilling]
[grunts]
[wind whooshing gently]
Help!
Hello!
[grunting]
Help!
Excuse me!
Hi there.
Sorry to intrude. I just, uh...
I was hiking and I...
I thought I heard someone
screaming for help.
That wasn't you, by any chance, was it?
I... I thought my ears
were playing tricks on me.
[chuckles]
Wow, I didn't think anyone was out here.
This is, uh...
Huh.
Are you okay?
What's your name, son?
[whispers] Nolan.
I'm sorry, I didn't catch that.
- Nolan.
Hi, Nolan. I'm Cole.
It's nice to meet you.
So...
where your folks at? They around?
My Momma's dead.
Oh, I'm very sorry to hear that.
How did she pass?
My brother's sick.
He needs food.
Okay. Well, I've got some food in my pack.
You know...
Nolan, I've got a truck
about five miles from here,
- and I could take you and your brother...
- [Samuel] Get back!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Okay. Okay, okay.
Whoa. Okay.
Uh... look,
I don't mean you boys any harm.
Nolan here says you're sick.
- We're not stupid.
- Sam.
I didn't say you were stupid. I just...
I just thought someone was in trouble.
- That's it.
- You killed my Momma.
No, son. I...
I don't know your Momma. Okay?
Look, this was just... This was a mistake.
I'm sorry. I'm gonna go.
- I'm gonna leave now, all right'? I ju...
- Don't move.
I just... Okay. Just calm down.
What if he's a real person?
We were happy.
Listen to me, okay?
I'm just gonna turn,
I'm just gonna go back,
I'm gonna go back
from Where I came from, all right?
- Just...
- I said, "Don't move!"
[exhales sharply]
Look, everything's fine.
- [Nolan] Just let him go.
- Everything's okay.
Let him go, Sam.
Please.
It's over.
She's gone.
- No!
- [Samuel grunts]
[groaning]
Sam...
[Cole groaning]
[groaning]
Help me!
[yells in pain]
Help!
- Nolan, don't.
- He said he has food.
- It's a trick.
- Help me!
[Nolan panting]
[Cole coughs, grunts]
[gurgling, groaning]
[gasps]
- [line ringing]
- [gasping for breath]
- [groans]
- [line rings]
[dispatcher] 911. What's your emergency?
[gurgling]
Sir? Sir, can you hear me?
- Can you tell me...
- [gasps]
[both grunting]
[dispatcher] Sir,
can you tell me Where you are?
[grunting]
[panting]
[dispatcher] Sir, tell me Where you are.
[grunts]
[knife clinks]
[gasps, effort grunts]
[effort grunts]
[sniffs, chuckles]
Mmm. [breathes heavily]
[door creaks]
- [door closes]
- Mmm. [breathes heavily]
It's from the man.
He's dead.
That wasn't a man.
Try it.
Did you let go?
No.
I touched him with the rope on.
He wouldn't have let me
if he was The Evil, right?
You still won't learn.
You're falling for it all over again!
Just try it.
No.
Maybe there's no evil.
Momma lied to us.
We're not the only ones left in the world.
If we thought
there was nothing out there for us,
then we wouldn't wanna leave her.
She killed herself to keep us safe
and you still won't believe it!
- Just try it!
- [thuds]
You'll see that it's real!
It'll make you feel better!
I promise.
Once upon a time, there were two brothers
who trusted each other.
She loved you!
She loved you.
And I'm so sorry for what I did.
But we're not safe.
We're dying.
At least then we'll be with Momma again.
Maybe that'll be enough for you this time.
- [ominous music playing]
- [insects trilling]
[wind whooshing]
[snoring]
- [chair creaking]
- [clicking]
- [thuds]
- [gasps]
Hello?
Who's in there?
Koda?
Hello?
[tense music sting]
[unsettling music playing]
- [tense music sting]
- [yells]
Momma?
[flies buzzing]
- [girl] Hello?
- [gasps]
I'm looking for my dad.
He asked me to wait by the car,
but he never came back.
Do you mind lowering that?
Thanks.
How did you get here?
I followed his footsteps in the mud.
He's tall, black hair,
a bit of gray on the sides?
Have you seen him?
Why is that rope around your waist?
To keep me safe.
From what?
Where did you get that flashlight?
That's my dad's.
It was a mistake.
I didn't mean to.
What are you talking about?
Where is he?
What did you do?
What did you do to him?
I thought he was The Evil.
No, wait!
I thought he was The Evil!
Come back!
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunting]
Come back! [grunts]
The rope... Oh, no.
Please! Come back! [effort grunting]
I know she's real.
- [thudding]
- [gasps]
[grunting]
- [rustling]
- [voices laughing]
[panting]
- [rustling]
- [gasps]
[insects trilling]
- [thudding]
- [gasping]
[scuttling]
[rattling]
[growls]
[yells]
- [gurgling]
- [yelling]
[gasping breaths]
[distorted, gasping breaths]
[exhales deeply]
[clinking]
[door opens, creaks]
[door closes, thuds]
Sam!
[Samuel] Nolan!
Sam?
Sam!
[Samuel] Nolan!
Where are you?
- [rustles]
- [gasps]
- [clinks]
- No!
[ominous music plays]
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
[door creaks, thuds]
Sam?
- [thudding upstairs]
- [gasps]
[floorboard creaking]
[whispering] It's not real.
It's not real.
[door creaks]
Sam.
Why did you cut my rope?
[ominous music playing]
Sam.
O blessed house of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
[yowling]
We'll keep you bright and never roam.
Heaven is here within our home!
[clinks]
- [grunts]
- [pants]
[yells]
Stop it, Sam!
Sam!
[doorknob clacking]
Sam! Sam!
Sam!
[whirring]
[effort grunts]
[panting]
Sam!
["The Big Rock Candy Mountain"
by Van Hunt playing]
[gasps, coughs]
[coughs, grunts]
Sam! You don't wanna do this!
[ominous music playing]
[grunts]
[gasping, coughing]
["The Big Rock Candy Mountain" continues]
[coughing]
[grunts]
[yelps, grunts]
The house won't protect you anymore.
[coughing]
[Momma] Nolan?
Come here, baby.
Come here.
I'm not mad at you, Nolan.
I was just like you when I was your age.
I wanna hold you again, baby.
Come on.
My sweet boy...
I missed you so much.
You're not her.
I-I saw what you did to Sam.
You saw What he really was.
I just helped him see it.
[dark music playing]
- [shutter clicks]
- [whirs]
Look at what you did.
You destroyed your whole family.
And I didn't even have to touch you.
I didn't mean to.
It's okay.
You don't have to be scared anymore.
You're not my Momma!
I'm more her than she ever was.
I'm the darkness that was inside her.
I'm the darkness that's inside you now.
I'm the darkness that's in your blood.
All you got to do...
is let go.
I can't!
["The Big Rock Candy Mountain" playing]
- [sobbing]
- [flames intensify]
[distorted playing]
There's nothing for you in that cellar.
[grunting]
- [yelling]
- [grunting]
[door opens]
Did you imagine it?
Yes.
Tell us about it.
[Nolan] I thought about
our birth in the house
and how safe it keeps us every day.
And I felt the darkness float away.
- [screaming]
- [grunting]
When we remember why we're holding on
and who we holding on for...
- [grunting]
- [screaming]
- [thudding]
We get strong again.
[screams]
The Evil can't touch me here.
Dawn to night and year to year.
- [screaming]
- [grunting]
O blessed house of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
Never let go.
- [Momma grunting]
- We'll keep you bright and never roam.
Heaven is here within our home.
I love you, Momma!
[somber music playing]
[breathes heavily]
[uneasy music playing]
[whirring]
[barks]
[panting]
My brother. I need to find my brother.
- [medic] You're safe now.
- My brother.
- But we can't leave him.
- You're safe just now. Just breathe.
- No! Where is he? Where is he?
- Just breathe now. Just breathe.
- [panting]
- It's okay. He's right here.
Sam.
I'm here. Hey, Sam. I'm here, Sam.
I'm here.
We're free.
She loves me more.
["Goodnight, Mother" by Dick Todd
with Orchestra playing]
[song ends]
[ominous music playing]
[music ends]