Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[soft, captivating
music playing]
[EÉowyn] All Middle-Earth
knows the tale
of the War of the Ring.
But there are older tales.
Tales told around warm fires
on cold winter nights.
Tales passed down
from the old to the young.
Tales that light a path
through the dark.
[chorus vocalizing]
[eagles screeching]
Almost 200 years
before the ring
ever came to Bilbo Baggins,
there lived a girl.
- Her name was Héra.
- [galloping]
- Only daughter of Helm ...
- [eagle screeches]
...King of Rohan.
Born under a harvest moon,
her mother did not live
to see the dawn.
Raised alongside two brothers
by a warrior king...
the girl could ride a horse
before she could walk.
- "Wild," some called her.
- [eagle screeches]
"Headstrong,"
railed her father.
Though, in truth,
he was so proud
of his tearaway child.
[grand, captivating
music playing]
[horse neighs]
Whoa. Whoa. [chuckles softly]
[grunts, pants]
[eagle screeches]
[grand, captivating music
continues playing]
- [feathers ruffling]
- [wind blowing]
[eagles screeching]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[eagle screeches]
[music intensifies]
[gasps, breathes heavily]
[ethereal choir music playing]
[exhales]
- [eagle screeches]
- [gasps]
[breath trembling]
[eagle screeches]
By her hand,
many great deeds were done.
But do not look for tales
of her in the old songs.
There are none.
[grand, orchestral
music playing]
[horse galloping]
- [bell tolling]
- [gasps]
[guard] Milady!
[Háma singing]
♪ Where is the horse?♪
♪ Where is the rider? ♪
♪ Passed into shadow
where I cannot find her ♪
CHILD: There she is!
Lady Héra!
- [Háma] ♪ Long is the road...♪
- Where were you?
[Háma]
♪ And far from her home ♪
♪ But fear not, my sister ♪
♪ You'll ne'er ride alone ♪
-  -♪ From mountaintop high... ♪
- [guards talk indistinctly]
♪ Cross riverbed low ♪
♪ To wild, whispered places
she's longing to go ♪
♪ Fearless she rides
into the unknown ♪
[horse galloping, neighs]
Héra!
[Héra breathing heavily]
You should have seen it, Háma.
[chuckles]
[grunts]
The fledgling took the lure.
Haleth said it wouldn't work.
He said, "It would tear you
limb from limb."
Wait, Héra...
Did you know that the Great
Eagles speak a language...
- [sighs]
- ...all of their own
but only to wizards?
[Háma] Will you listen to me?
Wait. Whose horses are those?
That's what I've been
trying to tell you.
Messengers arrived
from the West-march.
- [Héra breathes heavily]
- From Lord Freca? Why?
He has called for a Witan.
I thought only the king could
summon the lords to council.
That is the custom,
not the law.
[Héra] Olwyn! [exhales]
It's also the custom
to tell your lady's maid
if you're gonna run off
and make a snack of yourself
for some great flying beast!
[both chuckle]
[sighing] Oh, you...
Come on, you need to change.
What's wrong with
what I'm wearing?
[Olwyn sighs]
Hopeless.
[dramatic music playing]
Lord Freca hasn't been
to court in years.
Why would he show up now?
You don't think he means
to challenge father, do you?
[Haleth] I'd like
to see him try.
[Olwyn] Haleth.
[Héra] Brother.
I doubt Freca even remembers
how to swing a sword.
He's sat idle
in the West-march too long,
stuffing his face,
and his pocket.
Fat and prosperous
are when men are at their
most dangerous, Lord Haleth.
It fills them
with false courage,
and false courage
breeds discontent.
Which means what?
[Olwyn] It means Lord Freca
has had a long time
to think about all the things
he doesn't have.
[sighing grimly, grunts]
[Haleth] Freca has only what
we allow. Nothing more.
[Olwyn sighs]
[tense music playing]
[indistinct conversation]
[sighs wearily]
Lief, you're calling
the banners tonight?
[gasps] My Lord Fréaláf.
Yes. I am.
It's my first council.
I... I thought I'd learned
all the sigils.
[Fréaláf] Hmm.
[Lief] But I... [hesitates]
I don't recognize that one.
The banner of
the Shieldmaidens.
[clears throat] My Lady Héra!
[Fréaláf] Cousin?
[Héra] Oh...
[Fréaláf] Look at you. No mud,
- no twigs in your hair...
- [gasps]
[chuckles]
One could almost mistake you
for a princess of Rohan.
- [Héra gasps]
- [Fréaláf laughs]
[both chuckle]
The Shieldmaidens
were women of The Borderlands.
When all the men were slain,
they took up arms and fought.
They defended Rohan
when no one else could.
Those were darker days.
I've long thought it time
to retire that banner.
And I doubt there are
any of them left.
[Lief] They're all gone?
Not all of them.
[door opens]
- [sighs]
- [door thuds]
[enthralling music playing]
[Lief] Helm. Son of Gram,
Lord of the Eorlingas.
Ninth...
Yes, yes. They know their king
when they see him.
You all look like
you're at a funeral!
Fear not, faint hearts.
We'll be done with
this business soon enough.
[door bangs]
- [gasps]
- [Helm scoffs]
[indistinct conversation]
I see you have started
without me.
- [imposing music playing]
- [laughs loftily]
[sighs]
[Lief] Freca,
Lord of the West-march.
[Lief] Lord Wulf, son of Freca.
[sighs]
General Targg of Dunland.
[Helm] Lord Freca!
It has been a while.
You've missed many a council,
though it seems
very few meals.
- [court talks indistinctly]
- [Freca snarls]
[chuckles nervously]
Freca, the King jests.
I see age has not improved
your manners, my liege.
Am I not welcome
in this great hall?
All loyal men
are welcome here.
Ah, but loyal to whom? Hmm?
To Rohan?
- Or to Gondor?
- [indistinct conversation]
A rumor has reached my ears
that a Gondorian princeling...
[chuckling] has made an offer
for your daughter's hand.
[all talking indistinctly]
[gasps]
Do you deny it?
[tense music playing]
It's none of your business
whom my daughter marries!
I say it is.
I say it is
all of our business.
[all talking indistinctly]
I come before this council
with an offer to strengthen,
not weaken Rohan.
For too long
our houses have squabbled
while Gondor usurps
our greatness.
They would respect us,
nay, fear us,
were we truly united.
It is past time for Rohan
to stop being Gondor's lapdog.
Consider instead
a son of the West-march.
[both mutter] Hmm.
I, Wulf, son of Freca,
come before you, Héra,
daughter of Helm...
Wulf, don't.
...to seek your hand
in marriage.
[court gasps,
talks indistinctly]
[Helm sighs, grunts softly]
[Freca] Well, girl?
What do you say, hmm?
- [Héra sighs]
- [Helm] Enough!
[all gasp]
You speak of
uniting our people,
when it is I who has
faced down death, famine, war
to hold these lands together.
I know why you have come,
Freca, son of Dunland.
You do not seek an alliance,
you seek a throne.
Old kings that refuse
a proffered staff
may fall on their knees.
You do not command
the loyalty you think you do.
[somber music playing]
Sire, this is not the place.
My nephew speaks true.
A king does not brawl
in his own house.
[Freca grunts]
But men are freer outside.
Wouldn't you agree?
- [dramatic music playing]
- [Freca grunts softly]
[all whispering]
[somber music playing]
Is this wise, Uncle?
[Helm] I know Freca.
He hasn't a noble bone
in his body.
Mark my word,
he would not be satisfied
with marriage to Héra.
He would see his son
on my throne
and my boys in a grave.
Time to remind him
of his place.
The line of Helm
is not so easily broken.
[Olwyn] Come away, child.
Leave them be.
[sighs]
[soft, melancholic
music playing]
[Wulf] You did not give
an answer.
We should go.
- Would it be so bad?
- [gasps]
We were inseparable once.
We were children.
Is she with him?
[sighs] Aye.
[Wulf] Well, I did not think
so much had changed.
Wulf, please.
I care about you.
[Wulf] But...
you'd rather marry
a stranger from Gondor?
I have no thoughts
of marriage at all.
Our fathers speak as if I were
not even in the room.
This should be
my decision to make.
It should be yours, too.
And what if I told you
this is what I want?
What I've always wanted.
- I love you.
- No.
I do not want to marry you.
I do not want to marry
any man.
You asked for my answer,
you have it.
[Haleth] Héra!
[both gasp]
Come, sister,
or we'll miss all the fun.
[melancholic music
continues playing]
[sighs]
[breathes deeply]
[somber music playing]
- [indistinct conversation]
- [man coughs]
[Helm] Now, Dunlending,
you have only Helm
to deal with.
Just you and me. Unarmed.
You will live to regret this,
old man.
Dress the girl
however you like.
Can't you stop this?
- Your daughter's no lady.
- [Wulf sighs]
No wonder she's wild.
Raised by a brute like you.
"Feral" they call her.
Right at home
in the rough country.
[sighs]
[inhales sharply] But, no,
she's "too good" for my son.
- [grunting]
- [groaning]
[both panting]
Hmm.
Your daughter will come
crawling on her knees,
begging my son to marry her
before the end.
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[exhales]
Father!
[breath trembling]
Get up, Freca!
Get up and fight!
Father?
[gasps]
He's dead.
- [all gasp]
- [all shouting indistinctly]
- No!
- [sighs]
[grumbles]
Impossible! I only struck him
the once.
You saw.
You all saw.
[sighs deeply]
Hmm.
- [sobbing]
- [grave music playing]
[grunts] You killed him.
[crowd exclaims, muttering]
Put the sword down, lad.
[panting]
- No!
- [screaming]
- [sword clanging]
- [grunts]
[groaning]
- [shouts]
- [choking, wheezing]
[men grunt]
- [Wulf choking]
- [all talking indistinctly]
You dare draw your sword
against the King, Dunlending?
[dramatic music playing]
- [Héra] Father, no! [gasps]
- [grunts softly]
- [groaning]
- You're killing him!
- [grunting]
- [choking]
[shouts]
[groaning]
[Wulf gasping]
[Helm] Enough blood
has been spilt.
[panting]
There will be no more.
- [grumbles]
- [all whispering]
You will pay for this
with your life.
I swear it.
Save your breath, boy,
lest it be your last.
Wulf, son of Freca,
you are banished.
If you set foot
on these lands again,
it will be your head.
[dramatic music playing]
[sighs wearily]
[groans]
[Wulf breathes heavily]
Wulf...
[panting]
[somber music playing]
- Leave him.
- [sighs]
[breath trembling]
[indistinct conversation]
[somber music playing]
[EÉowyn] Seasons passed.
The death of Freca
was talked of for a long time.
[wind blowing]
Some whispered
it was an ill omen
for a king to kill
one of his own.
[rain pattering]
Wulf's fate weighed heavy
on Héra's mind.
Banished and reviled...
yet he was still the boy
she once called friend.
[kids laughing, chattering]
- We're not supposed to be here.
- They're not gonna find us...
[soft, melancholic
music playing]
[Young Wulf]
Are you ready, Héra?
[Young Héra]
Of course I'm ready.
Come on, Wulf!
[both grunting]
[Héra chuckles]
Got you!
[grunting]
Wait! Wulf!
- [grunts]
- [groaning]
I cut you!
I'm sorry.
I did not mean to hurt you.
- Leave me.
- You're bleeding.
- [gasps]
- [grunts] Go!
Before my father
finds you here.
I said, "Go!"
[both panting]
[soft, melancholic music
playing]
[EÉowyn] Héra tried to find
word of Wulf.
[horse neighs]
No sign of him
could ever be found.
It was as if he had vanished,
passing like a shadow
into night.
[Wulf shouts]
- [thunder breaking]
- [neighing]
A new threat arose
on Rohan's eastern border.
[creatures bellowing]
Strange sounds were heard
in the night.
[neighing]
[creatures bellowing]
The broken bodies
of wild horses
were found dead on the morn.
[flies buzzing]
No longer would the king
allow his wayward daughter
to ride out alone.
- [horse whinnies]
- [crows cawing]
- Crebain, from Dunland.
[Fréaláf] It's a Southron.
The armor marks him
as a mercenary.
See where those tracks lead.
[Lief] Ooh, he's quite big,
isn't he?
Okay. This way. Come on, Lief.
Ugh.
[Héra] What is a Southron
doing this far north?
- [flies buzzing]
- [grunts]
He's been here a few days.
The birds have picked
the body clean.
Spear and horn.
I think he was
some kind of Beastmaster.
Aye, but master of what?
What was that old poem
you used to recite to me
as a child?
Something about
"making the earth shake."
- [Lief screams]
- [horse neighs loudly]
[gasping]
[Lief] Run!
- [panting]
- [heavy thudding]
Run!
[roaring]
- [grunting]
- [horse neighing]
[Fréaláf] Mûmak!
- [gasping]
[groaning]
The beast is rabid.
- [growling deeply]
- [intense music playing]
[Fréaláf grunting]
Héra... get out of here!
Go!
[horses neigh]
Fréaláf!
[grunts, screams]
- [groaning]
- [neighing]
[panting]
[grunting]
[low growling]
[growls]
[panting]
[grunts]
[footsteps running]
[somber music playing]
- [mûmak stomping]
- [panting]
[shouts]
[gasps]
- [grunting]
- [mûmak growls]
[shouts, grunting]
[horn blowing]
- [mûmak growls]
- [inhales sharply]
[horn blowing]
[growling]
[pants, grunts softly]
[dramatic music playing]
[horn blowing]
[growling]
Héra! No!
[grunts softly]
- [panting]
- [mûmak growling]
- [mûmak growls]
- Faster, Ashere! Faster!
Héra!
[mûmak growling]
[tense dramatic music playing]
[grunts]
[growling]
Does she know what creature
lives in those woods?
- [Olwyn] Of course she does.
- [sighs]
[grunting]
[suspenseful music playing]
[mûmak growling in distance]
[animals chittering]
[grunts softly]
[insects trilling]
[Ashere trotting]
[Ashere neighs]
Whoa, Ashere, whoa. Whoa.
[breathing heavily]
[panting] Okay.
[Ashere whinnies]
[grunts softly] Yeah. Go! Go!
[trotting]
"Beware dark waters
that hide old secrets."
[grunts softly]
[gasps]
[low rumbling]
- [gasps]
- [rustling, thudding]
- [rustling]
- [birds screeching]
[low rumbling]
[exhales]
- [thudding, rustling]
- [gasping]
- [dramatic music playing]
- [growling]
[growling]
[screams]
[panting]
[gasps]
[Watcher growls]
[mûmak grunting]
[Watcher grumbling]
[growls, trumpets]
[panting]
[intense music playing]
[grunts]
[splashing]
- [Watcher grumbles]
- [growling]
[mûmak grunting]
[trumpets]
[crashes]
[gasps]
[bones crunching]
[exhales]
[man] The Watcher in the Water.
[gasps]
I never thought I'd live
to see such a sight.
General Targg.
What are you doing here?
You were banished.
I was dispatched on a mission,
but it seems that objective
may have changed.
What the...
Dispatched by whom?
I serve a new commander.
The High Lord
of the Hill Tribes.
The Wildmen
have no High Lord.
They do now.
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
- [Héra shrieks]
[grunting] How dare you!
- [men grunt]
- [shrieks]
Get your hands off me!
[grunting]
Put me down! [grunts]
[wildling grunts]
She's seen the mumak!
- Why not kill her now?
- [Héra] Let me go!
[Targg] No.
We take her to the High Lord.
[Héra] No! [grunting]
I said, "Let me go!"
[Héra grunting]
- [horse neighing]
- [men talking indistinctly]
[groans, breathes heavily]
[grunts, exhales]
[breathing heavily]
[men laughing boisterously]
- [grunts softly]
- [door rattles]
[horse neighs]
[drum beating in distance]
[drum beating continues]
- [crickets chirping]
- [men chattering indistinctly]
[Fréaláf] I found her.
They're holding her
in one of the guard towers.
- [breathes deeply]
- [horse neighs]
[Héra] Ashere! [gasps]
How can you eat
at a time like this?
- [men talking indistinctly]
- [breathes deeply]
There must be
another way out of here.
[Olwyn] Who would dare
occupy Isengard?
Someone bold enough
to kidnap a king's daughter.
I'm going after Héra.
Stay hidden.
Keep the horses at the ready.
If I do not return
by the hour...
Wait.
I have a plan.
[somber music playing]
[gasps]
- [Wulf] Always too curious...
- [gasps]
...for your own good.
Wulf!
- You're alive.
- [scroll clutters]
[Héra sighs]
You are the High Lord?
Did you think
I would slink away like a cur
and lick my wounds?
No, I have been busy.
All my life, I was scorned
for my Dunlending blood.
But look who answered
when I needed them.
The Hill Tribes have sworn
an oath to me.
Every last one.
You cannot hope to stand
against Rohan and Gondor.
[laughs slyly]
Your father will never
ask for help from Gondor.
His pride will not allow it.
No. Gondor is not coming.
[tense music playing]
First, I will kill
your brothers.
Then, I will kill your father.
And then,
I will take the throne.
And be king of what?
A land in ruins,
its people torn apart!
You had your chance
to unite Rohan.
- And you refused!
- [grunts]
Did I disgust you so much?
Hmm?
Was I so easily forgotten?
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
I never forgot you.
I tried to find you.
[breathing heavily]
- [Wulf grunts]
- [groans]
[breath trembling]
[somber music playing]
The boy I knew
would never wish for war.
Don't do this, Wulf.
Innocent people will die.
[breathing heavily]
What if there was a way
you could still save them?
A way you could still
save your people.
[Héra] If I agree to this...
If I agree to be your bride,
you swear
there will be no war?
[Wulf] If you agree? [grunts]
Is there no end to
the arrogance of your house?
Even now you can barely
stomach the thought, can you?
The boy you knew
is gone, Héra.
I am the man
your father made me.
- [grunts]
- [shouts]
[gasps]
[Héra] Olwyn!
Don't just sit there. Move!
[grunting]
[dramatic music playing]
[Wulf and Olwyn grunting]
You think you're still
a Shieldmaiden, old woman?
- [grunts]
- Your fighting days are over.
[both grunting]
[Olwyn] Go!
[grunting continues]
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
[panting]
Come on, greedy.
We're leaving.
[grunts]
Seize them!
[men clamoring]
- [Olwyn] Ride!
- [guard] Summon the guards!
- Stop her!
- [Olwyn] Go!
- [shouting indistinctly]
- [Ashere neighs]
[guard] Cut them off!
Make for the gates!
[guard] Move!
[dramatic music playing]
[guard 1] To the gate!
[guard 2]
They're coming through!
[guard 1] Quickly!
[Ashere trotting]
[Héra] We'll never make it
past the archers!
- Trust me. I have a plan.
- [breathing heavily]
[bow stretching]
- [pants, grunts]
- [screams]
[groans]
[grunts]
[groaning]
[triumphant music playing]
[panting]
- [Héra] This is your plan?
- [grunts]
I didn't say
it was a good one!
[both grunt]
[groans]
- [guard screams]
- [thuds]
[dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
[Lief] My lord!
I'm fine.
Let's get out of here.
[horse neighs]
[men shouting indistinctly]
I'll dispatch
our fastest horsemen.
Don't bother.
She will outride them.
Call the men to arms.
[Héra] Please, listen to me.
We do not know the full
strength of Wulf's army.
Do not underestimate him,
Father.
There is more to Wulf's plan,
I know it.
The mumak,
the Southron we saw.
That is no coincidence.
The beast was diseased,
you said so yourself.
We had reports
of a column of mumakil
moving west,
near our southern border.
One of them must have
broken its chains
and crossed into our lands.
It's got nothing to do
with the Dunlending boy.
The wisest move is to
fall back to our strongholds.
Light the beacons.
Call for aid from Gondor.
"The wisest move"?
You would have me
abandon Edoras?
Until we are
at full strength...
yes.
This is no rabble of Wildmen.
These men are well trained
and well-armed.
[Thorne] My liege, if I may?
Lord Fréaláf is young.
He has not fought beside you
in battle, as I have.
[indistinct whispering]
I pledge 300 riders
to protect the eastern flank.
The men of the Wold
- stand ready to fight.
- [all cheering]
I accept your pledge.
Lord Thorne shall have command
of the east.
I will lead the vanguard north
and meet Wulf on the plains.
[all cheering]
Let every man willing
step forth.
We fight for Rohan!
Please, Uncle, trust me.
Trust you? I trusted you
to protect my daughter.
To keep her safe.
And look what happened.
Kidnapped,
by a filthy upstart.
It was not his fault!
Fréaláf saved me.
She could have died!
[Fréaláf sighs]
[somber music playing]
[Helm sighs]
[winces]
Go back to Dunharrow,
Fréaláf Hildeson.
Dig some trenches
and crawl into them.
When the songs
of this day are sung,
when the names
of its heroes are read,
yours will not be
amongst them.
He's our kin.
He is no kin of mine!
Nor do I need a sword offered
by such a faithless hand.
[somber music
continues playing]
[Fréaláf] My Lord.
Fréaláf, wait!
[Fréaláf] The king has spoken.
You will always have
my sword, Uncle,
whether you value it or not.
[door rattles]
- No.
- [door closes]
[grave music playing]
[indistinct screaming]
[men shouting]
[crying]
They know
the attack is coming.
From here, we have
a clear path to Edoras.
Helm will expect us
to make camp
on the northern plains.
[Wulf] Good.
[horse whinnies]
War is upon us.
What do you say, old friend?
- Will you carry me once more?
- [horse whinnies]
What are you doing?
I pledge to fight for my king.
Don't be a fool, child.
If you will not listen to me,
then at least let me fight.
You know nothing of war.
I'm the fastest rider
you have.
I can carry messages
between the commanders.
I said "no."
The line of Helm
does not rest on you, Héra.
It resides in Haleth and Háma.
My brothers can defend
their home, but yet I cannot?
One day, you will marry.
You will live in Gondor
and have children
who know nothing of our ways.
To see me gone...
is that what would please you?
Yes, it will please me.
I will rejoice.
You will be alive because
I will have protected you.
Wulf's army is 20 leagues
from Edoras.
They're not setting up camp!
They're not resting!
What?
They're continuing to advance?
The Hill Tribes
are used to attacking
under cover of dark.
He means to strike tonight.
Muster the Rohirrim.
[sweeping music playing]
[all talking indistinctly]
[Héra] Wait!
[panting]
Do not look so grim,
little sister.
[sighs]
Helm Hammerhand
has never lost a battle.
[sighs]
Háma... you need
a faster horse.
Take Ashere.
[chuckles] Ashere will have
no one but you.
Besides, I trust the old girl.
[Héra sighs]
Keep this safe for me.
Always.
Maybe, one day,
someone will sing
ballads of me.
[Haleth grunts softly]
[Haleth] On the morrow,
little sister.
Ride strong, brothers.
[somber music playing]
[horses neighing]
Where is Thorne? He's late.
His men should be
covering the eastern flank.
[Helm] [grimly] hmm.
[Olwyn] I fought beside
your father once.
He saved my entire village
from a pack of
Dunlending raiders.
I broke my shield
in that battle.
Afterwards,
I wanted a new one.
But "No," he told me,
"it's not broken,
it's just broken in."
[chuckles]
[Héra] There's so many of them.
[Olwyn] Your father
is no ordinary man.
[sighs] It'll take more than
an army of Dunlending
to bring him low.
The blood of the ancients
flows in his veins.
The same blood
that flows in yours.
[soft, sweeping music playing]
Oh! [grunts]
[groans]
Oh, the pledges!
Oh, no! No, no, no, no!
The king left these
in my charge for safekeeping.
It's all right,
don't fret, lad.
The king's got other things
on his mind.
- [Héra] Whose mark is this?
- Oh...
That? That's the seal
of Lord Thorne.
- [Héra gasps]
- What is it?
What's wrong?
[Héra] I've seen this before.
Lord Thorne is in league
with Wulf.
He means to betray my father.
We have to get our people out.
Sound the alarm. Now! Go!
[all gasping]
Evacuate the city!
[heroic music playing]
[men shouting]
[horse trotting]
Riders of the Mark,
brothers of Rohan, arise!
Arise now!
We will paint the dawn red
with the blood of our foes!
[all cheering]
Draw your weapons!
- [all shouting]
- [swords clanging]
[horses neighing]
Forth Eorlingas!
- For Rohan!
- [all] Rohan!
[all cheering]
[horn blowing]
- Death!
- [all screaming] Death!
Death!
[heroic music playing]
[commander 1] Archers ready!
[commander 2] Aim!
[commander 1]
Mark your targets!
[soldiers screaming]
[commander 1] Fire!
[grunts]
[groans]
- [horses neighing]
- [man shouting]
Charge!
[groans]
[horse whinnies]
[Haleth screams]
[grunting]
[screams]
[horse neighs]
- [thudding]
- [grunts]
Wulf!
Where is he?
Where is their high command?
Find him!
[villagers muttering]
[Olwyn] Keep moving!
You've a long march
ahead of you.
[woman 1] Where are we going?
[woman 2] What about
the children?
Carry only what you need.
Stay together.
Keep the children
to the middle! Go!
- [panting]
- [Ashere whinnies]
Come on, Ashere.
Time to leave.
[Thorne] I fear it is too late
for that... my lady.
Traitor!
My father will see you
hang for this.
You will never know, will you?
- [grunts]
- [shrieks]
[grunting]
- [gasps]
- [Ashere neighs]
- [grunts]
- [Héra panting]
[grunts]
[both grunting]
[huffing]
[growls]
- [grunts]
- [Ashere whinnies]
- [Thorne groaning]
- [grunts]
[groans]
[gasping]
- [men shouting]
- [swords clashing]
[Haleth] Hold the line!
Wulf's nowhere to be seen.
Something's not right.
[mûmak growls, trumpets]
Mumakil!
He's using Variag mercenaries.
Edoras is completely exposed.
[shouting]
- Royal Guard! To me!
- [all screaming]
- [soldiers screaming]
- [mûmak growling]
[grunting]
[shouting]
[both grunting]
[trumpeting]
[grunting]
[neighs]
[grave music playing]
- [groans]
- [growls]
[swords clashing]
[screams]
- [grunts]
- [mûmak groans]
[gasps, grunts]
- [groans]
- [gasps]
- [growls]
- [grunts]
[grunts]
[Haleth] Háma!
[both grunting]
[groans]
[Háma grunts]
They may sing of your
valor yet, little brother.
[soldier] Forward! Keep moving!
- [chuckles softly]
- [neighs]
Whoa!
[grunting]
[mûmak growling]
[man] You sure about this,
my lady?
[Héra] Do it.
[both gasp]
[Wulf] Take the city!
[soldiers screaming]
[trumpeting]
Haleth! Háma!
Call the retreat.
[grunts] No!
Listen to me, Haleth.
You must reach the city
before Wulf.
Find Héra. Go.
- Go!
- [horse neighs]
[Haleth commands]
Break it down! Move!
No! It's afraid of the fire!
[trumpeting]
[Héra grunts]
[groans]
[gasps, grunts]
- [man] Look out!
- [men groan]
[grunts]
[triumphant music playing]
[Héra grunts, pants]
- [neighs]
- [grunts]
[trumpeting]
[warriors screaming]
[intense music playing]
[panting]
Where is everyone?
The city's deserted.
[Haleth] Find Héra!
[villagers muttering]
[baby crying]
[somber music playing]
[whimpers]
[Háma] Héra!
Háma! Lord Thorne,
he has betrayed us.
We know. You've already called
the evacuation.
- Yes.
- Good.
Get everyone to Dunharrow.
The road to Dunharrow
is crawling with Wildmen.
The Hornburg is
our only chance.
Olwyn is leading the retreat.
[mûmakil growling in distance]
[neighing]
[growling]
[men shouting]
- [horses neighing]
- [grunts]
- [grunting]
- [men groan]
- [grunts]
- [mûmak groans]
Riders! Fall back!
Cover the retreat!
[soldiers screaming]
[panting, growls]
[mûmak rider shouts]
[mûmak growling]
[wood creaking]
[crashes]
[trumpeting]
[gasps]
[men grunting]
[shouts, groans]
[intense music
continues playing]
[Targg grunts]
[trumpeting]
- [grunting]
- [groans]
[grunts]
[Héra] It's heading
for the Great Hall!
[trumpeting]
[panting]
- [grunting]
- [mûmak groaning]
[mûmak trumpets]
- [continues grunting]
- [mûmak groaning]
[neighing]
[mûmak groans]
[grunts]
For Rohan! For our people!
[Haleth shouts]
Haleth!
[groans softly]
[eerie music playing]
[Héra] No!
Haleth!
[Wulf] Archers! Ready!
[eerie music continuing]
[sobbing]
Fire!
[inaudible]
[screams] No!
[groaning, panting]
[sinister music playing]
- [grunting]
- [warriors groaning]
[Héra] Father!
[groans]
Hold on.
[arrows whooshing]
- [Háma] Get him out of here!
- [Héra grunting]
[Héra panting]
[Helm groaning]
[Wulf] Run them down.
[Targg] Get after them.
Now! Move it!
- [Héra panting]
- [Helm groaning]
- [horses neighing]
- [men shouting]
[guard 1] Royal guard,
protect the king!
[guard 2] To the king!
[guard 3] To the king!
Háma!
Go, Héra! I'll catch you.
- [panting]
- Come on, old girl. Come on!
[horse panting]
[breathing heavily]
[soft, somber music playing]
[horses neighing]
[horse panting]
[Háma sighs]
Songs of valor, old girl.
This is it.
[somber music continuing]
[breathes deeply]
[horses trotting]
[horses approaching]
[sighs]
[eagle screeching]
[sweeping music playing]
[Olwyn] Come on
with the last of you!
- You're nearly there!
- [people talking indistinctly]
Hurry now!
Inside the keep!
Come on, fast as you can!
[Héra] A healer!
The king needs a healer.
- [soldier] My lord.
- [Helm groans]
- [soldier] Sire.
- [Héra grunts]
[Helm groaning]
Háma...
Where is he?
Where's Háma?
[grave music playing]
- [guard 1] This way.
- [Helm] Leave me.
[guard 2] Sire...
[Olwyn] Hmm.
[Helm groaning]
[gasps] No.
Háma!
- [soldiers grunt]
- [Helm grunts]
[grunts, pants]
[Helm breathing heavily]
[softly]
He was right behind us.
[groans]
Enough!
[wind whooshing]
You have won, Wulf!
I surrender.
Let this end now.
My life for my son's.
No!
[grunts]
- [grunts]
- [Háma groans]
- [Wulf grunts]
[breath trembling]
[gasping]
[sighs]
- Kill me! Take the crown.
- [gasps]
Leave my people in peace.
[voice trembling]
Let my boy live!
[Háma] No! Father, don't!
Peace?
There will be no peace
for you, Helm Hammerhand.
No! Wulf, please, I beg you!
End this now.
Make the exchange.
Once they withdraw
behind those walls,
you will never get them out.
- Let them.
- [gasps]
- [Háma groans]
- [blood splatters]
[all gasp, exclaim]
Murderer!
What have you done?
[women crying]
You will suffer
as I have suffered.
You will know what it means
to be alone, as I was!
Then, and only then,
will I let you die.
Murderer!
- [groaning]
- [Héra gasps]
[Héra] No! No! No!
- [Héra gasping]
- [guard 1] Sire!
[Héra] No! No!
- [guard 2] My lord! Quickly!
- [Olwyn] Get the king!
Get him inside! Hurry!
- [guard 1] Help the king!
- [guard 2] Come on!
[guard 3] All right! All right!
- Come. Come inside.
- [Héra grunting]
[guard 3] I... I've got you!
- Come on!
- [Héra] Please. No!
[warriors shouting
in distance]
[shouting continues]
Close the gates!
- [whirring]
- [guards shouting]
Prepare the men for a siege.
Sire, winter is coming on.
A siege will cost both sides.
I don't care what it costs!
Surround the keep.
If anyone tries to escape,
even a rat, kill it.
[sighs]
What of the boy's body?
[breathing heavily]
[Wulf] Let it rot.
[gates clang shut]
[crying]
[mournful music playing]
- [Lief] My lady?
- [sniffles]
You're needed, my lady.
[sniffles]
[warriors shouting]
[shouting continues
indistinctly]
[Fréaláf] Any word?
[soldier] I'm sorry, milord.
[EÉowyn] High in the stronghold
of Dunharrow,
Fréaláf waited.
Yet the fate of his kin
remained unknown.
Had they survived?
Or were they buried now
amongst the ashes of Edoras?
[crows cawing]
Hmm...
[eerie, suspenseful
music playing]
[thuds]
Summon the lords
of Rohan to Edoras.
It's time they swear
their loyalty to me.
The king who last wore
that crown still lives.
Helm Hammerhand is but
a shadow of what he once was.
He will perish soon enough.
Fear not, Targg.
Shadows cannot hurt you.
Return to the Hornburg.
She thinks she is safe
behind those walls.
She will learn soon enough.
She is mistaken.
[Héra] We have a chance,
if we can just outlast
Wulf's army.
This is all of it?
It's not enough.
Search all the rooms.
Take stock of everything.
[clinking, footsteps]
[mysterious music playing]
[Olwyn] What's that?
I've been keeper of
these halls for 40 years.
I never thought
I'd see such times.
Supplies are running
terribly low.
It's going to be
a long winter.
I can feel it in my bones.
- [gasps]
- [Olwyn] Hmm.
[shrieks] Don't touch that,
my lady.
[groans]
That gown was made for a bride
that was pledged to
the captain of the keep.
But she never got to wear it.
A strange fever took her
the night before her wedding.
Some say many a lost soul
wanders these halls.
And worse.
Who says it?
I do.
Nonsense.
- [keys jangling]
- Here, give me that.
[Fryght] I've tried
to send for help.
All our messenger birds
are shot down.
None can get past
their archers.
What other choice is there
but to submit?
[Pryme] Don't be a fool.
There will be no surrender,
only slaughter.
We've barely any food or fuel.
The other lords of Rohan
have retreated
to their strongholds.
We are cut off!
How are we to survive?
[Héra] We find a way.
[gate creaking]
We cannot fight
amongst ourselves.
That is exactly
what he wants us to do.
Despair is Wulf's
greatest weapon against us.
We cannot succumb.
We find a way to survive,
and we do it together.
[sighs]
[Fryght] Pretty words.
Pretty words will not save us.
[somber music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Thank you.
[men shouting in distance]
[guard 1] Here!
Come take a look at this!
[somber music playing]
[guard 2] What are they
doing down there?
[men screaming]
What are they doing?
[shouting continuing]
He's building a siege tower.
He means to breach the walls.
[indistinct conversation]
[eagle screeches]
[EÉowyn] It is not easy
to hold on to hope
when an ill wind blows.
Winter bit hard that year.
None were spared
the endless cold.
Yet still the siege held fast.
The Rohirrim could do nothing
but watch and wait,
as their doom drew ever near.
[Héra breathes deeply]
[sighs] Any change?
[Olwyn] It makes no sense.
His body is mending,
and yet he does not wake.
I fear it is his mind
that is broken.
- [gasps softly]
- [bowls clang]
[Lief blowing]
What are you doing?
That's for the king.
[Pennicruik] Hmm.
[Pennicruik groans]
What about that?
What? No, not that.
[Héra] Take it.
But, my lady...
that was Master Háma's.
[Héra] And what use is it
without him?
[soft, melancholic
music playing]
[Pennicruik] Ah.
[Helm groans]
[Héra gasps]
I know this sickness is not
born of any mortal wound.
It is grief
that pulls you under.
Grief that you will
never again see your sons.
[voice trembling]
You think all is lost.
But I am here, Father.
[sniffles]
I am still here.
Please don't give up.
[whimpering]
[sobbing]
[wind blowing]
[wind whooshing]
- Huh? [exclaims]
- [eerie music playing]
Who's out there?
Show yourself!
[gasps. Exclaiming]
[screaming]
[men shouting in distance]
- [man screams]
- [gasps]
[men shouting fearfully]
[groans]
What happened here?
[man gasping]
Speak!
He killed them all. I saw.
He tore them apart
with his bare hands.
Who did?
Helm Hammerhand.
He's no living man.
It's not natural,
the thing I saw.
He's coming for us all!
[mysterious music playing]
[Targg panting]
Save us.
[grunts]
[gasps] Father?
- [gasping]
- [mysterious music playing]
Father?
[horn blowing]
[EÉowyn] Night after night,
a ghostly horn
echoed in the Deep.
[horn blowing]
A harbinger of death.
Fear took hold of Wulf's men.
Whispers spread that
Helm Hammerhand
was human no more.
He bore no weapon,
and no weapon could smite him.
A terror born of madness
and grief.
A wraith.
[horn blowing]
- [men grunting]
- [wind blowing]
Wulf returned to a camp
stalked by death,
his carefully-laid plans
in disarray.
He was king of nothing.
[wood creaking]
But Wulf, son of Freca,
would be damned before he was
defeated by a ghost.
- [villagers coughing]
- [somber music playing]
- Is it true what they say?
- [child coughs]
What?
Has the king become a monster?
[somber music playing]
[Pennicruik] A terrible,
unholy sight.
Eyes that burn like coals
as he feasts on the flesh...
[Olwyn] Helm Hammerhand
is no wraith.
[Pennicruik]
Then how did he disappear
from a locked
and guarded room?
Answer me that.
I don't know. But I do know
he can't walk through walls!
[Pennicruik] Perhaps he can.
Perhaps he can do
many unnatural things.
[Olwyn] Oh, aye? Such as what?
[Pennicruik] First comes
the sound of the horn.
Three blasts.
Then he appears,
fierce and gaunt,
stalking his prey!
The only ghoul haunting
these halls is you!
- [gasps]
- [stone scrapes]
Héra? Héra?
[Héra] Olwyn, can you hear me?
[silence]
Héra?
Where's she gone?
[Héra] Olwyn!
[breathing heavily]
[mysterious music playing]
[mysterious music
continues playing]
[breath trembling]
[wind whooshing]
[warrior] Huh... The bodies...
The bodies.
They're gone!
The wraith! It's eaten them.
It's eaten them all!
[warrior] I told you!
We shouldn't be here!
[warriors shouting fearfully]
[Lief] My lady?
Any sign of Héra?
No.
[sighs]
[breath trembling]
- [whooshes]
- [mysterious music playing]
Father?
- [wind blowing]
- [gasps]
[gasping]
[lamp clatters]
[echoing] Wait!
[tense music playing]
Father!
[panting]
[grunting]
[Héra grunts]
[Héra] Wait!
[grunting]
[panting]
[grunts, pants]
[wind blowing]
[panting]
[Wrot] Nasty.
I don't like them ginger ones.
Nothing worse than a bit
of ginga stuck in your teeth.
[wind blowing]
[Shank] Oi! Wrot!
- Check 'em before you eat 'em.
- [choking]
Ya fat slug.
[Héra] [gasps] Orcs.
[Shank] I told you before,
orders from on high.
What does Mordor want
with rings anyway?
[Shank] Hey, the less I know,
the better.
[Wrot] Hmm.
[sniffs] You smell that?
They can smell you
from Mount Doom.
No. No.
I smell fresh meat.
- [shrieks]
- [growls]
[breathing heavily]
[screaming]
[Wrot] Here, Shank.
[Héra] No!
[Wrot] We got ourselves
a live one.
[Shank] Not much meat on her.
May as well feed her
to the beast.
[grunts, gasps]
[beast growls]
[Helm screaming]
- [grunts]
- [growls]
[Helm grunting]
[screeching]
[grunts]
- [grunts]
- [shrieks]
[shrieking continues]
What is that infernal noise?
[warrior] It's the wraith.
The wraith of Helm Hammerhand.
- [Wulf] Get me General Targg!
- [panting]
[shrieking]
[roaring]
- No.
- [Helm grunting]
[grunts]
[beast shrieks]
[grunting]
[shrieking]
- [beast growls]
- [Héra gasps]
[blows hitting]
- [Helm grunting]
- [beast shrieking]
- [grunts]
- [beast shrieks]
[groans softly]
[grunting]
[gasps]
- [Helm grunts]
- [blood splattering]
[sinister music playing]
Huh...
[gasps]
[Helm] Héra...
I'm sorry, child.
I'm so sorry.
I thought I'd lost you.
I was trying to protect you.
You can't tear Wulf's army
apart one man at a time.
I can try.
I should have listened to you.
You're brave and clever,
and stronger than I knew.
And I was blind not to see it.
I've failed you.
All of you.
No.
Everything you've ever done
was for Rohan.
For those you love.
When I was little,
you told me,
"You only fail
when you stop trying."
You never gave up.
Never.
[sighs]
[wind blowing]
You're freezing.
Come on, move!
- [tense music playing]
- [gasps]
[Helm] Come. We have to make
a break for the gates.
It's the only way back in.
[both panting]
Don't let go!
[Héra grunts]
[both grunting]
[huffing]
[breathing heavily]
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
[blows horn]
[Héra] Help!
- What is that?
- [Héra] Open the gates!
Open the gates!
It's the king!
Open them!
- [wood creaking]
- [guards grunting]
[breathing heavily] Stop them!
[tense music
continues playing]
- [both panting]
- [guards screaming]
[grunting]
[wind blowing]
- [shields clanking]
- [guards groaning]
- [both gasp]
- [grunting]
[breathing heavily]
The gate is stuck!
[heroic music playing]
[Helm grunting]
- Go! Go!
- [indistinct shouting]
[gasps]
[both grunting]
[gates rumbling]
[grunting]
[Helm grunting]
[gasps]
[Olwyn grunts]
- [Héra] They're coming.
- [warriors screaming]
- [swords clattering]
- Hurry!
Hurry!
[Olwyn breathing heavily]
[grunting]
What are you doing? No.
No! [sobs] please!
I need you.
Rohan still needs you.
No, Héra,
they need you.
You must lead them now.
I can't.
[wind blowing]
You can.
You are a daughter of kings.
The day you were born,
I was brought to my knees.
My pride...
my joy.
You could rule the world.
[Héra] [sobbing] No.
- [grunts softly]
- [gates rumble]
[warrior screams]
- [grunts]
- [warrior groans]
[both grunting]
[screaming] Father! [sobs]
- Come away, child!
- Father!
[Olwyn] Come away
before you freeze to death!
- [all screaming]
- [grunting]
[mournful music playing]
Is there no one left?
Is there no one left
to face me?
[dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[Helm grunting]
[Targg] Fall back!
Sire! Come away!
You'll die out here!
- [Helm] Not while I live!
- [sighs]
Do you hear me, Wulf?
By my life,
Rohan still stands.
Helm Hammerhand
still stands!
[all grunting]
[grunting]
- [Helm groaning]
- [warriors grunting]
[dramatic music playing]
- [Helm groaning]
- [warriors grunting]
[EÉowyn] That is how
they found him.
Frozen in place,
still standing guard
before the gates
of the Hornburg.
His will unbroken,
his knees unbent.
[somber, mournful
music playing]
[Targg] Dead?
I'll give the order
to call off the siege.
We can decamp and be
out of here within the week.
We are not going anywhere.
You have won.
There is nothing
left to conquer
but a group
of starving refugees.
Sire, you need to look
to your own people.
They are suffering.
This long winter
has taken its toll.
Your stores of gold
are all but gone.
I implore you,
abandon this place.
Do you think
I want to be here?
Stuck in this filthy,
forsaken valley?
I cannot leave!
Don't you understand?
This is all I have.
Without vengeance,
this will have been
for nothing.
[sinister music playing]
No.
We cannot show weakness.
Not to her.
This keep will be her tomb.
How long do you think we have?
A few days
before he breaches the walls.
We cannot fight him.
We cannot call for aid.
[sighs] Even if we could,
who would answer now?
I'm afraid, Olwyn.
I cannot save them.
Perhaps not. But there is
something you can do.
You can choose.
You ask who would come
if you called for aid?
Rohan would answer.
[breath trembling]
People need hope, Héra.
Something to believe in,
no matter how out of reach
it may be.
So, you can wait and worry,
or you can choose.
You can choose how this ends.
[somber music playing]
[eagle screeching]
[inhales sharply]
[inhales] Hmm.
[Lief grunting]
[dramatic music playing]
[Olwyn] This is your plan?
[Héra] I never said
it was a good one.
[exhales]
[Lief panting]
Not that I mind carrying this
up 898 steps, my lady,
but why do you need
your father's armor?
[Héra] My father's
helmet and horn
are known throughout the land.
Why do I need
the king's armor, Lief?
For hope.
Hope?
Don't ask.
If I don't come back,
will you look after...
Right, enough of that talk.
You're coming back.
[dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[tense music playing]
[panting]
[grunting]
[tense music continues]
[dramatic music playing]
[axes clicking]
[Héra grunting]
[continues grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[imposing music playing]
- [breath trembling]
- [eagle screeching]
- [screeching]
- [Héra gasping]
[squawks]
- [screeches]
- [Héra screams]
[screeching]
I have read that
the Great Eagles
can understand
the common tongue of men.
- [squawks]
- [breath trembling]
Please, I beg of you.
I need your help.
My people need your help.
[Lief grunting]
[screeches]
[Lief gasps]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
- [eagle screeches]
- [dramatic music playing]
[commander] We've had enough!
Where's the money
we were promised?
This isn't about money.
Your mission is
to take that fortress
so we can end this damn war!
We care not
for your stone towers.
[Wulf] You should.
[coins jingling]
[indistinct conversation]
That fortress is full of
such riches. Room upon room.
[all whispering]
Those miserable rebels inside
that keep cannot use it.
They cannot burn it.
They cannot eat it.
- It's yours, all of it.
- [men laughing]
- Yours for the taking.
- [all talking excitedly]
- [coins jingling]
- [Wulf chuckles]
[tense music playing]
What are you doing?
The Hornburg has never
been used to store gold!
But they don't know that,
do they?
[men shouting indistinctly]
We can wait no longer.
Give the order.
Right, you lot.
You heard Lord Fréaláf,
time to abandon Dunharrow.
We make for Gondor
at first light.
- [eagle screeches]
- [gasps]
[suspenseful music playing]
[rhythmic drum beating]
[Wildmen chanting]
[Wulf] Leave none alive!
Kill them all!
He's moving the siege tower!
We're out of time.
Then all is lost!
[Héra] On the contrary.
An attack gives us a chance,
one small chance, to escape.
Wulf will throw everything
at us, which means...
His camp will be empty.
If we can clear
the secret tunnel,
our people can reach
the mountain pass.
From there,
they can make for Dunharrow.
It's too risky.
Wulf will see us.
No, he won't.
Because his eye
will be fixed on me.
[somber music playing]
[Héra] Are you ready?
Yes.
[Héra] Good.
Where are we going?
Somewhere safe.
Are your soldiers ready?
Aye, they are.
We'll get them to Dunharrow.
Or die trying.
Shh.
[all talking indistinctly]
[gasps]
[Héra] Lief?
No. No, this is all wrong.
I'm your guard, miss.
I want to fight by your side
till the end.
I need you to protect
what is most important.
our people.
[Héra sighs]
Well, go on with you then.
A straight line, mind you.
Don't be leading them
in circles.
[breath trembling]
[gulps]
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
[rhythmic drum beating]
[men groaning]
- [men shouting]
- [horn blowing]
[indistinct shouting]
He wanted a bride
and so a bride he shall have.
It's time.
I swore to your father,
from your very first breath,
that I would always be
by your side.
[sniffles] I swear it still.
- To my very last.
- [chuckles]
[Olwyn] What's so funny?
Why are you laughing?
- [kisses]
- Uh...
Because I get to choose...
and I choose not to be afraid.
[sighs loudly]
Ride strong, child.
- [rumbling]
- [all gasp]
- [woman crying]
- let's go.
We can't go out there!
They'll catch us!
No, they won't.
Someone stayed behind
to make sure they wouldn't,
to protect us.
Who did?
Have you ever heard
of the Shieldmaidens?
No.
They were women
of The Borderlands.
[heroic music playing]
When all the soldiers
had died,
they took up arms.
They defended Rohan
when no one else could.
Some believe
they're all gone now.
[child] Are they?
[Lief] Not all of them.
[horse whinnies]
[heroic music
continues playing]
[horse neighs]
[rhythmic drum beating]
- [Wildmen screaming]
- [rope whipping]
[wood creaking]
[sinister music playing]
[screaming]
[sinister music
continues playing]
[horse whinnies]
Advance!
[all screaming]
[neighing]
[Targg] Hold!
[whinnies]
What is this?
You come before me as a bride?
You think, after everything,
I would marry you?
[Héra] I am bride to no man.
[Wulf] Tell me then.
To whom are you pledged?
[heroic music playing]
Death.
Let us end this, Wulf,
as it began, with you and I.
If I best you in combat,
you let my people go.
[Wulf] Why would I agree
to such terms?
You have nothing to offer me.
You may wear a crown
upon your head,
but that does not
make you a king.
I am the last of the true
bloodline of Rohan.
I offer you a chance
to prove yourself
worthy of that throne.
You were too much of a coward
to face my father.
- So, face me now.
- [exhales]
[Targg] The girl is clever.
She is up to something.
Do not take the bait.
I accept your challenge.
You think I am afraid of you?
You should be.
- [yells]
- [neighs]
[grunts]
- [Targg] Hold positions.
- [men grumbling]
[both grunt]
[both panting]
- [Wulf grunting]
- [horse neighs]
[horse neighing]
[indistinct conversation]
- [man 1] This way.
- [man 2 coughing]
[man 3] Keep moving,
keep moving.
[all panting, coughing]
- [horse neighs]
- [grunts]
[both grunting]
[grunting]
- [men shouting]
- [breathing heavily]
[both grunting]
[thuds]
- [grunting]
- [gasps]
Call off your men.
You gave me your word.
I did.
Launch the attack.
No.
The girl was right.
You're a coward.
A coward with no honor.
[groaning]
[grave music playing]
With or without honor,
men bleed just the same.
Attack! Attack!
- [men shouting wildly]
- [Wulf] Leave the girl to me!
Hold your positions!
[guard] They're closin' in!
Move the last group now!
Go! Hurry!
You take care of this.
Our people still have a song
or two left in them yet.
[men shouting]
Héra!
[gasps]
[intense music playing]
Fire!
[men shouting]
[Olwyn grunting]
[grunts]
You have lost, Héra.
[somber music playing]
[all gasping]
[Wulf] The Hornburg
will fall...
just like your brothers.
Just like the great
Helm Hammerhand.
[gasps]
[gasps, grunts]
- [serene music playing]
- [eagle screeches]
[horn blowing]
Hammerhand?
[gasps]
[triumphant music playing]
The wraith! The wraith!
Helm Hammerhand has come!
The dead are upon us!
Run for your life!
For Rohan!
[Fréaláf] Forth Eorlingas!
[war cry]
[gasps]
[men shouting]
[Héra] Our people
do not call this keep
the Hornburg anymore.
[Olwyn] Héra!
They have named it
for its true king.
Helm's Deep.
[panting]
[men screaming]
[indistinct shouting]
[grunts]
I knew it.
[Wulf] From the moment
I first met you,
I knew you would be my doom.
[Wulf pants]
Héra...
- [yells]
- [grunts]
[intense music playing]
[all grunting]
[Héra grunts]
[screams]
[grunting]
Héra!
[grunts]
[both grunting]
- [intense music playing]
- [grunting]
- [Héra grunting]
- [groaning]
[Wulf exhales]
[sighs, breathes heavily]
[screaming]
[Fréaláf] After them!
Cut off the retreat!
[horse trotting]
Héra, you're hurt.
Let them go.
Let them return
to their homes,
their loved ones.
Rohan has seen enough war.
Show mercy, cousin.
Then let mercy rule this day.
[horn blowing]
[solemn music playing]
[sweeping music playing]
[birds chirping]
- [girl 1] Can't catch me!
- [girl 2 giggles]
[mother] Come on, now,
supper's ready!
[girl 2 laughing]
[EÉowyn] The long winter
had ended,
the green promise
of spring had come.
So began
the second line of kings,
and the hope
for a more peaceful age.
Fréaláf Hildeson,
tenth king of Rohan,
first lord
of the second line...
I present to you
the new master of Isengard...
[somber music playing]
Saruman the White.
If you should ever be in need
of assistance, my lord.
[whinnies]
[Fréaláf] It should have
been you, Héra.
[sighs] I never
wanted a crown.
It was always
meant for others.
Even so,
you would have worn it well.
I hear
you've received a message.
Yes. [chuckles]
An unexpected invitation.
Of course. Adventure beckons.
Go well, cousin.
[soft, joyful music playing]
But should your king
ever need you...
The king will
always have my sword,
my loyalty, and my love.
[horse whinnies]
[Héra] What are you doing here?
What does it look like?
You're no longer bound
to my service.
[Inhales deeply] I know.
[clears throat]
So, where are we going?
[sobs softly]
We ride for the Fords of Isen
to meet a wizard.
He has questions
about the Orcs I encountered
and the rings
they were stealing.
Oh, aye? And does this
wizard have a name?
He has many.
[suspenseful music playing]
But in the common tongue,
he's simply known as Gandalf.
[enthralling music playing]
[EÉowyn] Her name was Héra,
the only daughter of Helm .
"Wild," some called her.
"Headstrong and free."
And so she remained,
to the end of her days.
[sweeping music playing]
[ethereal music playing]