Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[Slap That Bass"
by George and Ira Gershwin playing]
Joker! Joker! Joker!
Mmm?
Huh?
And now without further ado... Joker!
♪ What the world needs now ♪
- ♪ Is love, sweet love ♪
♪ It's the only thing ♪
♪ That there's just too little of ♪
♪ What the world needs now ♪
- ♪ Is love, sweet love ♪
♪ No, not just for some
But for everyone ♪
Tell me about it.
♪ Lord, we don't need another mountain ♪
♪ There are mountains and hillsides ♪
♪ Enough to climb ♪
- ♪ There are oceans and rivers ♪
♪ Enough to cross ♪
♪ Enough to last 'til the end of time ♪
- ♪ What the world needs now ♪
♪ Is love, sweet love ♪
♪ It's the only thing that there's ♪
- I Just too little of ♪
- J& Just too little of ♪
I What the world needs now
Is love, sweet love ♪
Knock, knock.
[man whistling "When the Saints
Go Marching In"]
Morning, sir.
Nothing good about it.
Get up!
Let's go, get up.
Let's go boys.
Let's get this show on the road.
Come on! Come on!
Come on, get out of bed.
Let's go, get up.
Clean this fucking mess up.
Hey, Jackie, I need a hand.
- Put some clothes on.
Diaz, what the fuck?
You got a joke for me today?
Move!
All right, come on,
let's go, guys.
Move your fucking ass. Move.
Don't test me, Walters.
Come on, boys.
Get him on the ground.
Move your fucking ass, Bullock.
Fuck youl!
Get the fuck out my cell.
Leave me alone.
Hey, Arthur, you feelin'
crazy today or what?
I don't wanna come out today.
Take him down to F Ward.
You got a big day today.
You better put on a happy face.
Get the fuck off me.
Let's not do this again, Beanie.
Shut up!
Let's go, Arthur.
Come on, Fleck.
Don't need your fancy lawyer
blaming me if you're late.
She knows how much you like me, right?
Hey, Fleck, you got a joke for us today?
Yeah,
it's been a while, hasn't it?
[Jackie whistling
"When the Saints Go Marching In"]
Move.
Right on the line.
Let's go!
Back the fuck up, Ken.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Go on, front of the line.
Fleck. Fleck's next, my dear.
Hey, stay in line.
Yeah, you heard him.
Hey, hey, hey, back up.
Freak bit me!
Go.
All that kid's done
since he got here is fucking smile.
And today, all of a sudden,
he bites Moran?
It's because nobody likes Moran.
He was at Gotham State
for, like, eight years
before he got here,
and he's still a fucking temp.
Hey, Fleck, you got a joke for us today?
I already asked him.
I got a joke for ya.
This guy's dog dies, right?
And he really loved this dog.
So, he goes down to the church,
and he asks Father Mulcahy
if he'd perform a funeral for him. Right?
And Mulcahy says, "Oh, no.
I'm sorry my son,
we can't have a service
for an animal in our church.
Uh, but, I bet if you go down
- to the veterinarian in town..."
- Fuck.
"...he can do it for you.
You see?"
Goddamn it, Arthur.
Uh, so the guy says,
"Oh, thanks very much, Father."
And he says, "Do you think two grand
would be enough to cover the service?"
Father Mulcahy looks at him...
"Why didn't you tell me
the dog was Catholic?"
Eh?
Clean yourself up.
You like that one, Arthur?
Let's go.
"Why didn't you tell me
the dog was a Catholic?"
Look around, Arthur.
This is how the other half lives.
Could have been all yours
if you hadn't killed five people.
One live on national TV.
I When you close your
Earthly story... ♪
What the fuck is this shit?
♪ Will you join them in their bliss ♪
- ♪ Will the circle be unbroken ♪
Move, will ya? Moron.
Hey!
Come on. You fucking lunatic.
Jesus Christ, you couldn't
get him a fucking umbrella?
Aw, come on, counselor,
you know we can't
give these boys umbrellas.
It's for their own good.
Oh, don't give me your shit.
He's soaking wet.
Well, those are the rules, counselor,
but I'll break them if you ask me.
I bet you would.
Mm-hm.
Oh, you're welcome, by the way,
for getting him all cleaned up for you.
Sit down.
Here, Arthur.
Today, we're meeting with Dr. Beatty.
Remember her?
She's gonna be videotaping you this time,
so we can show it at your
competency hearing next week.
- And if they find you competent,
and they will, they always do,
then we're going to trial.
You need to be in an actual
hospital with actual doctors.
Not this Department of Corrections...
bullshit with these thugs.
Dr. Beatty thinks that with everything
that happened to you in your childhood,
it caused a split...
- this fragmentation in you...
...to help you cope with your pain.
She believes you have another
person living inside of you.
And it was this other person
who committed those crimes.
Do you understand
what that means, Arthur?
I'll be asking you
a few questions today, Arthur, okay?
Maybe you don't remember some things?
Or you're confused about what you did?
I'm here to help you
try and sort out what happened.
Arthur, I'm not here
only to help with your defense.
I'm here for you.
But for me to do my job,
I need you to be candid with me.
Does that make sense?
Can I have a cigarette?
Of course you can.
Let's start with the first incident, okay?
The three men who accosted you
on the subway, who bullied you,
did it feel like
they triggered something painful?
From your past? Your childhood?
Do you remember any of what happened?
Did you... black out?
See bright lights?
Mm...
Okay.
How about Murray Franklin?
What, if anything, do you remember
about that night?
The music.
That's good.
Arthur, that is good.
Can I tell you what I remember
about that night?
I remember you came out dressed as Joker.
And I remember Joker
was dancing to that music.
Right?
I really liked his band.
My mom and I u-- used
to watch the show together.
She liked
Murray Franklin as well?
"He's so handsome.
Look at those sparkling white teeth.”
Is that your mother's voice?
Mm.
Do you often hear her voice in your head?
All the time.
Did it change
at all after she died?
What does that mean?
Did you...
this other part of you...
Joker...
Did it come out more after she died?
You lived together, right?
In a one-bedroom apartment?
Maybe I could talk to Joker about it.
Would he like to talk to me?
[trumpet playing
"When the Saints Go Marching In"]
Hey, Arthur.
Arthur.
I mean,
he'll do anything. Anything.
The guards said you wanted
to show me how to kiss.
But they said Joker's
a really good kisser.
Nobody's ever gave me a kiss before.
Twenty bucks
says he chokes him.
There you go.
Ricky don't know what hit him.
There was no hesitation.
Kinda like...
I gotta be honest with you, Arthur.
I wouldn't have took you
for a hopeless romantic.
Can I have a cigarette?
Why not.
Oh, no, no, no. What are you doing?
He doesn't get a cigarette
unless he tells a joke.
No, come on.
He still makes us laugh, doesn't he?
Barely.
Hey.
Remember that music class we saw?
The other day? B Ward?
Remember, with all the singing?
I got you in. We're going next week.
Bullshit.
- The fuck you do that for?
- Eh, eh. No, no.
Went and saw Kellerman, I said...
you've been good. You deserve it.
The hell is he thinking?
Yeah.
He knows he can get
some good press for it.
Plus, I told him I'd go along with him.
Oh, ho, there it is.
- That explains it.
- Count! Let's go.
Line up by two.
Ricky. Come on, Romeo, line 'em up.
Let's go. Twos. Line up by twos.
Come on, let's go.
Are you being serious?
I am being serious.
On the Bible.
Wasn't that hard, either.
Ever since they made
that TV movie about you,
everybody still thinks you're a star.
How about you, Arthur?
Do you still think you're a star?
I bet you do, don't you?
& I said that's life ♪
All right, Arthur.
Come on, let's go.
♪ That's what all the people say ♪
[Jackie whistling
"When the Saints Go Marching In"]
Get out of bed.
Anderson, come on, let's go.
Clifford, what the fuck.
Let's go, boys, it's showtime.
Wakey-wakey!
- Move. Let's go.
- Get up.
Hey, come on. Let's go.
Look at you, Arthur.
Shot out of a cannon this morning.
All right, move it!
Hope they'll let me sing.
♪ Oh when the saints
Go marchin'in ♪
♪ I want to be in that number ♪
♪ When the saints go marchin'in ♪
♪ The sun is shining
Come on, get happy ♪
♪ The Lord is waiting to take your hand ♪
♪ Sing hallelujah ♪
- ♪ Come on, get happy... ♪
- Hold it, hold it. Hold it...
Group, I want you to welcome Arthur Fleck.
Now, I know it's odd to have
an inmate from E Ward in here,
but I have been assured
he's been a model patient
without any incidents.
I know this might feel strange, Mr. Fleck,
a new environment.
You see, we use music
in this class to make us whole,
to balance the conflicting forces, the...
...the fractures within ourselves.
All I ask is that you sing,
if and when you're ready to sing.
Okay, let's go.
♪ Forget your troubles
Come on, get happy ♪
♪ You better chase all your cares away ♪
♪ Sing hallelujah, come on, get happy ♪
How about this one? Try this.
No, no, no, I can't really.
Look, I don't know it.
Okay. Um...
Oh, this one.
Is it really you?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah? Great.
I'll give that one a go. Yeah, yeah, C.
♪ I got the world on a string
Sitting on a rainbow ♪
Excellent. That's it.
♪ Got the string around my finger ♪
♪ What a world, what a life, I'm in love ♪
My name's Lee.
Hi.
I'm Arthur.
I know.
- ♪ I've got a song that I sing
♪ I can make the rain go ♪
So, what's a nice guy like you
doing in a place like this?
I killed five people.
One live on national television.
What about you?
I set fire to my parents'
apartment building.
Actually...
...it was six.
Nobody knows, but also I killed my mother.
I should have done that.
My mother had me committed.
She says I'm psychotic.
You know, I must've watched that TV movie
they made about you, like, 20 times.
Yeah. Was it good?
They won't let me watch it.
It was good.
It was really good.
I grew up in the same neighborhood.
Me and my friends
used to take that staircase
to school every day.
My parents didn't
give a fuck about me either.
My father beat the shit out of me.
Well, guess what?
"Knock, knock."
"Sorry, kid, your dad
was killed in a car accident."
Sorry. That's not funny.
If only those friends could see me now.
When I first saw Joker,
when I saw you on Murray Franklin,
the whole time I was watching,
I kept thinking,
"lI hope this guy blows his brains out."
And then you did.
And for once in my life,
I didn't feel so alone anymore.
♪ Forget your troubles
Come on, get happy ♪
♪ You better chase all your cares away ♪
♪ Sing hallelujah, come on, get happy ♪
I Get ready for the judgement day
& The sun is shining
Come on, get happy ♪
♪ The Lord is waiting to take your hand ♪
♪ Sing hallelujah, come on, get happy ♪
Hey, Jackie.
You wanna know what I regret most
from being on The Murray Franklin Show?
What's that?
That I didn't shoot first and
let him ask me questions later.
That a joke, Arthur?
- Yeah.
All it took was you
getting a little old fashioned.
Thanks, pal.
Let's get your medication.
Not guilty by reason of insanity
makes no sense in this case.
He murdered five innocent people.
- His depraved acts of violence...
- Hey, Fleck.
- You're on the news.
- ...admired by his followers,
not only in our city,
but all over the country.
Vandalism, arson...
The judge says
you're competent to stand trial.
I fucking knew it.
And they are still willing
to commit acts of violence
in his name.
Now, these people,
they believe Arthur Fleck
to be some kind of... martyr.
- Well, he's not.
Arthur Fleck is a monster,
who knew exactly what he was doing.
- Yep.
- Hear, hear.
And our office will be
seeking the death penalty.
Thank you, we'll be taking
no questions today.
- Shit, bro.
You hear that, Fleck? The death penalty.
They're gonna fry you, Artie.
How does that feel?
I For once in my life ♪
♪ I have someone who needs me ♪
♪ Someone I've needed so long ♪
♪ For once, unafraid ♪
♪ I can go where life leads me ♪
♪ Somehow I know I'll be strong I
♪ For once I can touch
What my heart used to dream of J ♪
♪ Long before I knew ♪
♪ Someone warm like you ♪
♪ Would make my dreams come true ♪
♪ For once in my life
I won't let sorrow hurt me ♪
♪ Not like it's hurt me before ♪
♪ For once, I have someone
I know won't desert me ♪
♪ And I'm not alone anymore I
♪ Foronce I can say ♪
♪ "This is mine, you can't take it" I
Tell 'em!
♪ As long as I know
I've got love, I can make it ♪
♪ For once in my life
I've got someone who needs me
Go, Arthur.
♪ Foronce I can say ♪
♪ "This is mine, you can't take it" I
♪ Long as I know I've got love
I can make it;
♪ For once in my life, I've got someone ♪
♪ For once in my life ♪
Answer him, Arthur.
How's it make you feel? You scared?
Yeah, tell ‘em!
No, you cannot give
any statements to the press,
even if Kellerman asked you to.
You know they've been out there all week.
To see me.
They wanna talk to me.
Hey, Fleck.
- I told you before, I set up...
- Could you sign my book?
...an exclusive interview next month,
right before trial.
Okay, but Kellerman asked me
to make a statement now.
He's letting me go to this movie tonight.
- You know, like a normal person.
- What movie?
What are you talking about?
Come on, Arthur.
Okay. Um...
- Yeah, I'm sorry. I have to go.
- Arthur, I told you--
Okay, let's move it.
Hang on, Jackie. He's signing my book.
Make it quick, Arthur.
I don't want to miss the beginning.
Gonna be worth
a fortune when they fry his ass.
Easy, now.
Let's go.
Musical. Musical.
I'm sick of these artificial barriers
between the musical and the drama.
Well, then you
certainly don't need me.
Yes, we do.
Because you can be
greater than you ever were.
We are going to make you
explode on the theater scene
like a sky rocket.
Not just the old trademark
with the top hat, tie and tails,
but a great artist
- at the peak of his powers.
- Let's get outta here.
The new Tony Hunter.
- Tony Hunter, 1953.
- l can't.
They'll shoot me.
Come on. You already know
how this is gonna end.
- Everything's gonna work out.
- Shhh...
Well, what do you think I am?
What do you think they are?
What do you think the theater is?
It's all entertainment.
Believe me, there is no difference
between the magic rhythms
- of Bill Robinson's immortal feet and--
- You said that before.
- All right, all right.
Well, what did Bill Robinson do?
He danced on the stairs, didn't he?
Now, I happened to play Oedipus
the King on the same stairs.
What's the difference? We're all theater.
Show me the lowest
red nose comic in burlesque,
and I'll show you an entertainer.
We're all enter--
You're gonna miss the song.
♪ Everything that happens in life ♪
- ♪ Can happen in a show ♪
♪ You can make 'em laugh
You can make 'em cry ♪
♪ Anything
Anything can go ♪
♪ The clown
With his pants falling down ♪
♪ Or the dance
That's a dream of romance ♪
♪ Or the scene
Where the villain is mean ♪
♪ That's entertainment ♪
♪ The lights
On the lady in tights ♪
♪ Or the bride
With the guy on the side ♪
♪ Or the ball
Where she gives him her all ♪
& That's entertainment ♪
- Now that I understand.
- & The plot can be hot J}
♪ Simply teeming with sex ♪
J' A gay divorcée
Who is after her ex ♪
♪ It could be Oedipus Rex ♪
♪ Where a chap kills his father I
- ♪ And causes a lot of bother ♪
Fire!
Don't panic.
Easy, easy. Calm down.
Arthur, let's go.
Arthur, right now!
Slow down, one at a time.
♪ If they could see me now ♪
♪ That little gang of mine ♪
Come on, let's go. Go!
♪ I'm looking at your smile
And it's a healthy sight ♪
♪ I'd like those stumblebums
To see for a fact ♪
♪ The kind of top-drawer ♪
- ♪ First-rate chum I attract
Did... Did you do that?
I told you I wanted to get outta there.
Are you crazy?
♪ All I can say is "Wow"
Just look at where am ♪
♪ Tonight, I landed, pow
Right in a pot of jam ♪
♪ What a setup, holy cow
They'll never believe it ♪
♪ If my friends could see me... I
Oh, fuck.
Come on, this way.
- They're coming.
- Come on, let's go.
See, isn't this more fun than a movie?
♪ If they could see me now
That little dusty group ♪
♪ Traipsing around this
Million-dollar chicken coop ♪
♪ I'm rubbing elbows
With the cream of the crop ♪
♪ Whoever said
There ain't no room at the top ♪
- Whoo!
Let's go.
♪ To think this famous man
Which I must say is he ♪
♪ Should pick an unknown gal
Which there's no doubt is me ♪
♪ What a step up, wow, holy cow
They'll never believe it ♪
♪ If my friends could see me ♪
- ♪ If my friends could see me ♪
- ♪ Could see me ♪
- ♪ If they all could... ♪
- ♪ If they could see me ♪
♪ ..see me now ♪
Get the fuck off me!
You fucker!
Keep laughing, asshole.
Last one down on the left.
You wanna play
games on my watch, Arthur?
Two weeks in the hole.
Enjoy your stay.
♪ Take my hand
Stay here my friend ♪
♪ I'll find my way back to you ♪
♪ Here and now, I know somehow ♪
♪ We tell a story that's true ♪
I In our minds
We'd be just fine
♪ If it were only us two ♪
♪ They might
Say that we're crazy ♪
♪ But I'm just in love with you ♪
There's my guy.
Are you really here?
Yeah.
One of the guards let me in.
I'd do anything for you.
But we don't have a lot of time.
Come here.
What?
Come on. Can you get up?
Come into the light.
They're sending me home.
What? Why?
They're saying you're
a bad influence on me.
What?
This is gonna be good for us.
Now, I can be at your trial every day.
I can see you every day
until you get out.
And then what?
We're gonna build a mountain.
Wait, wait.
You brought make-up.
I want to see the real you.
Look what they did to you.
It's just us now.
You need to stop taking your medication.
I already have.
Can you do it?
Yeah.
What's he gonna ask me about?
Besides... you know.
Well, hopefully, about your life in here,
and what the conditions
are really like in this place.
He might ask you about Lee.
She's been out there giving
a lot of interviews about you.
And about herself.
Good.
You know, I love her.
She gets me.
Two minutes. Paddy's ready.
Arthur.
This is a chance for you to show
a different side of yourself.
So the public can see who you really are.
And I don't think you should smoke.
I think it makes you look cavalier.
Okay.
We need to use this time
to show people that you're human.
They need to understand
you were sick. Delusional.
Mm-hm.
You're not Joker. You're Arthur Fleck.
Hm?
Don't worry. You're gonna be great.
Arthur.
Are you okay? It's--
It's not too late to cancel.
So, uh... you want me
to call you Arthur or The Joker?
Mr. Meyers,
you know we have an agreement.
You can't call him "Joker."
It's Arthur. Arthur Fleck.
- When you're ready, Paddy.
She has to leave now.
You can watch from behind the glass,
but you can't be in here.
Just be yourself.
- We rolling?
- Rolling.
Cameras up.
Two years ago, the name Arthur Fleck
hit Gotham like a hurricane.
An unassuming part-time party clown
and struggling stand-up comic,
Fleck committed five horrific murders
in the span of just four weeks.
And now, with hundreds
already lining up to get a seat
at one of the first trials
ever broadcast live on TV,
Arthur Fleck, The Joker,
is sitting down for his first interview
since that infamous night
on Murray Franklin.
And yes, we all know how that turned out.
- Arthur Fleck, welcome.
Hello.
Take me back to that night
onstage with Murray Franklin.
What was going through your mind...
when you pulled out that gun
and blew his brains out?
Well, Paddy, um...
I was going through a lot back then. Um...
I don't really remember much
from that night. I, uh...
blacked out, I saw bright lights.
I was having a hard time
knowing the difference
between what was real or not.
Oh, please.
You did it on live TV, pal.
Doesn't get any more real than that.
Paddy, all I remember from that night
is I was gonna kill myself.
On television.
I thought Murray
was playing a part in my show.
But he was a bad actor.
So he got what he deserved.
Your last joke, if we can call it a joke,
"You get what you bleeping deserve."
That's what you said.
That's not fun, that's not funny.
You're right, I...
I should have told a better one.
You're trying to be funny now?
No.
Do you deserve to die?
The DA is calling for the death penalty.
You just said that you wanted
to kill yourself on TV.
So, tell us...
...you still wanna die?
Well, at the time, it certainly
seemed a lot easier than living.
Um, but that's...
that's not me anymore.
That's not...
That's not who I am.
That wasn't really you.
No, that's not right.
Let me get this straight.
- That's not what I meant.
- So your defense is,
"It was The Joker who did it."
- An insanity defense.
- Okay, I don't--
I don't know about a defense.
That this alternate personality,
this killer clown in you killed Murray.
Who am I speaking to now?
Which one of you is here?
The poor, low 1Q Arthur Fleck?
Or The Joker, who goaded
a bunch of no-good punks--
Do you really care?
You don't.
You're just like Murray.
You're just like everyone.
You want sensationalism.
You don't care about...
You just wanna talk about my mistakes.
You wanna talk about the things
that I did in the past.
Not about who I am now.
Not how I'm different now.
That's what we should be
talking about, Paddy.
Okay, okay.
- We should take a break.
- We're not taking a break.
All right.
Okay, so, tell us...
what's changed, Arthur?
Well, I'll tell you what's changed, Paddy.
I'm not alone anymore.
Right.
The girl who was singing.
The night you tried to escape.
We weren't trying to escape.
Miss Harley Quinzel.
You two put on
quite a performance that night.
Aww...
She's really something, isn't she?
You tell me.
I mean, don't you think it's all...
...don't you think it's a little too much?
A little much?
♪ She's a fool and don't I know it ♪
♪ But a fool can have her charms ♪
♪ I'min love ♪
♪ And don't I show it ♪
♪ Like a babe in arms ♪
♪ Love's the same old
Sad sensation ♪
♪ Lately
I've not slept a wink
♪ Since this half-pint imitation ♪
♪ Put me on the blink ♪
♪ I'm wild again ♪
♪ Beguiled again
♪ A simpering, whimpering child again ♪
♪ Bewitched ♪
♪ Bothered and bewildered ♪
♪ Lost my heart, but what of it ♪
♪ She is cold, I agree ♪
♪ She can laugh, and I love it ♪
♪ Although the laugh's on me ♪
♪ I'll sing to her ♪
♪ Bring spring to her ♪
♪ And long for the day ♪
♪ When I cling to her ♪
I Bewitched
♪ Bothered and bewildered ♪
- Excuse me. Yeah, thank you.
We'll be back
with more of Arthur Fleck
after a word from our sponsors.
The murder trial of Arthur Fleck
will begin today.
Assistant DA, Harvey Dent,
is preparing his opening remarks
in what some are calling,
"The Trial of the Century."
After months of protests,
police will be on high alert,
closing surrounding streets,
and setting up barricades for crowds
that could reach in the thousands.
If you ask me, this is what you get
when there's a complete
breakdown of social services.
And don't get me started
on this media frenzy.
All right, Denise, you're on the air.
Thank you for taking my call.
Enough is enough.
This idiot doesn't deserve a trial.
He should be sent straight to the chair.
An example should be made out of him.
& When you're smiling ♪
♪ When you're smiling ♪
♪ The whole world smiles with you ♪
♪ When you're laughing ♪
♪ Oh, when you're laughing ♪
♪ The sun comes shining through ♪
♪ But when you're crying ♪
♪ You bring out the rain ♪
♪ So stop your sighing ♪
♪ Be happy again ♪
♪ Keep on smiling ♪
♪ 'Cause when you're smiling ♪
♪ The whole world smiles ♪
♪ With you ♪
Coming in.
Okay. Showtime.
Shh! Shh! There he is.
Arthur Fleck...
Hey, shut the fuck up.
Arthur.
Milligan.
I'll split your head open.
Yeah, Arthur.
He's looking good.
All rise.
This court is now in session.
The Honorable Judge
Herman Rothwax is presiding.
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
Please be seated.
William, please invite the jury in.
Are you all right, Mr. Fleck?
Everything okay?
Yes, Your Majesty.
I'm just looking for someone.
Please, Mr. Fleck, sit down.
I realize there's a lot going on.
But this is still a court of law.
Any and all outbursts
will not be tolerated.
And that applies
to everyone in this courtroom.
Sidney, please call the case.
The People of the State of New York
versus Arthur Fleck.
Case number GC071963.
&' Everything that happens in life ♪
♪ Can happen in a show ♪
♪ You can make ‘em laugh
♪ You can make 'em cry ♪
♪ Anything ♪
♪ Anything can go ♪
♪ The clown with his pants falling down ♪
♪ Or the dance
That's the dream of romance ♪
♪ Or the scene
Where the villain is mean ♪
♪ That's entertainment ♪
♪ The lights
On the lady in tights ♪
♪ Or the bride
With the guy on the side ♪
♪ Or the ball
Where she gives it her all ♪
It's my view that there is
absolutely no evidence
that Arthur Fleck suffers from
multiple personality disorder.
Or that he ever behaved
in the role of "Joker,"
as a separate personality
dissociated from himself.
Doctor, in your opinion,
concerning the work you did on this case,
do you believe Mr. Fleck suffers
from a mental disease or defect?
No. In my opinion,
he's not psychotic
or unable to test reality.
I think he was sane
when he committed these crimes.
In fact, I believe he fakes
his mental illness.
Quiet.
And... if he's, uh...
...faking it, as you say,
then what is your opinion
on the defendant's mental condition?
I believe he has four relatively minor
and quite common mental disorders
that involve long-standing sadness,
narcissistic self-centeredness,
friendlessness,
an indifference to the feelings of others.
This is a very disturbed individual.
But I can't give you any kind
of psychiatric defense for him.
Thank you, Doctor Liu.
Nothing further, Your Honor.
Your witness, Ms. Stewart.
Thank you.
Doctor Liu, good morning.
Morning.
How long did you interview
Arthur Fleck for?
About two hours.
It was actually 89 minutes.
Tell me, how can you say for certain,
that Arthur isn't mentally ill?
How can you be so sure
after just 89 minutes,
that this "Joker"
isn't a distinctly separate
and split personality from him?
That that's not who he is.
Well, I also reviewed
all the test results.
Psychological tests,
neurological and medical tests.
And in my view, it's just a performance.
Did you read the records
from the Department of Social Services...
...that show that when Arthur
was seven years old,
they returned him to his abuser's home?
- His mother's home.
I did, yes.
And when you
interviewed him for 89 minutes,
did you ask him why Social Services
didn't believe the horrific stories
a seven-year-old boy told them
about the physical
and sexual abuse he suffered?
No, I... I didn't ask him about that.
Hmm.
So you want us to believe,
that after spending
just 89 minutes with Arthur Fleck,
and reading through his records and tests
from the same government
agencies that abandoned him,
you want us to believe
that you can say with absolute certainty
that Arthur doesn't suffer
from any serious mental illness?
That he didn't need
to retreat into fantasy
and create another identity
to protect that scared,
vulnerable, seven-year-old boy
from all the trauma and abuse he suffered?
And that that identity
didn't come out again,
when he was attacked and tormented
by three drunk bullies on the subway?
"After I woke up this morning,
I thought, ‘Murray, Murray, Murray.'
And then there's Murray.
Funny, right?
Then I remember Sophie.
- I had anoth--"
- Objection. Your Honor...
Again, my client's personal diary
is privileged.
Overruled.
Again, as long as Mrs. Kane
limits her comments
to Mr. Fleck's journals--
But these are my own
personal private jokes.
They weren't meant to be read out loud.
- Mr. Fleck. Quiet!
These are your words
she's reading.
And it's up to the jury to determine
what to make of them.
Please proceed.
Ms. Kane, please continue reading
from the, uh... the highlighted portion.
"Then I remember Sophie.
Had another dream about her. Forgot it.
I almost never dream.
What do I gotta do to remember?"
That's Sophie Dumond,
Mr. Fleck's neighbor,
whom he was obsessed with.
What was that date?
November 17.
Let the record show,
November 17th is the day that Mr. Fleck
stabbed Randall Kleinmanhoffer to death.
The very same day that he shot
and killed Murray Franklin.
Now, I know it's not
your area of expertise,
but you have read all
of Mr. Fleck's journal before, correct?
Yes, I have.
And in your opinion,
does this sound like a different voice?
Like a different, uh...
personality wrote this?
No, it sounds like Arthur.
Go on.
He often wrote about his fantasies.
And... the... women he had
imaginary relationships with.
And of course, his jokes.
There were always a lot of... these...
these unfunny jokes.
She's just a social worker.
I don't think she's even qualified--
You know, you're making him out
to be a fucking idiot in there.
He's never gonna get out
if you keep this shit up.
Ask her why she has me
sitting so far away from him.
Let's not do this here. Please?
Do you see all those people out front?
Who do you think they're here for?
How many T-shirts is Arthur Fleck on?
How many signs?
It's the Trial of the Century
and she doesn't even know
who her own client is.
- What do you mean by that?
- Can't you see how sick he is?
How much help he needs?
He's not sick.
He's perfect.
You don't really think he's just gonna
walk out of here, do you?
Yeah, he's gonna walk
right outta here.
- With me by his side.
- And then what?
Any further statements?
And then we're gonna build a mountain.
- A what?
- From a little hill.
- What does that even mean?
- Are you going to get married?
- Move!
You're not listening.
We can win this case,
and she's gonna fuck it all up.
No, you're not listening.
Lee's looking out for me.
She understands what I've been through.
What are you talking about?
We're from the same neighborhood.
She lost her father. You know...
her mom was awful to her.
She had her committed.
So just give her a break.
Okay, Lee cares about you, sure.
I know.
But she didn't grow up
in your neighborhood.
She lives on the Upper West Side
with her parents.
Her father is not dead, he's a doctor.
She voluntarily committed herself
to the hospital,
and then just checked herself out
when she wanted to.
She didn't check herself out.
Arthur.
I was a bad influence on her,
so they separated us.
Did she mention she went
to grad school for psychiatry?
You wouldn't get it.
My point is she's playing you for a fool.
I'm sorry, I just--
I know what it's like to love somebody.
But I don't think you can believe
a word she says.
From NCB Studios
in Gotham City.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's The Joker and Harley Show.
♪ There's a light ♪
♪ A certain kind of light ♪
♪ That's never shone on me ♪
♪ I want my whole life to be ♪
♪ Lived with you ♪
♪ There's a way ♪
♪ Everybody say ♪
♪ To do each and every little thing ♪
♪ But what good does it bring
♪ If I ain't got you ♪
♪ Oh, you don't know what it's like ♪
♪ Baby, you don't know what it's like ♪
♪ To love somebody ♪
♪ The way I love you ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ You don't know what it's like ♪
♪ Baby, you don't know what it's...;
What happened?
Well, you weren't even looking
at me anymore.
You were making it all about yourself.
- And the song...
is about loving me!
Now look who's making it
all about themselves.
- Oh...
So you're saying it's not about us?
It is, but we're singing for them.
- That's why we're here, honey.
Oh! 'Cause I got this sneaking suspicion
that we're not giving the people
what they want.
It's okay baby, you're right.
Let's give the people what they want.
Music. Let's take it from the top.
Is the honeymoon over?
What?
Why'd you-- Why'd you do that?
Pew!
- Get Healey.
- Pew!
- Ba-room!
Well, look at you.
Couple of weeks back on TV
and already acting like you own the joint.
What the fuck are you two doing
sitting on our bleachers?
Who said they're your bleachers?
Ricky, what the fuck has gotten into you?
You heard me. Up.
Guess who I just saw out front?
Your little lady friend.
All right, enough. Get up, both of you.
Hey, Fleck, you got a visitor.
See, Arthur? What'd I tell ya?
Move it!
Every day, this asshole.
You're a real
fucking whack job, Fleck.
Uh-uh!
Hey.
Five minutes.
How are you holding up?
Is everything okay?
Did you-- Did you lie to me?
Sure.
I mean, everybody lies a little.
And you're not
from the same neighborhood as me?
And your...
your dad's a doctor?
You're rich?
I just wanted you to like me.
Did you really check yourself in here?
Yeah.
That's crazy.
Just... because you wanted to meet me?
Just to meet you.
You could have just wrote me a letter.
And said what? I'm nobody.
I haven't done anything
with my life like you have.
Did you really watch that TV movie
they made about me 20 times?
Um... probably more like four or five.
Was it actually good,
or did you lie about that too?
It was great.
My lawyer... says you're
playing me for a fool.
I'm no fool.
Can't you see what she's doing?
They're laughing at you in there.
She doesn't care about you.
I do.
Do you know I moved
into your old apartment building
to make us a home for when you get out?
- Did your lawyer tell you that?
- You did?
- l don't want to live there.
I'm pregnant.
What?
& Why do birds suddenly appear ♪
♪ Every time you are near ♪
♪ Just like me ♪
♪ They long to be ♪
♪ Close to you ♪
♪ Why do stars fall down from the sky ♪
♪ Every time you walk by ♪
♪ Just like me ♪
♪ They long to be ♪
♪ Close to you ♪
R-Really?
♪ On the day that you were born ♪
♪ The angels got together ♪
♪ And decided to make a dream come true ♪
♪ So they sprinkled moon dust
In your hair of gold ♪
♪ And starlight in your eyes of blue ♪
♪ That is why ♪
- ♪ All the girls in town ♪
- ♪ Girls in town ♪
- ♪ Follow you ♪
- ♪ Follow me ♪
- ♪ All around ♪
♪ Just like me ♪
♪ They long to be ♪
♪ Close to you ♪
♪ Just like me ♪
♪ They long to be ♪
♪ Close to you ♪
Did you think he was gonna hurt you?
Or your daughter?
I did, yes.
You believed he was dangerous.
Well, he broke into my apartment.
You call the police?
No.
His mother told me, uh...
that he'd had problems
his whole life, but that he...
wouldn't hurt a fly.
And...
...was the man who broke
into your apartment that night,
was he different in any way
from the Arthur Fleck you knew?
I didn't really know him.
I saw him in the lobby,
the elevator a few times.
Like I said,
I knew his mother a little bit.
She was really sweet to my daughter.
And Ms. Dumond,
why is it that you didn't want
to come here and testify today?
And why did you initially
ignore our subpoenas?
Well, after Arthur did what he did,
the press wanted to talk to me about it.
And then I was a character
in that awful TV movie they made, and...
- It was awful?
- Then all these people...
No.
...supporters, I guess,
like the people outside,
started showing up
at my work and harassing me,
blaming me for what happened to Arthur.
So I was afraid for my safety
and for my daughter's safety.
We moved out of the city.
Well, then why did you
finally decide to comply?
Because I should have
called the police that night.
Then maybe all those people
wouldn't have been...
Maybe they wouldn't be dead now if I did.
Thank you. No more questions.
Your witness, Ms. Stewart.
Ms. Dumond.
What happened after you asked Arthur
to leave your apartment that night?
He told me he was having
a bad day. And then he left.
So, he never hurt or even threatened
you or your daughter?
No.
And did you watch him on TV
on Murray Franklin the following week?
I did.
And did that seem
like the same man
who was sitting
in your apartment that night?
Did he sound the same
or even look the same?
No, I mean, he was...
he was wearing clown make-up.
And while Arthur's mother
was being so sweet to your daughter,
what was she telling you
about her own son?
Um...
She told me that there was
something wrong with Arthur,
and that he lived in a fantasy world
and that he had this laugh.
She told you
it was a "dumb laugh."
That's what she called it.
"His dumb laugh.”
Yes.
What else did she tell you?
That she made up a story,
when he was a kid.
So that he would feel better about it.
So that he would stop crying,
so that he wouldn't kill himself.
What was the story?
That he was put
on this earth to bring joy.
Something like that.
It's why she called him "Happy."
And?
And she...
couldn't believe that
he based his whole life
around this made-up story.
He was a street clown,
and he wanted to be a comedian.
She made fun of him
for doing that?
She just thought
it was ridiculous
that he thought
he could make people laugh.
I mean, she said Arthur
wasn't funny at all.
Did she tell you
that he had been
in and out of institutions his whole life?
Yes.
Did she say
anything else about him?
♪ There's always a joker ♪
♪ In the pack ♪
♪ There's always a lonely clown ♪
♪ The poor laughing fool
Falls on his back
♪ And everyone laughs
When he's down ♪
♪ There's always a funny man ♪
♪ In the game ♪
♪ But he's only funny
By mistake ♪
♪ And everyone looks at him ♪
♪ Just the same ♪
♪ They don't see
His lonely heart break ♪
♪ They don't care
As long as there is a jester ♪
♪ Just a fool
♪ As foolish as he can be ♪
♪ There's always a joker ♪
♪ That's the rule ♪
♪ But fate deals the hand
And I see ♪
♪ The joker is me ♪
♪ They don't care as long as ♪
- ♪ There is a jester ♪
♪ Just a fool
♪ As foolish as he can be ♪
- There's always a joker ♪
♪ That's the rule! ♪
♪ But fate deals a hand
And I see ♪
♪ The joker is me ♪
♪ The joker ♪
♪ Ismeld
Yeah.
That he had never had a girlfriend
and she thought he was probably a virgin.
I can't do this.
- Oh! I can't do this anymore!
Your Honor, may I approach
the bench, please?
No, you may not.
I want to fire my lawyer.
It's about time!
Excuse me?
- I'd like to represent myself.
You're fired.
Arthur, don't do this. This is real.
- You'd better believe it's real.
I want order in my court. Order!
Bailiff! Take Mr. Fleck
to his holding cell!
Order!
I want to see all counsel
in my chambers immediately!
This way? Thank you.
Hey, no touching.
I'm so fucking proud of you.
You should see it out there.
They're all going crazy for you.
You did it.
I know, but maybe I should read
a law book or something.
You know I never went to high school?
I said, no touching.
You can do anything you want.
You're Joker.
Good evening,
it's 48 degrees at 6:00
on this Wednesday, November 8th.
I'm Stan L. Brooks
and here's what's happening.
Shocking developments at the trial
of Arthur Fleck downtown today.
Fleck, the accused Killer,
also known as Joker,
interrupted testimony and fired his lawyer
Maryanne Stewart in open court.
Then he kissed her goodbye.
Afterwards, Fleck
was extensively questioned
by Judge Herman Rothwax.
The right of self-representation
is not a license to abuse
the dignity of the courtroom.
Can you control your emotions, Mr. Fleck?
Yes, sir.
Judge Rothwax reluctantly
approved Fleck's request
to represent himself,
as long as he agreed to stand-by counsel.
A decision that both Fleck's
now former attorney,
Maryanne Stewart and Assistant DA,
Harvey Dent disagree with.
It's really tragic.
Arthur believes he has
all of these supporters,
but they don't care about him.
They care about Joker.
He's not dealing with reality.
He's mentally ill.
If we could have
just convinced him of that
then we would have won this case.
Fleck knows what he's doing.
He knows he's losing.
We cannot forget that he's evil.
This is all just part of his plan.
The Arthur Fleck trial
will resume on Monday morning.
In other news, Mayor Thorndike...
- There he is.
All right, calm down, everybody.
Hey, shut the fuck up!
Sit down. Sit down.
- Fleck, get off. Arthur!
- Yeah, Arthur!
Hey, come on. Get off the table.
Get down, Arthur.
- ♪ Oh, when the saints ♪
- Sit the fuck down, Ricky.
- ♪ Go marching in ♪
- Ricky!
♪ Oh, when the saints go marching in ♪
Ricky! Get the fuck down.
♪ Oh Lord, I want to be in that number ♪
- Give me the hat!
- > When the saints-- ♪
Get the fuck down when I tell ya.
Finish your fucking dinner.
Sit down!
- Calm it down.
- All right, show's over.
Calm down.
- Sit the fuck down!
♪ When the saints go marching in ♪
- Bullock!
- > Oh, when the saints! ♪
♪ Go marching in! ♪
♪ Oh, when the saints go marching in ♪
♪ Oh, Lord, I want to be in that number ♪
♪ When the saints go marching in ♪
I'll crack your skull open.
& When the saints
Go marching in ♪
After reviewing all the case law
that offers precedent,
Jensen v. Superior Court
being the most relevant,
I have reluctantly decided
that Mr. Fleck does have the right
as an attorney,
to dress himself how he likes...
- ...as long as he doesn't cause disorder
or interfere with
the functioning of the Court.
I will not allow this proceeding
to become as unruly as it is outside.
And I will not let you turn this
into any more of a circus
than you already have.
- Thank you.
Mr. Dent, call your next witness.
The State calls Gary Puddles.
Bailiff?
Will you please escort
Mr. Puddles to the stand?
Gary.
Go get 'em.
Please raise your right hand.
Do you solemnly swear that the testimony
you're about to give is the whole truth
and nothing but the truth,
so help you God?
I do.
Good morning, Mr. Puddles.
- Thank you for being here.
So one last question, sir.
The person who you saw
stab Randall Kleinmanhoffer to death,
are they in this courtroom here today?
Yes.
Can you point him out to all of us?
And... describe his clothing?
He's... He's sitting right there
at the table.
Wearing a red suit and clown make-up.
- May the record reflect
the identification
of the accused, Your Honor?
Yes, it will.
Nothing further, Your Honor.
Your witness, Mr. Fleck.
Mr. Puddles.
Gary Puddles?
Tell me, sir, is that your God-given name?
Yes.
Really?
Your last name is Puddles?
Why, it sounds like a... a joke.
Well, it's not.
You expect us to believe
that your last name is Puddles?
- Puddles?
Mr. Fleck, where is this going?
As I said, I'm not gonna let you
turn my courtroom into a circus.
Okay.
But, um, with all due respect, Your Honor,
don't you think
it's a little late for that?
- Don't try my patience.
- Okay. Okay.
Mr. Puddles...
earlier this afternoon you testified
that you saw me stab Mr. Kliman Manhoff
in the neck a couple of times. Correct?
Kleinmanhoffer.
Yes, I saw you.
Mm.
And what else did you see that day?
You stabbing him in the eye,
and bashing his head into the wall,
many, many times.
Yes, but, uh, Randall
was a bit of a bully, wasn't he?
He didn't deserve to die.
- l don't know.
Eh, never mind.
Gary, did you catch my act
on The Murray Franklin Show
later that night?
No, I didn't.
No?
Might I remind you
that you are under oath?
I was locked up at the police station.
In an interview room.
‘Cause they thought
you might come and kill me.
I was the only witness.
They kept me in there all night.
Isn't that convenient, Mr. Puddles?
That you didn't see the show,
you didn't see anything I had to say,
I can't believe it!
Mr. Fleck.
Okay.
Uh, when you were
in my mama's apartment,
God rest her soul,
when, as you say, you saw me
bash Mr. Klannonmen--
whatever's-- head into the wall,
"many, many times,"
did I seem crazy to you?
Did I seem like a different person?
Or was I the same old Joker
that I always been?
Arthur, don't do this
to yourself, it isn't you.
It isn't me?
So you don't think this is me?
Well, maybe... maybe...
you don't know who I really was.
I never saw that side of you.
Well, maybe you weren't looking.
Maybe no one was.
Because nobody knew I existed.
But look around, look at all these people.
Everyone outside. These cameras.
Who do you think they see, Mr. Puddles?
Joker.
Oh, sweet child,
what you have proven here today,
is that you are no different
than any of those people
that underestimated me.
From Murray Franklin,
to those goddamn fat,
stupid guards at Arkham.
They think that
they can treat me like trash.
But I will no longer allow you,
or you, or you,
or any of you to keep me down.
- l am free!
Why are you doing this
to me, Arthur?
What?
Gary, I like you.
I told you I wouldn't hurt you,
and I didn't.
Not hurt me?
I couldn't go back to work.
I still can't sleep,
and I'm scared all the time.
I never used to be scared.
I'm scared right now, here.
With you in front of me.
I couldn't do anything that day.
I felt so small.
I was reminded
how powerless I really am.
Oh... you got
a flair for the dramatic.
You are tugging at
my heart strings, little Gary.
No more-- no more questions, Your Honor.
Do you know what that feels like, Arthur?
Oh, fuck!
You were the only one at work
who never made fun of me.
You were the only one
that was nice to me.
I said, no more questions, Your Honor!
Very well, Mr. Puddles.
The court thanks you for your testimony.
Please step down, you're excused.
Mr. Dent, call your next witness.
We're not calling
any more witnesses, Your Honor.
That is the State's case.
The State rests.
Very well.
All right, Mr. Fleck,
at this point, you may mount your defense.
The defense rests as well, Your Honor.
Pardon?
Mr. Fleck, you don't want
to put on any defense?
No, Your Honor. The defense rests.
"Th-Th-Th-That's all folks."
- All right, all right.
All right.
That's enough!
This is a court of law!
With both sides having rested,
this court will recess
until tomorrow morning at 9:30.
You made our case
for us, you fucking idiot!
You're gonna fry
for killing my son!
Burn in hell!
Anything you want to say?
Arthur, will you be convicted?
Arthur, over here.
Let's see that smile.
Where do you think you stand, Arthur?
What are you
gonna do if they let you off?
♪ We're gonna build a mountain
♪ From a little hill ♪
♪ Gonna build me a mountain ♪
♪ Least I hope I will
♪ Gonna build a mountain ♪
♪ Gonna build it high ♪
♪ I don't know how we're gonna do it;
♪ Only know we're gonna try
♪ Gonna build us a heaven ♪
♪ From a little hell ♪
♪ And I know darn well ♪
♪ That if I build that mountain ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
- ♪ With a lot of care ♪
♪ I'll take our daydream up the mountain ♪
♪ And heaven will be waiting there ♪
♪ I'm gonna build a mountain I
♪ From a little heaven ♪
Do you?
I do.
And you?
- > Oh, yeah ♪
- > Oh, yeah I
- ♪ Look at that mountain ♪
♪ Look at that mountain ♪
- ♪ Gonna build a mountain
- ♪ Gonna build a mountain ♪
♪ Gonna build a mountain ♪
♪ Oh, let me build it ♪
♪ Just one mountain high ♪
♪ Gonna build a mountain
With a lot of care ♪
♪ I'll take my daydream up the mountain I
♪ And heaven will be waiting there ♪
♪ Gonna build ♪
♪ I'm gonna build us ♪
♪ I'm gonna build us
A mountain I
♪ Build us a mountain ♪
I High, let's build it ♪
♪ Mountain, mountain
Build a mountain ♪
♪ Mountain, mountain ♪
['Dancing in the Moonlight"
by King Harvest playing on radio]
I told him,
"I'm not dealing with those days."
I'm only working four of these days.
Good for you.
Joe, how goes it?
You know, same old bullshit.
Joker.
How's Kathy?
Is that really him?
Still busting my balls.
- Yeah, they always do.
- Yep.
See you fellas in the morning.
Give 'em hell, man.
Uh-oh.
I'm in trouble.
What?
Move.
Easy, darling.
Why is everyone so upset with me?
Move your ass.
Come on, Arthur.
I'm an attorney now!
- I will see you in court.
- Shut the fuck up.
And I'm the fucking Queen of Sheba.
I'm gonna fucking murder you.
Yeah?
Get up!
Grab his legs, Mac.
Let's go.
Had to go and be
a big shot on TV.
I think he knocked himself out.
Motherfucker.
Stand him up.
All right, I get it. I get it, Jackie.
You wanna-- You wanna hear a joke, right?
- You really think...
...fancy red suit
and muck on your face
makes you better than us?
You have no fucking idea what it takes,
put a little bit of joy
into this fucking place.
Let me tell you one I used to do
about my mother.
You can drop the act now.
- My mother was...
- Because we know
it's only Arthur in there, okay?
And she only dated abusive guys.
Yeah, is that right?
And, I asked her, I said,
"Mom, why do you stay
with your abusive boyfriend?"
And she said...
"Beats the hell out of me."
I told you to drop it.
Oh, he liked it!
Oh, Jackie...
aren't you gonna buy me a drink first?
Let's go, let's go.
- Let's fucking go!
- No!
- Get the fuck in there!
- Let go!
- Get that fucking jacket off.
Shut the fuck up.
Get his fucking rags off.
Jackie!
No! No!
- Arthur!
Mind your business, Bullock!
What'd you do to him?
Shut the fuck up, Ricky!
What happened, Arthur?
The saints are coming, Jackie!
The saints are coming!
& Oh, when the saints
Oh, when the saints ♪
♪ Oh, when the saints
Go marching in ♪
Shut the fuck up!
♪ Oh, Lord, I want to be in that number ♪
Get him fucking out of there!
♪ When the saints
Go marching in ♪
No, no! No!
Come here, damn it.
Fucking coming now, are they?
- Fucking asshole.
Are they coming now?
Ease up, Jackie.
Let him go, he can't breathe.
I told you to shut the fuck up.
Leave him alone.
Shut... the fuck...
- Jackie, take it easy.
- ...up!
He's gone.
♪ I've got the world
On a string ♪
♪ Sittin' on a rainbow ♪
♪ Got that string
Around my finger ♪
♪ What a world, what a life ♪
♪ I'min love ♪
♪ I've got a song that I sing ♪
♪ I can make the rain go ♪
♪ Anytime I move my finger ♪
♪ Lucky me ♪
♪ Can't you see, I'm in love ♪
♪ Life is a beautiful thing ♪
♪ As long as I hold that string ♪
♪ I'd be a silly so and so ♪
♪ If I should ever let it go ♪
♪ I've got the world on a string ♪
♪ And I'm sittin' on a rainbow ♪
♪ Got that string around my finger ♪
♪ What a world
♪ Yeah, there ain't no other
Kind of life ♪
♪ What a world, what a life ♪
♪ Hey now, I'm so in love ♪
Mr. Fleck, your closing statement.
A word of caution.
This is not a comedy club.
You are not onstage.
Excuse me.
Do you need a short recess, sir?
l... I wanted to come out here as Joker.
And I was gonna go on a... an angry rant.
And blame all of you,
and everyone...
...for this fucking miserable life.
But it wouldn't matter,
because I can't do this anymore.
‘Cause I can't be who you want me to be.
It was all just a fantasy.
There is no Joker.
It's just me.
I-I killed six people.
I wish I didn't, but I did.
Nobody knows, but...
I also killed my mother.
Put a... pillow over her face,
and smothered her to death.
I just wanna...
I just wanna blow it all up,
and start a new life.
Settle down.
Knock... knock.
Who's there?
Arthur Fleck.
Arthur Fleck who?
Hey, it's Harley,
leave a message at the beep.
Unless you're a reporter,
in which case you can just fuck off.
Thanks.
Hi, it's me. Arthur.
The jury has already
come back with a verdict.
Took 'em less than an hour.
So, you know.
But they let me call you
to see if you'd come back,
‘cause I want you here.
I didn't want you to go.
♪ If you go away ♪
♪ On this sunny day ♪
♪ Then you might as well
Take the sun away ♪
♪ All the birds that flew ♪
♪ In the bright blue sky
♪ When our love was new ♪
♪ And our hearts were high ♪
♪ And the day was young ♪
♪ And the night was long ♪
♪ And the moon stood still ♪
♪ For the night bird's song
♪ If you go away ♪
♪ But if you stay I'll make you a day ♪
♪ Like no day has been or will be again
♪ We'll ride on the rain ♪
♪ We'll sail on your touch ♪
♪ I'll talk to your eyes
That I love so much ♪
♪ And if you go, go, I won't cry ♪
♪ All the good is gone ♪
♪ From the word goodbye ♪
♪ If you go away ♪
♪ Ne me quitte pas ♪
Tension is mounting
as we wait to hear the verdict
in the trial of Arthur Fleck.
♪ If you go away ♪
♪ As I know you must ♪
♪ There'll be nothing left ♪
♪ In the world to trust ♪
♪ Just an empty room ♪
♪ Full of empty space ♪
♪ Like the empty look ♪
♪ I see on your face ♪
♪ I'd have been the shadow of your dog ♪
♪ If I'd thought it ♪
♪ Might have kept me by your side ♪
♪ If you go away ♪
As a reminder, regardless of the verdict,
I will not tolerate
any outbursts of any kind.
Foreperson, you may begin.
In the matter of The People
of the State of New York
versus Arthur Fleck,
case number GC071963.
As to count one, we, the jury,
find Arthur Fleck
guilty as charged,
with Murder in the First Degree
- against Maurice Franklin.
So say we all.
As to count two,
we, the jury, find Arthur Fleck
guilty as charged,
with Murder in the Second Degree
against Randall Kleinmanhoffer.
- So say we all.
- As to count three...
...we, the jury, find Arthur Fleck...
guilty as charged...
- Stop laughing, you sick fuck!
Fucking son of a bitch.
Sit down!
All of you will be held in contempt.
Bailiffs, get them
out of here immediately.
- Get them out of here.
- Don't move.
- You sick fuck.
It's you.
Come on, man.
We gotta get you the fuck outta here.
Come on.
I'll get somebody.
Hey! Hey!
I got the fucking Joker.
Can you get us outta here?
Yeah, get him in.
Get in. Get in, get in.
Holy shit, it's really him.
Where's he wanna go?
Drive. Just fucking go.
Those motherfuckers
got what they deserved.
Where does he wanna go?
Where should we go?
Just get us
the fuck outta here, man.
Hey, get down. Stay down.
- Get down, man.
Can you go any
fucking faster, man? Come on.
I'm trying. Fuck!
There's cops everywhere.
You did it, man.
You fucking did it!
You said you wanted
to blow it all up.
And somebody blew it the fuck up!
This is fucking crazy!
Fuck you.
Whooo!
We have devastating news
to report, right now.
A massive car bomb
has gone off in downtown Gotham.
- Holy shit.
- Exploding just outside
the county courthouse...
- Oh, my God.
- ...Wwhere thousands had turned out
to hear the verdict
in the Arthur Fleck trial.
Details are still coming in.
- Continue to stay tuned...
- You okay?
- ...as we bring you the latest...
- You hurt?
- ...on this situation.
- Are you okay, man?
Is he all right?
Fuck. Fucking A.
Can you cut around it?
No, chill out, it's red.
It's okay.
- Fuck!
- Calm down, man.
This is just
the beginning, man.
They're gonna burn
the whole fucking city down now.
No, no. Wait.
Wait, don't do this, man.
Come on, man. Get back inside.
- Get in. Get in.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Come back!
- Come back, man. Joker.
- Fuck.
- No!
Where are you going, man?
We still love you.
We love you, Joker.
Joker!
Lee?
Lee!
Look at you.
You cut your hair.
Someone blew up the courthouse,
and I'm free.
We can go away.
Lee, you hear me?
Someone blew up the courthouse.
We can go.
I escaped.
We're not going away, Arthur.
All we had was the fantasy,
and you gave up.
We were never going anywhere.
I'm that same guy you fell in love with.
I'm the same guy
that murdered Murray Franklin.
No.
No, you're not.
There is no Joker.
That's what you said, isn't it?
I can't--
I can't-- I can't live without you.
Please. We're having a baby.
♪ A show that is really a show ♪
♪ Sends you out ♪
Please stop.
♪ With a kind of a glow
And you'll say ♪
♪ As you go on your way ♪
♪ That's entertainment ♪
I don't wanna sing anymore.
♪ Asong ♪
Shh.
♪ That is winging along ♪
- Just talk to me.
- > Or a dance ♪
♪ With a touch of romance ♪
Just talk. Please stop singing.
♪ You believe ♪
♪ In all that we had dreamed ♪
♪ That's entertainment ♪
Goodbye, Arthur.
Touching, is it not?
Come, my little peanut of brittle.
I will help you.
♪ We're not a crowd...
& My echo, my shadow and me ♪
Fleck. Let's go, you got a visitor.
No fucking cigarettes left.
Let's go.
[whistling "When the Saints
Go Marching In"]
Hey, Arthur. Hold up.
Can I tell you a joke I came up with?
Um...
Is it quick?
Yeah, I can make it quick.
Okay.
So, a psychopath walks into a bar,
and sees this famous clown
sitting there all alone.
Totally drunk, it's pathetic.
"I can't believe you're here," he says.
"What a disappointment.
I used to watch you on TV.
What can I get you?"
And this clown turns and says,
"Well, if you're buying
you can get me anything."
"Perfect," the psychopath says.
"How about I get you
what you fucking deserve?"
Yeah!
♪ Whe... When... ♪
♪ When I build that mountain ♪
♪ As I will someday ♪
♪ And the Lord sends Gabriel ♪
♪ To take me away ♪
♪ I want a fine young son ♪
♪ To take my place ♪
♪ I'll leave a son ♪
♪ In my heaven on earth
♪ With the good Lord's... ♪
J..grace ♪
["True Love Will Find You
in the End" playing]