Place your bets!
Start!
Bet more, win more!
Keep your cards close to your chest!
Whoever's still standing in the end
wins it all.
Boss, it's starting.
New guy?
Just smuggled here.
You can fight.
Come work for me.
Not interested in triads.
Too good for the triads?
I want my money.
My boss is talking to you.
What's the rush?
Strapped for cash?
How will you spend the money?
I'm buying an ID card.
Perfect.
Your compatriots
got theirs from me.
Didn't you tell him?
That's right.
Come pick it up in two weeks.
Don't worry, we'll get it done.
Beat it.
Since July 1979,
the UN has listed Hong Kong
as a port of first asylum.
Refugees from all over flooded into Hong Kong.
The number of refugees in HK...
has reached 60,000.
Your ID's ready, come with me.
It's so phoney.
It's useless.
You paid for a fake ID
and you got one.
Are you stupid or what?
I don't want it.
Gimme my money back!
That's how we triads are.
I've got plenty of cash.
Still too good for us?
That's the real world for you.
That's what you get for turning us down.
You're done for, loser.
Scram!
Beat it!
Get outta here!
Move it!
Stop right there!
Go after him!
If you lose him, I'll kill you all!
Stop, egghead!
Stop.
Asshole.
Stop running!
Hello!
Hand it over!
Over here!
Give it back!
I'll be back for you!
Asshole.
Stop running!
This is Cyclone's turf.
Think I don't know that?
King.
What's up?
Are you lost?
Step up if you dare, punk.
Someone ran inside.
Watch them.
Get out of the way!
Watch it.
I'm working here!
Step aside!
Where did you buy that?
Leave the cash. The stuff's by the fence.
I've got stuff to sell.
What?
This is our turf!
Who let you sell here?
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
Why are you stirring trouble?
I'm not.
I just want money.
That's stirring trouble.
He's over here!
Don't let him escape.
Stop!
He's downstairs!
He's upstairs!
He's in Tai Woo!
Got him! He's downstairs!
He's in the barbershop! Go!
We're closed.
Let me go!
Need help?
Third Auntie.
Why didn't ya ask earlier?
Stick to your perm.
What happened?
This dummy tried to sell blow here.
Doesn't he know the rules?
I'm warning you.
Don't cause trouble in the Walled City.
Shit stirrers...
end up dead.
Leave!
It's still hot.
Hey.
Have a soda pop.
Crawl down from here.
Go down two stories.
Find the red balcony rails.
Cyclone will help you.
You're still here?
What do you want?
I want money for this.
Where'd that bag come from?
Mr. Big.
King and his men have been outside all night,
looking for him.
Who's your boss?
I'm not in the triads.
I got scammed.
You...
don't look like a local.
I'm a refugee.
Where's your family?
I don't have one.
Anyone who comes into the Walled City
is goddamn trouble.
Hand me the blow.
What's more important?
Money or your life?
Take him to AV.
Egghead.
Wait downstairs if you're still alive.
Rise and shine.
What are you doing here?
Leave.
I brewed you some pu'er.
Have some first.
I can't believe I made it in here.
Don't blame your goons, though.
I'm just too fast for them.
This is yours.
And it's paid for.
How is my thief your business?
Give it a rest.
Pick on someone your own size.
Is he related to you?
Butt the fuck out.
What if I say...
It's not settled?
How should I know?
It's the new issue.
Some real hotties in this one.
Check them out while you think.
You can keep it.
I thought you came in here
to start a fight with me.
He can stay in there.
I'll go get him myself!
Come in, if you can.
Inhale.
Exhale.
No broken bones.
Just apply some medicine.
Watch your diet.
No fatty foods.
No alcohol.
It was you last night?
In the Walled City...
If you give help...
You'll get help back.
Put that down.
Sorry, sorry...
What are you looking at?
Never seen one before?
No.
Hey!
You here for a doctor or for porn?
Porn.
They're helping you find her.
You dumbasses...
Mrs. AV isn't white.
You know she's an actress now.
Stick to the Asian stuff.
All right.
He's real sentimental.
Back in the day,
before he got chopped up,
he was hunky like Don Johnson.
Piss off.
Goddamn triad.
My boss
settled your mess.
He paid up for you.
Sign this.
You're in his debt now.
I'm the victim.
Why am I the one paying?
You're lucky.
You only owe cash
instead of your life.
What more do you want?
I want money.
In the Walled City,
anyone willing to work
will find work.
What do you want?
I'm looking for Fanny.
Shin sent you here?
Grab an apron.
Put on the rain boot and see the girl inside.
It ain't hard to marinade pork.
Douban, BBQ pork sauce, soy,
ground bean, fermented tofu.
Hoisin, sesame, dark soy sauce,
rose water, salt, sugar.
The portions are even simpler.
1 scoop, 2 scoops, 2, 3, 1 piece.
3 scoops, 2 scoops, 3 scoops, 1 scoop, 7 scoops.
You idiot, it ain't that hard to memorise.
Since we're co-workers, ask me if you get lost.
Keep them the same size. Hands steady.
Press with your thumb and index finger.
One scoop...
Three scoops...
Come on!
I'll go slow, listen up.
1 scoop, 2 scoops, 2, 3, 1 piece.
3 scoops, 2 scoops, 3 scoops, 1 scoop, 7 scoops.
Easy to memorise, ain't it?
Can you go slower?
Chuen, you've been showering for an hour!
There's not enough water to go around!
You're recovering fast.
What's his real job?
Your shampoo's all over Ho's veggies!
Veggies don't come with foam!
Cyclone?
He deals with this and that.
Everything here is his business.
LPG delivery!
Leave it there, thanks.
It keeps landing in my yard.
I dry my clothes in that yard!
He's a damn pervert, seriously.
He even steals underwear.
He's sick in the head!
Mary, Mary, have a seat first.
I exercise every morning. I dance.
I'm still feisty.
Still getting the aches?
It's good...
But the layout's a little lacking.
It's a nice flat.
The last tenant left because
he got assigned public housing.
It has great feng shui.
Exactly, the layout can't be touched.
Skipping another meal?
Hey, kid.
Like that shortbread?
Have you tried the famous
Walled City BBQ pork rice?
It's delicious.
Can't afford it.
I'll buy, come on.
Don't tell me you want an egg on top, too.
You're working multiple jobs
and pinching pennies.
What for?
To buy an ID card.
It's expensive.
You'll get arrested in Hong Kong.
Go elsewhere.
Where else can I go?
I almost died coming here.
Do you know anyone?
Aren't you afraid I'd scam you?
You wouldn't.
I'm the head of the
Walled City Security Committee, after all.
I was just asking anyway.
What's up with you?
Got a thing for sleeping on eaves?
I don't want to waste money.
Shin.
Yeah?
Clear out the attic.
Grape.
I don't want your rent.
When you've got a way out,
then go.
Have this if you'd like.
If you need anything...
Give me a holler.
It's more than enough.
What do I call you?
Egghead?
My name is Chan Lok-kwun.
Lo Hoi-pang, you're hysterical!
Want a hooker?
Fishball.
What are you doing here?
Waiting for my mum to finish work.
Hand it over!
I don't have any!
I really don't!
I've got nothing!
- You're lying!
- I told you, I don't have any!
Really?
What the fuck is this?
I bought that coke myself!
At least don't hit her face.
She makes a living with that.
Butt the fuck out!
You!
Stop gawking.
Gimme a hit!
The fish paste's going bad.
What are you doing here?
It reeks here.
Is there a dead rat?
That's why I called you.
Fishball.
Go home.
Poor thing, how did she end up here?
How do we get her down?
Shin.
Get AV over here.
Can I borrow some clothes?
Lok.
Thanks.
No wound on the arm.
If she tripped and fell...
She would've climbed back up.
Her head's smashed in.
She might have been pushed.
I don't wanna see this anymore.
I gotta get to work.
Kid.
Listen.
You're with me from now on.
You go wherever I go,
you hear me?
I saw that man beat her.
Shin knows, too.
Move the corpse to the public toilet.
Call the Urban Council, as usual.
Why doesn't anyone care?
This is the Walled City.
Even an illegal like you can stay here.
The Walled City's stench
will drive away
any normal person.
What else can we do?
Hey.
Are these all you have?
Fifty cents.
Goddamn woman beater!
Hit 'em harder!
Enjoy your sugar cane!
Eat this stick!
What a coincidence.
How'd you know I'd kick that prick's ass?
I don't need help...
I can take him alone.
Sure you can.
You're out of breath.
Thanks...
For the mask.
Are you Lok?
The guy who got his arm broken by Cyclone?
All of Walled City knows you.
He's half a Walled City man.
He's Twelve.
Master.
Twelfth Master.
Temple Street Tiger's best fighter.
You assholes
tore him up like tissue.
Will there be trouble?
We'll be fine.
We had masks on.
By the way...
Where did you buy these?
The corner store.
Me, too.
You look like you need food.
Come on. Let's celebrate.
BBQ pork rice!
Don't you think this mask suits me perfectly?
Yeah, you look just like it.
Stop being weird, you fucking dork.
You goddamn triad boys.
I'll kick your fucking asses.
Run!
Chow.
Kong.
Pong.
Win!
Are you three in cahoots?
Of course.
We're always down one player.
We finally have enough to play now.
Got a complaint?
Pay up.
Just take whatever you need.
That's a lot of cash.
Leave me some!
That's too much!
I had a really high score!
There, perfect!
Let's play again!
Send it up!
Cyclone, you weren't lying!
I wanna play, too!
I didn't think we can fly kites in walled city.
Are you into brawling now?
I told you to stay out of trouble.
Didn't you hear me?
Next time you start a brawl...
Count me in.
Sure.
Gonna stay here for good?
Oh, no, it broke!
Let's go pick it up!
Look at them...
They're so eager.
But whether they can pick up that kite
is up to them.
That damn kite
just floats in the air...
Who knows when it'll land?
This is a milestone year for Hong Kong.
The UK agreed to return HK to China.
Today's topic is "No Man's Land":
Kowloon Walled City.
What'll you have?
We have invited current affairs experts
Charles Ho...
and S.Y. Leung to chat with us.
How do you guys think
the Chinese and UK governments
will deal with the Kowloon Walled City issue?
I think it'll likely be demolished.
But that will involve far too many problems.
The law, compensation,
resettlement...
How will they verify eligibility?
What about property ownership?
It'll take forever to sort.
Why don't I talk to Shin?
Let him take you to the hospital
for an examination.
You're starting to have tinnitus and chest pain.
Your lung tumour is worsening.
Don't tell a soul.
I wonder if I'll live to see that day.
Take a seat.
Master will be out after his exercises.
Thanks.
Hey.
Sit down.
This month's Walled City rent.
Good work.
Give yourself a rest.
Stop pushing yourself.
I can't just sit back.
You've already helped me a ton
by killing Jim.
But my son is still dead.
That shithead...
won't have an heir, either.
I've looked for his wife and son for years.
I know that the wife is dead.
But his bastard son's still alive.
I'm certain I'll find him.
Have some tea first.
His son will pay for my son's life.
There's no sound...
This place isn't so bad.
Why tear it down?
What's so good about it?
It's cramped, dirty,
and nothing works.
What do the instructions say?
It's all in Japanese.
You watch their porn all day.
Take a gander.
(Japanese) "Connect the mic cable
to the audio output."
It works!
It's done?
It's done.
By singing along,
anyone can become a singer?
Pretty rad, right?
I've planned it for Cyclone already.
When this place is gone,
I'll open a Karaoke lounge.
It'll be a hit!
How about this?
You have the men and the muscle.
Let's start our own gang out there.
It's tiring to be a boss.
Dancing isn't tiring?
Actually...
It's easy to be happy.
Just gotta have fun!
Let's find a song to sing.
What's up?
I want to stay here.
I'll leave you the key. Lock up.
My mum died when I was little.
I grew up in foster care...
And never had a home to call my own.
But after coming here...
I can sleep soundly 'til dawn.
I don't want to leave again.
I want to stay in the Walled City.
This place will get torn down sooner or later.
I'll stay as long as I can.
The reason you can sleep soundly
isn't the Walled City.
It's the people inside it.
I want to work for you.
You want to be a barber?
Come here.
I'll teach you how to shave.
Speak.
Keep looking.
Why do you have shades on at night?
Because it's cool.
Can you see?
That's why I have this.
Chau doesn't know me.
Why am I invited to dinner?
Cyclone sees you as one of his own.
He wants the elders to meet you.
My boss, Tiger,
is gonna be there, too.
Are Chau and Cyclone friends?
They're sworn brothers who fought together.
When Chau went legit,
he went into real estate.
Now he's the Walled City's biggest landlord.
There's something I've wanted to ask.
Why are the walls so damaged?
That was a long time ago.
You really grew up in a bubble.
It was 30 years ago.
Walled City wasn't like this then.
It was a gold mine.
Then everyone wanted the cash cow for themselves.
It was an all-out war in the underworld.
In the end, only his boss Cyclone and
a man named Lui were left standing.
Lui stood a chance against my boss,
but not because of his skills.
It's because he had
a ruthless goon who killed without mercy.
The King of Killers, Jim.
To force Cyclone's defeat,
Lui took Chau as hostage.
Chau!
Help us, Chau!
He even killed Chau's wife and kids...
And took my boss's eye!
How did Cyclone win in the end?
The battle raged for 7 days, 7 nights.
It was one day, one night.
In the end...
Cyclone killed Jim.
Hey, we're late.
Lok.
What the fuck?
Why'd you order so much?
Won money at the tracks?
You'll know soon.
Boss Tiger.
Hey, you're late.
Had to deal with trouble on Temple Street.
This meal's on me.
What the hell's going on?
Fuck if I know, someone's being cryptic.
I finally found him.
Who'd you find?
Jim's son.
Chrysanthemum Room.
Thank you.
That's crazy.
The gods sent him back.
He deserves to die 10 times over.
Come on!
Let's drink to that first.
Cheers!
Boss.
Boss Chau, Boss Cyclone.
Boss Cyclone.
You're all late.
Where are your manners?
Sorry, but...
We dressed up out of respect.
Boss Chau.
Best wishes to your health.
Thank you.
I've never seen him before.
Kid.
Greet Boss Chau and Boss Tiger.
Boss Chau.
Boss Tiger.
The future of the Walled City
lies with you kids.
Sit.
Eat outside.
The adults sit here.
Let's go outside.
Drink up.
No one's leaving sober tonight.
You got it!
Let's order.
You weren't spotted, right?
I'm your lab rat again?
Take off your jacket first.
You're great at chopping goons.
But shaving?
Are you for real?
I got this!
I asked all my pals at the pier.
No one would come.
You're my only real friend.
- Lie down first.
- I change my mind.
Lie down, man.
It's dangerous.
Just lie down.
My wife's pregnant.
Congratulations.
You've got a bundle of joy coming.
You can be the godfather.
No fucking way.
If your boss knows your kid is my godson,
you're dead.
Then you can have the kid.
You're crazy, man.
Don't move.
I have to kill Lui.
You'll have to kill me first.
So, only one of us
will make it out alive?
What do you think?
If we can't see...
It'll be easier to strike.
If I die...
Get my wife and son out.
Learn how to shave and cut hair.
Take over my barbershop.
The boat will take you away.
You'll be picked up when you arrive.
Boss.
Watch your head.
Keep an eye on him.
Call everyone.
We gotta find him.
He's an illegal
named Chan Lok-Kwun.
Get a move on.
Message for 0723?
Password?
Message from Twelfth Master: Lok is Jim's son.
Say what?
Is Twelve drunk?
He said Lok is Jim's son.
All right,
number two Treasure Abound is a nose ahead.
Number five Joy of Reunion is on his tail.
Number two!
- Number two!
- Go!
Horse no. 2 wins by a nose!
You got lucky again!
You've got a real charmed life.
It's not just luck.
I've got brains, too.
We hit the jackpot, boss.
Winner takes all.
I need your help with the Walled City.
You know I can't touch it.
If there's nothing in it for me...
forget it.
Demolition comes with compensation.
What can the government afford? 100 grand?
A single unit isn't worth much,
but the whole Walled City
means hundreds of millions.
We'll have to go inside.
That's Cyclone's turf.
So what it's Cyclone's?
You scared of him?
Boss Chau, this way.
The usual, Boss Chau?
Yeah.
Boss.
Chau.
Mr. Big, surprised to see you
this early in the day.
I came to talk business with you.
There's not much for us to discuss.
Maybe not in the past...
But since the Walled City's coming down...
You're its biggest landlord.
I'd like to work with you.
You know that's Cyclone's turf.
He's my sworn brother.
What's your game?
Sworn brother? You're kinda dumb!
Show some respect.
We don't speak truths in here.
You're looking for a kid
named Chan Lok-Kwun, right?
Yeah, so what?
I know him.
Didn't you tell your "brother"
that you're looking for him?
He's practically leeching off Cyclone
in the Walled City.
Everyone knows about your grudge with Jim.
Even my boss is pissed about this.
Your wife and kid died so tragically...
You see him as a brother,
but he's taking you for a fool.
It's goddamn fate...
We got you a boat.
Leave now.
What do you mean?
You're Jim's son.
Chau and Tiger are out for blood.
Tiger said he wants an eye for an eye.
We're giving you a chance to live.
Get it?
Leave!
What are you doing?
What does their past have to do with us?
Shut up.
Don't get my boss in trouble.
Leave!
Do you want to kick me out, too?
I'm the man who killed your father.
I don't know him.
What he did is none of my business.
Leave.
I once thought I had nothing.
You were the only one who fed me
and took me in.
I'm not leaving!
You have no choice.
Leave!
Why didn't you tell me yesterday?
He owes me three lives.
I've waited years for this.
I'm claiming him now.
Simple question:
Yes or no?
Get him!
- Slaughter him!
- Over there!
Stop him!
Son of a bitch!
Another step closer...
And I'll kill you.
Your father's debt...
Will take you lifetimes to pay.
Kill him!
Don't come back to Hong Kong.
Don't you leave!
Boss.
Stop!
What's passed is past.
Leave it there.
Like hell I will!
Boss.
All bets are off!
What a hand!
Where's Mr. Big?
He's taking a nap.
You can talk to me.
I'll wait for him.
I end up doing the work anyway.
I want Chan Lok-kwun dead.
It'll cost you.
I'll pay whatever you want.
I'll have to go into the Walled City.
Go ahead, sit.
Since you've come to me,
that means you've fallen out with Cyclone.
Can I take his place, then?
As long as you kill Chan Lok-Kwun...
I'll give you whatever you want.
Deal.
How is he?
I stopped his bleeding.
His internal organs are hurt.
Chau won't give up so easily.
We have to get him out.
Will it be dangerous to move him?
It'll be more dangerous if he stays.
All right.
Make the arrangements.
You're very sick.
You need the hospital.
I'm fine.
Mr. Big has come in.
He's looking for Lok.
Boss.
You leave with Lok.
I'll handle Mr. Big.
I'm counting on you.
Shin.
Watch your boss's back.
Get to work!
Scram!
Have you seen him?
Have you seen this guy?
Look closer.
Have you seen this guy? Chan Lok-kwun!
Never seen him!
Have you seen him?
No? Are you sure?!
Messages for 3323?
What's up?
Mr. Big's entered the Walled City.
Boss Chau's not letting Lok go.
I have to go back in.
When I was 13, I almost OD'd in there.
I'm here today because Cyclone saved me.
He's going to save Lok like he saved me.
I won't abandon them!
I won't abandon the Walled City!
I get it.
Watch your back.
You still have to watch mine.
I knew I'm with the right boss.
Go back!
AV will get Lok out.
I'll go with you.
You said you're counting on me!
It's decided.
You can be my boss.
Stop!
Hey, stop!
Whoever spills where Chan Lok-kwun is...
can have this money.
Boss King.
I'll chop anyone that moves.
What's the problem?
Can't I look for a missing person?
You better know what you're doing.
Show some manners.
This is our turf now.
If you fuck around,
I'll kick your ass.
Mr. Big's in the barbershop.
My boss is waiting for you.
No one moves.
Protect the residents.
Leave the comic books for me.
I'm not invading your turf.
Your sworn brother Chau
leased this place to me.
What should I...
set up here?
A strip joint, of course!
If you hand Chan Lok-kwun over,
I'll leave you a spot by the door
so you can keep cutting hair.
I've wanted to retire for a while.
You can't protect him this time.
Boss,
Lok is at
Old Folks Street.
Take the back door.
AV!
Go!
Block!
Useless trash!
Put him down.
AV, get him out!
Block!
Spirit powers?
You know your shit.
Run!
Spirit shield!
Take this!
His power makes him untouchable.
Jeez, you're weak.
I'll take it from here!
Boss!
Open up!
Open up, Boss!
Boss!
Open up!
Why are you so emotional?
You can't be a boss that way.
Everyone dies sooner or later.
You son of a bitch!
Go to hell!
Stop it, you piece of shit!
Stop, King!
Let go!
Stop!
Boss!
It's goddamn fate...
Save yourself.
Stay alive.
Go...
Go!
Get Lok out.
He's all bloody!
He's keep bleeding.
Call the cops!
He's got no ID.
Cuff him first.
Will do.
What's the matter?
Pretending to be blue because
your brother got whacked?
Cry me a river.
If you don't kill Chan Lok-kwun,
don't you dare stay in here.
Now that we're in,
no way in hell we're leaving.
What?
You can't do a damn thing.
You think killing Cyclone means
you deserve his place?
Piss off.
I told you this chump is naïve.
He served himself on a silver platter.
Drag 'em in here.
Go on!
Go!
Move it!
Kneel!
Out of the four big landlords here,
you're the only holdout.
They've already
sold their streets to me.
It was a bargain!
Twenty bucks per feet.
What about you?
Know your damn place.
What is this, Mr. Big?
Hold him 'til he sells!
Head down.
Now that we own the Walled City,
we gotta expand.
In a few years,
when the government takes this place...
Even if we ask for $3,000 per feet,
they'll have to pay up!
You're gonna call the shots?
Of course not.
I'm just planning ahead for you.
I want you to take it easy.
How can I take it easy?
You're all fucking imbeciles.
You heard him.
Get to work!
Kick 'em all out!
Move it!
Take the shops!
Get outta here!
Clear out! We're taking the shops.
We're taking the shops.
What are you doing?!
Boss King.
Of course you call the shots.
You even killed Cyclone...
And Mr. Big is hurt.
Be the boss, we'll follow your lead.
What did you say?
I'll cut your tongue out.
Get outta here!
(Thank you so much for changing me)
(For giving so much silently)
(Your tenderness humbles me)
(Who! Can! Ever...)
(Take MY place!)
0723...
Chan Lok-kwun.
Tell the account owner
to wait for me.
0723 has cut his service.
You're a refugee.
You either accept deportation
or apply to go elsewhere.
Get it?
Where are you from?
I was born in Hong Kong.
According to the information you provided,
we've found your proof of birth.
Your parents really are from Hong Kong.
We'll issue your Hong Kong ID.
What are you doing here?!
What do you want?
Boss Tiger...
I want to see Twelfth Master,
Shin and AV.
They're all dead.
I don't believe that.
You got them killed.
I expect to die in Hong Kong.
I have to avenge Cyclone and the Walled City,
no matter what.
Tiger...
If something happened to you...
Twelfth Master would do the same.
The three of them are different men now.
You better expect the worst.
AV.
AV, it's OK.
You're not dead.
Since we're all here...
We should do something.
How about mahjong?
Mahjong!
You're fucking joking.
Gotta put a tile out.
You gotta believe me...
We didn't plan this.
Do you need a West?
Do you need it?
Since you're a buddy... Here you go.
Win!
Pay up.
Son of a bitch!
Keep playing!
We're one tile short.
I don't care, go!
How do we play with one tile short?
Shut up, or I'll whup your ass.
Go ahead,
but we're one tile short.
I'll whup you right now!
Where's Lok?
That shithead has ruined this place...
Karma's gonna get him one day...
You're back.
Wow, it's a Tornado.
That's right.
Tell everyone to go home now.
Don't step outside tonight.
Lok said to go home
and stay inside.
Stay inside.
Lok's back!
Let's go!
Move it!
- Let's go home.
- No!
Hey, kid.
Wanna play?
Son, we have to go.
Go play with him!
Go away.
Leave the kid alone.
Won't get scared if you can't see.
He's a kid!
It's fine, I'm just training him.
Don't be scared. Be brave!
No!
One.
Two.
Who the fuck is that?
He's still alive?
Don't count us out.
You know we're in.
Goddamn triad thugs.
You're leaving in a stretcher today!
Sure.
(Japanese) I'll fucking kill you all!
Y'all move fucking fast!
Shin!
Drop dead!
AV!
King!
You're fucking dead!
Block!
We can't beat him, tie him up!
He knows spirit power. Don't let him use it!
Tear him up!
Have to find his weak point.
Come on!
Shin, let go!
No fucking way!
Let go!
If we win, we win together.
If we lose...
We lose together, too.
Cyclone...
Swallowing the blade broke his power!
Don't let him pull it out!
Lok!
I'm fine.
Bring it on!
This place is so beautiful.
Look while you still can.
Hong Kong changes in the blink of an eye.
Buildings are constantly being rebuilt.
Everything changes.
Even the Walled City will go someday.
Whatever happens...
I believe that some things...
will never change.