[rain pattering]
[eerie score playing]
[thunder crashing]
- [line ringing]
- [man on phone] Hello, hello, hello?
Oh, is that the police?
We've got someone here
you might be interested in.
[chuckles softly]
I think we just foiled a robbery.
[siren wailing]
[reporters clamouring]
[gate clangs shut]
[neck cracks]
- [camera clicks]
- [judge] Feathers McGraw,
you have been found guilty
of the attempted robbery
of the Blue Diamond.
If not for the actions
of two upstanding citizens,
you would have succeeded
in your wicked plan.
Therefore, it is the decision
of this court
that for the rest of your natural life,
you'll be removed
to a high-security institution.
[children laughing]
[female guard chuckles]
There's no escape from here,
so don't even think about it.
[both gasp]
[ominous score playing]
[whimsical score playing]
[score ends]
[alarm ringing]
[ringing stops]
[machine suctioning]
[beeping]
[device buzzing]
[Wallace, over intercom]
Get me up, Gromit.
Another great day of inventing
beckons! [chuckles]
[laughing] Oh, top dog!
Here we go!
Away!
Oh!
Oh! Lovely.
[machine suctioning]
[giggles] Ooh! Tickles! [whoops]
Whoa!
[whooping]
Whee!
[chuckles]
Huh? [grunts]
Oh!
Ah.
Hit it, Gromit.
- [exclaims]
- [dings]
Morning, Gromit.
Oh!
How's my favourite pooch, hmm?
Oh, you do look after me, lad.
Very interesting.
- Oh, I must say...
- [toaster ticking]
Mmm. Oh, yes.
Mmm. Mmm.
Hmm.
Mmm. Cracking toast, Gromit.
[Wallace munching]
Oh, dear. More bills?
Inventing doesn't come cheap,
does it? [chuckles]
Maybe I'm just making too many gadgets.
[sighs]
Oh, don't worry, lad,
we'll think of something.
You look like you need a good pat.
Come here.
That's it, lad.
My new Pat-O-Matic will oblige.
And if you think that's progress,
wait till you see the next thing
I'm working on. Hmm.
Ooh!
[giggles eagerly]
[birds chirping]
[breathes deeply]
[wheels squeaking]
[Wallace] Oh, look out, lad.
Coming through.
Phew. [chuckles]
Oh, don't think I haven't noticed, Gromit.
You spend ages
toiling away in this garden.
Well, no more.
- [thudding]
- [ominous score playing]
Hey-hey!
[Wallace] This is my latest invention.
A smart gnome.
Hi, I'm your Nifty Odd-jobbing Robot.
Call me Norbot.
[Wallace] Norbot, meet Gromit.
Pleased to meet you, Master Gromit.
[Wallace] He's very friendly.
Whoa, steady on, Norbot. [chuckles]
Well, go on, Chuck.
Why don't you put him
through his little paces?
He is voice-activated.
[chuckles] A bit shy, are we?
All right.
Norbot, make Gromit's garden
neat and tidy.
Neat and tidy.
- Yes, Mr Wallace.
- [beeping]
[Wallace] I pre-programmed him
for you, lad.
He's watched every episode
of DIY Garden Squad there is.
[Norbot] Only two hours to go,
and they still haven't got the patio down!
[Wallace] Just watch him do
all those tedious gardening tasks.
Chop, chop, chop!
Mowing!
- [chuckles]
- Hey! More mowing!
[Wallace laughs] Don't forget the edges.
Strimmer!
[Wallace] Careful, lad.
[leaf blower whirring]
[Norbot] Pointlessly
blowing leaves around!
[Wallace] Oh! Whoops-a-daisy!
Hedge trim!
Last bit of mowing.
♪ I'm a happy, nifty Norbot ♪
♪ I love to do a job ♪
Neat and tidy!
[people exclaiming, applauding]
[Wallace chuckles]
Oh, he's a little treasure, that one!
Amazing job!
And very convenient.
Well, well, looks like
you've made the cut, Norbot.
Better take a bow, hmm?
[Norbot] Bowing! Bowing again!
- Where did you get him from?
- [Norbot] Thank you.
Well, actually, I made him myself.
What fun! Is he for hire?
Is he for hire? [chuckles nervously]
Oh!
Come on. I need your help.
Not you, lad. Norbot.
Yes, Mr Wallace.
How may I assist?
Come along, Norbot, lad.
We've got work to do.
[Norbot] Righto, Mr Wallace.
[Mackintosh] It's a crime.
That's what it is, a crime.
That you and I can't be together.
Not yet, my sweetness.
Soon, though.
- [knock at door]
- Oh! Eh?
- Got a mo, Chief?
- Huh?
I've just finished my investigation
into that missing bike saddle.
I've got witness interviews,
crime scene reports, full forensics.
Mukherjee.
And I checked
the National Bike Saddle database.
- There isn't one, apparently.
- Mukherjee!
Chief?
[sighs wearily]
How long have you been with us now?
Since 9:00 a.m. this morning, Chief.
Well, you can forget
what you've learned at training college.
Because at the end of the day,
there's just one thing
that matters in this job.
A copper's guts.
- Copper's guts, sir?
- Instinct.
The important stuff's not up here.
It's down here.
Yeah, I've got
quite a copper's gut meself, actually.
Oh, I can see that, Chief.
I mean, er... [chuckles nervously]
I didn't mean I can see... it.
Oh, is that Feathers McGraw?
[gasps] What? Where?
Oh. [chuckles] That.
Well, there you go, a copper's gut.
He stole the Blue Diamond, right?
Oh, he tried,
but he couldn't escape
the long arm of the law.
- [patriotic score playing]
- Oh, yes, I played my part.
[telephone ringing]
Hello, hello, hello?
[Wallace on phone] Oh, is that the police?
[Mackintosh] The Blue Diamond
ended up back in the museum vault.
I locked it up meself,
well out of harm's way.
Oh, I'd love to crack a case like that.
You must be dead proud, Chief.
It's not... It's not about pride, Mukherjee.
It's about duty.
Which is why I've accepted one last task
before I hang up my truncheon.
Oh?
The new Blue Diamond Exhibition.
The diamond's going back on display?
Oh, aye. I've designed
all the security arrangements meself.
Foolproof.
Yeah.
Well, not unless
Feathers cuts a hole in that skylight.
Skylight?
Or removes the back plate off the air-con.
- Air-what?
- Oh! Actually,
he could just get in
through the gift shop.
There's a gift shop?
Look! Feathers isn't gonna get in, is he?
He's safely banged up in the zoo,
literally doing bird.
Now, I've got a grand opening
to prepare for.
So get out there on the beat,
burn some shoe leather.
Yes!
[clears throat] I mean, yes, sir.
[grunts]
[Wallace] Oh, yes, that's it, Norbot.
Make the letters nice and big.
Oh. [chuckles] That's just smashing.
[chuckles] Ooh.
I think you're going to like this, Gromit.
Da-na!
[Wallace] Gnome Improvements.
A gnome-based
garden and maintenance service.
I told you we'd find a way
to pay the bills, lad. [chuckles]
Er, Norbot,
haven't you missed something?
- Oh. Yes, Mr Wallace.
- [whirring]
Oh, yes. Very good.
Oh, good job, Norbot.
[chuckling] Oh, yes.
- [horn honks]
- [woman] Yoo-hoo!
[Wallace] Hmm? Oh! It's Up North News.
Maybe they've heard about our Norbot.
Oh, this'll be great for publicity.
[announcer on TV] And now,
Up North News, presented by Anton Deck.
Good evening.
Now, we've all heard
of cutting-edge technology.
But how about "cutting hedge" technology?
[chuckles] Onya Doorstep has more.
Meet Norbot,
the latest thing in "gnome help."
He's the brainchild
of a smart-thinking local inventor.
Oh. "Smart-thinking."
Oh, thank you very much.
[Onya] So, Wallace,
what can Norbot do around the house?
Oh, well, pretty much everything,
Ms Doorstep.
No job is too small.
♪ I'm a happy, nifty Norbot ♪
♪ I like to trim the hedge ♪
Da-na!
Artistic!
I've been testing him out
here in my own garden,
and he's done a cracking job,
as you can see.
He certainly seems very "user-friendly,"
to use the jargon.
So what inspired you
to create this handy device, Mr Wallace?
[Wallace] Oh, I've always loved inventing,
making things that help people,
and Norbot is so very helpful.
I'd say he's my greatest invention so far.
We charge him up every night,
and the next day, he's raring to go again.
[Onya] He seems very obliging.
[Wallace] Oh, whatever your problem,
he's the answer.
[Onya] Well, sounds like this little gnome
is going to make
a huge difference around here.
This is Onya Doorstep for Up North News.
[foreboding score playing]
[female guard] Cage inspection!
[cell door opens]
Move aside, jailbird.
All clear.
What a deadbeat. [chuckles, snorts]
Don't know why everybody thinks
he's so clever.
[Wallace] AI, lad.
See how embracing technology
makes our life better?
[slurps, exhales]
I mean, thanks to that handy device,
we haven't had to use
the old teapot for years.
[chuckles] Oh, yes.
Tech, that's the thing.
So long as it knows who's boss, of course.
[chuckles] Look at him go.
[Norbot] Da-na!
[exclaims] A Wallace Onesie!
Oh! That's champion, that is, Norbot.
[chuckles]
[Norbot] A Wallace Onesie!
[Wallace chuckles]
Oh, I think this will fit perfectly.
[Norbot] Perfectly.
[Eric Coates's "By the Sleepy Lagoon"
playing on radio]
[door opens]
[door creaking]
- [Norbot humming happily]
- [door closes]
Evening, Master Gromit.
[music stops]
Norbot recharge time.
[moaning, shuddering]
[Norbot gurgling]
[gurgling faster]
[Gromit sighs]
[light humming]
[gurgling stops]
[Gromit sighs]
[gurgling and humming resume]
Recharge nearly 1%.
Recharge time reactivated.
[gurgling]
Recharge nearly 2%.
[owl hoots]
[gurgling continues]
[foreboding score playing]
[thunder rumbling]
[guard snoring]
[beeping]
[sniffs]
[inhaling]
[sneeze stops]
[exhales]
[inhaling]
[muffled sneeze]
[exhales]
[continues snoring]
[error tone buzzing]
- [videogame music plays]
- [Wallace] Welcome to my Top Secret Files.
[ominous score playing]
- [neck cracks]
- [thunder rumbles]
[warbling]
[warbling stops]
[thunder crashing]
[Norbot] New instructions received.
No job is too small.
- [tools whirring]
- [thunder crashing]
[tools whirring, clanking]
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder crashing]
[alarm rings, stops]
[machinery whirring, rattling]
- [Wallace] Get me up, Gromit.
- [device buzzing]
We've got a right busy day ahead.
- [machinery thudding]
- Thanks, lad.
Whee!
- [door creaks open]
- [mechanical footsteps]
[ominous sting plays]
- [door opens]
- [Wallace grunts]
Oh-ho!
Morning, team.
Mmm.
Oh! Loads of new messages.
[beeps]
[woman 1] Gnome Improvements?
I saw you on the telly.
Could Norbot come and mow my...
[man 1] ...new lily pond...
[woman 2] ...with a stump-grinder...
[man 2] ...and put well-rotted manure...
[woman 3] ...inside my conservatory...
Talk about celebrity, lad.
He's a "household gnome." [chuckles]
At this rate, we'll need
a whole army of Norbots. [chuckles]
[claps]
[loud rhythmic thudding]
Hmm?
Eh?
- [thudding continues]
- [objects rattling]
[thudding draws closer]
[dramatic score playing]
What on earth...
Hmm?
More Norbots for Mr Wallace.
Er... Eh...
[chuckles nervously]
Well, that is smart.
It's like he knows what we need
before we even know ourselves.
Ha! The more gnomes, the merrier.
Right, Gromit?
The more gnomes, the merrier.
[Evil Norbots] Yes, Mr Wallace!
[Wallace chuckles]
What could possibly go wrong?
[ominous score playing]
[Wallace] That's it. Up you go.
Uh-huh.
A bit of fine-tuning...
Oh, that's good.
No need for us to go with them, Gromit.
I just track them
with my new "gnoming device."
Ah! Lovely tea.
All we have to do is sit back
and let the machines take the strain.
Right, Gromit?
Gromit?
Gromit? Gromit?
[on radio] I said we don't need
to go with them. [chuckles]
Don't you trust my inventions, lad?
I don't know.
Hmm. Never mind.
Time to unleash the gnomes!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
- [whoops]
- [laughs]
[Evil Norbots whooping]
- Yeah!
- Rad!
[Wallace] Oh, yes.
All present and correct. Hmm.
Remember, I want you all working
- like a finely-tuned machine.
- [doorbell rings]
[whimsical music playing]
Ow!
[Evil Norbots]
♪ Oh, we're happy, nifty Norbots ♪
♪ We love to do our job ♪
♪ When we come round and fix your house ♪
♪ We make up quite a mob ♪
♪ We dig and paint, we plant and snip ♪
♪ We'll break our little backs ♪
♪ And never stop to have a brew ♪
♪ 'Cause we got battery packs ♪
This is the police.
Come down quietly.
You're only making this
harder on yourself.
[whimpering]
- [Evil Norbot] Beep, beep!
- [both gasp]
Beep, beep! Coming through!
[both shriek]
[music continues]
[woman moans]
Patio-chop!
♪ Oh, we're jolly, useful Norbots ♪
♪ We do all sorts of stuff ♪
♪ When we get asked to do a task ♪
♪ We can't work hard enough! ♪
♪ We push and pull and saw and chop ♪
♪ We think our chores are fun ♪
♪ We won't delay ♪
♪ Keep out our way until the job is done ♪
The Norbots are a triumph, Gromit.
We'll soon have those bills paid off.
- [music continues]
- [Evil Norbots vocalising along]
[weathervane clangs]
[Evil Norbots whistling along]
- [music ends]
- [Evil Norbot] Neat and tidy.
[Evil Norbots vocalising cheerfully]
- [vocalising stops]
- [foreboding score playing]
Oh, happy birthday, Mavis.
Oh, smashing!
Oh! What's happened to me glass table?
[gasps]
Where's me tools?
[gasps] Where's me shed?
Where's our drainpipe?
- [telephones ringing]
- Hello? Police.
- Another burglary? What's the address?
- [ringing continues]
Hello? Police.
- A weathervane? When did it go missing?
- [ringing continues]
Hello? Police.
[chuckling]
Someone's pinched your big butt?
Oh! Water butt!
[clears throat] I see what you mean.
- [ringing continues]
- Er, hang on.
[clears throat]
Hello. You have reached the Old Bill.
[Mukherjee yelps]
We're experiencing
a high volume of calls at the moment,
so please leave your crime after the beep.
Beep!
What's going on here?
Oh, Chief!
It's a spate of burglaries,
like, a proper crime wave.
I can't be dealing with a crime wave.
I've got enough on me hands as it is.
What do you think? Blue or black?
For the grand opening.
Er...
Blue?
Ah, yeah. See what you're saying.
Matches the diamond.
Anyroad, about these robberies...
I've been building this crime wall,
trying to find common themes and such.
Never... never mind crime walls.
What's your copper's gut telling you?
Well, all the clues
seem to point to this man,
a local inventor.
Wallace?
The upstanding citizen
who helped put Feathers behind bars?
Yeah. Hey, why not?
You catch one supervillain,
doesn't make you a saint, does it?
Well, should we say he's a suspect, then?
Just bring him in and book him.
I've got a speech to write.
Really?
Don't we need evidence?
Oh, I don't know.
All these fancy ideas you get
from training college.
[resigned sigh] Right. Come on, then.
[news intro plays]
[intro ends]
News just in.
We're getting reports of a crime wave
affecting gardens across the region.
Onya Doorstep has more.
[romantic movie score playing on TV]
- [score turns ominous]
- The robots!
They're taking over the world!
They'll destroy us all, I tell you!
Oh. That's a bit hasty, Norbot.
I might have been watching that.
Time to relax, Mr Wallace.
[Wallace] Oh, yes,
I do like a bit of relaxation.
- [warbling]
- Huh?
Eh?
[playing Brahms's "Lullaby"]
Ah... Oh!
Er, what's all this in aid of?
Massage, Mr Wallace?
Oh. Oh, yes. Oh.
Oh, oh, that's lovely.
Oh, dear, you are spoiling me.
Snoozy choc?
[chuckles] Oh! Don't mind if I do.
- Come along.
- Oh, steady on.
Drink up, Mr Wallace.
[Wallace moaning contentedly]
[hiccups, snores]
[foreboding score playing]
[tyres screech]
[tools whirring in basement]
[Wallace snoring]
[electricity crackling]
[dramatic score playing]
- [toy squeaks underfoot]
- [whirring stops]
[squeaks softly]
[toy squeaking]
[groggily] Hmm?
[moans, continues snoring]
[Pat-O-Matic whirring]
[grunting]
Hey! What the... What... [sputters]
Gromit? [grunts]
What on earth?
What? Is something wrong?
Is it the Norbots?
Well, this had better be important, lad.
I don't know what's got into you lately.
[huffs]
Well, I'll go to the top of my stairs.
That's absolutely...
spotless!
- [Evil Norbots humming softly]
- Oh! Look at them.
Oh, yes.
Oh, you are good gnomes,
doing all these chores
at this time of night.
I don't know why you were so keen
to show me though, lad.
Couldn't it have waited till the morning?
[Evil Norbot gurgling softly]
[chuckles] Daft pooch.
[yawns]
Well, I've got a nap to finish
before I turn in for the night.
Oh, yes. Norbot, my best invention ever.
[ominous score playing]
- [knock at door]
- Ooh.
Er, did you order a pizza, lad?
- [knocking continues]
- All right, all right. Hold your horses.
- [screaming] Police!
- [gasps]
- [crashes, yelps]
- Ooh!
[muffled] Oops. Sorry.
[sighs] Give me strength.
Right. Let's get this over with.
Get what over with?
We have a warrant to search your premises.
Mukherjee, read him his rights.
[clears throat]
Anything you say may be taken down
and used as evidence against you.
But I haven't done anything.
[Mukherjee] We believe you to be guilty
of theft by gnome.
I'm guilty of theft by gnome?
Ha-ha! There you go. He admits it.
Write that down.
Oh, this is ridiculous.
My Norbots aren't thieves.
They're down in my workshop right now,
doing a bit of spring cleaning.
[gasps] There's our evidence, Chief.
All right. Check them out, then.
[computer beeping softly]
- Well, I don't see any gnomes.
- Eh?
They were here a moment ago.
I don't understand it.
Er, they must have just popped out
to finish a job.
Look, sunshine,
I have not got time for your games.
Eh?
What... Where are you going, Chief?
I'm off to get me tash trimmed,
for the big day.
Anyway, look,
if you need evidence, Mukherjee,
find some.
I don't care what it takes.
Get this man behind bars
- where he belongs.
- [gulps]
I want this case wrapped up, pronto.
- Understood, sir.
- [door slams shut]
Right. Evidence.
Evidence?
This is PC Mukherjee calling for backup.
We'll need a van.
- A big one.
- [Wallace] Huh?
[alarm ringing]
[alarm stops]
[Wallace, over intercom]
Er, Gromit? Get me up, lad.
There's a good pooch.
Oh! Wait a mo.
You can't, can you?
They've taken all me inventions away.
For forensic examination or something.
[scoffs] Outrageous! [screams]
[muffled thud upstairs]
[Mukherjee] We believe you to be guilty
of theft by gnome.
[Wallace] They were here a moment ago.
[Mackintosh] Well, I don't see any gnomes.
[muffled thudding upstairs]
[panting] Who needs technology anyway?
Ha! Not me.
[gasps, yelps]
Whoa!
[shudders] That's nippy.
[screaming]
Whoa!
[grunts]
[groans] Me begonias.
[Wallace, upstairs]
I think I need a cup of tea, lad.
[glass shatters]
[suspenseful score playing]
[water drips, echoes]
[Wallace groaning]
Oh. Oh, right. Tea.
I suppose we'll just have to make it
the old way. Hmm.
Ouch!
Oh! Oh.
How do you do this now?
I haven't used one of these for so long,
I've forgotten how they work.
[straining]
It's broken!
There's clearly been a mistake.
My Norbots are innocent.
You believe me, don't you, lad?
Don't you, lad?
Oh.
Well, I think you've said
quite enough, Gromit.
You've never trusted my Norbot, have you?
And I made him just for you.
Mark my words, the police will be back
soon enough to apologise.
[knock at door]
Aha! What did I tell you? [chuckles]
There they are now.
Everything will be right as rain
before you can say...
Nasty, crooked, thieving little toerag!
- Huh?
- [angry shouting]
- [man] Where's our stuff?
- I... I want a refund.
What've your gnomes done with me bathtub?
And where's me glasses?
Oh. [chuckles] They're on me head. Sorry!
- [angry shouting continues]
- [woman] Where's my big butt?
I'm live
outside the West Wallaby Street house
of the evil inventor, Mr Wallace.
Evil?
Er, don't you mean "smart-thinking"?
Oh, you think it's smart
to teach gnomes to steal?
No!
But if only my gnomes were here,
maybe I could clear my name.
[laughs] Well, where are the gnomes?
For the last time, I don't know!
Oh, yeah? Very convenient.
[crowd chanting] Where are the gnomes?
Where are the gnomes?
- [chanting continues on TV]
- [ominous score playing]
- [chanting continues]
- [breathing heavily]
This is a nightmare, Gromit.
The police want to throw me in jail,
the neighbours all hate me,
and the press think I'm evil!
And how am I supposed to find my gnomes
if they've taken me gnoming device?
[engine stalling]
[crackles]
[dramatic score playing]
[engine starts]
[engine revving]
What?
Never mind Scotland Yard,
looks more like a scrapyard in here.
It's Wallace's stuff, Chief.
You told me to find some evidence.
I didn't mean
take the whole flippin' house.
I mean, what's this in aid of?
[device whirring, clicking]
Oh! Chief, I wouldn't...
[grunting]
Ow! Get off!
That gizmo
just assaulted a police officer!
Add that to list of charges, Mukherjee.
But that's just it, sir.
There's nothing here
to pin Wallace to the burglaries.
Huh. They're his gnomes, aren't they?
I'm just... I'm getting the feeling that...
Well, he may not be our man.
[Mackintosh] That Wallace is a wrong 'un.
End of story.
[Mackintosh] Now, if you don't mind,
we'll deal with that villain later.
Right now, we've got important duties
to attend to up at the museum.
But, sir...
It's my big day, Mukherjee.
The culmination of 40 years of service.
- Nothing can go wrong.
- [Mukherjee] Er, no, sir.
We have to stay focused.
Watch like hawks.
Absolutely, sir.
Miss nothing.
- [thuds]
- [Mukherjee] Huh?
- [Mackintosh] Eh?
- Hmm.
[Mackintosh sighs]
[radar beeping]
- [brakes squealing]
- [car horn blaring]
[tyres screeching]
[radar continues beeping]
[suspenseful score playing]
[soft rumbling]
[rumbling continues]
[bubbling softly]
- [animals growling]
- [elephant trumpets]
[animals calling]
[dramatic sting plays]
[baby seal purring]
[water bubbling]
[toy squeaks]
[ominous score playing]
[baby seal purrs]
[bagpipes playing ceremonial music]
- [screams]
- [music stops]
[water splashes]
[sawing]
[branch creaks]
[yelps]
Ah.
[chimes]
- Reset mode activated.
- [computerised trilling]
[gurgling]
[bubbling, splashing nearby]
[low growling]
[dramatic score playing]
[roars]
Hmm?
[grunting]
Huh?
[trilling, gurgling]
Restored to inventor settings.
Hi, I'm your Nifty Odd-jobbing Robot.
Call me Norbot.
Initiating pruning process.
[rapid snipping]
Neat and tidy.
[roars]
Huh? Hmm.
[Bach's "Toccata and Fugue in D Minor"
playing on organ]
[slurping]
- [Evil Norbot 1] Set coordinates.
- [Evil Norbot 2] Target located.
Two degrees West. Tracking.
[beeping]
No job is too small.
Neat and tidy!
[Norbot whoops]
[Mackintosh] Right. Here we go, then.
This is it, Mukherjee.
Are we ready?
Couldn't be readier, Chief.
[Norbot] ♪ I'm a happy, nifty Norbot ♪
♪ I love to do a job ♪
[Mackintosh] It's been my great pride,
over the years, to serve this community.
Knowing there's nothing more reassuring
than the sight
of an uninformed police officer.
[guests gasp]
[clears throat]
Sorry.
Oh! "Uniformed!" Uniformed police officer.
Can't read me own writing.
Anyway, now I have
one final happy duty to perform.
Contact imminent.
Going up.
[Norbot] Coming through!
[warbling]
Ladies and gentlemen, shall we?
[Mackintosh] And there we have it,
ladies and gentlemen.
Safely on display for all posterity.
- The Blue Diamond!
- [cameras clicking]
[gasps]
It's not as shiny in real life, is it?
You what?
[cameras clicking]
What...
That's a flippin' turnip!
[all gasp]
You didn't check inside the sack, Chief,
before you put it in the vault?
Er...
Oh...
Right. Anyone fancy a pint?
- Oh.
- [guests murmuring]
So, if you've been guarding a turnip
all these years,
then where is the Blue Diamond?
[radar beeping]
[plays discordant notes, sighs]
Gnomes have gone.
Gadgets have gone.
Even me dog's gone.
- [rumbling]
- Huh?
What on earth?
[gasps]
I didn't know it could do that.
What the dickens?
[door creaking open]
[Wallace] Come in, Gromit.
Everything's fine.
Just come straight in.
[muffled speech]
[in Wallace's voice] Everything's fine.
Just come straight in.
[in normal voice] Everything's fine.
Everything's fine.
- Everything's fine.
This is a disaster!
This has made me
the laughing stock of the town.
Er, sir, are you okay?
[clears throat] I'm fine.
Just got an allergy to turnips.
Should we haul Feathers in, sir?
He had the diamond last.
No.
No, he didn't.
What? You mean...
Exactly. Come on.
[foreboding score playing]
[owl hoots]
[Wallace grunting]
[panting] I'm sorry
I couldn't warn you, lad.
I got grabbed by the Norbots.
A very unpleasant experience.
Turns out they are bad, after all.
I just don't get it.
Why would me own gnomes turn against me?
A chicken? Behind all this?
Good grief! It's you!
Again!
But you're supposed to be locked up.
Well, you won't get away with it,
you know.
Whatever it is
you're trying to get away with.
Eh?
[Wallace mumbles in confusion]
Oh! Fancy a cup of tea, do you?
[scoffs] The cheek of it!
Well, I wouldn't bother with that teapot.
It doesn't work.
Eh?
- [dramatic sting playing]
- [teapot shatters]
- [magical tinkling]
- What?
Well, butter me crumpets! It can't be!
It's the Blue Diamond.
He must've switched it all that time ago.
Oh, is that the police?
We've got someone here
you might be interested in.
He's a slippery one.
Oh, so that's your plan.
You get away scot-free with the diamond,
and everyone thinks
I'm the evil inventor who stole it.
Why, that's...
That's... vengeance...
most foul!
- [door closes, lock clicks]
- Huh?
[muffled] Oi, let us out!
- [engine stalling]
- [mimicking engine revving]
[mimicking engine accelerating]
[mimicking tyres screeching]
[mimicking engine revving]
I can't believe
someone's nicked me bike saddle!
[panting] I know, sir.
Sorry, sir. You took me off that case.
Still, we've got our culprit.
[chuckles] All this time,
Wallace just wanted the diamond
for himself.
So, you were right all along, Chief.
- [sighs] He is a wrong 'un.
- Aye, too right.
And if he thinks he's got away with this,
he's got another thing coming.
Oh, this is all my fault, lad.
I only ever meant to invent good things,
things that help people.
I never imagined
they could be used for wrongdoing.
- [front door opens]
- [footsteps approaching]
- Oh, heck, it's the law.
- [door unlocks]
- I'm done for now.
- [door creaking open]
Morning, Mr Wallace. Master Gromit.
Norbot! Where have you been?
No job is too small.
Sounds like
he's back to his nifty odd-jobbing self.
We're saved! [laughs]
[Norbot] Neat and tidy!
- [door closes]
- Huh?
- [lock clicks]
- Wait, Norbot! Come back!
- [vacuum cleaner whirring]
- Don't worry, lad.
He's voice-activated. Hmm. Norbot!
♪ I'm a happy, nifty Norbot ♪
[Wallace muffled] Norbot!
♪ I love to clean the house ♪
Norbot! Norbot!
Steady on!
Huh?
What are you up to, lad?
[whirring]
Hardly the time to start leaf-blowing!
What on earth! [screaming]
[Norbot whooping]
[shouting] Gromit!
[Norbot] Collision warning!
Right. Someone's got
a big surprise coming.
- [Wallace] Sorry!
- Chief, they're getting away!
- Chief?
- [doorbell rings]
Did we get him?
♪ Born free ♪
♪ As free as the wind blows ♪
- ♪ As free as the grass grows ♪
- [Evil Norbots heaving]
[Wallace] Careful!
There's Feathers!
Nice work, Gromit!
Let's get after the bounder.
More speed, Mr Wallace?
[Wallace] Eh?
Whoa!
Steady, Norbot. Take her up, Gromit.
Hand over the diamond, you little tyke!
- Norbot, fetch.
- Righto.
[Wallace] That's it. That's it, Norbot.
- [tyres screech]
- [gasps]
[Evil Norbot] Banana alert!
Skidding!
[Wallace screaming]
[all screaming]
[crashing]
[Evil Norbots] Ow! Ow! Ouch!
[Wallace] There he is! After him!
[screaming]
Norbot, stop this thing!
Yes, Mr Wallace.
[Wallace] Not like that!
Whoa!
[thudding]
Emergency stop complete.
[Wallace groaning]
[engine starting]
Gromit?
Whoa!
- [engines chugging softly]
- [birds chirping]
[dog sniffing]
[woman humming softly]
[laughs]
[gasps] There they are, Chief!
Oh, nice-looking narrowboat, that.
A bit like mine.
Hang on a sec.
That is mine!
Hey! Stop in the name of the law!
[grunting, laughing]
[grunts] It's no use, lad.
If only there were some way
of rebooting them.
[groaning]
♪ I'm a happy, nifty Norbot ♪
♪ I like to clean the boat ♪
Ah!
[grunts]
Huh?
Another invention?
Are you sure, lad?
Right, then.
Technical assistance is on its way.
Can't believe he nicked me boat.
And you thought he was innocent!
[Mukherjee gasps] I think...
I think that's Feathers McGraw, Chief.
They're trying to stop...
- [over megaphone] ...Feathers McGraw!
- Feathers McGraw?
Don't be ridiculous!
He's banged up in the zoo!
That's just an innocent nun
out for a pleasure cruise.
I just think maybe Wallace has been
unfairly portrayed as a crazed inventor...
- [door opens]
- [both gasp]
[laughing manically]
Oh, this'll work a treat!
- [Mackintosh] Huh?
- ...to a certain extent.
What the...
What's he done
with me vintage boot collection?
Okay, Gromit. Let's give those gnomes
a good reboot up the backside!
- [cackling]
- Missed!
- [Wallace] Bullseye!
- Reset mode activated.
[Wallace] It's working, lad!
[laughs] Give it more welly!
Take that!
Hoodlums!
[Evil Norbot] Reset mode activated.
Reset mode activated.
This has gone far enough.
Chief Inspector Mac,
all units pursue
and arrest Wallace... [grunts]
Sorry, Chief, I'm using me gut.
Calling all units! Head to the border.
Suspect is not Wallace,
but a small nun in charge of a canal boat.
You're in big trouble, Mukherjee!
Yeah! This is going on
your assessment report, this!
[burbling] Reset mode activated.
[chiming]
[Norbots] Hi.
I'm your Nifty Odd-jobbing Robot.
Call me Norbot.
- [overlapping chatter]
- Pleased to meet you.
[warbles]
Caught a few tiddlers, have you?
Good lad.
Now we've got him.
Eh? Where's he gone?
[engine revving in distance]
Huh?
[Wallace] Well done, lad.
We've got him! [yelling]
Grom... it!
Don't let him get away! [screaming]
Whoa! [whimpering]
[yelping]
- [grunts] Sorry!
- Huh?
[squeals]
[Wallace yelping] Oh, Gromit!
[grunting] Huh?
[screams]
Oh, lummy!
Huh?
Why, ya...
[dramatic angelic score playing]
[Wallace screaming]
Ouch!
[sirens wailing]
[gasps] I knew it was Feathers McGraw!
Quick, close the gate.
[gasps] Gromit!
[whimpering]
[boat creaking]
Give him the diamond, lad.
I can live without inventing,
but I can't live without... [gulps]
...me best pal.
[dramatic score playing]
[score stops]
[boat creaking]
[gasps softly]
- [train chugging below]
- [horn blaring]
[boat creaking]
No!
[in slow motion] Gromit!
Hi. I'm your Nifty Odd-jobbing Robot.
Call me Norbot.
[Norbots] How may I help you?
No job is too small.
[Norbots] Aww!
I knew you would embrace technology
in the end, lad.
Thank goodness you're safe.
All right! Break it up!
This is a crime scene now.
Chief! Chief!
I haven't got time
for your apologies, Mukherjee.
- [exasperated sigh]
- Just arrest Wallace for...
Flippin' nora!
It is Feathers McGraw!
And he's got the diamond.
Oh, that's ruined me retirement, that has.
Wait? What?
[both laugh]
The old turnip switcheroo!
Oh, cracking move, lad!
- [Norbots cheer]
- [Norbot] Cracking move, lad!
[Norbots] Bravo!
[Wallace] Ha! That told him, Gromit.
He's a bad egg, that one.
And a scoundrel to boot.
I think you should have this, Officer.
Well, considering what I've just seen,
it looks like Mukherjee was right
about you being innocent.
You mean,
I'm not going to jail?
No. Thanks to the instincts
of a fine young copper.
You're a natural, Mukherjee.
Oh, thanks, Chief. That means a lot.
- Happy retirement, sir.
- [Wallace chuckles]
Well, this is a turnip for the books,
eh, lad?
Hmm.
[Norbots laughing]
[Norbot] Oh, yes! Very funny, Mr Wallace!
[whimsical score playing]
[sighs]
Oh.
Hmm. [chuckles]
[sighs]
[Mackintosh sighs] Ah, yes.
Oh, hey! Hey, What's this? What...
- [indistinct music on headphones]
- Can't you read, sonny Jim?
- Maximum speed four miles per hour.
- [siren wailing]
That's three points on your licence
for a start!
[Wallace] Morning, Gromit.
How's my favourite pooch, hmm?
Oh, I've got something
for your garden, lad.
[dramatic sting plays]
I've repurposed the Pat-O-Matic.
After all, necessity is
the mother-in-law of invention. [chuckles]
Da-na!
[Wallace] Aww.
Oh, but there's some things
a machine just can't do, eh, lad?
Aww! Aww! [chuckles] Aww!
Aww, yes. [chuckles]
Cheers, me old pal.
[Norbot] ♪ I'm a happy, nifty Norbot ♪
♪ I like to trim the hedge ♪
Da-na!
[whimsical score playing]
[Norbots] ♪ We're happy, nifty Norbots
We love to do our job ♪
♪ When we come round and fix your house
We make up quite a mob ♪
♪ We dig and paint, we plant and snip
We'll break our little backs ♪
♪ And never stop to have a brew
'Cause we got battery packs ♪
[score continues]