[ominous music plays]
[rousing choral anthem plays]
[foreboding music plays]
[haunting choral music plays]
[energy crackles]
[electricity crackles]
[haunting choral music continues]
[Neurolink powers up]
-He is alive?
-[chief technician] He is.
Just.
The Rue Kali was exhausted by the jump.
But we were able to force a little more
energy out of the ungrateful bitch
to heal the admiral.
-[switch clicks]
-[Neurolink powers up]
[Neurolink hums]
He had no brain function
for quite a while.
We don't know how bad the damage was.
We'll know what's left of him
when we bring him out of the chrysalis.
[ominous music plays]
[liquid gurgles]
[cable whirs]
[machine beeps]
[breathes heavily]
[gasps for air]
His airways are clear.
-He's breathing on his own.
-[Noble coughs]
Admiral.
Admiral, it's me.
Cassius?
[Cassius] Yes.
Where am I?
You're aboard your ship, sir.
The King's Gaze.
When we heard your ship was down,
we had the Kali jump us here to Gondival.
We have been holding in orbit
for your recovery, sir.
And thank the old gods,
our prayers have been answered.
Cassius, listen to me.
She's on Veldt.
Who?
Who is?
[coughs]
[inhales deeply]
The Scargiver.
She's on Veldt.
Set course for Veldt.
[Cassius] Yes, Admiral.
It will be done.
[dramatic choral music plays]
[electricity crackles]
[somber music plays]
-[uraki bellows]
-["From Far" plays]
[female singer vocalizes]
[uraki bellows]
I'm Hagen.
This is Den.
We welcome you to our humble village.
You must be tired and hungry.
And thirsty.
Well, we have prepared food
and drink for you in the Longhouse.
Come on. You'll see what great hosts
my people can be.
Let's bring these urakis to the stable.
They've come back.
Well, how do they look?
Strong, like warriors, I guess.
-How many of them?
-Six.
-With Kora and Gunnar.
-[Aris] Six.
It won't matter how strong they are,
will it?
[transmitter burrs rhythmically]
-[knobs click]
-[frequency tunes]
You can't be here.
[radio buzzes]
[radio warbles]
[frequency tunes]
Commander Cassius.
Soldier. All is as it should be, I trust.
Yes, sir. All is on target.
Nothing out of the ordinary?
-No, sir.
-[Cassius] Very well.
Ensure that the harvest
is brought in as planned,
and ready for our arrival
in five days' time.
[gasps]
Five days?
[tense music plays]
[foreboding music plays]
[scanner beeps]
[FLIR trills]
They have gone into the Longhouse.
Set up a transmitter.
See if you can find some firewood.
Understood.
This spot should do nicely.
Move out.
[scanner beeps]
[foreboding music continues]
Come. [clears throat]
Now, please eat.
You must all be very hungry.
Okay.
Our villagers have prepared
a bounty of food and drink
to show their fealty
and gratitude at your arrival.
But where is everyone?
[hesitates] How would you feel?
The lot of you, if you were not capable
of standing to protect your own home?
[Hagen] Mmm-hmm.
If you had to ask others
to lay down their lives for you.
[Milius] They should see there's no shame
in our being here.
To swallow their pride to ask for help,
that is bravery itself.
-Thank you.
-Yes.
And as it happens,
nobody need lay down their lives.
A defense won't be necessary.
-Admiral Noble's dead.
-[Hagen] What?
-He's dead?
-Really?
[laughs]
You need to say it again.
He doesn't believe it.
-[Hagen exclaims happily]
-He's dead.
[laughter]
You do not believe that they will return?
[Kora] I don't.
It's Imperial protocol
in the event of an admiral's death
to return to the Motherworld at once.
Then we owe you
an even deeper debt of gratitude--
[Aris] You're wrong.
I just received word.
[sighs] They'll be here in five days.
Is that true?
-[Den] Five days?
-Yes.
I thought you said
that you killed Admiral Noble.
I did kill him. His body was smashed
on the rocks. He is dead.
It's against protocol to come without
an admiral to command the ship, right?
That is true.
But death is not always deterrent enough
for the designs of the Motherworld.
They must be more in need of this grain
than we could have known.
-Hagen?
-Yes.
Call your villagers. Let me talk to them.
Okay.
-[villagers murmur]
-[somber music plays]
Dark days lie ahead of us all.
When the time comes…
we may all have to stand together,
in battle, as brothers.
To succeed,
there must be trust between us.
In time, we will teach you how to fight.
But first, you must show us your strength.
The way of the land.
If we do not act quickly,
the destruction of your village…
is all but assured.
Now, how long does it take
to bring in your crop?
Half a cycle around Mara.
No, it must be done in three days' time.
-What?
-It can't be done.
[villagers murmur]
[Titus] We need
every man and woman who's able.
The grain is our most powerful weapon.
Without it,
they are liable to blow us
out of existence from orbit.
If we bring it in fast,
we can use it,
both as a bartering tool and shield.
I thought you said
they wouldn't negotiate.
[Kora] Admiral Noble wouldn't have.
But whoever the second in command is
just might be willing to make a trade.
That's right.
Now rest well.
The work begins at dawn.
[Hagen] You heard the man.
Dawn.
[villagers murmur]
[somber music plays]
You think they'll learn
to trust one another?
They're frightened…
of outsiders, the battle to come,
for their lives.
Trust? I don't know.
I just hope they all have the courage
to stand and fight, if it comes to it.
I had no idea
what it would be like to fight.
How much it would scare me.
-You are afraid to die.
-[chuckles]
[chuckles] That's okay. Everyone is.
I didn't even think about dying
in the moment.
If you would've asked me before
how I feel,
I would have said I'd be petrified.
And I was scared.
The most afraid I've ever been in my life.
What was it you were so afraid of?
If it wasn't death?
It was you.
It was losing you.
[Kora breathes heavily]
-[birds sing]
-[crickets chirp]
[gentle music plays]
[Gunnar breathes heavily]
[Kora moans]
[moans in pleasure]
[pants]
[Gunnar chuckles]
[both moan in pleasure]
[Gunnar pants]
[both moan]
[Kora moans]
[Gunnar pants]
[both chuckle]
What Noble said…
about you being the most wanted criminal
in the known universe.
[Gunnar scoffs]
You don't become that
simply by running away.
[Kora sighs]
You remember how I told you
I was raised by Balisarius?
[Gunnar] Mmm-hmm.
Regent of the Imperium?
And how I was the bodyguard
to the Princess Issa?
Yes.
And that you were a decorated warrior.
Friend of the royal family.
What happened to them?
Under the healing influence
of his daughter,
the King had begun to see
many things in a different light.
[bell tolls]
[Kora] Word had reached him
that his most celebrated general
would fall without honor.
[King] What have you done?!
[Kora] And that his main weapons
were slaughter and cruelty.
So the King knew
he must not let him retain his command.
He should have destroyed Balisarius
and then me along with him.
But the King loved him,
and even through his rage,
saw him as a son.
[ominous choral music plays]
[music builds]
And so for his sins,
he was made a senator.
But for all his ferociousness
on the battlefield,
there was nothing compared
to his skill and cunning as a politician.
[sinister music plays]
[Senate applauds]
[Senate cheers]
Because that is what it means
to be a true soldier of the Realm!
[Kora] And in the echoing
marble halls of the Senate
did he find his true calling.
[Senate cheers]
[Balisarius]
But still I would give my life…
No, no, no, I would give my fucking soul
to protect our home from the darkness
that creeps towards us, my friends!
[indistinct chatter]
Ah, daughter, the news is dire.
I've learned that
the King plans to abdicate
and pass the kingdom onto the princess.
He also plans to disband
the Empire and execute the generals.
He said that, um,
Issa had looked into his eyes
and forgiven him,
but that now, you must make things right.
If what you say is true,
Issa will rule with wisdom and reason.
Yes.
That all may be true,
but when the cleansing begins,
you and I will be the first ones to go.
We can't allow that, can we?
The Realm is more than you
or I or some little girl.
And it will not be sacrificed
on the guilt of a spineless king
who, instead of ruling
in this blood-stained chamber,
would hide behind
the innocence of a child.
What can we do? It is the King's wish.
[Balisarius] The King is just a man.
Every general and half of the Senate
have their places because of me.
Listen, Arthelais, you are my family.
And when I am Regent Militarium,
you won't be the servant to the princess.
You will take her place.
[foreboding music plays]
[sighs]
[dramatic music plays]
[royal dropship whooshes]
[Kora] It was the dedication
of what would be
the last Dreadnought class battleship.
A symbolic end to an age of expansion.
In accordance with tradition,
the King would dedicate every ship,
but not this time.
This would be
the princess's first royal duty.
Her first official act.
The ship would be named Peacemaker
and bear her royal seal.
Make no mistake.
I was the loyal daughter
of my adopted father.
I could not betray him or defy him.
He had told me the princess must die.
And die she would.
[haunting choral music plays]
My father said he would not stand by
and watch this child
dismantle the war machine
we sacrificed so much for.
I had faith
that Balisarius would protect me
and the Empire he so loved.
[Guard of Honor] Attention!
[solemn adagio plays]
[King] Strange.
Something's wrong.
[door closes]
Balisarius.
Where is the Kali?
Why aren't the furnaces lit?
Balisarius, I am talking to you.
Answer me, man!
-Issa, run! Issa!
-[Issa gasps]
You bastard.
[tense music plays]
-No!
-[man grunts]
[King yells]
-[men shout]
-[guardian gun powers up]
-[dagger swishes]
-[King yells]
[plays tense notes]
-[King groans]
-[daggers swish]
[daggers swish]
[Balisarius] Do it.
What are you waiting for?
[breath trembles]
What are you waiting for, child? Do it!
[King whimpers]
-Do it.
-No.
-No, no.
-[Balisarius] Do it. Kill her.
[exhales heavily]
-Kill her!
-No!
[whimpers]
[music stops]
I forgive you.
Don't.
-[inhales]
-[guardian gun fires]
[divine resonance]
[gasps]
-[thud echoes]
-[coronet clatters]
-[pants]
-[King sobs]
[King groans loudly]
[dagger swishes]
-[Balisarius grunts]
-[dagger clatters]
[pants]
What have you done?
Seize her!
[Kora grunts]
There she is, gentlemen.
The assassin of the royal family.
An off-worlder.
[Kora cries out]
A cancer of ethnic impurities.
[shouts] Murderer.
-[senator] Murderer!
-[general] Murderer!
-Murderer!
-Killer!
-Traitor!
-[senator] Snake!
[man] Scum!
-[Kora grunts]
-[guardian gun fires]
[yells]
-[tense notes play]
-[breathing shakily]
[yells]
[Kora yells]
[breathes heavily]
[Kora] I fought my way to the shuttle.
And I've been living life
as an outlaw ever since.
I thought about letting them kill me
or just not fighting.
But somehow, the last words of the child…
Her forgiveness.
I felt the only way to honor her
was to run.
And try to be, I don't know…
more than a weapon.
More than a weapon.
It's what we're all trying to be.
It's what you are.
[Hagen] Good morning!
-[bell clangs]
-[Sam] Morning!
This is the wake-up call.
Wake up, everyone.
People, get up.
It's time to work.
Come on, you lazy people! Wake up!
-[groans]
-We don't have much time!
[Gunnar] Sorry, we're late.
Look who's here.
[Hagen] Gunnar.
Maybe you want to say a few words?
[Gunnar] Of course.
Sure. We have a few people here
who probably have never harvested grain…
Don't say anything.
-…made sheaves…
-I can't say good morning?
…worked a scythe.
But we will welcome them.
And through our work together,
win favor with the spirit of soil
and guarantee the future abundance
of these sacred fields.
You all know your jobs.
Don't be afraid to personally approach
our guests and put them to work.
Let's get started!
-[villager 1] Yeah!
-[villager 2] Yeah!
Here you go.
["From Far" plays]
[female singer] ♪ From far ♪
♪ I hear my homeland cry ♪
[female singer vocalizes]
♪ Under ever gloaming skies ♪
♪ Fire within fire ♪
♪ I follow your feet ♪
[female chorus vocalizes]
[blows air]
[wheat rustles]
[female chorus harmonizes]
[birds chitter]
[birds chirp]
[chorus] ♪ Far from far
Your wandering soul ♪
♪ Under stars I'll never hold ♪
♪ Must I let you go ♪
♪ Far from far
My heart, my home ♪
[percussive music plays]
[serene music plays]
[captivating music plays]
[spoon clanks]
[whispers] Hey.
Stop staring.
[chuckles]
[gulps]
[grunts]
[scoffs]
[King's Gaze engine thrums]
Commander, I have
the chief medical technician.
Put him through.
-[hologram buzzes]
-[Noble] Release me!
[chief technician]
You should come down here.
[Noble] This is treason.
I command this ship.
By the old gods, I'll have each
and every one of you court marshalled!
I swear it! Every one of you will die!
I need none of you!
[chief technician] Come down here now.
On my way.
[Noble] I'll murder
every one of you myself!
[chief technician]
Admiral, you're not ready for this.
[Noble] I am still commander of this ship!
Why do you stand there
staring at me? Cowards!
-This is treachery!
-Welcome back, sir.
Are you ready to resume your command?
Yes, of course I am.
Now tell these idiots to release me.
[chief technician]
Sir, as I've already told you,
there are protocols before you can
be cleared to resume command.
Tests that need to be conducted
to see if you are mentally and--
-[chief technician groans]
-[sinister music plays]
Let me help you with your evaluation.
[grunts loudly]
[chief technician] Lord Admiral, please!
Unhook him!
How far are we from Veldt?
A few days, sir.
The Kali is still recovering
from our jump to you.
Admiral, my apologies
for the scar that was left
by this incompetent medical team.
I'm sure it can be removed.
No.
No, leave it.
She gave it to me.
When I deliver her to Balisarius
and her body is displayed
in the rotunda of the Senate,
I shall bare my chest.
And it will stand as a symbol
that it is I who brought to justice
the Scargiver,
as it is I that stands before my people
as a savior.
[dramatic choral music plays]
[intriguing music plays]
[uraki bellows]
[female chorus harmonizes]
[children laugh]
[boy laughs]
[male voice vocalizes]
[water gurgles]
[female voice vocalizes]
[comms signal beeps]
How's the harvest been going?
Any protests from the villagers?
[Aris] No, sir.
All is to schedule.
I've not seen Faunus or Marcus
during your reports.
They've been busy
driving the villagers, sir.
Getting that extra bit of work
out of them.
Very well.
[Aris] I believe it was your phrase, sir,
"Every child screaming,
every mother crying."
[Cassius] That is one of mine.
Yet I cannot take authorship.
I believe it originates
with our Regent Balisarius himself,
during his time as a fighting man.
And it is my honor to quote him.
And now mine.
The work has continued around the clock.
We should have
all the grain milled into flour
just in time for your arrival.
Excellent, Private.
And if the villagers
have held up their end,
maybe some mercy's in order.
These dogs deserve nothing but our boot.
Is that right?
We'll see…
when the job is done.
For the slain King.
[Noble] Well, it's clear that what
the Hawkshaws are reporting is true.
That Marcus and Faunus
and the rest of their men are dead.
The Scargiver's among them.
And it seems our young private
has chosen a side.
What should we do, sir?
We wait for more information
from the Hawkshaws.
We let them think we know nothing.
Yes, sir.
[Gunnar] But here's the deal.
Once we finish the western fields,
we only need to mill the grain into flour.
[Tarak] Ten fields, we're halfway there.
[Gunnar] Well, yes, but--
[Tarak] Kind woman with silver hair…
-What was her name?
-[Kora] Hervor.
-Why?
-No reason.
-Listen.
-[Tarak] How many fields do we need…
-…to get done tomorrow night?
[conversation stops]
I've never been one
for making confessions.
[Gunnar] Mmm.
Now we know what each of us must do.
You're all here because I want you to know
who the hell you're fighting with.
Everyone must share the truth.
I'll go first.
Sarawu.
[somber music plays]
The Regent Balisarius had sent me
and my ship as a show of force
to hover above the parliament of Sarawu,
so the choice of whether or not to vote
for independence from the Realm
would be obvious.
But the brave people of that world
defiantly voted for freedom,
and in answer, I was ordered
to open fire on the capitol.
I refused, and my ship was shot down.
Crawling from the wreckage,
we fought the forces of the Motherworld
till our guns were dry.
I knew my men would fight with me
to the death.
So I struck a deal.
My men's lives
for the surrender of my own.
I begged for mercy from the Regent
to spare them.
But mercy is not known
to the Regent Balisarius.
To punish me, my men were executed
before my eyes.
[crackling]
[somber music continues]
[gun powers up]
[Titus yells]
The decision to defy Balisarius
had been mine alone.
Not a day passes that I don't think
of those men that died for me.
How my surrender betrayed their courage
and condemned them to their fate.
[somber music continues]
Never again.
I'll never surrender.
You should understand that today
before you choose to follow me tomorrow.
[somber music fades]
I've, uh, never fought in a battle
like the one that's coming.
But I was raised in a place
that was much like this.
My childhood made me understand that
the land is not the growing of the food
but the cultivation of the tribe itself.
When the ships appeared in the sky
above my world,
I looked to my tribal elders
for how we would respond.
They said, "What can we do
against the might of the Motherworld?"
They cowered
against the might of the Realm,
submitting and giving them everything
because they were too scared to fight.
Those who were too weak
or too old to work were killed.
The rest of us were scattered
to labor camps all over the universe.
Families torn apart.
It was as if my people never existed.
[ships approach]
[tense music plays]
[explosion]
[tense music continues]
[gunfire]
[music swells]
[Milius] My camp was liberated
by the Resistance.
And I found a new family
who showed me another way.
So when the time comes…
I'll give my life to protect this village
if need be.
To stand and die for a place to call home.
What more honorable end
could one ever hope for?
I had a life before.
[quavering] Long before…
[chuckles]
It seems.
[tense music plays]
We were a little fishing village.
The Imperium troops
slaughtered everything and everyone.
[melancholy music plays]
[lid thuds loudly]
We were a peaceful people.
But we hadn't always been.
Once, long ago…
we were a people of war.
I had never killed before,
never spilled blood,
until I spilled my own.
-My pain became rage.
-[gauntlet whirs]
[gauntlet clicks]
-And my rage became revenge.
-[gauntlet powers up]
But the bloodlust of my ancestors
still lived in those ancient gauntlets.
My blood awakened them.
They showed me how to fight.
And I was reborn.
But since that day,
I've been a creature of revenge.
And yes…
Yes, I will kill them.
None of us get to choose our parents.
And mine happened to be a king and queen.
My father, the King,
insisted on presenting our terms
to the armies of the Motherworld himself.
And their answer was to return his body
with the promise of invasion.
My mother told me then,
"A boy doesn't become a man
until his father dies."
"Then a prince becomes a king."
-[bennu screeches softly]
-That was the last time I cried.
Soon after,
their ships darkened our skies.
And my mother, for honor's sake,
she would not run.
[somber music plays]
[female singer vocalizes]
I wanted to stay to protect her,
but the Queen knew to preserve
the bloodline and the throne.
[distant explosions]
[somber music continues]
I lost my mother…
and my world that day.
I was smuggled off-planet,
hidden in a refugee transport
headed for a near bright star.
I ran for… for duty's sake,
for the preservation of a kingdom
and a bloodline that no longer exists.
I was robbed of my opportunity
to die defending them.
But no more.
When we finish here,
that is where I'll go.
Home.
To atone for my mistake
of misplaced honor.
[Titus] Kora.
We haven't heard from you.
What is your story?
I am a war orphan.
The discipline
of a military life suited me.
I served on a ship
very much like the King's Gaze.
Never having a family,
I believed I had found one.
That is until I arrived here on Veldt.
This place taught me what a home
and family could really be.
Anything else you'd like to add?
Hm?
No.
Sure?
How's the spring water?
[Tarak] What?
[Kora] For several days now,
Titus pretends to drink,
because he doesn't want us to know
how much he cares about the coming battle.
[cork opens]
[Kora scoffs]
It really is water.
[Milius chuckles]
Old stories can be hard to give up.
Yes, they can.
[Gunnar] Friends…
I can only say…
thank you for coming to this village,
and giving us hope.
Thank you.
Water.
Really, Titus?
And that's General Titus.
-Of course.
-To you.
-[punches]
-[Tarak groans, chuckles]
-[jolly folk music plays]
-[children giggle]
No, no, no.
Okay. Teach me.
Okay.
[Tarak laughs]
[uraki bellows]
[boy gasps, pants]
[children laugh]
[intriguing music plays]
[chuckles softly]
[spirited music plays]
[man grunts]
[Kora grunts]
[Gunnar] Sorry.
[both grunt]
["From Far" plays]
[they chatter]
-[festive folk music plays]
-[all cheer]
[Den] I've still got it.
This is how we party.
-Thank you. Thanks.
-Enjoy yourselves.
I'm gonna get a drink first.
I noticed you were good doing the harvest.
I come from a world
that was much like this.
What became of it?
The very thing we came to prevent.
[bell clangs]
Everyone, if I could just…
I wanted to welcome our new friends.
I want to give you
these small gifts I've made.
I know you all come from places
much richer and more sophisticated
than here,
so I hope my gifts don't insult you
with their simplicity.
But I've made them with gratitude.
When I first saw
you all ride into our village,
I felt like General Titus
was like the mountains themselves.
Strong and unmoving.
Thank you.
[Sam] Tarak.
Your spirit is untamable…
[chuckles]
…but your nobility is undeniable.
Like the snow elk.
Thank you. Thank you.
[Sam] Our own Den, who I include
because he is
as the land beneath our feet,
rising to defend us.
Young Milius…
who shines as the sun upon our faces,
warming us and bringing us comfort,
steadfast and true.
Thank you.
[Sam] Nemesis.
Fierce as a storm
with its flashes of lightning,
but with its life-giving rain.
That is the source of life.
The storm is the mother of us all.
Thank you.
[Sam] Gunnar.
You are our heart.
You give us hope.
[Gunnar chuckles]
It's beautiful. Thank you.
[Kora kisses]
Look at this.
And Kora.
You are our guardian wolf
with bared teeth.
You stand between us and annihilation.
The strength of all of us together.
[uplifting music plays]
[villagers applaud]
[upbeat folk music plays]
[villagers cheer]
[villager] Let's eat!
[villagers whistle]
[lively chatter]
[both laugh]
[upbeat folk music continues]
[all cheer]
You all right?
[both chuckle]
[Kora sniffles]
-Okay?
-Yes. Yeah.
Skoal.
[Kora exclaims]
[villagers whoop and cheer]
-Den, show us that move again!
-[Den] You ready?
-[Gunnar] That's it! [chuckles]
-[Den whoops]
[upbeat folk music continues]
[villagers clap]
[they chatter]
[chatter stops]
[breathes deeply]
[Titus sings in Fon] ♪ Maman tché… ♪
♪ Do atchê djitché ♪
♪ Wan gnigni toé ni wrlin mi gan ♪
♪ Dada sêgbo tché Lê ♪
[in distance]
♪ Wan gnigni toé ni wrlin mi ♪
♪ Do atchê djitché ♪
♪ Wan gnigni toé ni wrlin mi gan ♪
♪ Wan gnigni toé ni wrlin mi gan… ♪
[Sam chuckles]
-Where are we going?
-I promise it's safe.
[Aris chuckles]
-[Aris howls]
-[Sam chuckles]
This is…
What was your world like?
More moons.
I wish you could've seen it.
It was beautiful.
Is it not beautiful here?
Yeah.
It is.
[Sam sighs]
If we survive,
when all of this is over…
will you stay?
Here, with me?
[chuckles]
If you'll have me, I'll stay.
[sentimental music plays]
[Hawkshaw] Oh no. Disgusting.
They're pressing their mouths together.
[growls]
-Fucking hell.
-[scanner beeps]
Oy! Get ready to transmit.
One moment.
Now.
[transmitter beeps]
It's ready.
-[frequency tunes]
-[transmitter warbles]
Online.
Ah. Good.
[sighs]
[creatures chitter]
[bell tolls]
[Tarak chuckles]
-[bell tolls loudly]
-[grunts]
[villagers murmur]
[Titus] All right.
Today, we begin the preparation
for our defense.
We start by moving the grain
into the village,
so that they can't shoot us from orbit
without risking its destruction.
Gather and account
for every hunting rifle.
Every knife.
Every round of ammunition in the village.
[uplifting music plays]
We'll need to dig defensive positions
to give us the element of surprise.
All right.
Astrid. Let's see what you got.
[Astrid] Mmm-hmm.
Wait.
Tuck your elbow.
Keep both eyes open.
[gun powers up]
[Tarak] Okay. Today we're going to learn
the basics of attack and defense.
We have turned your harvesting tools
into weapons.
-So, what we're going to try and do is…
-[bolo blade slashes]
that.
Yeah.
[gun powers up]
[Gunnar chuckles]
[Titus] Like a professional.
[grunts]
[Tarak] Great.
-Really good.
-[grunts]
We've got a natural.
[blunderbuss powers up]
[explosion]
[blunderbuss powers down]
[villager] Here.
Go!
[Tarak] Coming down.
[pulley squeaks]
[birds twitter]
[grunts softly]
-[switch clicks]
-[system powers up]
[system trills and beeps]
-How'd you fix it?
-[Aris] Wasn't me.
[dropship engine starts]
Remember that Jimmy we brought?
It was him.
[Kora] All right.
Hold on.
[thrusters blast]
[dropship engine roars]
[urakis bellow]
[dropship warbles overhead]
[wind gusts]
[dropship powers down, engine stops]
[FLIR trills]
They have a dropship.
Oy! Prepare to transmit.
Right. Come on.
[ominous music plays]
[officer] Commander Cassius,
as we're coming around
the outer moons of the Mara system,
we're receiving an unscheduled
transmission from our Hawkshaws on Veldt.
[frequency tunes]
Transmitting.
[Cassius] What is so urgent
that it couldn't wait
till your normal report?
We're coming around Mara now.
We should be in low orbit
in less than a day.
Sir, the village has an asset.
We just discovered--
[Hawkshaw 1 screams]
What the fuck are you doing?
We're on the same side.
-[Hawkshaw 2 grunts, yells]
-[bone cracks]
[screams]
[hologram glitches]
-What happened to the signal?
-It just went dead.
[switch clicks]
[dropship rumbles]
[dropship engine stops]
[system powers down]
[machinery beeps, powers down]
[suspenseful music builds]
[gasps, exhales]
Hello, James.
[Jimmy] You know, the last person
who called me that
was the old commander
of the Mechanicas Militarium
as he died in my arms.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's all right. I like the way it sounds.
It makes me feel
something other than hopelessness.
You see…
I was given memories of a world
I will never see,
loyalty to a king I cannot serve
and love for a child I could not save.
But the sound of that name as you say it
lets me feel, even in the smallest way…
why I exist at all.
Is that why you saved Sam?
I'm not certain.
I know only that the thought of her
being hurt or destroyed
opened a part of me that had been closed.
[ethereal music plays]
You're choosing a side, James.
You and I are alike,
designed to kill for them.
Understand, their nightmare
is you and I fighting together.
Not because we are ordered or commanded,
but to defend something we love.
Let me show you something.
-How long?
-Yesterday.
This is the transmitter they were using.
I'm certain they were
in communication with the King's Gaze.
By now, they know everything.
You must know you cannot win.
Probably, right?
At least I'll die on the side of honor.
Is there still such a thing?
What do you feel, James?
[sighs]
How much do we think they know?
[Titus growls]
We would have to assume
they know everything.
Then it won't be enough
to fight defensively.
-We have to bring the fight to them.
-[Gunnar] Mm-hm.
How well do you know the Dreadnought?
What are you thinking?
[Aris] We've got
a ton of munitions for these.
And this. We found a rocket launcher.
Armor-piercing high-explosive detonators.
[explosive clicks]
-We've got some comms.
-[Kora] Good.
And the uniforms of the dead soldiers?
[Gunnar] Here.
The blood won't come out easy,
but we can try.
[Kora] No. We can use it. Leave it.
Do you have more?
[Gunnar] Sure.
[explosive clicks, beeps]
[breathes heavily]
[explosive trills, beeps]
[exhales nervously]
All set. [grunts]
[King's Gaze rumbles overhead]
[dramatic music plays]
Dreadnought.
Finish it! Finish up! Finish up! Come on!
Quick, quick, quick!
Finish your work! Find your positions!
Cover it up!
[villagers grunt]
[bell tolls]
[Cassius] These are the new formations.
It's the grain.
Look, they piled it against a building
so we can't destroy them.
And there and there, they've stacked it
as cover to shoot from.
[Cassius] Clever.
[Noble] Hmm.
Certainly not the plans of a farmer.
It seems General Titus hasn't
drunk away his wits just yet.
Look here.
Thermal imaging shows clusters of people
in the Longhouse
at the top of the village.
No doubt they're women and children.
Hmm. Good. We'll do our best to forestall
a pitched battle in the village.
While I negotiate,
we'll dispatch the Krypteia.
Hmm. We'll capture the women and children.
Then we'll see
how motivated they are to fight.
[tense music builds]
[foreboding music plays]
[water bubbles]
[haunting choral music plays]
[scissor snips]
[ominous music plays]
[Mech carrier engines blast]
[dropship engines sputter]
[fighter ship engines rumble]
[Den] Everybody inside now!
-Let's go. Come on.
-[villager] Come on, everybody. Faster.
Get inside. Let's go. Move, move!
[King's Gaze engine hums overhead]
[sinister music plays]
[dropship engines rumble]
[dropships power down]
[dramatic choral music plays]
-[wind gusts]
-[dropship engine rumbles]
[boarding ramp whirs, thuds]
[Noble] No village welcome, no?
Where's my warm embrace? [scoffs]
I was never given that cup of ale,
you know.
Arthelais.
Tell me what we're trying to achieve here.
The same thing as the last time we met.
I kill you.
Yes.
What an honor it was.
A scar. From the Scargiver herself.
[Kora] No blood
need be spilled here today.
I will offer you one chance
to avoid slaughter.
You do understand
what the Regent Balisarius will give me
when I bring you to your knees before him?
A seat in the Senate is what you seek,
I would imagine.
It's what I deserve.
If so, take the grain you need
to feed your men
on your voyage back to the Motherworld.
No more and no less.
You leave the villagers unharmed.
Report to Balisarius that the warriors
you sought evaded capture.
And I should take nothing, yes?
Nothing at all?
You take your lives.
This is your choice.
Disgrace and relegation,
or your head cleaved from your shoulders.
Your ship serving as your tomb.
Your families
and all of the Motherworld to know
that you were slaughtered
by the peasants of Veldt.
I've been tasked
with bringing honor to the Motherworld.
I intend to see
that task through to its end.
What amuses me most about all of this?
You think you have any power
with which to negotiate? You do not.
You think I don't know
you're hiding your women and children?
As you stand there talking to me,
your plan is already failing.
Well, unless of course a different
arrangement could be made, perhaps.
I could take the grain you offered.
I could do as you asked
and leave the villagers their lives.
There would be one cost
to this concession, however.
And that cost is you.
Of course every member of your band would
be greatly treasured by the Imperium,
but there is no denying
the one most sought after
by the Honorable Regent is you.
Arthelais herself.
[exclaims, inhales deeply]
So herein lies your choice.
Arthelais, surrender to me.
And I'll permit the villagers to live.
However, if you refuse,
those this village holds most dear,
the elderly, the children,
currently sheltered up in that Longhouse,
will be slaughtered by my men
on their way now.
Has enough blood not been spilt
in that beautiful building already?
Are you truly prepared to allow
this to continue in your name?
It's time, Arthelais.
What?
Kora.
Kora, what are you doing?
[Noble] I thought so.
Why don't you say goodbye to your friend?
Your father awaits you.
[Gunnar] Kora, look at me.
Huh?
-[Kora sniffles]
-What's happening, huh?
[Kora, softly] I'm sorry.
I won't allow this place to die for me.
I know what I'm doing.
He's lying to you.
-Just let me go. Just let me go!
-[Gunnar] No!
[tense music plays]
[guardian gun powers up]
No. No.
No!
[bell tolls]
[gasps]
-[soldiers shout]
-[soldier 1] Huh?
[Noble gasps]
-No. No!
-Come on.
[Javelin powers up]
[rousing choral anthem plays]
[explosion pulses]
[soldiers scream]
[explosion continues]
[man grunts]
[Gunnar] Move! Move!
-[dramatic music plays]
-[Noble groans]
[villagers clamor]
[Gunnar grunts]
[distant explosions]
[gasps]
[soldier grunts]
[soldier screams]
[Gunnar] Come on, Kora!
We need to get you up to that ship.
-[grunts]
-[uraki bellows]
Come on.
Why did you stop me?
He'd have said anything
to have you surrender without a fight,
but his words are worthless.
We won't let you
sacrifice yourself to a lie.
Now, come on!
[both grunt]
Let's go.
[uraki bellows]
Get up. Go!
[distant explosions]
[tense music builds]
-[sinister music plays]
-[growls]
-[Noble yells]
-[neck snaps]
[Noble grunts]
[blade slices]
[villager grunts]
-[woman whimpers]
-[Noble grunts]
-[soldier 1] Get up, soldier!
-[soldier 2] I can't.
[soldier 1] Let's go!
-[soldiers whimper]
-[gun powers up]
[soldier 1] Right to the front!
[officer]
AA-77, get out of there immediately.
Lift off. We need lift off now!
[thrusters blast]
[grunts]
Bring around the main gun.
[Den yells]
-[alarm blares]
-[explosive beeps]
Oh, damn.
[debris clatters]
[distant explosions]
-Go!
-Come on!
[gunfire]
[Oracle steel blade hisses]
[battle rifle powers up]
[Krypteian guard groans]
[shouts] Hold!
[Krypteian sword slashes]
Eyes to the right!
[gunfire]
-[villagers scream]
-[gun powers up]
[Aris groans]
[villagers grunt]
[villager 1] Over there! Go! Go!
[villager 2 groans]
-[Javelin clicks]
-You're set! Go!
[yells, groans]
-[gun fires]
-[villager 3 groans]
[yells]
[soldier grunts]
-Let's go!
-[Den yells]
[Noble groans]
-[Noble growls]
-[Den strains]
[dropship engine rumbles]
-[Noble grunts]
[rousing choral anthem plays]
[tense music plays]
[system powers up]
[engine starts]
[thrusters blast]
[both grunt]
[groans]
[Seax Bowie blade slices]
[dramatic choral music plays]
[thrusters blast]
[tense music plays]
Hold on.
[dropship engine revs]
Here!
We'll drop into formation.
When I give the signal, start the smoke.
[Gunnar] Holy shit.
Kora, are you sure?
Now. Start it now.
[hatch door opens]
[alarm blares]
[breathes heavily]
[dropship engine roars]
[alarm continues blaring]
[dropship engine warbles]
-[alarm continues blaring]
-[sighs heavily]
-[switch clicks]
-[system buzzes, trills]
[exhales]
[Kora over comms] Docking.
That ship has taken damage.
[Kora over comms] I have casualties.
My instruments are not responding.
[alarm continues blaring]
[over comms] I'm surrendering control.
[officer] We've got you, soldier.
I'm gonna put you down
into the main hangar
[over comms] for maintenance
and medical extraction.
[system trills, beeps]
[system beeps]
[dropship engine sputters]
I have the blood here in a skin.
We should dress in it. Right?
[Kora] Ready?
[Gunnar] All right, the helmets.
[energy field warbles]
[wind howls]
The time has come for all that you love.
For your home.
Protect each other and show them no mercy.
For Sindri!
[all shout]
We can't let Titus
and the others do all the work.
Are you ready?
To fight and die!
[all shout]
Let's leave the dying to your enemies!
[Oracle steel blade swishes]
[blades collide]
-[ancestral energy crackles]
-[Nemesis grunts]
-[Krypteia soldier yells]
-[Sam gasps]
[Aris grunts]
[Sam chokes]
[Aris yells]
Stop! [screams] Stop!
[Aris pants]
[Sam] I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.
Stop. Just stop. I'm here.
[Aris breathing heavily]
[sizzles]
[Nemesis grunts]
Prepare the second wave.
Yes, sir.
You heard the Admiral.
Have the second wave sent to the ships.
Yes, sir.
The hell are you doing?
[shouts] Get away from me!
[sinister music plays]
[door slides open]
[tense music plays]
[grunts]
[screams]
[Titus grunts]
[grunts and coughs]
-[yells]
-[somber music plays]
[wheezes]
[explosive beeps]
[beeping continues]
[somber music continues]
[breathes heavily]
[explosive beeping rapidly]
-[soldiers panic]
-[explosive clicks, beeps]
[all scream]
[wind gusts]
[medic 1] One down in the hold!
-Can you hear me?
-Hey. Are you all right?
I'm going to attempt to move you now.
I got you. It's going to be all right.
[medic 1] All right.
-[medic 2] It's all right.
-[medic 1] Two down, non-responsive!
Bring the gurneys!
Load 'em up. All right, come on, take him.
Take the shoulder.
All right, I got the legs.
Pick the arm up. Here we go.
All right, let's go.
All right, calling it in.
Some shrapnel damage, infantry seems
to be suffering from a small ammo wound.
Two minutes out.
Visual inspection on the elevator.
Let's go.
[elevator starts]
[Nemesis yells]
-[Krypteia officer grunts]
-[Nemesis groans]
No.
[boy yells]
[Krypteia officer screams in pain]
-[Krypteia officer grunts]
-[boy struggles]
[Krypteia officer sputters]
[distant explosions]
[breathes weakly]
[mournful music plays]
[chuckles softly]
[boy cries]
[boy sobs]
It's okay.
You did good.
[sniffles]
[mournful music continues]
[Aris pants]
[soldiers grunt]
[suspenseful music plays]
[yelling echoes]
[guns fire in slow motion]
[solemn choral music plays]
[solemn choral music continues]
[breathes heavily]
[dramatic music builds]
[yells]
-[all yell]
-[triumphant music plays]
[villagers cheer]
[heavy footsteps approach]
[Imperium Mech blares]
[mechanical warbling]
[distorted blaring from Imperium Mech]
[foreboding music plays]
[turret powers up]
Yeah?
Help me with his helmet. Support the neck.
Strange. I'm not seeing any wounds.
How about that one? Stable?
Pulse is elevated.
Don't see wounds either,
but there's a little blood.
Maybe under his armor.
[medic 1] Get the balaclava off.
There's a wound.
Checking the pulse.
This one's pulse is very low.
-[tense music builds]
-Wait. That's…
Give me the charges.
-[Gunnar] Charges.
-Wait.
[announcement over speakers]
Make your way back to our ship
and have it running.
We won't have long
to get off this thing before it blows.
Okay.
I'll be waiting for you.
-Should be an elevator down this hall.
-I got it. Be quick.
[Imperium guard over intercom]
All personnel, stay alert.
[Imperium Mech blares]
[footsteps march]
[buttons beep]
[door hisses]
-[Neurolink hums]
-[mystical music plays]
[pants]
[automated voice]
Copy. Targeting the safe--
-[metal clanks]
-[turret whirs]
[powers up]
[rapid gunfire]
[yells]
[dramatic music plays]
[grunts]
[exhales]
[explosive clicks, beeps]
[distant explosions]
-[gunfire]
-[soldier groans]
-[Imperium Mech creaks]
-[turrets whir]
[Imperium Mech creaks]
[Imperium Mech blares]
[man groans, screams]
[soldier groans, screams]
[turret whirs, thuds]
-[Javelin powers up]
-[grunts]
[suspenseful music plays]
[haunting choral music plays]
-[energy powers up]
-[Kali screams]
[haunting choral music continues]
It's all right, Kora.
I know you don't want to kill me.
But I also know it's the only way.
So, like Issa… I, too, forgive you.
Because one day you will wake my sisters,
and their wrath will be my vengeance.
[electricity crackles]
[guardian gun powers up]
[Imperial officer screams]
[Imperial soldier grunts]
Intruder alert. Repeat. Intruder alert.
Sending backup. What is the nature
and number of the intruders?
[officer] It is a woman. Just one woman.
[officer] Shots fired.
There are men down.
It's a woman, I'm telling you--
[line disconnects]
A what? What's going on?
There is a situation in the engine room.
He said a woman has infiltrated the ship.
[gasps]
[Noble] Arthelais.
Arthelais is aboard this ship.
That is impossible.
[Noble] No, it's her.
She's come to us.
It's perfect.
Alert all sectors.
I want her captured at once.
And Cassius?
You may fire on the village.
Sir, the grain.
There's no need for the grain now.
The Scargiver has come to us.
Plus, I'd rather our men starve
than risk exposing ourselves
to more of Titus' dirty tricks.
But we have men on the ground.
Yes. A few less mouths to feed.
Now hold the second wave
and fire on that fucking village.
You heard me.
Destroy it.
You heard the Admiral. Charge the cannons.
Main gun.
Charge the cannons.
You will be weapons free once we notify
the second wave to stand down.
Yes, sir.
[sinister music plays]
[announcement over speakers]
[gate buzzes]
[officer over speakers] Red alert!
Secure the engine room.
-[gate buzzes]
-Red alert! Secure this area immediately.
[general 1] You'll never guess
what I just heard.
The second wave
has been ordered to stand down.
The Admiral has decided
to vaporize the village
with our big guns here on the King's Gaze.
[general 2] Guess the rumors of
taking the fugitives alive were just that.
[general 1] Typical.
Move out!
[pants]
[footsteps march]
[officer] Secure the area immediately.
[alarm blares]
[door slides]
[soldier] Waiting for contact!
Move!
[guard over comms] She's on level three.
-We need to move!
-[Kora grunts]
[soldier screams]
[comms buzz]
[Gunnar] Kora. Noble is turning the guns
toward the surface.
He doesn't give a shit about the grain.
He wants the village destroyed.
[Kora] But the charges are set
and counting down.
-There won't be enough time.
-To do what?
-Just get to the ship.
-All right.
[officer over speakers] Initiate lockdown,
seal all access ports…
[soldier 1] Sir.
Lieutenant. Sir.
[alarm blares]
[explosion]
-[soldier 1] Forward! Forward!
-[soldier 2] Let's go!
-[yells]
-[soldier 1 groans]
[grunts, shouts]
[Milius] No!
-Come on. I'm going!
-No.
No, you can't help them.
You cover me with this
or you cover me with dirt.
The choice is yours, General.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Are you hit? Are you okay? Come on.
[both panting]
[ominous music plays]
I thought dying in battle
was all I wanted.
Fighting for something.
I think I was wrong.
I don't think I want to die at all.
But if I must… [sniffles]
Come on.
[Imperium Mech blares]
[wind howls]
[solemn operatic music plays]
[ethereal music plays]
[dramatic music plays]
[grenade clicks]
[beeping intensifies]
[grenade explodes]
[grunts]
-[tense music plays]
-[alarm blares]
[over speakers] All commanders
report their headcounts to Command.
Initiate lockdown. Seal all…
[elevator powers up]
[officer over comms] Gunnery Commander,
you're weapons free to target the village.
[commander] Right away, sir.
The gun is charged and ready to fire.
-[button beeps]
-[system clicks]
[rousing choral anthem plays]
[handwheel cranks]
[scanner beeps]
[cannons thud]
Target acquired.
We have a lock on the village.
Confirmed.
Fire at will.
[gun powers up]
Go, take the shot!
Fire! Fire now!
[Sword of the King cannons thud]
Please! I have a family!
[explosion booms]
Damage report?
It missed, sir.
It missed?
The gun tilted off target
seconds before it had fired, sir.
[tense music plays]
[powers up]
[Cassius] What is he doing?
[officer] Main gun, what is your
current status? Return to target.
Tell me, what's going on?
Sword of the King,
what is your current status?
[over comms] Sword of the King?
[Sword of the King cannons whir]
Sword of the King,
why are you raising elevation off target?
[Sword of the King cannons thud]
-[officer 1] Sword of the King?
-[officer 2] Communication's down.
Tell me, what the hell is going on?
[officer 2] Sword of the King,
please respond.
What is your status?
They're not answering.
[Sword of the King cannons whir]
Sword of the King?!
Wait! Admiral.
No. Admiral!
[strains] No! Sir!
[Cassius grunts]
Sir!
[shouts] No!
-[exhales]
-[elevator starts]
[music builds]
-[lever clicks]
-[plasma fires]
It's Kora!
[alarm blares]
[gun powers up]
[dramatic choral music plays]
[ship engine sputters, revs]
Kora. Kora, where are you?
[over comms] The engine's running.
I'm waiting for you.
We're running out of time.
I'm almost to you.
Okay, good.
[guard over speakers] Stay alert.
We have a fugitive aboard the ship.
[breathes heavily]
[elevator stops]
[elevator alarm blares]
[soldiers grunt]
[dramatic music plays]
[Kora yells]
-[yelps]
-[Krypteian sword buzzes]
[suspenseful music plays]
[alarm blares]
[guard over speakers] Battle groups
aboard six, open the hangar.
[alarm blares]
Arthelais.
I suppose I should say thanks
for not accepting my offer of surrender.
It'll make a better ballad
when I slay you in battle.
You've done well to get this far.
[scoffs]
Much better than I expected.
Much better than could be expected
from a bunch of fucking farmers.
But you must know
this ship can operate without a bridge.
Hmm?
Yeah, I do.
But can it operate without its engine?
Hmm?
Sir!
What?
[explosives beep]
Oh, no.
[beeping stops, buzzes]
[explosion pulses]
[dramatic music plays]
-[explosions]
-[metallic groaning]
[Krypteian blade buzzes]
Take her.
[body thuds]
[groans]
No! No!
[grunts]
[both grunt]
[both strain]
[yelling]
[Noble shouts]
[shrieks]
[grunts and growls]
[Kora yells]
[blade trills]
[Kora yelps]
Kora! Kora!
[Noble shouts]
[Kora screams, grunts]
[both grunt]
[Kora shouts]
[Kora grunts]
[Noble chuckles] Come here!
-[Kora yelps]
-[Noble grunts]
[Kora grunts]
Open your eyes. Open your eyes!
Look at me!
[cries out]
[chokes]
-[Krypteian blade trills]
-[Noble garbles]
[Noble gasps]
[grunts]
[gasps for air]
-[Kora shouts]
-[Noble grunts]
[grunts, struggles]
[door buzzes]
[Noble groans in pain]
[head clatters]
[breathes heavily]
-[Kora] Come on!
-[both grunt]
[explosion]
[dropship thrusters blast]
[strains]
Come on.
[explosions]
[dropship engine sputters]
-[crashes]
-[alarm beeps]
[Kora yelps]
[grunts, pants]
-[Gunnar groans in pain]
-[Kora] Hey. Hey.
Hey, hey. Hey. Come here, come here.
Come here.
[both grunt]
[Gunnar groans]
Wait. Okay.
Hey. Stay with me.
Stay with me. Stay with me. Stay with me.
[tearfully]
Why can't I have this one thing?
[sobs]
-Stay with me. Please.
-No. It's okay.
Look at what you've done.
You saved us.
All of us.
Hey.
[Kora sobs]
I love you.
Please.
I know what you are.
And I love you.
Please.
[squadron passes overhead]
[dramatic music plays]
Look!
Form up on me!
Yes, Commander. On you.
Target those dropships!
[Devra] Black Mountain Squadron,
take those fighters.
[villagers cheer]
[ship engine whines]
[yells]
[villagers cheer]
[both shout excitedly]
Titus! Yes!
[yells]
Yes!
[Kora] Look, it's Devra Bloodaxe,
and the entire rebel fleet.
It's really over. It's…
No. [sobs]
No.
[wails]
[mournful music plays]
I love you.
[sobs]
[Hagen] From other worlds
they came to fight for us.
[mournful music continues]
To die for us.
May they find their peace.
We honor them now in the only way we can.
By remembering their names…
when next we bring in the harvest.
A season from now, a hundred seasons.
And by carrying on.
By carrying on.
[mournful music continues]
All of you, honor the fallen.
You honor my brother and his bravery.
Do not speak of me
when you speak of honor and bravery.
I've lied to you.
To all of you.
Titus.
I know, child.
I know.
You know that I'm Arthelais?
Adopted daughter of the Regent Balisarius?
And the assassin of the Princess Issa?
I know your name. Yes.
But you were not her assassin…
for the princess is still alive.
You thought she could be killed so easily?
No. She's more than death.
What am I to do?
You have a reason now, do you not?
To find her and to fight?
If you do choose to fight,
I will stand with you.
All of us.
And I as well.
[uplifting music plays]
[Kora cries]
[Jimmy] If I could be of use…
I, too, have this.
You wish to fight with us, robot?
Help find this lost princess?
If what you say is true,
and the princess lives,
I have no choice.
I serve the line of the slain King.
It is my honor to fight.
To find her and to fight.
[uplifting music continues]
[girl singing] ♪ From far ♪
♪ My homeland calls to me ♪
♪ Over the rolling fields ♪
♪ My heart is taken out of me ♪
♪ Far within far ♪
♪ I follow your feet ♪
♪ My end will I meet ♪
♪ Far from far, your wandering soul ♪
♪ Under stars I'll never hold ♪
♪ Must I let you go? ♪
♪ Far from far, my heart, my home ♪
♪ Far from far, my heart, my… ♪
♪ Home ♪
[melancholy music plays]
[ominous chants]
[sinister music plays]
[guard] Sire, we've discovered--
[Balisarius] Shh! One moment.
I do love this part.
Come, you can tell me as we walk.
You've brought word
from Admiral Noble, I assume.
When can we expect his return?
Yes. Well, we felt you should know
as soon as we could confirm that
we have no contact with the Admiral
and fear the King's Gaze is lost.
Lost?
Destroyed, sire.
We were able to confirm that the ship
disintegrated upon impact with Veldt.
As far as we can surmise,
there may be no survivors.
Survivors?
No.
No, there will be no survivors.
She would have seen to that.
She, sire?
[foreboding music plays]
[menacing music plays]
[somber music plays]
[haunting ethereal music plays]
[menacing music plays]
[suspenseful music plays]
[mournful music plays]
[threatening music plays]
[solemn choral music plays]
[somber choral music plays]
[ethereal choral music plays]