Sung-jin, it's me.
Did I surprise you?
I wanted to tell you in person.
But I was afraid
I'd change my mind if I saw you.
I'm leaving now.
For Berlin.
I don’t know…
My relationship with you...
I'm not sure about it anymore.
I don’t understand you.
So I'm really angry, and…
I keep doubting everything,
and it worries me.
And it hurts.
It hurts so much.
I don’t think I’m ready
for marriage right now.
So, it's better not to do it.
I’m just weird.
It‘s not your fault.
It's mine.
That’s why I have to leave.
But having you by my side all this time…
It made me truly happy.
So, you should be happy too.
Goodbye.
Sung-jin, watch this video.
HIDDEN FACE
Let's begin at measure 104,
second beat of the first movement.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Conductor.
Yes, Manager.
Wow, look at your face.
You look terrible.
Me?
Anyway, I need to discuss
something with you.
It's about the cellist.
We can’t keep rehearsing
with an empty seat, can we?
The balance is off.
It doesn’t sound right at all.
But everyone’s just exchanging glances,
pretending not to notice.
Yes, I know we have to
wait for Su-yeon to return.
But people are starting to talk.
I thought I should at least let you know.
Yes. I’ll take care of it
as soon as possible.
You understand, right?
This is Geisha coffee.
Give it a try.
Okay.
It’s already been twelve days, hasn’t it?
Yes, almost.
I’m sure she didn’t go to Berlin.
Yes, her cello is still there
and she barely took any clothes.
Don't worry too much.
She‘ll be back soon enough.
She was talking nonsense.
Like an idiot.
Does she think she can do anything
just because she’s the director’s daughter?
I‘m sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
She‘s probably enjoying room
service at a hotel right now.
It's my fault—
I didn't raise her properly.
I had her when I was immature,
and I spoiled her,
now look at her.
Or maybe I raised her well after all…
but in the end,
she turned out just like me.
Either way, it‘s my fault.
It‘s all on me.
By the way,
a cellist is coming for an audition today.
She‘s probably waiting in your office now.
A cellist?
Yes,
seems like, she contacted
one of her juniors
to fill in for her.
She does have a sense of
responsibility, after all.
But... shouldn‘t we wait a few more days?
Is that so?
Yes. If she suddenly comes back...
...and finds someone else in her place,
she’ll be really disappointed.
Honey,
I heard you told the manager
that we can’t wait any longer.
That we need a replacement.
You said the orchestra was out of sync.
I think you’re right.
After all, you’re the conductor.
But you should have told me yourself,
not let me hear it from someone else.
But, Director..
- That is...
- Go do the audition.
your profile?
Yes.
I heard you‘re Su-yeon‘s junior,
but you didn’t go to
a single school together.
We had the same teacher,
Professor Park Hyun-seong.
And when I was preparing
for my entrance exam,
Su-yeon was a teaching
assistant at the school.
She said there’d be an opening here
and suggested I apply.
Did she tell you anything else?
The call was out of the blue,
so I was a bit confused.
Am I in the wrong place?
No, that's not it.
Let‘s hear you play.
Actually, my instrument's
having some issues today.
If it's okay, could you listen
to a recording first?
Sure.
Schubert’s "Arpeggione Sonata"
Are you applying just for fun?
What do you mean by that?
Well,
how can you apply with such a common piece?
I like Schubert the most.
Because his music is the saddest.
The music is so sad that,
when I listen to it,
I don’t even feel sad anymore.
That's why I love him the most.
I'll leave my profile here.
Please throw it in the trash for me.
I‘ll leave the USB too.
You can wipe it and
use it for something else.
Or just throw it away.
Anyway, it was nice meeting you, Conductor.
I like Schubert the most.
Because his music is the saddest.
What brings you here?
I saw your profile.
I didn’t catch you at a bad time,
did I?
Well.
I was too rude earlier today.
I was upset about something else,
and I think I took it out on you.
I came here to apologize.
I‘m sorry.
Yes.
I understand.
And your performance,
I really liked it too.
Please join our orchestra.
Really?
Well,
for me,
this is definitely great news.
Oh, it’s Schubert.
Yes, that's right.
It's Schubert.
It’s the piece we’re performing.
I think that’s it.
Please practice and come over.
Ah, actually,
Schubert is my favorite too.
And the reason…
It’s the same as yours.
Ah, well...
For now
Her instrument is too cheap.
You can hear it right away.
It doesn't blend at all.
Right, Director?
Well, she’s practiced quite a bit,
but she’s still pretty unpolished.
We really needed Su-yeon
for this practice.
See?
We should’ve waited for Su-yeon.
What do you think of her
performance today?
Well, it’s just her first time.
We need to watch her play more.
But still...
there should be some
kind of intuition, right?
Or perhaps, a feeling?
You could say she’s the
hardworking type.
Given her practice time, her performance
exceeded my expectations.
Well, her attitude is also very good.
Well then,
as a conductor,
if you have no complaints,
it’s all good.
But still,
I guess you’re satisfied with her
'only as a substitute,' right?
That's what you meant, right?
Isn‘t it?
Right?
The conductor himself said he's satisfied.
So why are you more concerned than him?
He literally said she's hardworking
and has a great attitude,
and he's satisfied! Didn't he?
Looks like she doesn’t even
need to come back.
That crazy bitch.
This happens a lot,
and after a few tries,
I can usually get it to work.
But this time,
it won’t start at all.
Okay.
This is Goyang City.
What?
Can’t you please come quickly?
Something wrong with your car?
It broke down.
Are you off work?
Yes.
The cello looks really small.
It seemed so big in the backseat of my car.
At least it fit.
I doubted it would fit.
When did you see it?
That day...
The day you came for the interview.
I happened to see it through the window.
Really?
It‘s a bit embarrassing.
Over there...
Shall we grab dinner?
Yeah, sounds good!
By the way, I like grilling meat too.
I never even touched the tongs before.
I have a bit of a complex.
A complex?
I‘m the son of a diner owner.
If I grill too well,
people will say, "No wonder
he's the son of a diner owner."
It's raining.
Oh no, we don't have an umbrella.
But it's nice that it's raining.
By the way,
I heard from other members that
something happened between you two.
Did you have a fight?
- Did she leave...
- Can we not talk about this?
I don‘t really want to discuss it.
Oh, right, I have a complex too.
What is it?
I‘m an orphan.
When I was in high school,
my parents had an accident.
A car accident.
They passed away together.
My mom and dad,
both of them.
So I have an orphan complex.
Cheers.
Thank you.
Go on.
It's cold.
Yes, take care.
Yeah.
Yeah, go on.
Go.
Should I sit in the back?
I'm smaller and slimmer, after all.
Ah, it's not needed.
Once the driver arrives,
we'll take you home first,
and take the cello down.
and then only it makes sense
for me to sit in the front, right?
You‘ve said that five times already.
Really?
Because it's raining,
the alcohol went down so smoothly.
Ah, I want to drink more.
They must have closed it by now, right?
Mi-joo.
Yes?
Shall we have one more drink?
From where?
Do you want to go to my place?
Actually, I don't know anything about wine.
This must be a good wine.
Honestly, I have no idea either.
You don‘t have to agree with me.
You sure know a lot about it.
I really don‘t. I just drink it like this.
And I...
People who go into detail
about wine or coffee...
I just can’t stand them.
What?
Like saying it smells like August earth...
Or that it has absorbed the sun of May...
Stuff like that,
ridiculous.
Then,
let’s toast as people who
don’t really understand it.
This house is really nice.
I‘m completely drunk.
I knew it, wine is poison for me.
I'm all dizzy, even after washing my face.
Drunk & Soaked in the rain...
It's a complete mess.
Don‘t do this.
Not in this room...
We can’t do this here.
This feels wrong.
How am I supposed to face her after this?
Wait a moment.
I did that because I like you.
Why did you take everything off?
Apparently, that’s civet cat poop.
They eat coffee beans and poop them out.
Cool, right?
Yeah.
It’s all about how you present it.
Even poop looks fancy when they
present it well and sell it for a fortune.
Well, it looks pretty fancy,
doesn’t it?
The actual content doesn’t really matter.
It’s all about how people see it.
Perception is everything.
That’s why people need to
present themselves well too.
People are all about how they
present themselves too, right?
By the way,
speaking of Su-yeon,
don’t you think she’s a bit strange?
I thought she was acting this way
because she‘s about to get married.
But this feels kinda strange.
Do you know what‘s the strangest thing?
She‘s not using my card.
Su-yeon is the kind of person
who would still use my card
even if I died the day before.
But she hasn‘t been using it at all.
That’s so strange.
What if that’s just her way of
showing how angry she really is?
I mean…
Maybe she just wants to make it
look like she disappeared completely.
That‘s what it seems like, right?
I‘m starting to worry about her.
She’s not usually this determined.
Yeah.
It rained a lot yesterday.
That wasn‘t my fault.
But everything else was.
Drinking too much,
going to your place…
Especially going into the bedroom.
To make sure I don’t mess up again…
I won’t reply to your messages anymore.
I hope you’ll understand me.
[Cello Kim Mi-joo]
Hello?
You think I’m crazy, don’t you?
I wasn‘t supposed to come here.
But I‘ve come here twice already.
You played the piano
and made me come here.
Twice already...
That, too, in her bedroom..
What‘s wrong?
Suddenly, only hot water
is coming out of the shower.
It‘s okay.
- Hot water? Why?
- It‘s really fine.
- It wasn’t hot at all.
- Are you alright?
You should go out.
[Three months ago]
What the heck? So annoying.
I was planning to hug you at the gate.
What’s more urgent than me?
I don‘t know.
Sung-jin, Mom said she couldn‘t come.
So she sent someone.
I‘ll ask him to come here.
We‘ve got way too much luggage.
It’s okay, no worries.
Sung-jin, let‘s grab a hot Americano.
I smelled it,
and now I want some too.
Do we have to?
Hey, it's me.
Please come to Gate 4.
Okay.
Wow!
I didn‘t expect you to come to the airport.
I was just bored,
so I came to give you the keys.
And also to welcome you?
Forget the welcome.
Didn‘t we agree to leave
the keys at the door?
Here you go.
About the renovation,
even though it‘s done,
- I‘m not sure if it suits your taste.
- Hey.
I kept watching everything on video
during the renovation
And you proceeded
only when I said 'Okay.'
So, of course, it should
suit my taste, right?
Why say unnecessary things?
Got it.
The thing that does not suit my taste is...
you showing up at the airport like this.
Don't you think this is a bit too much?
That’s right too.
I’m grateful, but being grateful
is still one thing...
What’s not right is just not right.
Got it?
Yes.
Let‘s go.
Do you like it?
Wow, this is so huge!
When I used to come here as a student,
I would always wonder why my
teacher lived in such a creepy house.
But as I got older,
I kept thinking about it again.
It looks nice now, since it's been
completely redone, right?
Do you like it?
Of course, I like it.
You can play music as loud as you want,
and there's also this beautiful garden.
Living in a house like this
was my dream,
but I got it without even trying.
Why?
Don't you like it?
I said I like it,
but it's a bit overwhelming...
Do I even deserve to live here?
You have to get used to it.
What?
To everything.
Everything you've never
experienced before, Sung-jin.
Do you know why?
Because you, Sung-jin...
You're a maestro.
Maestro
For a maestro,
everything is a given.
For my mom, getting us a house
like this isn’t even a big deal.
Don‘t feel burdened.
It’s not a burden, but…
I’m just not used to it.
Everything comes naturally
for you, Sung-jin.
Got it, my Maestro?
There's a place I visited recently…
Did you like it?
Yeah, the place was great. The back is
all jungle, and the front is the ocean.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Amazing!
A jungle at the back,
and the ocean in the front?
Sung-jin, look at this!
Isn't it amazing?
Don't look at her bikini.
Ah, that...
Wow, this is insane!
30 million won for 5 nights
is a bit expensive...
But it's worth it.
Good, right?
You're having the ceremony
right after the performance, right?
Yes.
But since it’s peak season then, the
price will probably go up a little more.
Well, it doesn’t matter.
Oh wow, look at you!
Darling.
I can smoke here, right?
Yes, of course.
But why wash the dishes?
There aren't enough cups.
It really suits you.
By the way, did your mom say
anything after meeting?
Well, she really liked you.
She said you were very elegant.
and she's very happy that
I'm marrying into a good family.
But,
after the family meeting,
I started seeing you
in a new light.
You really are a remarkable person.
You have incredible willpower
and a strong sense of self.
I could sense just how much effort
you put into your image.
Why all of a sudden...?
It’s nothing, just how I felt.
Wow, as they used to say
in the old days,
you're really a self-made man.
I've come to like you even more.
I was really worried about
the housewarming party.
But in the end, it was both
fulfilling and grand.
Right?
How about that place we saw earlier?
That place?
The resort we saw in the pictures.
I really liked it.
Didn't we agree that you'd
handle those things yourself?
Darling, You don’t seem
to be in a good mood.
By any chance,
Is it because of what they said earlier?
What did they say?
They said it was unexpected
when I told them I seduced you.
Like they couldn’t even imagine
it happening the other way around.
That never crossed my mind.
Is that so?
Okay.
Then, that resort it is, right?
Five nights, 30 million won?
You think that’s expensive?
Why stress?
Mom’s paying anyway.
Also, darling,
I absolutely hate that attitude.
The one where you talk like
you're mocking me.
I like everything the best,
which is the most luxurious and cozy.
But when you criticize and
mock me for things like that,
that's what I hate the most.
Let's fix that, okay?
Okay.
Got it.
You go ahead and sleep.
Kiss me before you go.
Yeah
How was it?
What?
I'm getting better, right?
I feel like you're much more
at ease now than before.
If you're going to compliment me,
do it properly, director.
Let‘s skip that.
Now, look at this.
Performance Plan
The planning
department gave it to me.
We need to make
a decision together.
They insist on opening
with "Unfinished Symphony."
So, let's go with that.
After that, it should be more lyrical.
This was the performance program
arranged for the Vienna event.
I think it's quite good.
Of course, it was very successful.
This should go the same way,
even the opening piece.
- Of course!
By the way,
What were you talking about
with that violinist earlier?
The violinist?
Wasn't it In-jeong on stage earlier today?
It looked like you two were having
a really fun conversation.
Did we?
When she suddenly reached out her hand,
you gazed at it with such care.
She said she's worried
because her nails are weak.
And that they keep breaking.
What's the matter?
What do you mean?
Why do you seem different
since coming to Seoul?
What are you talking about?
You're kind to the violinist,
and to everyone else too.
But why are you so cold to me?
Everything I do, you either
mock it or just don’t care.
Why is that?
Should I say something too?
What is it?
Why are you making me feel
so embarrassed?
Who? Me?
Did the two of you really have to have
a private meeting in front of everyone?
Do you really have to let everyone
know the conductor is just a puppet?
No, that's not it.
Mom wanted to discuss it with me first
and then decide with you.
So that first discussion...
did it really have to be there
with all the members watching?
Is it really that
embarrassing to you?
Should I be proud to
be treated like a puppet?
You‘re wearing a bracelet today.
I was too much at the airport last time.
I want to apologize.
Well, that’s understandable.
By the way, why didn‘t you
come to the housewarming party?
You didn‘t invite me.
Oh, I must be crazy.
I thought I invited you.
That's exactly your style.
Ah, you’re always cool.
I really like it.
I‘m really going crazy because of Sung-jin.
He’s good-looking and
promising as a conductor,
Although his family is not well-off,
it doesn‘t matter.
But one thing bothers me.
What is it?
He doesn‘t seem to like me.
But you like him?
Are you out of your mind?
But not liking me is not acceptable.
Even if I don't like him,
he still has to like me.
That's only natural.
How is that natural?
It is.
So, are you giving me advice right now?
Mi-joo.
Do you remember the day I
kissed you for the first time?
When was it?
In the warehouse behind
the teacher‘s house.
Since that day,
I haven‘t liked anyone else but you.
You feel the same, right?
Even though I‘m betraying you now...
Yes, I'm betraying you.
But I will never betray our memories.
I hope you understand that.
I understand.
Okay.
Did you go to the warehouse
when you were fixing it?
Yes.
That means the key is with you.
So, you decorated it like this.
It looks really good.
What’s the point
if only the house is nice?
The relationship has to be too.
Come with me.
You brought the key, right?
Do we really have to go this far?
I’m really angry, that’s why.
I saved him.
I saved him
when he had no money or nothing.
He doesn’t even appreciate it and
dares to play hard to get with me.
I must have kept him in check
before marriage.
Just because I keep being kind to him,
he thinks it's right.
I hate that the most.
What, kindness?
Anyway...
I want to see what his
attitude is when I‘m not around.
Oh, this is surprisingly fun.
This is the place,
right?
What are you doing?
Come here.
Are you really going in?
Push it.
Open it.
Oh, it's so cold.
Wow, this place hasn't changed at all.
It reminds you of old times
when we were in here, right?
I'm a little scared here.
What's so scary, you dummy?
I'm here,
so what’s there to be scared of?
From now on,
If I signal like this with my chin,
you have to come in here and wait,
no matter what.
Got it?
Like a subordinate to you?
Like a subordinate...
and a slave.
You like me, don't you?
Yes.
Then you're my slave.
Understood?
Yes.
Then kiss me.
What do you mean by kissing you?
You said you like me, right?
Okay, close your eyes.
Okay.
I’m closing my eyes.
I don’t think...
I’m ready for marriage right now.
So, it's better not to do it.
It‘s not your fault.
It's mine.
That’s why...
I have to leave.
But having you by my side all this time…
It made me truly happy.
Goodbye.
It's so sad, right?
Yes.
Seriously,
He won't know what to do
after watching this video.
Because it's so sad.
Sung-jin, watch this video.
It's so sad.
Is this one a bit too much?
Well, it's very cold.
But,
Is it Schubert?
Yeah.
Oh, you have no idea
how stubborn he is.
He says Schubert's music is the saddest,
and that's why it's the best.
Right.
Gotta make it messy,
to make it feel like I left suddenly.
He says that it is so sad that
he doesn’t even feel sad anymore.
Did you pack everything?
Yeah.
Okay.
So heavy.
You should give me the key too.
How long are you going to stay there?
I don't know. Three days, tops.
Because there's practice,
might as well watch my diet.
I'm going in.
Put the bookshelf back properly.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
No service.
Sung-jin, it's me.
Did I surprise you?
I'm leaving now.
For Berlin.
I don't know...
- My relationship with you...
- Oh, so sad.
I'm not sure about it anymore.
I don’t understand you.
So I'm really angry, and…
I keep doubting everything,
and it worries me.
Please let me go.
It was my fault.
Please let me go home.
I'm begging you.
Ah... you look like you're
about to die from sadness.
Let’s see...
Sung-jin, I'm here.
Sung-jin, I'm right here.
Sung-jin.
I'm here! I said I'm here!
I'm locked in here!
Hey!
Sung-jin!
I'm locked in here.
Sung-jin.
I'm telling you,
I'm locked in here!
Sung-jin, Sung-jin!
Sung-jin! Sung-jin!
What the hell took you so long?!
I totally freaked out,
thinking I was trapped.
Are you doing well?
You...
How did you get in?
How did you get into our house?
I'm drunk.
It’s because Sung-jin kept making me drink.
I told him I can’t drink wine,
but he keeps making me!
I guess he just wants to fuck me.
Are you out of your mind?
I kind of changed the key.
Just to mess with you.
You must be really pissed…
And totally freaked out, right?
Want me to let you out now?
So… if I let you out,
will you forgive me?
So you're gonna forgive me?
Then I guess I’ll have to do
something you can’t forgive.
What?
What is it?
Mi-joo.
I‘m completely drunk.
I knew it, wine is poison for me.
Sung-jin… what…
what are you two doing right now?
Mi-joo, don’t do this.
You.. you’re being childish, huh?
Mi-joo.
Don‘t do this.
Don't do this!
Stop it!
Mi-joo, you don’t like being
touched by men, remember?
Mi-joo, please don't.
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop touching her there!
Please stop it, Mi-joo.
Stop.
Yes… Yes… That’s good.
You did well.
Don't do this,
are you crazy?
Are you insane?!
Mi-joo.
Sung-jin, have you lost your mind?!
- Why did you take everything off?!
- Stop!
Stop it!
Stop it, stop it!
No! Stop! Stop it!
Stop... Stop...
7 months ago
I miss you
I thought you guys hated this place.
Why, teacher?
Didn’t I nag you a lot when
you took lessons in this house?
Well, thanks to that,
we all make a living playing the cello.
If Su-yeon buys this house,
that’d be great for me.
It’s pretty much the same here.
Yeah.
It’s because the bookshelf
is just so pretty.
So, is the inside still the same too?
What?
Did you think I wouldn’t know?
I knew from the beginning that
you guys were going in there.
I’m sorry.
What is there to be sorry about?
Back then, I thought
it was just a kid’s game,
I didn’t realize
you’d been dating so long
and were looking for a new house together.
By the way,
what is this space in here?
I've always wondered.
My father made it
when he was building the house.
My father...
You know that notorious Unit 731
from the Japanese occupation?
He was a medical officer there.
So, it seems like
he did some bad things.
Maybe that's why he was always anxious
and wanted to stay hidden.
When he got home from work,
he would always spy on Mom
and us sisters through the mirror,
then call us over
and put shackles on us.
Right.
The shackles are still in there, right?
Are they?
How is it?
I like it!
It's super cool and exciting!
I always wanted to try it.
Give me the key.
Hey, what are you doing?
Bring it here and untie me.
What if I don't?
You will.
I trust you.
Trust me?
Yes.
Only you.
I won’t untie you.
Yes, you will.
Because, I'm yours.
She
Hello.
It's me.
What's up?
It's finished.
I was just recording a video
to send to you.
Ah, you worked so hard.
By the way, I have something to tell you.
What's it?
When I come to Seoul,
do you know who I will be with?
With who?
A man.
The man I’m going to marry.
I met him here.
We’ll come back together.
Wow...
Yeah, it’s 'Wow', right?
Then, what about me?
You know.
I know?
Congratulate me.
I'm getting married.
Living with a man.
A real life that others recognize.
A real life?
It’s a real life,
from now on.
If that's real life...
then what about me?
Was it fake with me?
I’ll just be honest. It's okay, right?
You were...
just a tool for me to know where I’m
sensitive and where I like to be touched.
I was your tool too.
We both knew it, didn’t we?
Let’s stop following each other.
And then...
You think I’m crazy, don’t you?
I wasn‘t supposed to come here.
But I‘ve come here twice already.
When you are out...
you're going to hand me over
to the police, right?
No, no.
No, no, Mi-joo.
I made the mistake first, right?
I won’t make it an issue at all.
Seriously, I won’t!
Please stop it here.
Please open it, will you?
Yeah, well, there's
nothing I can say about that.
But you know...
I finally understand what you were saying.
About real life.
The real isn't the real real,
it's what everyone thinks it is.
Right?
I got that.
Also,
that life...
I think I need it too.
What do you mean?
That man...
I will have him.
I will live that real life.
What?
Sorry.
I think you should stay there forever.
Mi-joo.
Mi-joo, Mi-joo!
No, I was wrong.
I was wrong,
it’s all my fault!
What‘s wrong?
Suddenly, only hot water
is coming out of the shower.
- Hot water?
- It‘s okay.
- Why?
- It‘s really fine. It wasn’t hot at all.
- Are you alright?
- You should go out.
We need to tear down
the whole wall to get to the pipe.
Or we can simply cut off
the main water line
and connect a new one.
That’s a lot of work too,
but still the better option.
Seriously, is this place
a bomb shelter or something?
These walls are way too thick...
- you can’t tear this down!
- Here, here, here!
There’s someone in here!
Hey, man…
Hey!
Cut off the main water line ?
No, no!
If there's no other choice,
then do it that way.
When can we start?
Today, I can start right away.
No, no.
No!
But hey, don’t you hear this ‘woong’ sound?
Woong...
No way! No!
What the… fu…
Ah! That scared me, damn!
Ah… so creepy.
I'm heading out.
Sung-jin, Sung-jin!
That was me, I did it!
So weird!
There are no immigration records.
So she hasn’t left the country.
No card usage at all
her phone is still switched off,
and she hasn't contacted me even once.
I'm her mom.
I know Su-yeon well.
Su-yeon would never do
something like this.
There’s something going on.
She’s not the type of person
who could just disappear like this
without any reason.
Right? Darling.
Don’t you think so too?
Yeah.
So
I called the police.
I should have called them earlier.
The police will be at
your house tomorrow.
To our house?
Don’t take it the wrong way.
They're not doing this
because they suspect you,
they're just making sure.
Director,
are you suspecting me now?
Suspicion?
What suspicion is there?
Ah, look at him, searching so carelessly.
No wonder he's a civil servant.
What is it that he's searching for
so carelessly?
Is he looking for the body I buried?
Oh, come on,
don't take it personally.
We're only following orders.
In fact, while doing this,
observing your expression
is part of our technique
just to see how you react.
How's my reaction?
Clear.
Clean.
Pure.
Don't make fun of
me because it's small.
Doesn't it feel too stuffy here?
It's more comfy.
Our house is too big.
I don't like that saying
'Our house'.
What?
The front door code is 1117.
What about that number?
It's the same as Su-yeon's birthday.
really?
I’m just using the one
the previous resident set up.
Interesting,
that’s her birthday.
I'm not really good at
changing those kinds of things.
Yes.
Take a look at this.
Director,
I've seen this a hundred times.
Wait a second,
I want you to look at something.
Oh, it's here.
Look at the mirror behind Su-yeon.
There's a hand.
Someone else's hand.
I never noticed this before because
I was always looking at Su-yeon's face.
But today,
I suddenly had a strange feeling.
So I looked again
and found a hand.
Do you see it?
Yes.
There was someone with her when she left.
What's up.
Did you suddenly miss me?
Yeah.
That's romantic.
Don't ring the bell,
just enter the code and come in.
No one's been particularly mean to me.
Everyone seems really nice
and treats me well.
I've gotten really close
with the cello team
and last time, I even had a
meal with the principal cellist.
Ah, she's really kind,
and how come someone uses the bow
so smoothly and with such charisma?
I might learn by watching that.
Ah, there's one person.
I'm talking about
the concertmaster.
You know her personality.
She always blames the strings,
even when it’s the wind section’s fault.
If it weren’t for her, our orchestra
would have a great atmosphere, right?
Why aren't you eating?
I need to ask you something.
What is it?
You were with Su-yeon
when she left home, right?
What are you talking about?
I saw your wrist in the mirror.
That bracelet.
The one with the blue stones.
Didn't you wear it today?
Blue stones?
This one?
You're right.
I was in her room the day she left.
So you've been lying all this time?
So what you said about Su-yeon
contacting you after a long time
and that you weren’t close,
and that this was your
first time coming to our house,
all of it was a lie.
I'm sorry.
But can you just not say
it's 'our house'?
What?
What's the purpose?
Why are you doing this to me?
She told me to do it.
She asked me to fix the house, so I did.
She told me to help her leave, so I did.
She asked me to fill in for her, so I did.
I only did what I was told to do.
What?
Are you a servant to follow
whatever she tells you to do?
Are you her slave?
Am I really a slave?
It seems like the only thing
I decided on my own
was sleeping with you.
Where is Su-yeon right now?
You must know.
I really don't know that either.
Don't lie.
You two like each other, don't you?
You mean I like her?
I have seen all the photos
you two took.
What are you saying?
It's nothing serious,
just kids' stuff.
Like a friendship pact or something.
Stop lying.
Tell me.
Where is Su-yeon right now?
I really don't know.
I really, really don't know.
I'm going to cut off the water.
It's me.
Turn on the water.
Okay.
It's me!
Over here!
Su-yeon, is that you?
Turn it off.
Su-yeon!
Are you by any chance
inside this house?
Over here, over here!
Are you locked in?
I'm locked in.
Help me!
Help me, Sung-jin.
Su-yeon.
Are you in here?
Su-yeon...
Sung-jin, here.
Right here.
Right in front of you.
Over here! Over here!
I’m here. Right here.
Su-yeon.
Are you here?
I'm standing right here!
So, you’re in here.
Yes.
Sung-jin, what’s wrong?
Huh?
Why?
What's wrong?
So, you must have seen
everything from there?
Right?
What I did with Mi-joo.
You saw it all.
It doesn’t matter.
Just let me out.
I don't care.
I don't care anymore.
Let me out of here.
Let me out!
So, Mi-joo..
came here knowing everything, right?
She did it on purpose to show you.
Right?
Even though she knew
you were watching.
I don't care.
Really, I don't.
- Ah, fuck!
- It really doesn't matter.
I seriously don’t care.
You two…
just what are you up to?
Please, help me.
Sung-jin, help me.
Help me... please!
Ah, please... help me!
Please let me out…
It's her fault.
She used me and then dumped me.
So you locked her up
because of that?
I didn’t lock her up.
She walked in there on her own.
But something went wrong.
I just didn’t let her out,
that’s all.
Isn't that the same thing?
It's different.
Locking someone up is a crime.
Letting her out
it's just being kind.
I don't have any kindness
left for her now.
She’s a bad person.
Someone who uses people
and dumps them.
So what are you going to do?
Just leave her like that?
What if she dies from hunger?
Isn't that interesting?
There must be no food left.
Mi-joo.
Isn’t this basically murder?
This is murder.
Then what do you want me to do?
So now, after everything…
simply let her out?
And say sorry &
I was just kidding.
Is that what you mean?
And she’ll just say,
'I was wrong too',
And that's it?
But still, this isn’t right.
You know what she's like.
Not just me.
She's gonna make us both accomplices
and put us in jail together.
Isn't that why you came to me?
Because you're scared?
Or else,
you would have already called the police
and construction workers to get her out.
Then what are you going to do?
Just leave her like that…
until she dies?
I don’t really know either.
Now that you know about it,
I feel relieved.
You make the decision.
I'll follow it,
no matter what.
You definitely won’t forgive me.
I struggled so much
to get this far… damn it.
The moment you get out,
you’ll destroy me completely, won’t you?
You’ll destroy me so badly that
no one will even find a trace, right?
I guess so.
Well, that’s just how you are.
Right.
Shit...
But Su-yeon...
You lied to me too.
You like women.
Don't you?
Bravo, well done!
Wow, today's final
rehearsal was amazing!
We still need to
fine-tune it a bit more.
Sit down, sit down.
I really enjoyed it.
I totally thought today was
the actual performance.
But why do you look so gloomy?
Me?
Are you hiding something from me?
Nothing like that.
Have you heard anything about Su-yeon?
No.
I thought we are finally
on the same team,
but now I doubt it.
Su-yeon,
she left saying she doesn't like you.
So, as her mom, if I keep hiring you...
No, if I keep appointing you,
I suddenly had this thought that
it would be hard for her to come back.
It really was sudden.
If Su-yeon keeps staying away like this,
what am I supposed to do
with our relationship?
I’m worried.
Right?
Ah, today was going so well..
Su-yeon(2)
Su-yeon: it's me.
SHE(Su-yeon):  Have you guys been getting
along well while I wasn't around?
What are you going to do?
Mi-joo, cheer up.
If she's gone, that means she's alive.
So we haven’t committed any serious crime,
right?
That's right,
But...
I've committed a great crime.
But it's better than murder, right?
I checked,
and the key is still
inside my bag as it is.
To be honest, I doubted you.
Me?
Yeah.
I mean,
let's just
wait and see.
That's not an easy place to get out.
We're staying calm, right?
No.
Go open it now.
Or I'll call the police.
The conductor suddenly had an emergency
and had to cancel the afternoon rehearsal.
And manager,
cellist Kim Mi-joo,
went to the hospital because
she was not feeling well.
That's all.
You can go.
This is scary.
Director, what is this?
After reading the text,
If someone is innocent,
they’ll rush into this room.
Or leave early if they’re guilty.
Wow.
So an agent can activate
the same phone number again
with just a copy of their ID card.
They probably never even thought of this
that you can activate the
same number again.
They’re totally panicked.
I... I’m so scared.
What have they done?
I'm really scared.
Is this the entrance?
It was behind this?
How do you open this?
Sung-jin.
There's no going back
if we do this.
How do I open this ?
I'm telling you,
there's no way out of here after this.
Mi-joo.
Su-yeon.
Su-yeon, are you okay?
See?
I told you she can't
get out of here easily.
Then what the hell was that text message?
Su-yeon.
Are you alright?
She's still alive.
Su-yeon.
Wake up.
Su-yeon, enough.
Suyeon, stop it.
She's out of her mind.
She's crazy.
- Let go!
- Let's get out of here.
- She's crazy.
- I'm telling you to come out.
Sung-jin, let's get out of here quickly!
- Let go of me!
- She's crazy.
- Let's get out of here.
- Let go!
Just let go of me!
Su-yeon.
Get up.
Are you okay?
Let's go out, Sung-jin.
- Let's go.
- I can handle it myself.
Wash up and eat something.
I'm going to the police station.
No.
I said no!
I'm hungry.
Order me something.
Kimchi stew.
Okay.
I'll take a shower first.
I really wanted to shower.
Help me take it off.
Mi-joo.
You're standing right
in front of the mirror, right?
I'm going to take a shower now,
in hot water.
Hey.
If you do something stupid like me,
You know, right?
I won’t give you any water.
Let's talk about the rest,
after I take a shower, Mi-joo.
I was worried since you
didn’t contact me at all.
I didn’t expect you to show up like this
and pay the balance as well.
Of course, it's Shin Su-yeon.
How's Mi-joo?
Teacher
You know everything, right?
About you two?
Hey! I’m your teacher!
Now that I'm getting married…
things got a bit awkward between us.
Still,
I want to keep our bond from breaking.
We shouldn’t lose people, you know?
I used to look at you and think,
“No one can match your possessiveness."
In the end, you get everything, huh?
Even my house is yours now.
Now that I hear you say it,
I guess you're right.
But, teacher...
by any chance...
did you say something
bad about me to Mi-joo?
That I just use people
and throw them away.
I used to like you, teacher.
Wow, the flowers are so nice.
And teacher,
your house is so good.
I'm so happy!
Really,
It's a house that brings happiness.
Going golfing?
Oh, did I wake you up?
No.
I was just about to get up.
You’re really into golf these days.
Yeah. It’s fun.
Mom,
said we should go out together
next week.
Yeah, I heard.
Sleep a bit more.
I'll be back.
Have a great game!
Did you lock it well?
Toss me the key.
You really dressed up nicely.
Were you waiting for me?
Yeah.
Take it off.
[HIDDEN FACE]