[wind blowing]
[children's chorus playing]
[singing continues]
[umpire] Ladies and gentlemen,
this final round match will be
the best of
three tie-break sets.
To the right of my chair,
we have Patrick Zweig.
- [crowd applauding, cheering]
- Yes, Patrick!
[umpire]
To the left of my chair,
we have Art Donaldson.
[crowd cheering, applauding]
[umpire]
Donaldson won the toss
and has elected to serve.
First set.
- [woman 1] All right!
- [man 1] All right,
let's bring it!
- [crowd applauding]
- [man 2] Hey,
we love you, Art!
Donaldson to serve.
Ready? Play.
[Art grunts]
[Patrick grunts]
[woman 2] Out!
[umpire] Fifteen, love.
[woman 3]
That's our boy.
Go, go.
[both grunting]
[crowd cheering]
[umpire] Fifteen all.
[both grunting]
[upbeat music playing]
[grunting continues]
Let's go!
[umpire] Fifteen, 30.
[woman 4 whooping]
[alarm ringing on phone]
- [faucet clanks]
- [water running]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[rubbing skin]
Let's go.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Art exhales]
[announcer on TV]
Every premiere event
and the...
[Bryan] Man,
that ankle's jammed.
I'll just stretch it
from here.
Good. Nice and relaxed.
All right,
put a little pressure back
and I want you to inhale.
[male commentator] Okay,
let's check out today's
first round matchups.
Mary Jo, let's be honest...
[Bryan] Again.
I mean, it's safe to say that
Donaldson is a huge favorite
against the French teen,
Du Maurier.
[female commentator]
Well, on paper, he is.
But because
he had surgery
last year...
[Andrew] Bryan,
we have the practice court
booked at 8:00,
so we should
probably head out
in about 15 minutes.
[Bryan] Yep,
he'll be ready by then.
[female commentator]
In your first two-fifty,
as a qualifier...
- Hey, Art? Just relax.
- [Tashi] Lily,
you have to have some fruit
with your breakfast.
[female commentator]
If Art can start to get
some confidence
and play well.
This is a great opportunity
to end that losing streak
going into the US Open.
[male commentator]
Feels like he needs this win.
Remember what he's
going for this year.
He's got the six
Grand Slam titles,
two at Wimbledon,
two Aussie Opens,
two French Opens,
but he has been
chasing in vain,
for years,
that elusive
US Open title
to complete
the Career Slam.
What do you think,
any shot that he
gets it this year?
[female commentator]
I mean,
it's not looking good.
I mean, if we just go
on the results this season,
it's going to be
tough for him.
But you can never
count a guy like Art
out of the conversation.
He's got himself back healthy,
he's in really good shape,
he's got a great
support team around him.
His coach, Tashi Donaldson,
who also is his wife,
has added a couple
of people to his team.
He's got a new physiotherapist,
and he's got
a new hitting partner.
So everything's there
for him to do well.
Now it's just the matter
can he get his game
back on track.
[male commentator] Yeah,
his fans are hoping we'll start
to see more of the...
All right, I'm going
to go check on the car.
Can you have pancakes?
I don't know, can I?
Feed me.
- No, you're too old.
- No, who says that?
- Who said I'm old?
- [Lily] You said that.
- [man] Here.
- No,
grandmas can
have pancakes,
come on.
[male commentator]
Just a matter of...
[Grandma whispers]
One bite.
I won't tell.
[male commentator]
...if he can click
into that mindset.
[female commentator]
Exactly.
And you know he's got
a lot of things
going for him here.
He knows this tournament,
he likes this tournament,
and he's won here a few times.
And he's got
a great record on hard courts.
So, if he can somehow
- find a way to get...
- [TV audio mutes]
[Grandma]
Your mom and dad are
going to go to work,
and then you and me
are gonna do
some reading,
and then go swimming
at the pool.
[Lily]
Can we watch a movie?
[Grandma] Later,
first we're gonna
keep reading the book
we started yesterday.
[imperceptible]
[Lily]
The one about the giraffe?
[Grandma] Mm, no,
we finished that one.
We're gonna keep
reading the one...
[Tashi] Inside out!
[indistinct yelling]
[Tashi] Cross.
Inside out.
Down the line.
[Bryan] There was
a massager in the car?
- [Andrew]
You grabbed that, right?
- No, the other one.
[Andrew] Oh, yeah,
it's in there.
I want you to force him
into as many
backhand rallies as you can.
He has one big weapon,
and he wants to use it
against you,
so take it away from him.
[woman over PA]
The BB and T Atlanta Open
is a non-smoking event.
All use of tobacco products
and e-cigarettes
is strictly prohibited
on event grounds
except for designated
smoking areas.
[fan] Mr. Donaldson...
Mr. Donaldson, would you?
- Thank you so much.
- [Art] No problem.
- [fan] I'm rooting for you.
- Did you see that look?
- He's gonna crush me, huh?
- Don't think about it, Leo.
[fans yelling]
[woman]
Art, over here, over here!
[crowd cheering in distance]
[Tashi] Yeah?
They're ready for you.
You ready?
Decimate that little bitch.
[upbeat music playing]
[music stops]
[commentator on TV] Yeah,
this match is looking like
what we've come to expect
from Donaldson.
[commentator 2]
Just can't seem
to find his footing.
[commentator 1]
And it's given Du Maurier
the confidence he needs.
- [woman] Out!
- [commentator 2] Ouch,
this is getting brutal.
[commentator 1] You just can't
be missing shots like that.
[ball thudding]
[crowd cheering]
[commentator 1]
And there goes the racket.
- [commentator 2] Yeah, you...
- He was playing really well.
...can really see
the frustration setting in.
[commentator 1]
I mean, I get it.
[sighs] I'm pulling you
out of Cincinnati.
- Baby.
- Might as well
pull you out of the Open too,
if this isn't gonna be
your year then,
why bother?
I'm just rusty.
It's a confidence thing.
Get your fucking
confidence back.
I can't do that for you.
No one's asking you to.
When you play
like that, you are.
I would've killed
to have a recovery
like yours.
I literally would
fucking stab someone.
A child, an old lady, like...
[Grandma] I think that
they're almost done, okay?
- [Lily] Where are they?
- [Grandma] In the living room.
They're watching Daddy's match
from earlier today.
[Lily] Mom said
we could watch it.
What do we need to do
to get you to play again?
What do you
need me to do, hmm?
- Hey, baby.
- Mommy?
- What's up?
- Can we watch Spider-Verse?
Of course we can.
Come here.
We're just talking about
tennis right now.
But you're always
talking about tennis.
I know. I know.
Uh, ooh, how about this?
How about you
start it with Grandma?
And then,
I'll come in a second
and we can
order some room service
and watch it together.
- How about that?
- [Lily] What do they have
for room service?
[Tashi] I don't know.
I don't know, I...
[upbeat music playing]
[Tashi] She likes it here.
We can keep staying here.
We can.
We can stay here.
We can just be rich people.
That's all you
think you can handle.
We can travel.
We can do
the foundation full-time.
Or you keep being
a tennis player.
Which is what you are. Still.
What do you want?
[whispers] What do you want?
[whispers]
I'm gonna be a tennis player.
Good. Good.
[Iin normal voice] Okay,
well, we need to get you
some more match time then.
I can play Cincinnati.
No. No, you cannot.
Not like this.
Okay, how about,
how about New Rochelle?
- That's a challenger.
- Yeah, I know that.
It's in a couple of days.
Maybe we can get you
a wildcard.
- Art?
- Hmm.
You need to start winning.
Right now,
you're getting crushed
by guys like Du Maurier.
So we need to go somewhere,
where there's absolutely nobody
on the other side of the net
who can shake
your fucking confidence.
Okay?
That's why we're going to...
- Phil's Tire Town Challenger.
- [Art chuckles]
- Don't get knocked out
the first round.
- You're evil.
Yeah, well, I'm gonna call Tom,
see if he can get you
in the draw.
- Hey.
- Yeah.
I love you.
I know.
[commentator 1] How much
do you think you'd pay
the first serve today?
[commentator 2] Honestly.
He looks like he doesn't
even wanna be out there.
[upbeat music playing]
[music stops]
[music playing over speakers]
[whirring]
[metal rattling]
[woman laughs]
[compartment opens]
Hey!
Can I pay tomorrow?
I've been driving all day,
I'm exhausted.
You know, if we gave out
a bed to every tired person
who walked in here
asking for one...
[Patrick laughs] Right.
...we'd be a homeless shelter
not a business.
[Patrick] Uh-huh.
Listen, I'm a tennis player.
- [woman] Hmm.
- You know the tournament
down the road?
Oh, that, uh... The thing
- at the country club.
- Right, right.
- Yeah.
- Well, you get $7,000
if you win.
And you get money
just for qualifying.
I just...
I need a place
to stay tonight
so I can rest before
my first match.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I need a card on file.
What if I signed a racket
and gave it to you?
- Sir.
- Mm-hmm.
Sir, I don't know
who you are.
[chuckles]
- [Patrick] I told you I'm...
- Look at this guy.
...a professional
tennis player.
- He's a disaster.
- I don't know,
- I think he's kind of cute.
- Carl, he smells.
- The racket alone...
- [Carl] He's an athlete.
- ...is worth like...
- [man 1] He doesn't look
like an athlete,
he looks like a hobo.
...$300.
[Carl] Very tall,
very handsome hobo.
- [woman chuckles]
- [man 1] You're like a dog.
We need a card that works.
[man 1] Look at him,
he can't pay for the room.
[Carl] Should we invite him
- to come stay with us?
- [man 1 shushing]
[Carl] Hey!
Hello! Name?
[man 1] Barry Gardner.
You know,
this looks very different
from the website.
[woman]
Oh, we're doing
some renovations.
[Barry] I just think you should
maybe update your pictures
to reflect, you know...
[woman over radio]
The Clinton campaign paid
a million dollars
to use your GPS to hire...
[Patrick exhales]
[objects clattering]
[grunting]
Sir, you can't sleep here.
I'm not.
I'm playing at the...
Sir, this is a private club.
- I'm gonna have to ask you...
- [Patrick] No.
- ...to leave.
- No, no, no.
I'm in the Challenger.
I'm a player.
- Oh. Well...
- [racket clatters]
You're a bit early
for check-in.
We're just opening up.
[Patrick sighs]
[footsteps receding]
[car door opens, closes]
Just head right in there.
She's just setting up.
[TV playing indistinctly]
- [door opens]
- [woman] Can I help you?
[sighs] I'm a tennis player.
[door closes]
[sighs] I'm playing
in the Challenger.
Name?
Patrick Zweig.
[woman] Oh, wow!
That's right.
You are!
You probably
don't remember this,
but I was
one of the line judges
at the Junior US Open
back in '06.
Huh, wow.
You hungry?
Uh...
Yeah. Yeah.
Thanks.
[woman] Mm-mm.
Well, we're happy
to have you here.
You got your first match
against Grosu this afternoon.
Should be a nice tournament.
Supposed to get
a little windy mid-week,
but hopefully it'll clear up
before the finals.
- Fingers crossed.
- I was wondering,
is there any chance
for an advance payment
on the prize money?
- Oh.
- Just because I'm...
I know I'm guaranteed
a minimum of $400
even if I get
knocked out today.
Well, generally, we don't give
out the winnings until
player makes his way
through the tournament.
Right. It's just...
I had a problem
with my card at the hotel.
- And...
- You could
just always lose today...
[chuckles]
Then we'd have to cut
your check this evening.
Right.
By the way,
there's a rumor
going around
that we had
a last-minute wildcard.
Wanna guess who it is?
Who?
[indistinct conversation
continues on TV]
[crowd clapping]
[crowd murmuring]
[both grunting]
[crowd exclaiming]
[crowd cheering]
[umpire]
Advantage, Donaldson.
[sniffs]
[crowd cheering]
- [woman] Come on!
- [man] Go, let's go!
- Fault!
- [crowd exclaim]
- Fuck!
- [crowd gasping]
[umpire] Code violation,
audible obscenity.
Warning, Donaldson.
Deuce.
[crowd applauding]
- [man] All right.
- [woman] Come on, Art.
[chuckles softly]
[exclaiming in surprise]
[umpire] Advantage, Zweig.
[man] Get it together, Art.
You got this.
[woman]
He almost got
another penalty.
[crowd murmuring]
[both grunting]
Yeah!
Yes!
- Let's go!
- [Art laughing]
Yeah!
- Yeah!
Come on. Come on. Come on.
- [Patrick] Hey, guys!
- [Art] Hey, guys!
[Patrick] Thank you, man.
- Good play.
- [Art] Good one, man.
- [Patrick] Nice meeting you.
- Good one, man.
[Svoboda] Yeah.
[crowd cheering]
[man yelling]
Fire and Ice, baby.
Let's go!
[woman] Take it off!
[crowd cheering, applauding]
- Can you do me a favor?
- [Patrick] Mm-hmm.
Can you not
demolish me tomorrow?
- Shut the fuck up.
- Listen,
I'm at peace with the fact
that you're going to win.
- It's not a fact.
- I'm just saying,
throw me
a couple of games,
maybe a set.
If it matters to you so much,
I can just give it to you.
- [Art] Really?
- [Patrick] Yeah.
- Wow! Thanks.
- I mean,
every once in a while
a kid who wins juniors
turns out to be
an actually great player,
but most of them end up
in, like, the top 300.
- It's a curse.
- You said,
you seemed pretty excited
about winning
the doubles trophy.
That was different.
That was just you and me.
This is really fun.
[Art] Huh.
All right, well...
But you have to actually play.
You know,
you can't just retire.
I need it to look like
I really beat you.
Mm. Have you got money
on this or something?
No. My grandma,
she's gonna be watching
with her nursing home.
She keeps calling me
telling me
how proud she is.
Don't guilt me
with your dying grandmother.
[both chuckle]
[indistinct chatter]
[umpire]
Now entering the court...
[Patrick] Did Mark tell you
about the party
on Long Island?
- The Adidas thing?
- Yeah.
- [umpire] Anna Mueller.
- Yeah, I'm not going.
What? Why not?
[Art] We have
a final tomorrow.
- I just told you
I'd let you win.
- [Art] Mm-hmm.
- Don't you want
to meet Tashi Duncan?
- [Art burps]
You don't get it, man.
You've never seen her
in person.
She's in another league.
- [umpire] And now entering...
- You mean her game?
No, I mean,
she's the hottest woman
I've ever seen.
[umpire] And winner
of the Junior Australian Open,
Tashi Duncan.
- [upbeat music playing]
- [crowd cheering]
Yeah, baby! Yeah!
[umpire]
Ladies and gentlemen,
this final round match
will be the best
of three tie-break sets.
To the left of the chair,
from Switzerland,
Anna Mueller.
To the right of the chair,
from the United States,
Tashi Duncan.
Duncan won the toss
and elected to serve.
Fuck.
[umpire] First set,
Duncan to serve.
Ready?
Play.
[both grunting]
Look at that
fucking backhand.
[umpire] Fifteen, love.
[crowd cheering]
[Tashi and Anna grunting]
- [Patrick gasps]
- [crowd cheering]
[umpire] Forty, love.
Come on!
[umpire] Forty, thirty.
[Anna speaking German]
[grunting]
[continues speaking German]
[hip-hop song playing
over speakers]
[indistinct chattering]
[Patrick] She's gonna
turn her whole family
into millionaires.
She'll have a fashion line,
a nutritional supplement,
a foundation.
The Tashi Duncan Center
for Girls.
Taking at-risk youth
off the streets
- and onto the courts.
- Come on. Don't make fun, man.
She's a remarkable
young woman.
I know.
I know,
she's a pillar
of the community.
I'd let her fuck me
with a racket.
[chuckles]
Oh, God.
Look, Anna Mueller.
[Anna sobbing]
[Art exclaims in disgust]
[song continues playing]
[women laughing]
[woman whooping]
- Oh, my God.
- Oy.
[Tashi laughs]
I'm gonna go get my drink.
[exhales]
- Hey, I'm Patrick Zweig.
- Art Donaldson.
I know who you are.
You're Fire and Ice, right?
- Oh, my God.
- In the flesh.
Which one's which?
What do you think?
[Art] You were
fucking incredible today.
- Thank you.
- No, really. I mean,
it wasn't even,
like, tennis.
It was an entirely
different game.
I felt bad for Anna.
Oh, uh, don't.
She's a sore loser
- And a racist bitch.
- [Patrick chuckles]
She'll be okay.
You're going
to Stanford, right?
Yeah, how'd you know that?
Um... [chuckles]
I just accepted my offer
and they mentioned you.
- Really?
- [Tashi] Yeah.
- [Art] Oh.
- You're not going pro?
No, not yet.
Why do you waste your time
playing college tennis?
[Tashi's father] Baby...
I need to steal you
for a second.
- Over at the trophies.
- Uh, okay.
I have to go
take pictures.
So, um, it was nice
meeting you both.
- Yeah.
- [Art] Yeah.
[chuckles] Okay.
[rock music playing]
[Patrick sighs]
Now what?
What do you mean?
That was it.
You don't wanna
stick around,
- try to talk to her again?
- No, no, that'll seem
too desperate.
We should just wait
for the shuttle back
to the hotel.
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
[cameraman] Bring it up
for me a little bit.
All right.
Great, great.
Good job.
- Let's go.
- Yeah. Let's go.
[man] Bye,
Miss Stanford University.
[Tashi] Okay, bye.
- Hey!
- Hi!
Hi.
You guys are still here.
- [Art] Great party!
- [Patrick] Uh-huh, yeah.
Thank you.
[clicks tongue]
Um, don't you guys
have a final?
Shouldn't you be, like, um,
preparing or something?
- Oh, it's just the juniors.
- I think we both know
how it's gonna go.
[Tashi chuckles]
Okay, well, um,
it's cool that you stayed.
- Yeah. I actually wanted...
- Yeah.
...to ask you about
that point earlier--
- Hey, do you smoke?
- Cigarettes?
- Yeah.
- No.
- Do you?
- Yeah.
Want to go down
to the beach?
Sure.
[Patrick]
This place is ridiculous,
isn't it?
[Tashi] What do you mean?
What do you mean? It's nice.
[Patrick]
It's like a castle.
Like, they wanna be
feudal lords or something.
[Tashi] Oh, and what does
your parents' place look like?
Exactly.
- [Patrick] Not like this.
- [Art] No, it's bigger.
No. I mean, yeah,
technically it is. Yeah.
[gentle music playing]
[Patrick] So,
I have to ask you about
this Stanford thing.
[Tashi] Okay.
What's the angle?
Why do you want to go beat up
on a bunch of girls
who were the best players
at their high schools?
You know,
they offer classes
in college.
I don't want
my only skill in life to be
hitting a ball with a racket.
I get it.
You're making us
wait for you.
The 18-year-old
tennis phenomenon
who cares about
her education.
Is this why you
came to my party?
It's brilliant. Seriously.
I can already see
the Adidas campaign.
And when are you going pro?
Soon as I can.
Hitting a ball with a racket
is a great way
to avoid having a job.
Well, that's also
your problem.
'Cause you think
that tennis is about
expressing yourself,
doing your thing.
- That's why you
still have that serve.
- It works.
Yeah, but you're not
a tennis player.
You don't know
what tennis is.
What is it?
It's a relationship.
Is that what you
and Anna Mueller
had today?
It is, actually.
For about 15 seconds there,
we were actually
playing tennis,
and we understood
each other completely.
So did everyone watching.
It was like we were in love.
Or like we didn't exist.
We went somewhere
really beautiful together.
You screamed.
When you hit the winner.
Never heard
anything like it before.
I should go
before my dad comes
looking for me.
- I'll see you at school, Art.
- Wait,
- are you on Facebook?
- What?
[Art] He's asking
for your number.
And so am I.
- You both want my number?
- Very much so, yeah.
- [Patrick] Yeah.
- Okay, well,
- I'm not a homewrecker.
- We don't live together.
- It's an open relationship.
- Also, Patrick has
a girlfriend.
I do not. Hey,
come hang out
with us later.
They put you up at the hotel
in Flushing, right?
- We're in Room 206.
- Want me to come
tuck you in?
No. We just keep talking...
About tennis.
Good night.
- We have beer.
- [laughs] Okay.
[gentle music playing]
[man] I'm looking
in my bag right now.
[woman] Did you look
in the small pocket
on the side?
I promise that's in there.
[man speaking indistinctly]
- [metal clanking]
- It's broken.
- And she's not coming.
- She might.
You made it sound like
we wanted to fuck her in here.
We do want to
fuck her in here.
Okay, yeah, maybe.
But what was your plan?
All right, let's say
she did come over.
Then what?
We just like,
keep shooting our shot
until she ends up making out
with one of us, hopefully,
and the other one,
sits in the bathroom?
Sure, if it came to that.
- What?
You think that's beneath you?
- I think it's beneath her.
What if she chooses you?
You won't feel comfortable
sending me away?
She's not coming, Patrick!
[knocking on door]
[man speaking indistinctly
over radio]
[knocking on door]
- [Patrick] Art!
- [Art] What?
- [Patrick] Fucking ash!
- [Art] I found it.
Oh, dude.
[objects clattering]
[Art] Wait.
Oh, shit.
- Hi!
- Hey!
Did you guys go to, like,
Mommy And Me classes
together?
[Art and Patrick chuckling]
[chuckles] What?
You just seem like brothers.
Well, that's what
the Mark Rebellato
Tennis Academy will do for you.
[chuckles]
Oh. Right, right, right.
You guys went
to boarding school.
Mm.
We've been bunkmates
since we were 12.
- So...
- That's really cute.
You ever thought about
doing something like that?
- Boarding school?
- [Art] Mm.
No. No, no, no.
We couldn't afford it.
And even if I could get
a scholarship or something,
there's no way that
my parents would want me
coming of age
in an environment like that.
Huh.
Why? What were
they afraid of?
- Oh, yeah.
- Right.
So, um, is that
where you met your girlfriend?
Oh, she's not my, um...
Yeah, yeah.
[chuckles] And you?
Why aren't you pretending
not to have a girlfriend?
- Art's in between ladies.
- Oh, no, no.
That makes it sound
like I'm some sort of...
- [Tashi] Player.
- Yeah.
Yeah,
Art does fine
for himself.
- I mean, look at him.
- [Tashi chuckles]
So...
How often
does this happen?
- Uh...
- Going after the same girl.
Not as often
as you think actually.
- Really?
- [Patrick] No.
Yeah, no, we, uh...
We usually have
different types.
Hmm. So you're saying
I should be flattered?
- Well...
- No.
Aren't you
everybody's type?
[Tashi chuckles]
What about the two of you?
What do you mean?
Oh!
No.
[chuckles] No.
Why? Is that surprising?
What?
- Well...
- No.
- I mean...
- Patrick, no.
- [chuckles] Sorry.
Yes. I think you need
to tell me now.
- No.
- I think it's a sweet story.
- Uh-huh. All right.
- Well, let's hear it.
Yeah, no, go ahead.
- Uh...
- [both chuckle]
I taught Art
how to jerk off, so.
Okay. Patrick was
an early bloomer, okay?
And I think
that I was on time.
And one time,
when we were 12,
he thought I was asleep
and he was, you know...
- Jerking off.
- Jerking off. And, yeah...
And I asked him,
"What are you doing?"
And he told me.
- He's jerking off.
- Jerking off.
He asked me if
I had ever done it before
and I told him no.
And so, he just...
He showed me how.
[man speaking indistinctly
over radio]
What do you mean
he showed you how?
[laughs]
No. I mean...
- Well...
- [Art] I mean, he did it
- on his bed.
- Okay.
I did it on my bed.
We did it together,
but like on opposite sides...
- in the room.
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
You know. [clears throat]
Silent?
- Oh, no, no.
- No, no.
No, we were talking
about Kat, weren't we?
- Kat Zimmerman.
- Patrick said
- it's always better...
- Yeah.
...if you're like thinking
about somebody
when you're doing it.
And so I asked him
who you're thinking about,
and he was talking
about this girl,
- Kat Zimmerman.
And so, I thought
about her, too.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
[chuckles] Okay,
and who finished first?
- Oh, I don't remember.
- I think you.
[chuckles] And, well,
how was it afterwards?
[chuckling] I think Art
was a little surprised
by the whole thing.
He was...
He was just sitting there
covered in all of it.
- [Tashi chuckles] What?
- He looked like a kid
who'd spilled milk
all over his lap.
- [Art] Jesus, Patrick!
- [both laughing]
I knew enough already
at this point
- to have a sock nearby.
- Right.
Forgot to tell Art
about that part.
[Art] Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
[Patrick] Yeah, so.
- [Art] Yeah.
- Right. Okay.
And what about
Miss Zimmerman?
Whatever happened to her?
You guys...
Neither of us...
She got injured
a week later
and had to quit.
[Tashi] Really?
[Patrick] She wasn't
very good in the first place.
- No, she sucked.
- [Patrick] Yeah.
Yeah. [clicks tongue]
Yeah, no, you're right.
That is a very cute story.
[Patrick laughs] Thanks.
[music playing over radio]
We're out of beer.
[both] Um...
[Tashi sighs]
Come here.
- [tapping bed]
- Which one of us would you...
[Art chuckles]
[both moaning]
[Art and Patrick chuckling]
[Tashi chuckles]
[music continues playing
through radio]
[music builds]
[Tashi] Okay.
[music drops intensity]
I'm going to bed.
[sighs]
[Patrick]
What about your number?
- I told you,
I'm not a homewrecker.
- [Art] Please.
[chuckles] Um...
Okay, uh...
I will be watching
your match tomorrow.
Whoever wins
can have my number.
- [Art exhales]
- [Patrick] All right.
You can beat him,
you know that.
You should
beat him actually.
[Art] Are you saying
you want me to?
I'm saying you're not going
to get my number if you don't.
[Art] But what do you want?
I want to watch
some good fucking tennis.
Good night.
[Art]
Remember when you said
you'd let me win?
[Patrick] That was
a lifetime ago.
- What about my grandmother?
- Hope she has
- a fucking stroke.
- [Art groans]
- [Patrick grunts]
[ball thudding]
[crowd exclaim]
- [crowd exclaim]
- Wow.
[crowd cheering]
[umpire] Thirty, forty.
[crowd member whooping]
[woman] That's how you do it!
[man 1] Nice!
That's the way you play!
[man 2] Go!
[crowd exclaim in dismay]
[umpire] Thirty, love.
- [umpire] Forty, love.
- [woman] Come on, Art,
you got this!
- [man] It's not over, Art!
- [woman] Hang in there, Art!
Fault!
[sighs]
- [Patrick grunts]
- [crowd exclaim in dismay]
Game and first set, Zweig.
Zweig leads one set to love.
[crowd chattering indistinctly]
[Victor] So stupid losing
to guys like this, Victor.
[sighing]
Fucking idiot.
[Victor grumbling in Romanian]
[in English] Fuck.
[Victor continues grumbling
in Romanian]
[in English]
Nice match, Zweig.
You too, Grosu.
- Tough break.
- [players laughing]
[Victor cursing in Romanian]
[in English] Calm, Victor.
[Victor grunting]
[toilet flushing]
- [chuckles softly]
- [locker door slams]
[Victor in English]
What are you doing
with your life?
How did you get like this?
You can't beat some
fucking loser like him?
How can you call yourself...
[Victor continues grumbling
in Romanian]
[in English] So, do you,
like, play at Wimbledon
or the US Open or what?
Yeah, sometimes.
When I qualify.
- Really?
- Yeah.
What does that mean?
Well, those big tournaments
usually have spots
for 128 players.
So if you're ranked
in the top 100,
then you instantly get a spot,
but everyone else has
to play a sort of, uh,
tournament before
the tournament.
- Okay.
- Some years I make it,
some years I don't.
But, um, if I win this thing
in New Rochelle,
my ranking will be
high enough for the Open.
So, you'll get a spot?
I'll get a spot
in the qualifiers.
- Oh, okay. [chuckles]
- [chuckles]
I told you tennis is boring.
No, really...
It's, um, it's interesting.
Excuse me.
Can I get a tea
with some lemon?
[server] Coming right up.
Uh, so, tell me
about real estate law.
Uh, I don't know,
well, um...
- My firm...
- Mm-hmm.
Well, it's not my firm,
but the firm that I work for,
we actually do something
called estate planning.
Which is a little different.
I used to do real estate law
with this firm in Hartsdale...
which I don't know
if you know where that is
- but it's just five minutes...
- Thank you.
...down the road
if you're driving,
but, um, yeah,
I left that firm.
It was small. Anyway.
- Um, I deal with trusts and...
- Trust.
...uh, power of attorney...
Go ask them about the beds.
- Oh, okay.
- Okay.
Do you want us to wait
to FaceTime with Dad?
No, no, it's okay.
Do you mind taking this
upstairs for me?
- Okay. Sure.
- Okay. Love you.
- We'll be right up.
- All right, honey.
All right, see you.
Anything that, you know,
you have to deal with
when someone crosses over...
- Are you okay?
- Huh?
Are you... Are you okay?
Uh, yeah. Yeah.
Can you excuse me?
I just have to...
Yeah.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
I'm playing
at the Challenger.
Yeah, I know that.
But you're not
staying here,
are you?
No. Why are you staying here?
I assumed you guys would
rent a villa or something.
Lily likes hotels.
Our daughter.
Oh.
Art can't see us together.
He already thinks
I planned this
to humiliate him.
- Didn't you?
- [chuckles]
Not this part.
Are you on a fucking date?
No.
Well, yeah, but it's not...
I just need
a place to sleep.
- What?
- Wow.
Can't all stay at the Ritz.
Mm. Okay, well.
Can you seal the deal
and leave?
You're on opposite sides
of the draw.
You're not gonna
play each other unless
you're both in the final.
I don't think we have
to worry about that.
No, you typically fall apart
in the second round.
[whispering]
Your mom looks good.
I know she does, Patrick.
[elevator dings]
[in normal voice]
Do me a favor.
Stay the fuck
away from us.
[elevator doors close]
Sorry, that was a, uh...
Uh, hey...
[woman 1 over PA]
Junior training sessions
will now take place
on court six.
[indistinct chatter]
[woman 2 over PA]
Will Coach Stevens
please report to
the main office?
Coach Stevens.
[Art] What do you mean
you won't say?
- I don't kiss and tell.
- Since when?
Since she told me
she'd stop seeing me
if I told anyone.
[coach 1] And go!
- [coach 2] Yep, yep, good.
- All right.
[coach 2 yelling indistinctly]
Right, but she had to know
that you were gonna talk to me.
She didn't indicate that
there were any exceptions.
All right, fine.
Then give me a signal.
Isn't this hard
for you to hear?
Like, wouldn't you
rather not?
No. I'm very happy for you.
I just don't wanna
feel left out.
[upbeat music playing]
[coach 2] There you go!
Okay, how about this?
If the two of you
slept together,
do a normal serve.
- Art.
- I'm not asking
you to tell me.
I'm just saying,
if you fucked,
serve like me.
- Like you?
- [Art] Yeah.
You know you have
a tic, right?
Before you throw the ball up
you place it
in the exact center
of the neck of the racket.
Okay, fine, yeah.
Do that.
If you fucked.
[Patrick]
I'm not telling you
anything, Art.
You won't be
telling me anything.
Come on.
[chuckles]
[Patrick chuckles]
[upbeat music continues]
[music drops]
- Everything okay?
- I'm okay, thank you.
- [fan] Excuse me, Tashi.
- No, it's okay.
- Thank you.
- [fan 1] Thank you.
Of course.
Time. Second set.
Donaldson to serve.
[crowd cheering]
- [Art exhales]
- [Patrick sniffles]
[grunts]
[student 1 speaking
indistinctly]
- [both grunting]
- [coach] There you go!
[women speaking indistinctly]
[student 1]
He's pretty funny.
[chuckles] He's, like,
always cracking jokes.
[student 2]
It just sounds so hard.
[student 1] It's not.
I don't know I feel,
like, out of all my classes...
[Art] All right,
so when are you going pro?
[Tashi] Um, well,
if we win the championship,
- then I'll leave.
- So, May.
- I said, if we win.
- Right. So, May.
[chuckles] Um...
Did Patrick tell you
he's coming
- to the Pepperdine match?
- Hmm. Yeah, he told me.
We should get dinner
or something.
Sure. If you want.
[progressive rock song playing
over speakers]
What's up?
Nothing.
Art.
The whole thing you're doing,
you're not good at it.
- It's fucking stupid.
- I'm not doing a thing.
I'm just surprised that
you guys are
still seeing each other.
That's all.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
Why did you ask me
to come to lunch with you?
I told you,
I had extra meal credits
and they were
going to expire.
Don't be such
a fucking pussy.
Is he seeing other girls
on tour?
- No, I mean...
- Is that what this is?
- I don't know.
- What?
That's not what
I'm trying to say.
Then what are you
trying to say?
- [plates clatter]
- Okay.
He's not in love
with you.
What makes you think
I want someone
to be in love with me?
Did I ever say I was
in love with him?
- You didn't.
- So why would I give a fuck
- if he loved me or not?
- I guess you wouldn't.
- Cool.
Don't you think
you deserve it?
[Tashi]
Jesus fucking Christ.
I mean,
who wouldn't be
in love with you?
[Tashi] Think you might be
the worst friend in the world.
Maybe.
[Tashi] Definitely!
Thank you.
For lunch, Art.
[indistinct chatter]
[Patrick]
Whoo-hoo! Let's go!
[student 1]
Who the fuck is this guy?
- Does he go here?
- [student 2] I don't know.
- I don't... I don't think so.
- [Patrick] Come on, Donaldson,
big serve! Big serve!
That's right, baby!
Show that motherfucker
who's boss.
Finish it up, Donaldson,
come on.
[student 2] Whoa!
[Patrick] All right.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
[student laughing]
Art!
Out of the way,
out of the way!
[students laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
[clicks tongue]
So, how's the tour?
No fun stuff?
Like what?
I don't know.
Are you seeing anybody?
What do you mean?
I'm taken.
What do you think
I'm doing here?
You're not here
to visit me?
What?
You're really committing
to this thing?
- To Tashi?
- Hmm.
Yeah. I mean,
we're taking it step by step,
but, you know...
I like her.
I think she'd make me
an honest man.
- You don't believe me?
- No, I'm just...
I'm not sure how
she's thinking
about all of this.
I don't want you
to get hurt.
[chuckles softly]
You don't want me to get hurt?
[Art] Hmm.
- Did she say something to you?
- No.
I just got the impression
she's not thinking
about this as
a serious relationship.
You got that impression?
From a conversation we had.
- Huh!
- Hmm.
You fucking snake.
Honestly, I'm proud of you.
- I'd be doing the same thing.
- I'm not doing anything.
It's fine. It's exciting
to see you this way.
It's what's been missing
from your tennis.
What?
It's nice to see you
lit up about something.
Even if that something
is my girlfriend.
That's what the two of you
are calling each other now?
[Patrick] Hmm.
You know this makes
it hotter for me, right?
You sitting here
pining for her.
I would never do anything
- to get in the way of you...
- I know.
- ...and your girlfriend.
It's not your style.
You're playing
percentage tennis.
Waiting for me to fuck up.
Come on,
walk me over there.
[toilet flushes]
[exhales] I missed you.
You have any idea
how lonely it is on tour?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Is that why you haven't won
any challengers?
I just told you I missed you.
[grunting]
[Tashi moans]
I watched
the Shinoda match online.
And you could've won,
but then you started tanking
in the third set.
- Tashi, come on.
- What?
Look at me.
When were you gonna
tell me about Art?
[chuckles]
Thought you knew
about that.
I mean...
I feel bad because
I know he's in pain,
- but...
- Right, but?
What? You're not
intimidated by him?
No.
- Really?
- No.
- Well, you should be.
- Uh-huh. Why?
- Because he's smart.
- Yeah.
- He's good looking.
And he's really
fucking good at tennis.
Oh, he's always
been very good.
[chuckles] Yeah,
but he's gotten a lot better
since he's been here.
Are the two of us
still playing for your number?
- [Tashi chuckles]
- I thought I won.
That's your problem.
You always think you've won
before the match is over.
Are we talking
about tennis?
We're always
talking about tennis.
Can we not?
Sure.
[Patrick]
What are you doing?
I'm getting ready
for my match.
Start my routine.
I'll see you there.
- Tashi.
- What?
If you're not interested
in me fixing your game
for free,
don't worry about it.
It's fine.
Why do you care so much?
Well, we're dating, right?
So, I don't know.
Should be
a little embarrassing
if you suck.
- I suck now?
- God.
It's not college tennis
out there.
We can't all walk around
calling ourselves
"The Duncanator."
- Wow.
- I'm sorry. I just...
Okay. No, it's fine.
Look, I'm happy
they like you here.
I just don't need you
to be my coach.
Well, someone needs to be.
Can we just start over?
What do you think
you need from me?
Honestly,
what do you think
you need from me?
A cheerleader?
A girlfriend?
A fuck buddy? [scoffs]
Like, there's plenty
of girls out here
that would
love to be
your girlfriend, okay?
You're charming.
You're talented,
you got a big dick.
Just go be with one of them.
Is this like,
a new strategy
you're using
to pump yourself up
before the match?
Have a little fight
to get the energy going?
I don't need a fight
to get the energy going.
No. Just an hour
of meditation.
[chuckles] And what?
You think that's lame?
I think it's unnecessary
given you're playing
Sally Fucking Country Club
from Pepperdine.
[exhales] And how's coasting
by on talent going for you?
You know
how ridiculous it is
to hear you
call me every week,
talking about all the ways
that you're getting
screwed over on tour?
As if that's a good use
for my fucking time?
- Well, excuse me
for inconveniencing you.
- You are, actually.
I need to be alone.
So can I just
meet you there?
- No.
- What?
I'm not going to the match.
Not if you think you can just
dismiss me.
I'm not some fucking lapdog
who's gonna sit around
and let you punish me.
I'm not Art.
Or maybe you need
someone like that.
Someone who's
gonna hop on board
and be Mr. Tashi Duncan.
Is that what
you think I want?
Yeah. A member
of the fan club.
You're not a member
of my fan club?
I'm your peer.
I'm not your fucking groupie.
And I'm definitely
not your student.
All right.
Good luck, champ.
[music drops]
[breathing heavily]
[indistinct chattering]
- [woman] Come on.
- Hi.
- Sorry.
Thank you.
[man over speakers]
And now, your 2002, 2005,
and 2006 NCAA champion,
give it up for
Stanford Women's Tennis.
[man 1] Go Stanford!
Hey!
- [spectator whistling]
- [man 2] Tashi!
Tashi!
Tashi! We love you, Tashi!
[whooping]
Yeah, whoo!
[woman] Tashi!
Yeah, let's go!
[cell phone chimes]
[crowd chattering indistinctly]
[announcer] On court one,
Maria Foster from Pepperdine,
and from Stanford,
Tashi Duncan.
[crowd cheering]
[woman 2]
We love you, Tashi!
[upbeat music playing]
[Tashi and Maria grunting]
[grunting continues]
- [bone cracks]
- [Tashi groans]
[crowd gasping]
[woman 3]
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
[Tashi crying, squealing]
[crying]
[medic] Okay, Tashi,
you're okay. You're okay.
- [door clanking]
- [Art] out of the way!
[medic] On your back.
Okay, try to breathe.
Okay, you're okay.
[crying]
Okay, okay, okay.
Look at me.
Tashi, look at me, okay?
Just breathe.
Breathe.
[medic1]
It's torn up pretty bad,
but we won't know for sure
until we get the X-rays
from the hospital.
[medic 2]
Did you see it happen?
[medic 1]
Yeah, it was pretty quick.
Just a slip and then
she landed on it
the wrong way.
[medic 2]
That's all it takes.
[medic 1] Yeah.
Let's just hope
it's not as bad as it looks.
Did you get an ETA
on the ambulance?
[medic 2] Yeah, they said
they're on their way.
[footsteps approaching]
- I'm sorry.
- Out.
- Listen, Tashi! Tashi...
- Get out! Out!
- Tashi, Tashi, listen, please.
- [Tashi] Out!
- Out!
- Patrick, get the fuck out!
[panting]
- [medic 1
speaking indistinctly]
- [Tashi sighs]
[indistinct chattering]
[both grunting]
- Out!
- [crowd cheering]
[umpire] Thirty, love.
That was out!
That was way out!
The ball was called in.
- Are you blind?
- [umpire] Zweig!
Are you here to do your job,
or you're just excited
that Art Donaldson's
over there?
I'm going to give you
a code violation
if you don't stop this.
[Patrick] Hey, Art!
This lady wants
your autograph.
[crowd booing]
[crowd exclaim in dismay]
[umpire] Code violation.
Unsportsmanlike conduct.
Point penalty, Zweig.
- [woman 1] Come on, Patrick!
- [man 1] Just play the game.
This how you wanna
get your points?
- I'm ready to serve, Patrick.
- Yeah, I bet.
[umpire] Forty, love.
Stop going easy on me.
I'm not.
- [Tashi] Hit the ball!
- Tashi--
Actually fucking
hit the ball.
Come on.
You afraid you're
gonna hurt me?
Pussy.
Wait!
Okay?
And actually try to win.
Please.
[Tashi groans]
- [Art] Hey.
- [Tashi] I'm fine.
[Art] You okay?
[Tashi] I'm good.
I'm okay.
[grunting]
I'm fine.
I'm okay.
[Art] Come here.
[Tashi]
I'm okay. I'm okay.
[indistinct chattering]
[children's chorus playing]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[song continues]
[sighs]
[breathing shakily]
[sniffles]
[music fades out]
[indistinct chattering]
More aggressive.
Little higher.
Just invite her to serve.
[ball thuds]
[Art] Oh, come on, you can
sleep in tomorrow, right?
Katerina's match
isn't until nighttime.
[Tashi chuckles]
No. Are you kidding?
I wake her up early
to run drills.
[Art] Oh, she's lucky
to have you.
[Tashi chuckles]
You're getting
too much height
- on your ball toss.
- [Art] I am?
- [Tashi] Uh-huh. Yeah.
- [server] Whenever you guys
are ready.
- [Art] Thanks.
- You're a great spot server,
but right now,
you're checking in
at like 129, 130.
But I think with, like,
a few adjustments,
you'd get to 135.
But you should listen to Karl.
He is your coach.
I'm just Katerina's
hitting partner.
Maybe you wanna jump ship?
Come be my assistant coach?
Oh, I get it.
You want to work
with someone who has
a little bit more potential.
No! No.
No, it's not that.
I mean, you have plenty
of potential. It's just...
You think that would be
a good idea?
Why not?
- That was a long time ago.
- It was not that long ago.
Well, it feels like
a long time ago.
[Tashi chuckles]
So, you're saying
you're not in love
with me anymore?
I'm really
proud of you, Tashi.
- I'm serious, I'm serious.
- Oh, God.
- You're doing really well.
- Okay.
What?
You think I was
going to, like,
- kill myself
after the injury?
- No.
No, I'm just glad
that you didn't quit tennis.
Yeah, well, unfortunately,
my only skill in life
is hitting a ball
with a racket.
[Art chuckles]
This is really stupid,
but, uh...
[clicks tongue]
After your injury...
I couldn't help but just...
think about what
would have happened
if I had beaten Patrick.
So you want me
to join your team
because you feel guilty?
No.
I want you to join my team
because I want to win.
I think you'd beat him now
if you guys played.
Don't you think?
Don't know.
We, uh...
haven't played professionally,
and don't keep in touch.
- [chuckles]
- What?
[clears throat] Just...
I was a homewrecker,
wasn't I?
[Art chuckles]
- Art.
- Yeah.
You never really said
if you're still
in love with me or not.
Who wouldn't be?
[chuckles]
[car beeps]
[chuckles] What?
I really wanna
kiss you right now.
[chuckles]
But I'm afraid if I try,
you'll think I'm
the worst friend
in the world.
To who?
[glass clattering]
Oh, my...
[laughs] Oh, my God!
[both laughing]
[cracking]
[umpire] Game and
second set, Donaldson.
- Six-two. Match is tied.
- [Patrick grunting]
- [racket thudding on court]
- [umpire] One set all.
Code violation, racket abuse.
Point penalty, Zweig.
Please, please.
[indistinct chattering]
New balls, please.
[lounge music playing
over speakers]
He's not bad. I've played him
at a few of these things.
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be
prostituting yourself
for a place
to sleep tonight?
I'm staying at
that girl's house.
- Mm. Must be the love.
- Hey, come have
a cigarette with me.
I have to talk to you.
[Tashi chuckles]
Yeah, I don't smoke.
And I'm not talking to you.
[clears throat]
[tapping cigarette packet]
I'm going to propose
something to you.
Can you blow it
away from me, please?
Sorry. It's gonna
make you angry.
It's gonna make you
very angry.
I want you to be my coach.
What?
Even if he wins the Open,
completes his
career Grand Slam,
Art's still gonna retire
as someone
who's just really, really good.
That's what you guys
will have done together.
But imagine if you could turn
Patrick Zweig
into a guy who wins a Slam.
I still have a season.
I still have
one good season,
and I need you
to bring it out of me.
So...
what do you think?
- How fucking dare you?
- [groans]
Jesus Christ!
You want my
best piece of advice?
- Do you want me
to coach you?
- Yeah.
Okay, quit.
Quit right now.
Right the fuck now, quit.
You know that when I'm good,
I'm one of the best
- in the world.
- You are 271st best
- in the fucking world.
- I still have a shot.
You're 31.
You have a better shot
with a handgun in your mouth.
[chuckles]
I mean,
why don't you go home?
Go home, ask your parents
for a seat on the board,
or you know what,
matter of fact,
ask them for some money. Okay?
Go be like
any other spoiled kid
who has ever
amounted to nothing
in their fucking life,
and stop this performance
of being
a down-on-your-luck
professional.
- Tashi...
- No, you're not
20 years old anymore,
and it's not cute to be
walking around pretending
like you need to grind it out
at these bum-fuck tournaments,
and sleep in your fucking car.
And it is unforgivable
that you would ask me
to devote a single second
of my fucking time
to help you achieve
your fucking dreams.
What dreams, Patrick?
You never had any!
Is that what
you and Art
are doing?
- Living the dream?
- That is exactly
what the fuck we're doing.
Then how come
you hate him?
You do.
It's obvious, you do.
You can feel him
giving up already,
even though you know
he's not going to retire
- until you let him.
- He is a grown man.
- He can do
whatever he wants.
- Sure, sure,
but he doesn't.
He does whatever
you want.
Except now, he's not
even pretending to like it.
- [sighs]
- He's dreaming about
eating hamburgers again.
Watching your daughter, um...
[snaps fingers]
Uh, Lily, grow up.
Maybe doing some commentary
on the Tennis Channel.
He's ready to be dead.
And you're starting to realize
you might not want
to be buried with him,
'cause who is he to you
if he's not playing tennis?
So that's what
you think he is to me?
A racket and a dick.
Does Art know
about Atlanta?
You keep saying you came here
because Art needed matches.
I think you came
for something else.
[chuckles]
You think
I came here for you?
You think I came here
to throw it all away for you?
Maybe you just
wanted to see me.
I have seen you.
You look like shit.
I'm going to beat him.
If we both
make it to the final.
I'm going to beat him.
Even if you could beat him,
it wouldn't change anything.
It'll break him.
You know it will.
It won't make you. Okay?
It's too late for that.
My number,
in case you
change your mind
- about the coaching.
- I won't.
[gentle music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[man 1] Just text me.
I'll meet you by the car.
[indistinct chattering]
Time.
Final set.
Zweig to serve.
Love, one.
[crowd cheering]
- [woman 1] This is it!
- [man 1] Keep it up, champ.
[man 2] Come on, man!
[woman 2]
Let's go, let's go, Artie.
[crowd cheering indistinctly]
[Art grunts]
[ball thudding]
[tense music playing]
[music intensifies]
[Patrick grunts]
[music playing over speakers]
[indistinct chatter]
[man] Grab those!
Make sure
that tent is secure.
[door opens]
[Patrick]
Can you do me a favor?
Can you not, like,
demolish me tomorrow?
[door closes]
[scoffs]
Hey, congrats on being
a Phil's Tire Town
Challenger finalist.
Yeah, you too.
Hopefully,
the wind dies down
before tomorrow
and we can have
a fair fight.
Yeah. [sighs]
Art. Come on.
Can we talk?
Can you put
your dick away?
[chuckles]
This is a sauna.
Look, we've been here
for a week
and we haven't said
two words to each other.
It's just...
It's silly, man,
it's dramatic.
I mean, really,
why are you
so angry with me?
Look, I don't buy
that it's because of Tashi,
or I don't think it's because
of what happened to her.
I think maybe you're still
just really disturbed
by the fact that she could've
been into someone like me.
When we were teenagers.
[Patrick] Huh!
[reporter 1 on TV]
...which will be taking place
tomorrow evening.
He has really been
in tip-top form this year,
hasn't he, Jason?
[reporter 2] Yeah,
it's actually pretty remarkable
the difference
we've seen in his game.
He's far and away
the favorite right now
to win the US Open.
[reporter 1]
I completely agree.
And then, of course,
on the women's side
we have Anna Mueller,
who's already got
the Wimbledon title this year.
[reporter 2]
She's been having
a great season.
[reporter 1]
Absolutely incredible.
There just hasn't been
really anyone
on the women's side
who can give her
much of a challenge.
[reporter 2]
In the case of Donaldson,
what do you think it is that...
[upbeat music playing]
[reporters speaking
indistinctly]
[sighs]
It's his grandmother's.
How is she?
She died.
Stroke.
[sighs]
I miss you.
[music stops]
You're right.
I do find it disturbing.
There's no need, man.
Lots of girls were into me.
None of them
wanted to marry me.
- That's not what I was for.
- What were you for?
[indistinct chattering]
[indistinct chatter on TV]
[reporter 1 on TV]
You're exactly right, Jason.
Just to back you up
a little bit...
His first serve last year
was around 130,
which is excellent.
But now we're seeing him
get up to 135, 140 sometimes,
it's giving him a lot more
free points when he serves.
[reporter 2] Yeah, it's just
little things like that...
[fan] Art? Mr. Donaldson?
Oh, my God,
I can't believe my luck
that I would run
into you so late at night.
Um, would you, uh...
[Art] Sure, yeah.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
- [Art] Thank you.
[reporter 2] The edge
over the opponents.
That's often the difference
between a good player
and a great player.
[reporter 1] And I think
Donaldson right now is
starting to look like
a great player.
[reporter 2] That's for sure.
And I'll be very surprised
if he doesn't
come away tomorrow...
[Patrick] Honestly,
I thought you'd be happy
I was in the draw.
I mean, you always wanted
to beat me in a tournament,
and a few weeks
before the Open,
that's the perfect
confidence booster.
I know what you're
trying to do right now.
[chuckles] I'm not trying
to do anything, Art.
This is a challenger.
I don't need to play
- mind games with you.
- Right. You don't give a shit.
I... Hey, I didn't say that.
We both know you have
considerably more
at stake here than I do.
- Do I?
- [chuckles]
What the...
Oh, fuck, where do get
- your swagger from, man?
- [chuckles]
I mean, you come in here
swinging your dick around
like I'm supposed
to be afraid of it, but...
Do you realize
how embarrassing it is
that you are here
right now?
Not quite as embarrassing
as you being here.
I'm just stopping by, man.
This is where you live.
You know...
I always tried to figure out
what happened to you,
but, you know, the more
I've thought about it,
the more I realize...
[sighs]
It's what didn't happen.
You never grew up.
You still think
you can talk to me
like you're my peer,
because we came
from the same place.
But it's not about
where you come from
in tennis, Patrick.
It's about winning.
And I do. A lot.
- You've never beaten me.
- So what?
I haven't beaten
most of the guys
who play at these things.
This is a game about winning
the points that matter.
I don't matter?
Not even to the most
obsessive tennis fan
in the entire world.
We're not talking
about tennis.
What the fuck else do I have
to talk to you about?
I wanted to come in here
and wish you luck, Art.
[chuckles]
That makes no sense.
I wanted to say that
I'm looking forward to it.
And I miss playing with you.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Well, I don't miss
playing with you, man.
I'm too old for it.
[door closes]
Kiss for me. [gasps]
Thank you. And Grandma.
[Grandma] Mwah!
- [Tashi] Thanks, sweetheart
- Good night, honey.
[Tashi] All right,
tuck you both in.
Oh, there we go.
[kisses] Night, sweetheart.
[softly] Good night.
Thank you.
What time you want me
to come get her tomorrow?
I'm saying, whenever,
whenever you want to
'cause she can
stay with Andrew
- while we're doing warm-ups.
- Okay, hon.
And you're talking
to Ralph in the morning?
Oh, thank...
Yes, I do.
I have that.
- Okay. Thank you, Mom.
- Okay, sleep tight, okay?
- [Tashi] I love you.
- I love you, sweetie.
- Have you... Do you have it?
- [Grandma] Okay, got my key.
- Yes, I do. Bye-bye.
- Okay.
Good night.
[sighs]
- [toothbrush whirring]
- [water running]
- [faucet squeaks]
- [water stops]
Tell me it doesn't matter.
Tell me it doesn't matter
if I win tomorrow.
No.
You tell me if it matters.
You're the professional
competitor, Art.
It can't be about
avoiding my judgment.
I'm not a nun.
I'm not your mommy.
I'm just asking
that you love me
no matter what.
[chuckles]
What am I, Jesus?
Yeah.
You can beat him.
What if I don't?
How are you
gonna look at me
if I still can't beat
Patrick Zweig?
Just like this.
[Art] I'm going to
say something.
It's probably gonna
make you angry.
I need you to
hear me out, okay?
I wanna retire this year
whether we win the Open or not.
[Tashi sighs]
I'm still going to go for it.
I'm still going to try, but...
I'm tired.
I don't want to be
one of those guys
who doesn't know
when to walk away, okay?
It's embarrassing
to still be doing this shit
when you're 40.
Okay.
Okay?
If you wanna
quit playing tennis,
you can quit playing tennis.
You don't need
my permission.
We've been
doing this together.
We've always been
I'm your coach.
Okay, I work for you.
- Coach me then.
- I am coaching you.
I'm playing
for both of us, Tashi.
I know that.
[sighs]
If you don't win tomorrow,
I'll leave you.
[sighs]
I'm serious.
Does that help you?
[Brazilian pop song playing]
[Art sniffles]
Can you just hold me
until I fall asleep, please?
Okay.
[wind whistling]
[Art and Patrick grunting]
[exhales]
[grunts]
[crowd cheering]
[umpire]
Advantage, Donaldson.
[both breathing heavily]
[Art inhales, grunts]
[crowd cheering]
- [Art grunts]
- [umpire] Game, Donaldson.
Donaldson leads
six games to five.
[crowd speaking indistinctly]
[announcer]
Phil's Tire Town reminds you
to drink some water.
Beverages are available
at the snack bar.
[wind blowing]
[Patrick]
What are you doing?
I told him
you're an Uber driver.
Just drive.
[Tashi sighs]
[wind howling]
[brakes squealing]
I don't wanna be
parked here long.
Someone's gonna think
I'm a hooker and call the cops.
We can go back
to my hotel.
The money just came in
this afternoon.
I am not here
to fuck you, Patrick.
- You're not?
- No.
[Patrick] Uh.
- [Tashi sighs]
- Well?
I want you
to lose tomorrow.
I'm aware of that.
I'm asking you
to lose tomorrow.
Fuck off.
He's doing really well
this week.
He's ready to come back.
He's ready to
make a shot at the Open,
and if he wins tomorrow,
he'll know he can do it.
He needs this.
- He needs this?
- Yes.
What about what I need?
[sighs] I can't believe
you'd do this to him.
I mean,
fucking me
would be one thing,
but this?
This is unforgivable.
Actually, I'm being
incredibly fucking kind
to the both of you right now.
Okay?
I'm taking such good care
of my little white boys.
No. No fucking way.
Drive me back
to my fucking hotel.
Drive the fucking car, Patrick.
Hey, you know what the most
frustrating part of this is?
- What?
- You know what really
drives me crazy?
You did come here to fuck me,
but you're so full of shit
that you won't
even admit that to yourself.
If it's the only way
to get you to throw
the fucking match, then sure.
Go fuck yourself.
You absolute loser.
[scoffs] I'm the loser?
Yeah.
Yeah, you are.
Look at you.
Time for your Uber driver
to drop you back off
to your family.
[crowd exclaim]
[umpire] Thirty, love.
[Andrew] Come on, Art.
[crowd cheering indistinctly]
- Unbelievable.
- I know. Let's go!
- [wind howling]
- [upbeat music playing]
Fuck it. I'll do it.
- Why?
- What do you mean, why?
Because I want you
to actually do it,
so I need to know
that you understand why--
I'm not married to you, Tashi.
Just be happy
I'm doing what you want
- and shut up about it.
- You are such a fucking child.
Of course I am.
I spent my entire life
hitting a ball with a racket.
Why the fuck
am I in your car?
- Because you're stupid.
- You're stupid.
I know. I'm just not
as disturbed by it
as you are.
I don't have nearly that
high an opinion of myself.
You are the most
egotistical person
- I have ever met in my life.
- Oh, sure, sure.
But I've never been
confused about the fact
- that I'm a piece of shit.
- [sighs]
That's what you like
about me.
I don't like
anything about you.
No, you like precisely
one thing about me
and it's that
I'm such a piece of shit
that I could actually see you
for what you are.
And what is that?
In reality? A really,
really insanely hot woman.
- Oh, fuck off.
- I guess now
you'd say a MILF.
- Pull over.
- Come on, don't be dramatic.
Pull the fucking
car over, Patrick.
- Fine, let me... Fine.
- Pull over.
[Tashi sighs]
Hey! Hey!
Your hotel's that way!
- [breathing heavily]
- [upbeat music continues]
Are you gonna
hit me again, huh?
[Tashi spits]
- [music stops]
- [wind howling]
[breathing heavily]
[children's choir playing]
[choir continues playing]
[wind howling]
[sighs]
[card reader beeps]
[gentle music playing]
[wind howling]
[sighs]
[Patrick] I miss
watching you play, Tashi.
You're so beautiful.
You have to make him feel
like he earned it tomorrow.
You can't just give up
in the middle of the match.
Are you sure
this is what you want?
What else could I want?
How am I supposed to know
if you're going to do it?
You won't.
- [grunts]
- [crowd gasping]
- [man 1] All right.
- [woman 1] Come on!
[crowd clapping]
[exhales]
[ball bouncing on court]
[panting]
[ball thuds against racket]
- [crowd exclaim in dismay]
- [umpire] Thirty, forty.
[upbeat music playing]
- [man 1] All right.
- [woman 1] Hang in there.
[man 2] Let's go!
- [woman 2]
Yes, that's it, that's it!
- [man 3] Come on, Patrick.
[woman 3]
Yes, yes, the deuce!
- [woman 4] All right!
- [man 4] Yes!
[intense music playing]
[woman 5]
Donaldson! Let's go!
[woman 6]
Blame it on the court!
[woman 7] Whoo! [chuckles]
[Patrick breathing heavily]
- [line judge] Fault!
- [crowd gasp]
[Tashi gasps]
[crowd applauding]
[man 1]
Come on, get back in it.
[woman 1] No! Zweig!
[indistinct chattering]
[Tashi breathing heavily]
- [man 2] Come on!
- [man 3] Whoo, whoo!
[crowd murmuring]
[upbeat music playing]
[woman 2]
Come on, Patrick, let's play!
[Art breathing heavily]
Time violation.
Warning, Zweig.
[crowd chattering indistinctly]
[upbeat music continues]
[music drops]
- [ball thuds on court]
- [crowd exclaim]
[umpire] Deuce!
[crowd applauding]
[crowd shouting indistinctly]
- Fuck off!
- [crowd exclaim]
[umpire] Code violation,
audible obscenity.
Point penalty, Donaldson.
[umpire] Advantage, Zweig.
[Tashi sighs]
[intense music playing]
Art?
He can serve.
You need to
get into position.
[breathing heavily]
[man 4]
Come on, Art.
Let's go!
[exhaling]
- [Art] Serve.
- [pensive music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
- [umpire] Game, Zweig.
- [indistinct chattering]
Final set, tie break.
[crowd cheering]
[man 5] Come on,
let's do this.
Let's close it out.
Let's close it out, baby.
[music fades out]
[upbeat music playing]
[line judge 2 grunts]
[imperceptible]
[music fades out]
[upbeat music playing]
[music fades]
- [Art grunts]
- [ball thuds on racket]
[Art and Patrick grunting]
[panting]
[grunts]
[crowd cheering]
[Art and Patrick chuckling]
Come on!
Ah! [laughs]
[crowd cheering]