(GIRL SINGING EERILY)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (BELLS JINGLING)
- (CHILD LAUGHING)
(GIRL CONTINUES SINGING)
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
Sure I won't get in trouble, Bill?
(STUTTERS) Don't be a wuss.
I'd come with you if I weren't
(COUGHS) dying.
(SIGHS) You're not dying!
(STUTTERING) You didn't see the vomit
coming out of my nose this morning?
That's disgusting.
Okay. Go get the wax.
In the cellar?
You want it to float, don't you?
Fine.
(PIANO CONTINUES PLAYING)
(GROANS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FAINT METALLIC CLANGING)
BILL: (ON WALKIE-TALKIE) Georgie.
Hurry up.
(CLICKING SWITCH)
(WHISPERING) Okay. I'm brave.
(SIGHS)
Where's the wax?
There's the wax.
Yes.
(GEORGIE GRUNTS SOFTLY)
- (CRASHING)
- What was that? What's that?
Oh, jeez.
All right.
There you go.
(STUTTERING) She's all ready, Captain.
She?
You always call boats "she."
"She."
Thanks, Billy.
- (GEORGIE GIGGLES)
- (CHUCKLES)
See you later. Bye.
Be careful.
(GEORGIE CHUCKLING)
(CONTINUES CHUCKLING)
No!
Oh, Bill's gonna kill me.
(LOW GROWL)
(YELPS)
Hiya, Georgie.
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
What a nice boat.
Do you want it back?
Um, yes, please.
You look like a nice boy.
I bet you have a lot of friends.
Three, but my brother's my best best.
Where is he?
In bed. Sick.
I bet I can cheer him up.
I'll give him a balloon.
Do you want a balloon too, Georgie?
I'm not supposed to take stuff
from strangers.
Oh... Well, I'm Pennywise
the Dancing Clown.
"Pennywise?" "Yes."
"Meet Georgie.
"Georgie, meet Pennywise."
(CHUCKLES)
Now we aren't strangers, are we?
(WIND CHIMES TINKLING)
What are you doing in the sewer?
A storm blew me away.
Blew the whole circus away. (CHUCKLES)
Can you smell the circus, Georgie?
There's peanuts, cotton candy,
hot dogs,
and...
Popcorn?
Popcorn! (CHUCKLES) Is that your favorite?
- Uh-huh.
- Mine, too. (LAUGHS)
Because they pop.
Pop, pop, pop.
(GIGGLES)
- Pop.
- (BOTH LAUGHING)
(LOW GROWLING)
(WHIMPERS) I should get going now.
Oh.
Without your boat?
You don't wanna lose it, Georgie.
Bill's gonna kill you.
Here.
Take it.
Take it, Georgie.
(GROWLING)
(GEORGIE SCREAMING)
Help!
(CRYING)
(SCREAMS)
Billy! (ECHOES)
- (WIND CHIMES TINKLING)
- (CAT MEOWS)
(CHILDREN SINGING INDISTINCTLY)
(SHEEP BLEATING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
LEROY: Pull it, Mike.
Go on now, pull it.
(MIKE SIGHS)
Here, reload it.
You need to start taking
more responsibility around here, Mike.
Your dad was younger than you
when he took...
I'm not my dad, okay?
Yeah.
- (FLIES BUZZING)
- Look at me, son.
Look at me!
There are two places you can be
in this world.
You can be out here like us
or you can be in there,
like them.
You waste time hemming and hawing,
and someone else
is gonna make that choice for you.
Except you won't know it until
you feel that bolt between your eyes.
(SHEEP BLEATING)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
So, there's this church
full of Jews, right?
And Stan has to take this
super Jewy test.
But how's it work?
They slice the tip of his dick off.
But then Stan will have nothing left!
- That's true.
- Wait up, you guys!
Hey, Stan, what happens
at the Bar Mitzvah, anyways?
Ed says they slice
the tip of your (STUTTERS) dick off.
Yeah, and I think the rabbi's
gonna pull down your pants,
turn to the crowd and say,
"Where's the beef?"
(ALL CHUCKLE)
At the Bar Mitzvah,
I read from the Torah,
and then I make a speech
and suddenly, I become a man.
I could think of funner ways
to become a man.
STANLEY: "More fun" you mean.
RICHIE: Oh, shit.
Think they'll sign my yearbook?
"Dear Richie,"
"sorry for taking a hot, steaming dump
in your backpack last March."
"Have a good summer."
(KIDS CHATTERING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (DOOR BANGS)
GRETTA: Are you in there
by yourself, Beaver-ly?
Or do you have half the guys in the school
with you, huh, slut?
I know you're in there, little shit.
I can smell you.
No wonder you don 't have any friends.
Which is it, Gretta?
Am I a slut or a little shit?
Make up your mind.
You're trash.
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
We just wanted to remind you.
GIRL: Such a loser.
(GIRLS CONTINUE LAUGHING)
GRETTA: Well, at least now
you'll smell better.
GIRL: Gross.
Let's go, girls.
Have a nice summer, Beaver-ly.
- GIRL: Pathetic.
- (SIGHS)
(KIDS CHATTERING)
Best feeling ever.
Yeah?
Try tickling your pickle
for the first time.
Hey, what do you guys wanna do tomorrow?
I start my training.
- EDDIE: Wait, what training?
- Street Fighter.
Is that how you wanna spend your summer?
Inside of an arcade?
Beats spending it inside of your mother.
- Oh!
- What if we go to the quarry?
Guys, we have the (STUTTERS) Barrens.
Right.
Betty Ripsom's mom.
STANLEY: Is she really expecting to
see her come out of that school?
EDDIE: I don't know.
As if Betty Ripsom's been hiding
in Home Ec. For the last few weeks.
STANLEY: You think
they'll actually find her?
RICHIE: Sure.
In a ditch. All decomposed,
covered in worms and maggots.
Smelling like Eddie's mom's underwear.
Shut up! That's freaking disgusting.
She's not dead. (STUTTERS) She's missing.
Sorry, Bill. She's missing.
You know the Barrens aren't that bad.
Who doesn't love splashing around
in shitty water?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Nice Frisbee, flamer.
- Give it back!
- (LAUGHS)
PATRICK: Fucking losers!
(BURPS)
HENRY: Loser.
(STUTTERS) You suck, Bowers.
EDDIE: Shut up, Bill.
(STUTTERS MOCKINGLY)
You say something, Billy?
You got a free ride this year
'cause of your little brother.
Ride's over, Denbrough.
(INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
This summer's gonna be a hurt train
for you and your faggot friends.
(PATRICK LAUGHING)
I wish he'd go missing.
He's probably the one doing it.
(CAR ENGINE REVS)
You gonna let me go by?
Or is there a secret password
or something?
BEN: Oh.
- Um, sorry.
- Sorry isn't...
(CLATTERING)
A password.
Henry and his goons are over
by the west entrance.
So you should be fine.
Oh, I wasn't...
Everyone knows he's looking for you.
(SIGHS)
What you listening to?
(POP MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
New Kids on the Block.
I don't even like them. I was just...
Wait. You're the new kid, right?
Now I get it.
There's nothing to get.
I'm just messing with you.
I'm Beverly Marsh.
Yeah. I know that
'cause we're in the same class.
Social Studies. And you were...
I'm Ben. But pretty much
everybody just calls me...
The new kid.
Well, Ben, there are worse things
to be called.
Let me sign this.
Stay cool, Ben from sosh class.
Uh, yeah.
You too, Beverly.
BEVERLY: Hang tough, new kid on the block.
(CHUCKLES)
"Please Don't Go, Girl."
That's the name of another
New Kids on the Block song.
(POP MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES)
BILL: (STUTTERING) "He thrusts his fists
against the posts..."
"He thrusts his fists against..."
(CONTINUES STUTTERING) Shit!
"Post."
Need some help? I... (STUTTERS)
I thought we agreed.
- Before you say anything...
- Bill.
Just let me show you something first.
(WATER FLOW STOPS)
The Barrens.
(STUTTERING) It's the only place that
Georgie could have ended up.
He's gone, Bill.
But if the storm swept Georgie in,
we should have gone...
He's gone! He's dead!
He's dead! There is nothing we can do!
Nothing!
Now take this down
before your mother sees it.
Next time you wanna take something
from my office...
Ask.
I guess you get your tunnels back.
(SQUEAKING)
HENRY: Get in!
WOMAN: Creep!
(PANTING)
MIKE: Oh, Jesus.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SIGHS)
- (SOFT GROWL)
- (CHAIN RATTLING)
(CHAIN CLINKS)
WOMAN: Mike! (SCREAMS)
(WOMAN CONTINUES SCREAMING)
MAN: Hurry, son!
WOMAN: Help! It burns!
MAN: Mike!
(WOMAN CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(METALLIC CLANKING)
(DISTORTED GRUNTING)
(SHEEP BLEATING)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(MIKE GRUNTS)
(ROCK MUSIC BLASTING
ON CAR STEREO)
Stay the fuck outta my town!
- (TIRES SQUEAL)
- (BREATHING SHAKILY)
- (CHAIN RATTLES)
- (GASPS)
Mike?
- Are you okay?
- (CONTINUES BREATHING SHAKILY)
(STANLEY RECITING IN HEBREW)
(CONTINUES RECITING IN HEBREW)
(RABBI URIS CONTINUES IN HEBREW)
You're not studying, Stanley.
How's it going to look?
The rabbi's son
can't finish his own Torah reading.
Take the book to my office.
Obviously you're not using it.
(EXHALES)
(CLATTERING)
(LIGHT BUZZING)
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
(BREATHING RAGGEDLY)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(GASPS)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(METALLIC CLATTERING)
(GASPING)
(DISTORTED VOICES CHATTERING)
(LOW GROWL)
(SCREAMING)
EDDIE: Take everything
but the Delicious Deals, guys.
My mom loves them.
Hey! First you said the Barrens,
and now you're saying the sewer.
I mean, what if we get caught?
BILL: We won't, Eds.
(STUTTERS) The sewers are public works.
We're the public, aren't we?
Hey, Eddie,
these your birth control pills?
Yeah, and I'm saving it for your sister.
This is private stuff.
HOSTESS: (ON TV) Hello, and welcome to
the Derry Children's Hour.
Eddie Bear, where you boys off to
in such a rush?
Um... (STAMMERS)
(STUTTERS) Just my backyard, Mrs. K.
I got a new...
A new croquet set.
Jeez, spit it out, (MOCK STUTTERS) Bill!
Okay.
Oh, and sweetie, don't go
rolling around on the grass.
Especially if it's just been cut.
You know how bad your allergies can get.
Yes, Mom. Let's go.
MRS. KASPBRAK:
Aren't you forgetting something?
HOSTESS: Water is all around us.
It's even above us.
(EDDIE SIGHS)
Don't believe me?
Then try it yourself at home.
- (RICHIE CHUCKLES)
- Whenever you're outside...
Do you want one from me too, Mrs. K?
- I was kidding.
- EDDIE: No, no, no.
Sorry, Mommy.
"Your hair is winter fire,
January embers..."
"My heart burns there too."
RICHIE: Slow down!
BILL: Hi-ho, Silver!
Away!
RICHIE: Your old lady bike's
too fast for us!
LIBRARIAN: Found it.
Isn't it summer vacation?
I would think you'd be ready
to take a break from the books.
I like it in here.
A boy should be spending his summer
outside with friends.
Don't you have any friends?
Can I have the book now?
(PANTING)
(GIRL GIGGLES)
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(SIZZLING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(GIRL GIGGLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GIGGLING CONTINUES)
(CLATTERING)
(PANTING)
PENNYWISE: Egg boy.
- (GRUNTS)
- (GASPS)
LIBRARIAN: What on earth are you doing?
(PANTING)
Where are you off to, tits?
Gotcha.
- BEN: Wait.
- (BOYS CHATTERING)
HENRY: Fucking hold him.
BEN: Leave me alone!
PATRICK: Smack him.
HENRY: Don't let tubby get away.
BEN: Help!
HENRY: Get him! (LAUGHS)
- Hold him, Hockstetter.
- VICTOR: Get him, Belch.
(EXCLAIMING)
BEN: Stop!
- Just leave me alone.
- Look at all this blubber!
Let me light his hair,
like Michael Jackson.
HENRY: Just hold him.
Get off me! Get off me!
(CAR APPROACHING)
Help!
(BEN GRUNTING)
- (EARS RINGING)
- (MUFFLED YELLING)
Okay, new kid.
This is what us locals
call the Kissing Bridge.
It's famous for two things.
Sucking face,
(CHUCKLES)
and carving names.
Henry, please.
- (SCREAMS)
- (BULLIES LAUGHING)
Whoa, whoa! Henry!
Shut up!
I'm gonna carve my whole name
onto this cottage cheese!
(GRUNTING)
I'm gonna cut your fucking tits off.
I swear to God!
Get him!
Come on!
(GRUNTING)
Get him!
You can't run!
(BULLIES LAUGHING)
- Oh, no!
- HENRY: We need to find Fatty!
(GRUNTING)
My knife. My old man will kill me!
- You two, get him!
- PATRICK: Come on!
Move your fucking ass!
PATRICK: He's going that way! Come on!
(PANTING)
He's down there.
EDDIE: I don't know. I guess.
That's poison ivy.
And that's poison ivy.
Where? Where's the poison ivy?
Nowhere. Not every fucking plant
is poison ivy, Stanley.
EDDIE: Okay, I'm starting to get itchy now
and I'm pretty sure
this is not good for my...
RICHIE: Do you use the same bathroom
as your mother?
EDDIE: Sometimes, yeah.
RICHIE: Then you probably have crabs.
EDDIE: That's so not funny.
Aren't you guys coming in?
Uh-uh. It's greywater.
What the hell's greywater?
It's basically piss and shit.
So I'm just telling you,
you guys are splashing around
in millions of gallons of Derry pee. So...
Are you serious? What are you...
(IN SPANISH ACCENT)
Doesn't smell like caca to me, señor.
Okay, I can smell that from here.
It's probably just your breath
wafting back into your face.
(SCOFFS) Have you ever heard
of a staph infection?
Oh, I'll show you a staff infection.
EDDIE: This is so unsanitary.
You're literally...
This is literally like swimming
inside of a toilet bowl right now.
Have you ever heard of Listeria?
(SCREAMS)
(STAMMERS) Are you retarded?
You're the reason why
we're in this position right now.
BILL: Guys!
Shit. Don't tell me that's...
BILL: No.
(STUTTERS) Georgie wore galoshes.
EDDIE: Whose sneaker is it?
It's Betty Ripsom's.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God. Oh, fuck!
I don't like this.
How do you think Betty feels?
Running around these tunnels
with only one frickin' shoe?
(RICHIE CHUCKLES)
What if she's still here?
Eddie, come on!
My mom will have an aneurysm, if she
finds out that we're playing down here.
I'm serious.
Bill?
If... If I was Betty Ripsom,
I would want us to find me.
(STUTTERS) Georgie too.
What if I don't want to find them?
I mean, no offense, Bill,
but I don't want to end up like...
I don't want to go missing either.
- He has a point.
- (STUTTERS) You too?
It's summer.
We're supposed to be having fun.
This isn't fun.
This is scary and disgusting.
- (GRUNTS)
- (GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
Holy shit! What happened to you?
(CLATTERING)
(SPRAY CAN RATTLING)
(DISTANT CLATTERING)
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
I hear ya, tits.
Don't think you can stay down here
all damn day now.
VOICE: (WHISPERING) You found us, Patrick.
(VOICES WHISPERING)
You found us, Patrick.
- (GASPS)
- Patrick.
- (SCREAMING)
- (DISTORTED CHATTER)
(GIRL LAUGHS)
(GROANS)
(GASPING)
(PANTING)
Fuck!
(GIRL LAUGHING)
(CHILDREN SINGING)
- (SCREAMING)
- (YELLING)
EDDIE: I think it's great that
we're helping the new kid,
but also we need to think
of our own safety.
I mean, he's bleeding all over
and you guys know
that there's an AIDS epidemic happening
right now as we speak, right?
My mom's friend in New York City got it
by touching a dirty pole on the subway.
And a drop of AIDS blood got into
his system through a hangnail. A hangnail!
And you can amputate legs and arms.
But how do you amputate a waist?
You guys do know that alleys are known
for dirty needles that have AIDS, right?
You guys do know that?
- Hey...
- Ah, we're screwed.
Richie, wait here. Come on.
Glad I got to meet you
before you died.
Okay.
BILL: Can we afford all that?
It's all we got.
You kidding me?
Wait, you have an account here,
don't you?
If my mom finds out
I bought all this stuff for myself...
I'm spending the whole rest of the weekend
in the emergency room getting X-rayed.
(MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY
ON SPEAKERS)
GRETTA: See you later, Dad.
KEENE: See you, Gretta.
BILL: You okay?
I'm fine. What's wrong with you?
None of your business.
There's a kid outside.
Looked like someone killed him.
(STUTTERS) We need some supplies,
but we don't have enough money.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
I like your glasses, Mr. Keene.
You look just like Clark Kent.
Oh. (LAUGHING)
I don't know about that.
Can I try them?
Mmm. Sure.
(BEVERLY CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
What do you think?
Well, how about that?
You look just like Lois Lane.
(CHUCKLES) Really?
Mmm.
Well, here you go.
(CLATTERING)
Shoot, I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
(EDDIE GRUNTS)
(DOORBELL JINGLES)
RICHIE: Just suck the wound.
EDDIE: I need to focus right now.
RICHIE: You need to focus?
EDDIE: Yeah, can you go get me something?
- Jesus! What do you need?
- Go get my bifocals.
I hid 'em in my second fanny pack.
STANLEY: Why do you have two fanny packs?
EDDIE: I need to focus right now
and it's a long story.
I don't want to get into it.
BILL: (STUTTERS) Um, thanks.
Even-steven.
STANLEY: Oh, God, he's bleeding.
Oh, my God!
Ben from sosh?
RICHIE: You have to suck the wound
before you apply the Band-Aids.
- This is 101.
- You don't know what you're talking about.
Are you okay?
That looks like it hurts.
Oh. No, I'm good. I just fell.
Yeah, right into Henry Bowers.
(STUTTERING) Shut it, Richie.
Why? It's the truth.
You sure they got the right stuff
to fix you up?
You know, we'll take care of him.
Uh, thanks again, Beverly.
Sure. Maybe I'll see you around.
(CONTINUES STUTTERING)
Yeah, we were thinking about
going to the quarry tomorrow,
if you wanna
come.
Good to know. Thanks.
Nice going bringing up Bowers
in front of her.
Yeah, dude, you heard what she did.
What'd she do?
More like "Who'd she do?"
From what I hear,
the list is longer than my wang.
That's not saying much.
(STUTTERS) They're just rumors.
Anyway, Bill had her
back in third grade.
They kissed in the school play.
The reviews said you can't fake
that sort of passion.
(IN BRITISH ACCENT) Now, pip-pip
and tally-ho, my good fellows,
I do believe this chap requires
our utmost attention.
Get in there, Dr. K.
Come on, fix him up.
Why don't you shut the fuck up,
Einstein, because I know what I'm doing
and I don't want you doing
the British guy with me right now.
(IN BRITISH ACCENT)
Suck the wound. Get in there.
HOSTESS: (ON TV)
Toilet and bath water travel down
- the drains and into the sewer.
- (DOOR OPENS)
The sewer is a fun place to play
with all of your friends.
Just follow the water into the drains
and down into the sewers you go.
When you're with your friends in the
sewers, you can be as silly as a clown!
That's right, it's the word of the day.
Hi, Daddy.
Hey, Bevvie.
Whatcha got there?
Just some things.
Like what?
(PLASTIC RUSTLES)
(SNIFFING)
Tell me you're still my little girl.
Yes, Daddy.
Good.
ANNOUNCER: (ON TV) A deep fly ball
to the left. His last at bat.
He scratched the foul pole.
Wade Boggs, of course,
leads the league in hitting so far.
(BEVERLY SOBBING)
(FAUCET SPUTTERING)
(SNIFFLES)
This is what you did.
This is what you... (GRUNTS)
This is...
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
(BOYS CLEARING THROATS)
EDDIE: Lay it out.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, my God.
- So easy.
- Poor tree.
So easy!
Oh, my God, that was terrible.
I win.
- You won?
- Yeah.
- Did you see my loogie?
- That went the farthest!
- It's by distance.
- Mass. It's always been mass.
(STAMMERS) What is mass?
Who cares how far it goes?
It matters how cool it looks, like it's
green or it's white or juicy and fat.
- All right.
- Thanks for that.
- Who's first?
- That was terrible.
BEVERLY: I'll go!
Sissies.
RICHIE: What the fuck!
Oh, holy shit! We just got showed up
by a girl.
Do we have to do that now?
Yes.
BEVERLY: Come on!
Oh, shit.
(WHOOPING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
RICHIE: I already won! We already won!
(ALL LAUGHING)
They're down! Yes!
(EXCLAIMING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
RICHIE: Ah, fuck! What was that?
STANLEY: Something just touched my foot
right here.
That work?
- Where are we looking?
- Right here, right here!
It's a turtle.
(UPBEAT RAP MUSIC PLAYING
ON CASSETTE PLAYER)
- (ALL GASP)
- (BOYS CLEAR THROATS)
News flash, Ben. School's out for summa!
Oh, that? That's not school stuff.
RICHIE: Who sent you this?
BEN: No one. Give it...
No one.
RICHIE: What's with the history project?
BEN: Oh...
When I first moved here,
I didn't have anyone to hang out with,
so I just started spending time
in the library.
RICHIE: You went to the library?
On purpose?
BEVERLY: Oh, I wanna see.
STANLEY: What's The Black Spot?
EDDIE: The Black Spot was a nightclub
that was burned down years ago
by that racist cult.
STANLEY: The what?
EDDIE: Don't you watch Geraldo?
(STUTTERS) Your hair...
Your... Your hair
is beautiful, Beverly.
Oh.
Right. Thanks.
RICHIE: Here, pass it.
Why is it all murders and missing kids?
Derry's not like any town
I've ever been in before.
They did a study once,
and it turns out
people die or disappear
six times the national average.
You read that?
BEN: And that's just grown-ups.
Kids are worse.
Way, way worse.
I've got more stuff if you wanna see it.
(SOFTLY) No, no.
(PANTING)
EDDIE: Don't freak out, just tell us.
RICHIE: Yeah. I heard he has
a rollercoaster and a pet chimp
and an old guy's fucking bones.
Yeah.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wow.
Cool, huh?
No. No, nothing cool.
There's nothing cool.
This is cool, right here.
Wait, no. No, it's not cool.
What's that?
Oh, that? That's the charter
for Derry Township.
Nerd alert.
No, actually, it's really interesting.
Derry started as a beaver trapping camp.
Still is, am I right, boys?
Ninety-one people signed the charter
that made Derry.
But later that winter,
they all disappeared without a trace.
The entire camp?
BEN: There were rumors of Indians,
but no sign of an attack.
Everybody just thought
it was a plague or something.
But it's like
one day everybody just woke up and left.
The only clue was a trail of
bloody clothes leading to the well house.
RICHIE: Jesus. We can get Derry
on Unsolved Mysteries.
(DOOR CREAKING)
EDDIE: Let's do that. You're brilliant.
RICHIE: I might be.
(BOYS CHATTERING)
RICHIE: I don't know.
Maybe he's just trying to
make some friends, Stanley.
Where was the well house?
I don't know.
Somewhere in town, I guess.
Why?
Nothing.
(CHOIR SINGING SPIRITUAL SONG)
Nobody knows the trouble I've seen
Nobody knows my sorrow
(EDDIE PLAYING HAND FLUTE)
(WATCH BEEPING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(GROWLING)
HOARSE MALE VOICE: Eddie...
What are you looking for?
- (PILLBOX RATTLES)
- Oh!
(SOFTLY) Fuck.
My mom's gonna fucking flip.
(EDDIE MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY)
Do you think this will help me, Eddie?
(GROWLING AND MUMBLING
INDISTINCTLY)
- (GASPS)
- (GROWLING)
(EDDIE WHIMPERING)
(CONTINUES GROWLING)
Help! Help!
(ROARING)
(EDDIE SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
Where you going, Eds?
If you lived here, you'd be home by now.
Come join the clown, Eds.
You'll float down here.
We all float down here.
Yes, we do.
(LAUGHING)
(SCREAMING)
(DISTORTED LAUGHTER)
(BALLOONS POPPING)
(LOCK CLICKS)
BEVERLY: (WHISPERING)
"Your hair is winter fire..."
"January embers..."
"My heart burns there, too."
GIRL: Beverly...
(WATER DRIPPING)
Beverly.
Help me.
Help me, please.
VOICES: (ECHOING)
We all want to meet you, Beverly.
We all float down here.
BEVERLY: Hello? Who are you?
VERONICA: I'm Veronica.
BETTY: Betty Ripsom.
PATRICK: Patrick Hockstetter.
VERONICA: Come closer.
BETTY: Wanna see?
VERONICA: We float.
PATRICK: (HOARSELY) We change.
(DISTORTED GIGGLING)
- (TAPE RATTLES)
- (GIRL GIGGLING)
(SIGHS)
(SCREAMS)
(WHIMPERS)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
Daddy!
Help!
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERING)
(SOBBING)
(SOBBING AND SCREAMING)
The hell's going on?
(STUTTERING SHAKILY)
The sink...
(CONTINUES STUTTERING)
And the blood... It's...
What blood?
The sink. You don't see it?
(STAMMERING)
There was blood.
(MUMBLES SHAKILY)
You worry me, Bevvie.
You worry me a lot.
(SOFTLY) But don't you see?
Why'd you do this to your hair?
Makes you look like a boy.
(SOBBING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(SWITCH CLICKS)
(PUTS DOWN BUCKET)
(SOBBING SOFTLY)
(FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
(GASPS)
(SOFTLY) Georgie.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(STAIRS CREAKING)
GEORGIE: I lost it, Billy.
Don't be mad.
(STUTTERS) I'm not mad at you.
GEORGIE: It just floated off.
But, Bill, if you'll come with me,
you'll float, too.
Georgie.
You'll float, too.
(CHUCKLING) You'll float, too.
(IN HARSH VOICE) You'll float, too.
You'll float, too. You'll float, too.
You'll float, too.
(DISTORTED) You'll float, too!
You'll float, too!
(ROARING)
STANLEY: No, we gotta go
through the alleyway.
EDDIE: The alley takes way too long.
STANLEY: No, the alley is so much faster.
EDDIE: The alley is more dangerous
and it's disgusting.
STANLEY: How is it more dangerous?
EDDIE: It smells like piss and it's gross.
- Just take the side streets for once.
- STANLEY: Oh, my God.
The side streets are the same.
They smell like piss and shit.
EDDIE: Okay, okay. Can you just tell me
what she said exactly?
STANLEY: She didn't say anything.
She just said that
you guys need to hurry over.
EDDIE: She didn't say
anything. Okay. Okay.
BEVERLY: You made it. I...
I need to show you something.
What is it?
More than we saw at the quarry?
Shut up! Just shut up, Richie.
My dad will kill me if he finds out
I had boys in the apartment.
Then we'll leave a lookout.
(STUTTERS) Richie, stay here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What if her dad comes back?
Do what you always do. Start talking.
It is a gift.
In there.
STANLEY: What is it?
BEVERLY: You'll see.
EDDIE: Are you taking us
to your bathroom?
I just want you to know that 89%
of the worst accidents in homes
are caused in bathrooms.
(STUTTERING)
And, I mean, that's where
all the bacteria and fungi are
and it's not a really sanitary place...
(MUMBLES)
- (DOOR CREAKING OPEN)
- (EDDIE WHIMPERING)
I knew it! (GAGS)
BEVERLY: You see it?
EDDIE: Yes.
STANLEY: What...
What happened in here?
My dad couldn't see it.
I thought I might be crazy.
BEN: Well, if you're crazy,
then we're all crazy.
(STUTTERS)
We can't leave it like this.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(EXCLAIMS)
- (BEVERLY CHUCKLES)
- BILL: All right, so you've
never been
to the Derry Summer Fair?
- No, I don't think so.
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
Not that I know of.
BILL: Well, I go there every year,
but I was there one time with Richie and
technically won 'cause I hit the target.
But there were so many prizes,
I didn't know which to pick.
It's not true, you know.
What they say about me.
I was only ever kissed by one guy.
It was a long time ago.
It was a nice kiss though.
"January embers."
(STUTTERING)
Was that in the play?
No, the poem.
Oh... (CHUCKLES)
(STUTTERING) Oh,
I don't really know much poetry.
Oh. I was just...
Never mind then.
Um...
Just so you know, I...
I never believed any of the rumors.
(STUTTERING) And none of us Losers do.
We like hanging with you.
Thanks.
You shouldn't thank us too much.
Hanging out with us
makes you a Loser, too.
(LAUGHS)
I can take that.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
RICHIE: No, I love being
your personal doorman, really.
Could you idiots have taken any longer?
EDDIE: All right, shut up, Richie.
STANLEY: Yeah, shut up, Richie.
Oh, okay, trash the trashmouth,
I get it.
Hey, I wasn't the one
scrubbing the bathroom floor
and imagining that her sink went all
Eddie's mom's vagina on Halloween.
She didn't imagine it.
I...
(STUTTERS) I saw something, too.
STANLEY: You saw blood, too?
Not blood.
(STUTTERS) I saw Georgie.
It seemed so real.
I mean, it seemed like him,
but there was this...
The clown.
Yeah, I saw him, too.
Wait, can only virgins see this stuff?
Is that why I'm not seeing this shit?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING
IN DISTANCE)
EDDIE: Oh, shit,
that's Belch Huggins' car.
- We should probably get outta here.
- RICHIE: Yeah.
Wait, isn't that
the homeschooled kid's bike?
EDDIE: Yeah, that's Mike's.
We have to help him.
RICHIE: We should?
Yes.
- HENRY: Come on.
- (STRAINING)
Eat that meat!
- Eat it, bitch!
- You little fucker!
- Bitch!
- Motherfucker!
BELCH: Eat it, you little bitch!
VICTOR: Pussy!
BELCH: Fucking...
Whatcha gonna do, huh?
Get up!
Get the fuck up!
(LAUGHS)
VICTOR: You little fucker!
(YELLS)
(PANTING)
(GROANING)
Come on, Henry, smack him!
- (HENRY GRUNTS)
- You little bitch.
- Nice throw.
- Thanks.
HENRY: You losers
are trying too hard.
She'll do you.
You just gotta ask nicely,
- like I did.
- (LAUGHS)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
What the fuck?
(GRUNTING)
HENRY: Come on, get 'em! Fuck!
Rock war! (GRUNTS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
HENRY: Get 'em!
STANLEY: Watch out!
RICHIE: Fuck you, motherfuckers!
BILL: Eddie!
- RICHIE: Fuck outta here!
- Ow!
Ah, shit!
Fuck you, bitch!
EDDIE: Come on, guys!
Let's get 'em!
VICTOR: Fuck this.
BELCH: Fuck out of here.
VICTOR: Fuck you, losers!
(PANTING)
Go blow your dad,
you mullet-wearing asshole!
Thanks, guys,
but you shouldn't have done that.
They'll be after you guys, too, now.
Oh, no, no, no. Bowers?
He's always after us.
(STUTTERS) I guess that's one thing
we all have in common.
Yeah, Homeschool.
Welcome to the Losers' Club.
(EXCITED CHATTER)
WOMAN: Right there.
(PLAYING TUBA)
STANLEY: They say they found
part of his hand
all chewed up near the Standpipe.
He asked to borrow a pencil once.
(STUTTERS) It's like she's been forgotten
because Corcoran's missing.
(RICHIE CONTINUES
PLAYING TUBA)
Is it ever gonna end?
RICHIE: What the fuck, dude?
What are you guys talking about?
What they always talk about.
I actually think it will end.
For a little while, at least.
What do you mean?
So I was going over
all my Derry research
and I charted out all the big events.
The Ironworks explosion in 1908,
the Bradley Gang in '35,
and The Black Spot in '62.
And now kids being...
I realized this stuff seems to happen...
BOTH: Every 27 years.
EDDIE: Okay, so, let me get this straight.
It comes out from wherever
to eat kids for, like, a year?
And then what?
It just goes into hibernation?
Maybe it's like...
What do you call it?
Cicadas.
You know, the bugs that come out
once every 17 years.
My grandfather thinks
this town is cursed.
He says that
all the bad things
that happen in this town
are because of one thing.
An evil thing that feeds off
the people of Derry.
But it can't be one thing.
We all saw something different.
MIKE: Maybe.
Or maybe It knows what scares us most
and that's what we see.
(STUTTERS) I saw a leper.
He was like a walking infection.
But you didn't.
Because it isn't real.
None of this is.
Not Eddie's leper
(STUTTERING) or Bill seeing Georgie
or the woman I keep seeing.
She hot?
No, Richie.
She's not hot.
Her face is all messed up.
None of this makes any sense.
They're all like bad dreams.
I don't think so. I know the difference
between a bad dream and real life, okay?
What'd you see?
You saw something, too?
MIKE: Yes.
Do you guys know that burned-down house
on Harris Avenue?
I was inside when it burned down.
Before I was rescued,
my mom and dad were trapped
in the next room over from me.
They were pushing
and pounding on the door,
(WOMAN SCREAMING FAINTLY)
trying to get to me.
MAN: Hurry, son!
WOMAN: It burns!
But it was too hot.
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
When the firemen finally found them,
the skin on their hands had
melted down to the bone.
We're all afraid of something.
- (CRACKER WHIZZES)
- Got that right.
EDDIE: Why, Rich?
What are you afraid of?
(CRACKERS BURSTING)
Clowns.
BILL: Okay.
Look.
(STUTTERS)
That's where Georgie disappeared.
There's the Ironworks.
And The Black Spot.
Everywhere it happens,
it's all connected by the sewers.
And they all meet up at the...
The well house.
It's in the house on Neibolt Street.
You mean that creepy-ass house where
all the junkies and hobos like to sleep?
- (GASPING)
- BEVERLY: I hate that place.
It always feels like it's watching me.
EDDIE: That's where I saw It.
That's where I saw the clown.
(STUTTERS) That's where It lives.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
STANLEY: I can't imagine anything
ever wanting to live there.
EDDIE: Can we stop talking about this?
(STUTTERING)
I can barely breathe.
This is summer.
We're kids. I can barely breathe.
I'm up here having
a fucking asthma attack.
(GASPS) I'm not doing this.
What the hell? Put the map back.
Mmm-mmm.
(PROJECTOR CLICKING)
What happened?
STANLEY: What's going on?
MIKE: I got it. Hold on.
Guys.
BILL: Georgie.
STANLEY: Bill?
(PROJECTOR CLICKING RAPIDLY)
(ALL GASPING)
RICHIE: What the fuck?
BILL: It's It!
What the fuck is that?
I don't fucking know!
(ALL WHIMPERING)
Turn it off! Turn it off!
RICHIE: Yeah. Yeah,
turn it off. Turn it off!
(ALL PANTING)
- (GROWLS)
- (ALL SCREAM)
- (LAUGHS)
- RICHIE: Run, Stanley!
(ALL SCREAMING)
EDDIE: What is it?
RICHIE: What the fuck?
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALL PANTING)
Thanks, Ben.
EDDIE: It saw us.
It saw us, and it knows where we are.
It always did.
So, let's go.
BEN: Go?
Go where?
Neibolt.
(STUTTERS) That's where Georgie is.
After that?
Yeah, it's summer.
We should be outside.
If you say it's summer
one more fucking time...
BEVERLY: Bill!
Wait!
(STUTTERS) "He thrusts his fists"
"against the posts"
"and still insists he sees..."
BEVERLY: Bill!
Bill, you can't go in there.
This is crazy.
Look, you don't have to come in with me.
But what happens when
another Georgie goes missing?
Or another Betty?
Or another Ed Corcoran? Or one of us?
Are you just gonna pretend it isn't
happening like everyone else in this town?
Because I can't.
I go home, and all I see is
that Georgie isn't there.
His clothes, his toys,
his stupid stuffed animals, but...
He isn't.
So walking into this house,
for me,
it's easier
than walking into my own.
RICHIE: Wow.
BEN: What?
He didn't stutter once.
Wait!
Um...
Shouldn't we have some people
keep watch?
You know, just in case
something bad happens?
(STUTTERS) Who wants to stay out here?
(SIGHS) Fuck.
(DOOR CREAKING OPEN)
RICHIE: I can't believe
I pulled the short straw.
You guys are lucky
you're not measuring dicks.
EDDIE: Shut up, Richie.
I can smell it.
RICHIE: Don't breathe through your mouth.
How come?
Because then you're eating it.
- (EDDIE GAGGING)
- (UNZIPS FANNY PACK)
- (INHALER HISSES)
- (EDDIE INHALING SHARPLY)
What?
It... It says I'm missing.
(STUTTERS)
You're not missing, Richie.
RICHIE: "Police department,
City of Derry."
That's my shirt. That's my hair.
That's my face.
Calm down, this isn't real.
That's my name. That's my age!
That's the date!
It can't be real, Richie.
No, it says it! What the fuck?
- Am I missing? Am I gonna go missing?
- Calm down. Calm down.
Look at me, Richie. Look at me.
That... That isn't real.
It's playing tricks on you.
GIRL: Hello?
Hello?
Help me, please!
(GIRL GASPING)
(RATS SQUEAKING)
(GIRL CHOKING)
(GIRL COUGHING)
(GASPS AND COUGHS)
Betty?
Ripsom?
- (SCREAMS)
- (ALL GASP)
(ALL BREATHING SHAKILY)
HOBO: Eddie...
What are you looking for?
Guys, can you hear that?
(BREATHING RAGGEDLY)
RICHIE: She was just here.
Where the fuck did she go?
(EXHALES SHARPLY) Guys.
- (DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
- (GROWLING)
EDDIE: (GASPING)
Oh, my God.
Guys. Guys!
(DOOR SLAMS)
- Guys! Guys!
- What? Eddie?
(SCREAMS) What the fuck?
(PANTING)
HOBO: Time to take
your pill, Eddie.
(GROWLING)
(WHIMPERING)
(WATCH BEEPING)
(GROANS)
(DOOR JAMMING)
- Eddie. Open the door!
- BOY: Richie.
BILL: You okay?
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Eddie, what's going on?
Eds.
Eddie.
BOY: Come here, Richie.
(LAUGHS)
Eddie.
Where the fuck are you?
We're not playing hide-and-seek, dipshit.
BILL: Richie?
Richie! Richie!
Bill, come on, open the door.
It won't open!
- What's going on? Richie!
- I can't!
- (DOOR JAMMING)
- BILL: Open the door, Rich.
(BREATHING RAGGEDLY)
RICHIE: Oh, shit.
(EERIE LAUGHTER)
(LAUGHTER CONTINUES)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
(RICHIE GASPING)
(LIGHTS BUZZING)
Stupid clowns.
Oh, fuck.
(SQUELCHING)
Ugh!
- (YELLING)
- (SCREAMS)
Beep-beep, Richie.
- (YELLS)
- (SCREAMING)
Let's get outta here.
(GRUNTS AND LAUGHTER)
You wanna play loogie?
(RETCHING)
- (DISTORTED LAUGHTER)
- (RATTLING)
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
(WINCES)
(TAPPING)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
- (PENNYWISE LAUGHING)
- (WHIMPERING)
(GRUNTING)
(PENNYWISE LAUGHING)
Time to float.
(WHIMPERING)
(MOCK GASPING)
(CONTINUES GASPING)
(SCREAMS)
- (EXCLAIMING)
- (WHIMPERING AND SOBBING)
(PENNYWISE LAUGHING)
- (IMITATES SOBBING)
- (SOBBING)
BETTY: Where's my shoe?
(BOTH SCREAM)
Where the fuck were her legs?
Holy shit, what the fuck was that?
This isn't real.
Remember the missing kid poster.
That wasn't real, so this isn't real.
- Tasty, tasty, beautiful fear.
- (WHIMPERING)
Come on. Ready?
RICHIE: No!
EDDIE: No.
- (GROWLING)
- (WHIMPERING)
EDDIE: No, no!
Oh, thank fuck.
BILL: Where's Eddie?
EDDIE: Help!
Help!
RICHIE: Eddie!
Holy fuck.
Eddie!
This isn't real enough for you, Billy?
I'm not real enough for you?
Oh, shit.
It was real enough for Georgie.
(PENNYWISE LAUGHS)
(ROARING)
- RICHIE: Holy shit!
- (YELLS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (BOTH GASP)
(WAILING)
- Get Eddie!
- (EDDIE SCREAMING)
- (ALL CLAMORING)
(GROWLS)
Oh, fuck! We gotta get out of here!
(BOYS SCREAMING)
(DEEP GROWLING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
BILL: Get Eddie. Let's go!
RICHIE: Guys, watch out!
- EDDIE: No, no, no, no!
- Eddie, look at me!
EDDIE: He's gonna get us!
Guys!
No! (SCREAMS)
- (SCREAMS)
- (YELPS)
(LAUGHING)
- (GROANS)
- BILL: Ben!
RICHIE: Ben!
- (GRUNTING)
- (KIDS CLAMORING)
RICHIE: Let's get out of here!
Don't let him get away!
(ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
BEVERLY: Bill,
we have to help Eddie!
No! No!
RICHIE: I'm gonna snap your arm
into place.
Rich, do not fucking touch me.
- Okay, one, two, three.
- Do not touch me!
- (BONES CRACK)
- (SCREAMS)
- (KIDS CLAMORING)
- MIKE: Holy shit!
You. You did this.
You know how delicate he is.
- (STUTTERS) We were attacked, Mrs. K.
- No. Don't.
Don't try and blame anyone else.
- Let me help.
- Get back!
Oh, I've heard of you, Miss Marsh.
And I don't want a dirty girl like you
touching my son.
Mrs. K, I... (STUTTERS)
No! You are all monsters.
All of you.
And Eddie is done with you.
Do you hear? Done!
(ENGINE STARTS)
I saw the well.
(STUTTERS) We know where it is
and next time we'll be better prepared.
No!
No next time, Bill.
- You're insane.
- BEVERLY: Why?
We all know no one else
is going to do anything.
Eddie was nearly killed!
And look at this motherfucker.
He's leaking Hamburger Helper!
BEVERLY: We can't pretend
it's gonna go away.
Ben, you said it yourself,
It comes back every 27 years.
Fine! I'll be 40 and far away from here.
I thought you said you wanted to
get out of this town, too.
Because I wanna run towards something.
Not away.
I'm sorry, who invited Molly Ringwald
into the group?
- Richie...
- I'm just saying, let's face facts.
Real world.
Georgie is dead.
Stop trying to get us killed, too.
Georgie's not dead.
You couldn't save him,
but you can still save yourself.
(STUTTERS) No, take it back.
You're scared and we all are,
but take it back!
BEVERLY: Bill!
RICHIE: You're just a bunch of losers!
- Fuck off!
- STANLEY: Richie, stop.
You're just a bunch of losers
and you'll get yourselves killed
- trying to catch a fucking stupid clown.
- Stop!
This is what It wants.
It wants to divide us.
We were all together when we hurt It.
That's why we're still alive.
Yeah? Well, I plan to keep it that way.
- Mike...
- Guys...
I can't do this.
My granddad was right.
I'm an outsider.
Gotta stay that way.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(FIRES GUN)
(GUNSHOT)
- Yeah! Bonus!
- Yeah, there we go.
Put the next target out there.
(CAT MEOWS)
- Just hold it.
- (CAT MEOWING)
What the hell's going on here?
Just cleaning your gun, like you asked.
You're cleaning my gun, huh?
- Dad...
- Hey!
- (HENRY WHIMPERING)
- Look at him now, boys.
Ain't nothing like a little fear
to make a paper man crumble.
(MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY
ON SPEAKERS)
KEENE: Here for the refills, Eddie?
Yeah.
GRETTA: You know
it's all bullshit, right?
What is?
Your medication.
They're placebos.
What's placebo mean?
Placebo means bullshit.
No friends, huh?
Your cast.
No signatures or anything?
So sad.
I didn't want it to get dirty.
I'll sign it for you.
VICTOR: You okay, Henry?
(KIDS LAUGHING IN DISTANCE)
(LAUGHTER CONTINUES)
HOSTESS: (ON TV) And this is my most
favorite part of the afternoon.
Getting to know all about
so many of you.
Is there someone here
that wants to share with us
- what they most enjoyed about today?
- GIRL: Me!
HOSTESS: How about you?
GIRL: I liked seeing the clown.
HOSTESS: You did?
You liked the clown?
KIDS: Yes!
HOSTESS: What about the rest of you?
BOY: I liked when the bubbles float.
HOSTESS: You did? Me too.
I just love watching things float.
BOYS: We all float.
That's right.
And you will, too, Henry.
Make it a wonderful day.
Kill him.
ALL: Kill him. Kill him.
Kill him. Kill him.
(KNIFE CLICKS)
ANNOUNCER: Oh, no.
Give a big round of applause!
(OFFICER BOWERS GROANING)
(HENRY PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
HOSTESS: Well done, Henry.
Kill them all. Kill them all.
Kill them all!
Kill them all! Kill them all!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
KIDS: Kill them all! Kill them all!
Kill them all!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
MR. MARSH: Where are you
sneaking off to?
(STAMMERS) Nowhere, Daddy.
You're looking prettied up.
I'm not prettied up, Daddy.
I wear this almost every day.
Come.
You know I worry about you, Bevvie.
I know.
People in town have been
saying some things to me about you.
Sneaking around all summer long
with a bunch of boys.
The only girl in the pack.
They're just friends, I swear.
I know what's in boys' minds
when they look at you, Bevvie.
I know all too well.
My hand...
Are you doing womanly things
down in the woods with those boys?
No, no, no, nothing.
You don't have to worry. I promise.
What's this?
It's nothing. It's just a poem.
Just a poem?
But you had to hide it
in your underwear drawer.
Why would you have to hide it there?
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
Are you still my girl?
No.
MR. MARSH: What did you say?
I said, no!
- (GRUNTS)
- (BEVERLY YELPS)
No!
Get away, no!
(SCREAMING)
Get off!
No!
(GASPING)
Those boys.
Do they know that you're my...
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
(PANTING)
(DOORKNOB RATTLES)
(GRUNTS)
- (YELLS)
- (GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROANING SOFTLY)
BILL: Beverly?
(GROANING)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
Beverly!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- BILL: Richie.
- What do you want?
See that guy I'm hitting?
I'm pretending it's you.
(STUTTERS) It got Beverly.
What are you talking about?
It, Richie.
It got Beverly.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
Okay.
(SIGHS)
I'll meet you there.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
And just where do you think
you're off to?
Out with my friends.
Sweetie, you can't go.
You're getting over
your sickness, remember?
My sickness?
Okay, what sickness, Ma?
You know what these are?
They're gazebos!
They're bullshit!
(PILLS CLATTERING)
They help you, Eddie.
I had to protect you.
Protect me?
By lying to me? By keeping me locked
inside this hellhole?
I'm sorry but the only people that were
actually trying to protect me
were my friends.
And you made me turn my back on them
when I really needed them.
So I'm going.
Eddie. Eddie. No.
You get back here.
- Sorry, Mom, I gotta go save my friends.
- (SOBBING) Eddie!
Don't do this to me, Eddie!
Guys, spikes.
(GRUNTS)
(RAT SQUEAKING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
BEN: Stan?
Stan, we all have to go.
(STUTTERS) Beverly was right.
If we split up like last time,
that clown will kill us one by one.
But if we stick together,
all of us,
we'll win.
I promise.
RICHIE: Hey, Eddie, you got a quarter?
I wouldn't want to make a wish
in that fucking thing.
Beverly? (ECHOES)
MIKE: How are we supposed to
get down there?
All right. Come on.
(RATTLING)
All right.
(GRUNTS)
(BILL GRUNTING)
- (STRAINING)
- (METAL CREAKING)
(WHISPERS) Guys, guys. Help.
- RICHIE: All right, buddy?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
(GRUNTING)
PENNYWISE: (ON SPEAKERS) Step right up,
Beverly. Step right up.
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING)
Come change. Come float.
You'll laugh. You'll cry.
You'll cheer. You'll die.
Introducing Pennywise the Dancing Clown.
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
(MUSIC BOX CONTINUES PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(LAUGHS)
(CIRCUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC PLAYING DISTORTEDLY)
(PENNYWISE LAUGHING)
(STRUGGLING)
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
I'm not afraid of you.
(SNIFFS)
(GRUNTING)
You will be.
(BOY SCREAMING)
BOY: Help! Help me!
(MIKE SIGHING)
(EXHALES)
- (GRUNTS)
- Ahhh!
HENRY: Die!
BEN: Mike!
STANLEY: Mike!
EDDIE: Mike!
STANLEY: You okay? Mike!
RICHIE: Bowers.
Mike. Fuck.
(LAUGHS)
BILL: Mike!
BEN: Where is he?
(LAUGHS)
RICHIE: We're next.
STANLEY: No, no, no!
- Grab it!
- EDDIE: Get the rope! Get the rope!
Oh, shit.
BILL: Mike!
RICHIE: Mike!
Leave him alone!
You didn't listen to what I told you,
did you?
You should've stayed out of Derry.
Your parents didn't
and look what happened to them.
I still get sad every time
I pass by that pile of ashes.
Sad,
that I couldn't have done it myself.
STANLEY: Run, Mike!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
ALL: Mike!
HENRY: Fuck down!
(STUTTERS) I should get up there.
Are you insane? With what?
(COCKS GUN)
(GRUNTS)
(HENRY BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
(YELLING)
(HENRY YELLING)
RICHIE: Holy shit.
BILL: Oh, my...
EDDIE: Mike!
I'm okay.
- (ALL EXHALE)
- I'm okay.
Shoot!
BEVERLY: Stanley.
STANLEY: Beverly?
Is that you?
(PENNYWISE LAUGHING)
(GASPING)
(METAL CLANGS)
Guys?
EDDIE: What?
RICHIE: Guys, where's Stan?
EDDIE: Stanley!
Stanley!
Stan!
Oh, shit. Greywater.
Stan?
BILL: Stan?
EDDIE: Stanley!
(FOOTSTEPS)
(GASPS)
- (FOOTSTEPS)
- (GASPS)
(FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
(SCREAMING)
(STANLEY SCREAMS)
MIKE: Stan!
RICHIE: Shit! Stan!
EDDIE: Stanley!
- We're coming, man!
- We're coming! Don't worry.
(ALL STRAINING)
BILL: Stan?
EDDIE: Stanley! Stan!
His flashlight!
(ALL GASP)
RICHIE: What the fuck is that thing?
Oh, shit.
(EDDIE SCREAMS)
(ALL EXCLAIMING
AND WHIMPERING)
RICHIE: Oh, shit.
(SCREAMS)
(BOYS SCREAM)
Oh, shit!
Stanley!
BILL: Stanley! Stan!
EDDIE: Stanley!
(SCREAMING) No! No! No!
- (ALL CLAMOR)
- BILL: It's okay.
You left me!
You took me into Neibolt!
You're not my friends!
You made me go into Neibolt!
EDDIE: Stanley, I'm sorry.
STANLEY: You made me go into Neibolt!
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
STANLEY: This is your fault.
EDDIE: We would never let anything happen
to you.
We're here for you.
BEN: You know we wouldn't do that to you.
Come on.
Bill! Bill!
MIKE: Bill!
EDDIE: Bill!
(BILL PANTING)
(STATIC WARBLES)
Beverly!
(GRUNTS)
I'll come back for you, Bev.
BEN: Bill!
Bill!
- (EDDIE GAGS)
- RICHIE: Come on.
Get out of there, dude.
That's greywater.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, my God, my fucking flashlight?
- (ALL GASP)
- RICHIE: Eddie!
(ALL SCREAMING)
RICHIE: Come on, let's get the fuck
out of here! Come on!
RICHIE: Holy shit.
MIKE: Bev? Bev?
BEN: Beverly?
RICHIE: Holy shit.
BEN: Bev.
RICHIE: How is she in the air?
Guys.
Are those...
STANLEY: The missing kids.
Floating.
BEN: Just let me grab her.
RICHIE: Shit.
(GRUNTING)
BEN: I'm slipping.
Bev.
Beverly.
(YELLING)
Why isn't she waking up?
What is wrong with her?
Beverly, please! Come on!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
RICHIE: Wow.
(GASPS)
BEN: Bev?
"January embers"
"My heart burns there too"
Jesus, fuck.
Oh, God.
Where's Bill?
BILL: Georgie.
GEORGIE: What took you so long?
I was looking for you this whole time.
I couldn't find my way outta here.
He said I could have
my boat back, Billy.
(PANTS)
Was she fast?
I couldn't keep up with it.
"She," Georgie.
You call boats "she."
Take me home, Billy.
(TEARFULLY) I wanna go home.
(SOBS)
GEORGIE: I miss you.
I wanna be with Mom and Dad.
I want more than anything
for you to be home.
With Mom and Dad.
BILL: I miss you so much.
(SNIFFLES)
I love you, Billy.
I love you, too.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CRYING)
But you're not Georgie.
- (FIRES GUN)
- (BILL GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(DISTORTED ROARING)
(ROARING CONTINUES)
(ROARING STOPS)
(PENNYWISE GASPS)
EDDIE: Kill It, Bill! Kill It!
RICHIE: Shit.
- RICHIE: Kill It, Bill!
- (BOYS SHOUTING)
- Kill It! Bill, Kill It!
- (EDDIE SCREAMS)
- (ALL SHOUTING)
- EDDIE: Kill It!
- Kill It!
- Kill!
Kill It!
It's not loaded.
RICHIE: Do it now, Bill!
Kill It! Kill It!
Hey! It's not loaded!
- (GUN FIRES)
- (GRUNTING MANIACALLY)
RICHIE: Holy fuck.
- (PENNYWISE GRUNTS)
- RICHIE: Oh, shit.
- (ROARING)
- (ALL GASP)
- (ALL YELPING)
- (GROWLING)
RICHIE: Bill, watch out!
BEVERLY: Leave him alone!
- (YELLS)
- (GROWLS)
EDDIE: Beverly, no!
STANLEY: Mike!
(MIKE SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
BEVERLY: Help him!
- (GRUNTS)
- RICHIE: Fuck!
(BEN GRUNTS)
EDDIE: Ben!
- (GRUNTS)
- (BEN YELLS)
- BEVERLY: Stanley!
(YELPS)
(BILL GRUNTS)
EDDIE AND STANLEY: Bill!
- EDDIE: Bill!
- (LOW GROWLING)
BEVERLY: No, don't.
Let him go.
No.
I'll take him.
I'll take all of you.
And I'll feast on your flesh
as I feed on your fear.
Or,
you'll just leave us be.
I will take him, only him
and then I will have my long rest
and you will all live to grow
and thrive
and lead happy lives
until old age takes you back
to the weeds.
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
Leave...
I'm the one who dragged you all into this.
(STUTTERS) I'm so sorry.
PENNYWISE: (IMITATES STUTTER)
Sorry.
(PENNYWISE LAUGHS)
- Go!
- (PENNYWISE LAUGHS)
Guys, we can't!
BILL: (STUTTERS) I'm sorry.
I told you, Bill.
I fucking told you.
I don't want to die.
It's your fault.
You punched me in the face.
You made me walk through shitty water.
You brought me to a fucking
crackhead house.
And now...
I'm gonna have to kill
this fucking clown.
Welcome to the Losers' Club, asshole!
- (ROARING)
- (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL SCREAM)
- BEVERLY: Mike!
- Mike!
- (MIKE STRAINING)
- (STANLEY GRUNTS)
(RICHIE GRUNTS)
BILL: Stan, watch out!
- (STANLEY YELLS)
- (YELLS)
EDDIE: Mike!
- (PANTING)
- (LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
(PENNYWISE GASPS)
EDDIE: Kill him!
(BEN YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(BEN GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
(ROARING)
(GASPING)
(BILL GRUNTS)
(RICHIE GRUNTS)
(ALL GRUNTING AND YELLING)
(COUGHING)
(WHIMPERING)
(GAGS)
I'm gonna kill you!
- (EDDIE GRUNTS)
- (PENNYWISE GROWLS)
PENNYWISE: Hey, Bevvie.
Are you still my little...
- (YELLING)
- (SCREAMS)
(CHOKING)
- (GRUNTS)
- EDDIE: Oh, shit!
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING MANIACALLY)
(GASPING)
(CHUCKLING)
That's why you didn't kill Beverly.
(STUTTERS)
'Cause she wasn't afraid.
- And we aren't either.
- (MOCK STUTTERING)
Not anymore.
Now you're the one who's afraid.
Because you're gonna starve.
(GURGLING)
(GRUNTS)
PENNYWISE: "He thrusts
his fists against the posts
"and still insists he sees the ghosts
(STUTTERS) "He thrusts
his fists against the posts"
(STUTTERING)
(GRUNTS)
(LOW GROWLING)
Fear...
I know what I'm doing
for my summer experience essay.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(BEVERLY SNIFFLES)
Guys. Guys.
The kids are floating down.
(RICHIE SIGHS)
(SOBBING)
(SNIFFLES)
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
BEVERLY: I can only
remember parts,
I thought I was dead.
That's what it felt like.
I saw us, all of us together
back in the cistern,
but we were older,
like, our parents' ages.
(STUTTERS)
What were we all doing there?
I just remember how we felt.
How scared we were.
I don't think I can ever forget that.
Swear it.
Swear
if It isn't dead,
if It ever comes back,
we'll come back, too.
(EXHALES)
(WINCES)
(WATCH BEEPING)
STANLEY: I gotta go.
I hate you.
(ALL LAUGHING)
I'll see you later.
BILL: Bye, Stan.
EDDIE: Bye, guys.
BEVERLY: Bye, Mike.
MIKE: See you later, losers.
RICHIE: See you around, Bill.
BILL: See you, Rich.
BEN: See you guys later.
BEVERLY: Bye, Ben.
(STUTTERS)
You all packed for Portland?
Yeah, pretty much.
I'm going tomorrow morning.
How long will you be gone?
My aunt, she says I can stay
for as long as I want, so...
Just so you know...
I never felt like a loser
when I was with all of you.
See you around.
Bye.
(PENNYWISE LAUGHING)